Chapter 1967: New Otherworldly Demon

Volume 6: Demon Venerable's Eternal Life

"Wake up! Hey, wake up kid."

Peng Da opened his eyes with difficulty, in his blurred vision, he saw a human face. It belonged to a middle aged man, he had a beard and a pair of crystal clear triangular eyes, there was a white headscarf covering his head.

Peng Da was shocked.

He remembered sleeping in his room earlier, why did a stranger barge into his room suddenly?

He exerted force to sit up but at the next moment, he was stunned.

"Where am I?!" He was shocked to find himself in the middle of a desert, there were no clouds in the sky, the sun was blazing and it was extremely hot.

"Hahaha, this kid is dazed."

"He is really lucky, he was attacked by the desert wolves but managed to survive."

There was not only the bearded middle aged man, there were several others surrounding him.

Not far away, there was a group of camels resting on the ground.

"Kid, this place is called wolf desert, when we found you, your companions were already dead. The desert wolves ate their corpses, after we chased them away, we found that you were still alive."

"My name is Mo Li, I am the leader of this caravan, I saved you and healed your wounds. You are quite lucky to have met us, do you remember anything now?" The bearded middle aged man spoke and explained.

Peng Da was dazed in the desert, the heated sand and glaring sunlight made him gradually accept this.

It was not a dream!

"I transmigrated!"

"Damn it, something like transmigration really exists, and it happened to me of all people!"

"But how did I get here? Yesterday, I was still doing some programming and coding, but today, I ended up here."

"Looking at their attire and speech mannerisms, this is obviously another world."

"Also, why do I know this world's language? It seems like speaking this foreign language is part of my innate ability!"

Peng Da could not help but feel nervous, his heart was pounding rapidly. This situation was really out of his expectations, he started to panic as he felt troubled internally.

But around him, there were several strong men staring at him, Peng Da had to force himself to stay calm as he held his head, shaking it: "I... I only remember my name is Peng Da. As for the rest... damn it, why don't I remember a thing?"

"No way, you lost your memories?"

"This is so disappointing."

Everyone discussed.

The bearded middle aged man looked at Peng Da deeply, bright light flashed in his eyes: "Since you do not remember, forget it. I hope you can regain your memories one day, now, what plans do you have? Do you want to travel with my merchant caravan?"

Peng Da quickly nodded his head, he did not dare to travel alone in the desert: "Uncle Mo Li, I will definitely repay this debt of saving my life. No matter where you are going, please bring me along, I do not know where to go now."

He had a lost expression but he spoke truthfully. He had just arrived in this world, he did not know what to do.

"Then follow us." Mo Li nodded, instructing a person beside him: "Provide a camel for this kid Peng Da."

"Yes." Someone responded immediately: "Kid, follow me."

Peng Da was brought away to the camel, he stared with wide eyes, feeling shocked: "This is a camel?"

The Gu Master who brought him here felt strange: "Kid, are you really from Western Desert? You don't even know about the fire pit camel?"

The fire pit camel did not have a hump, instead its back was concave, forming an oval pit. The person riding the camel would lie in the round pit, with soft fur and warm body temperature, it was very comfortable. The Gu Master started nimbly packing away the goods in the round pit and building a tent on top of it. A portion of the cargo was tied to the camel's sides and the bottom of the tent.

Peng Da continued to pretend that he was in pain as he said: "I don't remember, damn it, I don't remember anything!"

That Gu Master gave him a glance: "I don't care what you forgot, but remember this, our leader saved your life. Since you are joining our caravan, you are eating our food, drinking our water, and living in our quarters, you need to work. Understood?"

Peng Da quickly nodded: "Of course, please give me the instructions. I will do my best!"

"Mm." The Gu Master nodded lightly, showing slight satisfaction.

But at this time, the bearded man's voice could be heard: "Don't make life difficult for him, let this young man rest for now and recover from his mental fatigue. It was fate that we met in this huge desert, it is not easy to live here, no matter who you are."

The Gu Master sighed as he quipped: "Leader, you are still so kindhearted."

Peng Da heard this, he felt a sense of deeper gratitude towards Mo Li, he shouted loudly: "Uncle, thank you so much, I will definitely repay you!"

Mo Li laughed loudly: "Good, kid, go and recover on your camel for now."

Next, he shouted at everyone: "We've had enough rest, let's continue on our way."

Thus, the camel bells rang as the merchant caravan moved forward again, traveling over this vast desert.

Peng Da lay on the fire pit camel's back, he felt very comfortable.

After being alone, he was shocked to find that his body was not his original body, it was a body that belonged to this world. His skin was brown from tanning, his arms and legs were thick, his joints were bulging.

"So only my soul came over, I went into the body of an inhabitant of this world."

"No wonder I can speak their language. It is a pity that I did not gain this inhabitant's memories."

"But this is not bad either. My original body was weak as I did not train it, but this body is very strong and young too."

Peng Da could not sleep, after inspecting his body, he started to look around and observe this world.

There was nothing in the desert, but the travelers were quite an eye-opener to him.

The food of the fire pit camel was actually some bright red charcoal.

The people in the merchant caravan could create water from nothing, they did not need to find oases or water sources. Moving in this desert was very secure because of them.

By night time, they started to prepare dinner. A Gu Master planted some seeds in the desert as trees grew out after a few breaths of time, bearing fruits.

Peng Da did not know what fruit this was but the flesh was tender and sweet, it was fragrant and filled his stomach with satisfaction.

Peng Da was amazed at every small detail of this world. When he ate dinner, he could not help but ask the leader Mo Li.

"Kid, it seems you really have amnesia! We are Gu Masters! These are Gu Master methods." Mo Li looked at Peng Da with a strange gaze.

"Gu Master?" This was the first time Peng Da heard this phrase.

Mo Li's expression was even stranger now as he pointed at Peng Da: "Kid, you are also a Gu Master, in fact, you are a rank two Gu Master."

"What?!" Peng Da was shocked.

After some explanation, Peng Da realized what that meant, he became more excited.

"So a certain group of people of this world are called Gu Masters. They are able to cultivate using Gu worms!"

"Gu Masters rank from one to nine, most of the caravan members are rank two, Uncle Mo Li is the highest at rank three. Meanwhile, I am a rank two Gu Master, or rather, this body's original owner was a rank two Gu Master."

"When Gu Masters cultivate to rank six, they will be known as Gu Immortals, they will be able to overturn mountains and seas, they can collect the stars and moon!"

"By rank nine, they will be invincible in this world, unparalleled and unmatched!"

"Oh heavens, this is such a wonderful world. Since heaven transmigrated me here, there must be a reason for my arrival."

"I must be unique, I will definitely rise above all others. Right! Once I get rank nine cultivation, I will be invincible in this world, that feeling must be very amazing!"

In Peng Da's original world, he was a very ordinary person. He was an orphan with no parents, lovers, or any other attachments.

He was extremely excited, by night time, he could not resist the fatigue, he fell deeply asleep.

What he did not know was, the Gu Masters in the merchant caravan were talking about him.

"This kid actually lost his memories. What should I say? Is he really lucky or unlucky?"

"Is he really amnesiac or pretending to be so?"

"There is no need to do that? From what I saw, he was very shocked by the fire pit camels and our Gu Master methods, it is unlikely to be an act."

"Whether he lost his memories or not, he is still a rank two Gu Master, he will be useful to us, there was no loss in saving him." Mo Li said.

Nobody could refute this.

Gu Masters were far more valuable than mortals, if Peng Da was a mortal, these Gu Masters would not have bothered to save him after realizing he was still alive back then. But since he was a Gu Master, he had value to them, thus he was able to travel on the camel and also got food and water from them.

While they were talking, Mo Li suddenly frowned, his expression turned grim: "Listen, do you all hear something?"

Everyone's expressions changed, at the next moment, this sound became louder, it was such a huge commotion that heaven and earth shook.

"Damn it! It seems like a hurricane, a super-sized hurricane!"

"This is a desert, why are there hurricanes?"

"Quickly move, protect the caravan and move out!"

The Gu Masters left the tent hurriedly but once they got out, they were stunned.

There was a boundless qi tide approaching from all directions, it was like a grand tsunami that overwhelmed heaven and earth. The qi tide was everywhere, it carried sand along with it and had an unstoppable might.

Extremely shocked expressions were shown all over the Gu Masters' faces.

This was a calamity far worse than any hurricane, at once, the Gu Masters felt an intense threat of death.

The merchant caravan was doomed, they only wanted to save their own lives now!

"Escape!" Mo Li gritted his teeth, before he finished his words, he quickly retreated with all his strength.

The other Gu Masters quickly reacted as they mimicked him and escaped.

In the abandoned merchant caravan, the mortals screeched, the camels were stirred too.

They were helpless now, only death awaited them.

But within this chaos, Peng Da was still deeply asleep, he had no idea that this fatal danger was upon him.

Chapter 1968: Spectral Soul Hunts

The sky was dark, there was only two to three faint starlight specks.

This was black heaven.

The surroundings were quiet, three Gu Immortals were moving stealthily in black heaven.

At the left was an elderly hunchbacked Gu Immortal, he had many wrinkles on his face, he was thin and dry like a stick, he was truly resembling a man about to step into his grave.

At the right was a female immortal, she had a graceful figure with hair that extended to her waist, and was adorned in a beautiful purple robe. Her eyes were like deep pools, with a sense of sorrow shrouding her face.

And at the center was a black robed Gu Immortal, he looked like a middle aged man with a pale face, his black hair was chest length, he had a deep and cold killing intent that surrounded his entire body.

They were Old Man Zheng Yuan, Fairy Zi Wei, and Spectral Soul Demon Venerable!

The three were moving quietly in black heaven, at this time, Spectral Soul paused and said plainly: "It's here again."

Fairy Zi Wei's and Old Man Zheng Yuan's expressions did not change, they guarded Spectral Soul as they started to put up their defensive methods.

Soon, the three immortals heard a loud sound.

Next, a huge and wild qi tide came from all directions. Wherever the qi tide went, lifeforms perished, it was a terrible sight.

The qi tide crashed towards the three immortals, after several minutes, it went past them.

The three including Spectral Soul finally let out a sigh of relief, they canceled their defensive methods as they came out again.

Old Man Zheng Yuan looked towards the qi tide with an expression of sadness towards the people, he sighed deeply: "After the five regions fused into one, such a change actually happened. Once in a while, qi tides will surge, rampaging wildly all over the world. Not just the five regions, even the two heavens are not spared, they cause destruction everywhere they go, I wonder how many people will suffer from this."

Even though Old Man Zheng Yuan was subdued by Spectral Soul, he was only absolutely loyal to Spectral Soul, his original personality did not change.

Fairy Zi Wei's eyes flickered with uncertainty, she seemed to be deducing something but she soon gave up in dejectedness.

Fairy Zi Wei analyzed: "The heaven and earth qi of the five regions vary. Thus, when Gu Immortals go to different regions, absorbing the heaven and earth qi there would cause problems in their immortal aperture. This is also why Gu Immortals often have to return to their region to undergo tribulations. The difference in heaven and earth qi also caused the regional walls to form. Now that the five regional walls are gone, the heaven and earth qi of the five regions are converging into one, this is the reason for the birth of these qi tides."

"But it is impossible to calculate how long this qi tide phenomenon will last, or whether it will get stronger or weaker, we can't even predict a trend."

To deduce the result of this question, it was likely that Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable was needed, he had the deepest understanding of qi path after all. Other than that, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could also make such a large scale deduction.

Spectral Soul snorted coldly, his voice was hoarse and icy: "This qi tide is a hindrance to us! Wherever it goes, soul beasts are unable to resist it, even if they survive, their soul cores will be damaged."

Spectral Soul wanted to recover his strength now.

Devouring souls was the fastest method.

Originally, he wanted to retrieve the Door of Life and Death, but it was actually moved away in secret.

The fight in Heavenly Court was over now, in Spectral Soul's current state, he could not take action rashly.

Thus, he brought his two subordinates to leave Heavenly Court and come to black heaven, they prepared to hunt soul beasts instead.

Within black heaven, there were countless soul beasts that formed into hordes. They often rampaged in black heaven with nether ants paving the way, they often had hundreds of thousands or even millions of soul beasts in an horde.

"Master, the qi tide is a calamity, please let us stay to help you." Old Man Zheng Yuan advised as a loyal servant.

Spectral Soul snorted coldly: "What use is there in staying by my side? I alone am sufficient, furthermore, I have tasks for you two."

Old Man Zheng Yuan and Fairy Zi Wei looked at each other as they said: "Please give us your instructions, master."

Spectral Soul squinted as he said eerily: "Back then, I expended my assets to refine sovereign immortal fetus Gu, leaving it for Fang Yuan to create a complete otherworldly demon. Now that fate Gu is destroyed, the plan succeeded, it is time to retrieve sovereign immortal fetus Gu now. I want you two to find and capture Fang Yuan alive, I will refine him back into sovereign immortal fetus Gu."

Spectral Soul's strength was at its lowest now, otherwise, he would have taken action during the battle in Heavenly Court.

If he wanted to grow stronger now, there were three crucial things: Door of Life and Death, dream realms, and sovereign immortal aperture.

Now that the Door of Life and Death was gone, Spectral Soul felt slightly disappointed. But he could use soul beasts instead.

Most of his dream realms were taken by Fang Yuan. Even though Fang Yuan used a portion of them in Heavenly Court's battle, the rest were still stored in Fang Yuan's possession.

Spectral Soul needed to take back his dream realms, only with his dream realms could he regain his attainment level of great grandmaster in all paths.

Other than that, the sovereign immortal aperture was necessary too, it could ensure that Spectral Soul would quickly reach the apex of his strength.

Spectral Soul had reason to believe that the sovereign immortal aperture was well developed by Fang Yuan. If he could take it back, it would be the same as gaining Fang Yuan's hard work.

If he could retrieve all three crucial keys, Spectral Soul would rise to the top, he would be unstoppable in this world!

He could not find the Door of Life and Death, but both the dream realms and sovereign immortal aperture were in Fang Yuan's hands, it was understandable that Spectral Soul targeted Fang Yuan first.

Old Man Zheng Yuan frowned as he recalled: "Master wants to deal with Fang Yuan? After this demon destroyed fate Gu, he left Heavenly Court immediately and did not participate in the battle afterwards. He acted very strangely then, nobody knows where he went after that."

Spectral Soul smiled coldly: "That is because of the heaven path dao marks, Fang Yuan could barely save himself, he had to make that choice. Since he could discern the arrangement that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable placed on wisdom Gu and thus used it in the refinement unhesitantly, he naturally can infer the arrangements I placed in sovereign immortal fetus Gu as well."

"Thus, when refining the Gu, he used Red Lotus' method to restrict me. Fang Yuan is very crafty, he managed to thwart my plan by borrowing others' strength. Red Lotus wanted to see that happen as well, hmph, after I get rid of Fang Yuan, I will deal with this old scoundrel Red Lotus."

Spectral Soul and Red Lotus worked together to destroy fate Gu for good. Now that the plan succeeded, Spectral Soul and Red Lotus returned to being enemies.

Two tigers cannot share one mountain, not to mention two venerables.

"But how do we locate Fang Yuan now?" Fairy Zi Wei felt a headache.

Why was it that after changing sides and betraying Heavenly Court, she still had to face this troublesome problem!

When she was in Heavenly Court, she tried all ways possible to deal with Fang Yuan.

As a wisdom path great expert, she had noticed Fang Yuan's threat long ago.

But so what?

Fang Yuan was too good at hiding and concealing himself, his most skilled wisdom path aspect was in blocking deductions.

And he was too vigilant, he never left any traces behind. Even if Heavenly Court wanted to find him, they were helpless and clueless.

Like how humanity had Immortal Venerables and Demon Venerables that the variant humans could not resist, they went into hiding and left even Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable without options against them.

Fairy Zi Wei lacked crucial clues, she could not deduce Fang Yuan's location.

That was the case when she was in Heavenly Court, until now, it was still true!

Thus, she had to get help from Spectral Soul, hoping that this Demon Venerable's soul had some way to deal with him.

But against this question, even Spectral Soul was silent for a while.

Sovereign immortal fetus Gu was refined by him personally, he had made an arrangement to sense the sovereign immortal body. But after the heaven path dao marks were absorbed by Fang Yuan, he lost his method. The connection was completely cut.

Eventually, Spectral Soul ordered: "We temporarily can't find Fang Yuan, we have to force him to show up."

"How? Fang Yuan is a solitary demon, he has no attachments at all. Even if he did have friends or family, with his cruel nature, if we threaten him, he will not appear." Old Man Zheng Yuan felt very troubled.

Spectral Soul snorted coldly: "During Heavenly Court's battle, everyone saw the scene of Fang Yuan destroying fate Gu through the killer move everybody's vision. You will go spread the secret of the sovereign immortal aperture, tell everyone in the world that Fang Yuan was able to reach rank eight and destroy Fate because the sovereign immortal aperture can annex immortal apertures to avoid tribulations and raise his cultivation level rapidly."

"Once in a while, Fang Yuan will have to annex immortal apertures to sustain his life. Whoever kills Fang Yuan will gain countless venerable inheritances, they will even possess the sovereign immortal aperture, they will be qualified to become a venerable and become invincible in the world!"

After pausing, Spectral Soul continued: "In that case, Fang Yuan will be an enemy of everyone. We also have to tell everyone about his current weakness, that he has no battle strength due to the heaven path dao marks troubling him. If not, he would not have escaped immediately after refining the Gu."

"With everyone in the world helping us find him, where can Fang Yuan hide? Even if he can hide for a while, he cannot hide forever. Both of you will go and find the secret treasuries that I left behind afterwards, the cultivation resources that I did not need when refining sovereign immortal fetus Gu are kept there, they are not of low value. Using these resources, you can rebuild Shadow Sect and help me recruit more members."

"Fang Yuan's subordinates like Bai Ning Bing and Hei Lou Lan are all outside now? If we find them, we might find clues to Fang Yuan."

Old Man Zheng Yuan and Fairy Zi Wei quickly responded.

Spectral Soul looked down at his feet, his gaze seemed to be piercing through the darkness and looking at the five regions: "The five regions fused into one, heaven and earth qi is converging as qi tides form and spread around the world. If the heaven and earth qi does not fuse completely, there will not be peace, it will be as if the five regional walls are thinned and spread all over the five regions. Thus, the Gu Immortals of the five regions will feel tremors in their immortal apertures as the two qi collide, they are forced to recuperate now. The stronger the immortal aperture foundation, the longer they need to recuperate."

"Fang Yuan will be forced to lay low for a very long time. But you two are ex-Heavenly Court members, you had phantom apertures so you are unaffected by this. We need to make use of this time, work hard!"

"As master decrees." Fairy Zi Wei and Old Man Zheng Yuan replied respectfully.

Spectral Soul waved his sleeves: "Then why are you still here?"

"Master, please take care! We will take our leave." Fairy Zi Wei and Old Man Zheng Yuan left quickly.

Chapter 1969: Black Heaven's Gu Immortals

Roar—!

Within black heaven, an ancient soul beast was escaping in a hurry.

This soul beast resembled a horse but had a human face. On its face now was terror and fear.

The ancient soul beast was panicking and escaping in a random direction, soon, its movements slowed down as its anguished cries became softer and weaker.

After several breaths of time, it completely stopped in the sky, floating silently in the night sky.

Soundlessly, its colossal body disintegrated as a Gu Immortal appeared.

This Gu Immortal had a pale face and chest-length hair, he was Spectral Soul.

Spectral Soul grabbed the soul core, which was the soul path essence of the ancient soul beast. But Spectral Soul was not satisfied, he placed this soul core into his mouth and ate it like a candy, swallowing it after a few seconds.

"Without using a soul path killer move, I need to wait a while to digest it completely." Spectral Soul said unhappily as he snorted.

After splitting up with Old Man Zheng Yuan and Fairy Zi Wei, he had been hunting soul beasts in black heaven.

But for some reason, maybe due to bad luck or the extermination of lifeforms due to the qi tides, he met very few soul beasts.

Until now, he had only met lone soul beasts or those that formed into groups of five or fewer. The quantity was so small that he even felt like he was not in black heaven!

"This efficiency is just too low!" Spectral Soul continued his journey.

"If my attainment level was still around, I can find the soul beast armies with just my instinct. Even Fang Yuan would not be able to escape my detection. It is a pity I need to start over!"

"However, fate Gu is finally destroyed. Heaven's will cannot obstruct my path to becoming venerable again, after I succeed, I want to see who dares to obstruct me, even if it is a venerable, I will kill them."

"Oh?" While Spectral Soul moved stealthily, a flash of joy suddenly appeared on his face.

He finally found an army of soul beasts.

He got closer and saw that this soul beast army had over three million members. The quantity was not small, and what made Spectral Soul happy was that they had high quality.

He had only taken a quick glance but he already saw six immemorial soul beasts and over thirty ancient soul beasts!

"Kill!" The desire to kill emerged in Spectral Soul's heart as he was about to charge over, but he noticed something.

This discovery was quite surprising: "Why are there soul path Gu Immortals?"

There were three Gu Immortals controlling the soul beast army.

Two males and one female immortal.

The female was at the center as the leader, she had a plain appearance and grey eyes, her rank eight aura was naturally emitted.

Of the two male immortals, one was tall and armored, with strong arms exposed and soul beast markings on his arms. The other was tall and thin, holding a bamboo staff.

The three immortals wore black robes of similar design, they were obviously from the same force.

"They are black heaven Gu Immortals." Spectral Soul soon discerned their aura, he snickered as he changed his earlier idea of charging in, he stealthily mixed in with the soul beast army.

The three immortals controlled the soul beast army with much difficulty, the two males were showing signs of tiredness, sweat gathered on their foreheads.

The rank eight female immortal seemed to have rested earlier, she spoke at this moment: "You two can stop, I will control the army now."

Hearing this, the two male immortals let out sighs of relief, the thin one started to boot-lick her: "Aunt, only you can control a soul beast army of such a size, even if the two of us cultivate for eight lifetimes, we would not even reach half of your strength."

The rank eight female immortal looked at the male immortal with displeasure: "If eight lifetimes are not enough to reach my level, you should just end your own life!"

"Ugh." The thin man knew that his boot-licking had backfired, he showed some awkwardness on his face.

The female immortal sighed: "You two are the most likely Gu Immortals in the clan to advance further besides me. Now that fate Gu has been destroyed, we are taking control of our own fate. The great era has arrived, the peaceful and quiet life of the past is long gone. You must have the spirit to work hard, if you do not have such an awareness, sooner or later our Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven will be drowned by the tides of the era!"

"Aunt, you have taught me a lesson." The tall and thin man nodded his head in succession.

As for the male immortal at the side, he remained silent.

The female immortal sighed again and continued: "The five regions were fused, the heaven and earth qi are merging, to the extent that qi tides swept across the whole world, even black heaven and white heaven are not exempted. Wherever the qi tide reaches, heaven and earth will shake, grotto-heavens can no longer be concealed, their positions will be exposed. This time, we as Gu Immortals of black heaven's grotto-heavens are meeting to discuss how to face this situation. At that time, the two of you will be representing yourselves as well as our Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven, don't forget this."

"Yes, aunt (madam), don't worry, we will remember this!" The two immortals responded respectfully.

The three immortals did not know that Spectral Soul had already gotten near them, he heard their entire conversation without missing anything.

"So that's it." Spectral Soul realized: "With the convergence of the heaven and earth qi, the grotto-heavens concealed in black heaven and white heaven are affected too. The reason is the same as why the five regions' Gu Immortals are forced to recuperate. but the five regions' Gu Immortals are more affected while the two heavens are not as troubled, the Gu Immortals are still able to move around with difficulty."

Within black and white heaven, many grotto-heavens were hidden.

Even Spectral Soul could not precisely count the number of grotto-heavens here.

This current change in the world was unprecedented, all of the grotto-heavens were unable to hide anymore, they were like fish forced out of the water.

Spectral Soul felt that this was a perfect opportunity, he immediately continued to hide, following the three immortals.

After spending half a day, the three immortals controlled the army of soul beasts and finally arrived at their destination.

This was also a grotto-heaven.

The grotto-heaven's entrance was open, many people were already waiting outside, the commotion was not small.

The soul beast army of millions that the three Soul Pacifying immortals brought here was not exceptional at all, they were only superior to the norm.

"So our friends from Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven have arrived." Seeing the three immortals, a Gu Immortal flew out from a pack of night heavenly wolves.

This Gu Immortal had rank eight cultivation level, he had a pair of sharp eagle eyes and had an appearance of a resolute character.

"Night Heavenly Wolf Lord, you arrived early." The rank eight female immortal from Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven replied while smiling.

"Actually, we were late, Lady Cold Ash." Night Heavenly Wolf Lord smiled bitterly, pointing at the grotto-heaven entrance: "Those variant human Gu Immortals have entered already. I waited for you to enter together, otherwise, as lone rank eight Gu Immortals, we will be pushed aside."

Lady Cold Ash nodded with a grim expression: "We have gathered here today because of Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's request. He is a snowman Gu Immortal to begin with, he opened up his Ice Crystal grotto-heaven as well, this will definitely be dominated by variant human Gu Immortals. Let's go in and see first."

Lady Cold Ash quickly arranged for the two rank sevens to stay behind and look after the soul beast army.

She only brought some immemorial soul beasts with her into the grotto-heaven.

Unknown to her, Spectral Soul had already possessed one of her immemorial soul beasts, he followed after them.

Once they entered the grotto-heaven, the temperature fell drastically, it was an icy world.

Looking at the ground it was all white. The mountain stood tall, made entirely of frost crystals, this was very rare.

At the peak of the frost crystal mountain, there was a palace made of ice and snow.

Lady Cold Ash and Night Heavenly Wolf Lord arrived in front of the palace hall, they left their accompanying immemorial soul beasts and immemorial night heavenly wolves outside, entering themselves.

After Spectral Soul looked for a while, he successfully saw through the foundation of this icy palace, he immediately found a loophole and entered the hall.

There was a snowman Gu Immortal sitting at the main seat, he had a squarish face and dignified demeanor, he was Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch.

Other than that, there were three rank eight variant humans, they were rockman, hairy man, and eggman respectively.

"To think that in black heaven, variant humans are the superior force, they actually have four rank eights while the humans only have two." Spectral Soul thought about it for a moment before understanding why.

After humans dominated the world, variant humans could not live in the five regions anymore, they were chased into the peripheries of the world to live pitiful lives.

Black and white heaven became their top choices to relocate and live.

This place was extremely huge, once their grotto-heavens were concealed, even venerables would not be able to find them without sufficient clues.

Thus, black and white heaven became the foundation of the variant humans, they developed here.

Even though human Gu Immortals also explored both heavens, they only explored them to seek resources. Few rank eight Gu Immortals would place their grotto-heavens within the black and white heavens.

Human grotto-heavens were different from variant human grotto-heavens, the latter were taken care of by heaven's will, their tribulations were weaker, but the former were different.

As time passed, more and more human grotto-heavens that were placed were destroyed, few could develop successfully. Meanwhile, the variant human grotto-heavens were able to last a long time, their forces grew stealthily.

The six rank eight Gu Immortals discussed for a long time.

"The five regions have become one, qi tides rampage the heavens. Our grotto-heavens will be exposed, I propose that we unite ourselves and resist the enemies of the five regions together!"

"How will we resist them? Even though our grotto-heavens are doing well, how can our resources compare to the five regions? Even if we all work together, we are not the match of the five regions' humans!"

"Moreover, we cannot cooperate sincerely with each other, we are of different identities after all."

"Everyone, don't worry, even though we are humans, our Soul Pacifying Ancestor was forced to live in black heaven, we have already broken all ties with the five regions."

"I'll be more straightforward, my Night Wolf grotto-heaven does not want to expose ourselves. After all, we have an immense enmity with Northern Plains' Longevity Heaven!"

"Friends." Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch spoke: "Do you all only want to go on the defensive, do you not want to progress further? Now that fate Gu has been destroyed, the reign of humanity has been disrupted. The five regions' Gu Immortals need to recuperate now, this is the best chance for us to take action!"

"Because we were in black heaven, we became the least affected ones, we can move around with difficulty. If we don't make use of this chance, we will regret it in the future."

"Immortal Monarch, what plan do you have?"

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch sighed as he said with a grim expression: "The five regions are huge, they have abundant resources, even if our grotto-heavens are added together, we cannot compare to them. The world will definitely go into chaos, if we do not try to improve ourselves, when the five regions settle down, they will find a chance to eliminate us all. Only by taking this lead can we have a hope of survival."

Chapter 1970: Heavenly Court's Dilemma

Lady Cold Ash flew first towards the entrance of Ice Crystal grotto-heaven.

The two rank sevens from Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven quickly went to receive her.

"Aunt." The tall and thin Gu Immortal asked in concern: "How was the discussion?"

Lady Cold Ash shook her head lightly, at this time, Night Heavenly Wolf Lord also flew out of Ice Crystal grotto-heaven.

The two conversed for some time before parting ways. Night Heavenly Wolf Lord brought his wolf group along while Lady Cold Ash led her soul beast army, going back to their respective grotto-heavens.

Along the way, the three immortals conversed, not knowing that Spectral Soul was lurking around them.

Spectral Soul had originally wanted to hunt the soul beasts, but after seeing this, he changed his mind.

Just by the name of Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven, he could tell its foundation was soul path. Seeing that Lady Cold Ash and the two rank sevens were soul path Gu Immortals, Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven must be a place filled with abundant soul path cultivation resources.

Let alone anything else, just the soul beast army that they controlled was a scrumptious meal to Spectral Soul.

"Qi tides rampage in the five regions and two heavens, the grotto-heaven forces in black and white heaven will not lay low. Hehe, I can use this to my advantage and assault the other venerable forces and speed up my growth!"

Spectral Soul not only had to deal with Fang Yuan, there were also venerable forces like Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven.

Now that fate Gu was destroyed, Spectral Soul was able to revive, the other venerables were also able to revive themselves.

With Fang Yuan missing at the moment, Spectral Soul had to consider the whole situation. Even though his true nature was killing, there were many ways to kill. Using others as one's lethal weapon was also a high level killing method, he was going to use it now.

Lady Cold Ash and the rest did not know that their Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven was currently targeted by a huge monster, Spectral Soul. Meanwhile, Night Heavenly Wolf Lord returned to his Night Wolf grotto-heaven.

Many Gu Immortals in Night Wolf grotto-heaven quickly greeted him.

Night Heavenly Wolf Lord said: "Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch wants us to form an alliance to resist the five regions. This is quite a difficult situation."

Gu Immortal Ye Zhi nodded: "It is quite difficult. In the current situation, fate Gu is destroyed, the five regions merged, as the heaven and earth qi fuse together, qi tides rampage in the world, no grotto-heaven can conceal itself. We are small and lone forces, when the five regions attack us, we will not be able to resist them. However, we do not need to fight the five regions, we are humans but Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and the rest are variant humans after all. The five regions are stronger than the two heavens, this is an obvious fact, why can't we join the five regions instead?"

Night Heavenly Wolf Lord laughed: "Ye Zhi, you know me best, that is how I feel too. If we work with the variant humans, we will be considered spies of humanity. Even if the five regions do not want to attack us, if we ally with the variant humans, they will want to."

Ye Zhi frowned: "But we cannot join the five regions. Firstly, Northern Plains of the five regions is impossible. Secondly, the other four regions might not welcome us. And finally, if we join them, we will be attacked by Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and the rest."

Night Heavenly Wolf Lord sighed: "Indeed, that is why I made an agreement with Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven's Lady Cold Ash, we will advance and retreat together, we will combine the forces of the human grotto-heavens here. As for which region to join, in my opinion, Central Continent's Heavenly Court is the most appropriate. We can secretly contact them first."

Night Heavenly Wolf Lord was an experienced leader, not only did he have rank eight cultivation level, he was shrewd in politics, nobody in Night Wolf grotto-heaven defied his rule.

Since he made a decision, the Gu Immortals in Night Wolf grotto-heaven did not dare to raise objections.

Heavenly Court.

Central Great Hall was finally repaired, Qin Ding Ling was currently the person taking charge.

They failed to repair fate Gu, Heavenly Court had undergone an intense battle, the damage was huge, even now, many areas were still in ruins.

"This is a humiliation!" Qin Ding Ling put aside the letter Gu as she rested temporarily. Her expression was calm but her eyes flickered with light, as memories surfaced in her mind, rage built up within her.

After Red Lotus' goal was achieved, Duke Long died while fighting and Fang Yuan retreated rapidly. But the three regions' Gu Immortals wanted to destroy Heavenly Court, nobody backed off.

At the moment of life and death, Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's method started to activate. All sorts of rage qi, unlucky qi, grief qi, and others plagued the three regions' Gu Immortals, their physical conditions weakened.

This move was originally meant to deal with Fang Yuan, but Limitless Demon Venerable blocked it for him. After Red Lotus' plan succeeded, the battle between two venerables in Imperfection Regret Pavilion also concluded, with Limitless laughing as the two venerable silhouettes faded away. Without Limitless' power to restrict it, Primordial Origin's method started to work again.

And the other good news was that even though Feng Jiu Ge turned on them, he only helped Fang Yuan to refine the Gu, he did not do anything against Heavenly Court.

Heavenly Court was able to recover because of this and retaliate, maintaining their position in this difficult battle.

The three regions' Gu Immortals had no choice, with Dragon Palace, Calamity Luck Altar, and Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building as their foundation, they retreated gradually.

After leaving Heavenly Court, some people wanted to loot Central Continent but the first qi tide happened at this moment.

The immortal apertures of the three regions' Gu Immortals became unstable, they had to leave.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals stopped chasing them, after witnessing Fang Yuan refine destiny Gu in front of them, their morale and fighting spirit had fallen.

After the battle ended, Heavenly Court, which was greatly damaged, tried to reduce its losses and take care of the aftermath.

Duke Long died while Fairy Zi Wei betrayed them for Spectral Soul, after Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals talked over it, they decided that Qin Ding Ling would be the new leader.

During this period of time, Qin Ding Ling had been the one in charge, taking care of all the matters, big or small.

Qin Ding Ling had a plain expression but a fire was burning in her heart. The great Heavenly Court had actually lost, it was a complete loss! She was eager to make up for this humiliation, but logic told her to not act rashly. Because everything had changed, Heavenly Court was no longer the old Heavenly Court, the enemies were no longer the same, even the world had changed.

After resting for a while, Qin Ding Ling continued to deal with the matters at hand.

"Oh?" She held an information path mortal Gu as her expression changed slightly: "Night Wolf grotto-heaven?"

Night Heavenly Wolf Lord was not willing to fight alongside the variant humans, he wanted to join the stronger side of the five regions. Among them, although Heavenly Court had lost this fight, it was still the number one human force for the last few million years.

Night Wolf grotto-heaven had grudges with Longevity Heaven, in the five regions, only Heavenly Court had the foundation to stand up against the vicious Longevity Heaven members.

In this information path Gu worm, Night Heavenly Wolf Lord also explained the ill intentions of the variant humans.

"Hmph, those of other races have such motives! Once fate Gu got destroyed, these variant humans jumped out immediately." Qin Ding Ling snorted, deep killing intense rose in her heart.

After calming down, Qin Ding Ling started to think about this situation.

Qin Ding Ling knew very little about Night Heavenly Wolf Lord and Night Wolf grotto-heaven. With just one information path Gu worm, she could not confirm if Night Heavenly Wolf Lord was really trying to sincerely join them, or if they were scheming against Heavenly Court.

"If this Night Heavenly Wolf Lord is sincere, how should we deal with Longevity Heaven and the variant human forces of the grotto-heavens?"

Night Heavenly Wolf Lord talked about the history of his ancestor truthfully in the letter, he did not conceal the grudges they had with Longevity Heaven.

Qin Ding Ling was slightly troubled.

Heavenly Court was at an unprecedented level of weakness.

Qi tides rampaged in the world, heaven and earth qi converged, the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals who had phantom apertures were even more mobile than the Gu Immortals in black or white heaven.

But Heavenly Court could not move them.

Firstly, most of Heavenly Court's members had limited lifespan. Secondly, they had to reinforce Star Constellation's will.

Thus, a portion of Heavenly Court's members had to enter the immortal graveyard to hibernate and help Star Constellation's will, to prevent her from being completely assimilated with heaven's will.

But in that case, Heavenly Court's battle strength would be far lower.

Thus, Qin Ding Ling could not make up her mind.

"If only Fairy Zi Wei was still around." Qin Ding Ling sighed, the worry in her heart intensified.

Fairy Zi Wei and Old Man Zheng Yuan were enslaved by Spectral Soul, they left with him. The two of them knew a lot about Heavenly Court's secrets, together with the soul of a Demon Venerable, who could underestimate them?

Qin Ding Ling thought about it for a while before feeling the severity of this situation, she decided to discuss it with Zhou Xiong Xin and the rest.

Zhou Xiong Xin suggested: "This is an important matter, but the situation is not very clear now. The six Gu Immortals including Night Heavenly Wolf Lord are merely the rank eights of the black heaven above our Central Continent. What about the other four regions' black heaven? We do not know how many grotto-heavens there are, or how many rank eight Gu Immortals exist in these grotto-heavens. I am willing to go and investigate the two heavens myself!"

Zhou Xiong Xin cultivated information path, he knew the importance of information.

He had a phantom aperture and was not afraid of the heaven and earth qi convergence.

Qin Ding Ling agreed with his suggestion, she chose to continue keeping in contact with Night Wolf grotto-heaven while investigating the situation.

Jun Shen Guang took out an information path mortal Gu, saying: "The list of names have been chosen, they are all Gu Immortal seeds with great talent and aptitude. Most importantly, they are loyal to Heavenly Court and the ten great ancient sects. But there is one person whom I need everyone's input and discussion on."

Jun Shen Guang's list contained the names of many mortal Gu Masters, they were all exceptional geniuses.

Heavenly Court lost this battle and the immortal graveyard was even destroyed by Fang Yuan, everything had to be rebuilt from scratch. With the threat of the five regions chaotic war, Heavenly Court decided to nurture new Gu Immortals, disregarding the costs.

Qin Ding Ling received the Gu worm and looked into it.

There were many names on this list: Immortal Crane Sect recommended Sun Yuan Hua, Spirit Butterfly Valley recommended Xiao Qi Xing, Ancient Soul Sect had Gu Ting, Heaven's Envy Manor had Wei Wu Shang... but at Spirit Affinity House's section, the list was empty without a name.

Qin Ding Ling sighed as her expression turned complex.

She knew about the person Spirit Affinity House nominated, it had to be Feng Jin Huang.

But after the battle over Fate, Feng Jiu Ge betrayed Heavenly Court and went missing, his daughter Feng Jin Huang ended up in an awkward position.

She was originally Duke Long's disciple and the future Great Dream Immortal Venerable. But with the death of Duke Long and the destruction of Fate, she was no longer certain to be Great Dream Immortal Venerable.

Zhou Xiong Xin's concern was: If Heavenly Court continued to nurture Feng Jin Huang and she betrayed them like her father, what would they do?

Even though Feng Jin Huang was Duke Long's disciple, the disciple that he nurtured wholeheartedly spent a million years to plot and destroy Heavenly Court's fate Gu. Would his second disciple Feng Jin Huang also inherit this 'great tradition'?

"We will talk about this again next time."

Chapter 1971: Struggle Between Feng and Zhao

Central Continent, Lake Heart Mountain.

Spirit Affinity House's public blessed land headquarters was situated here.

Within the blessed land, there was an area called Quiet Rain Valley.

When Feng Jin Huang was strolling in the valley, it started to rain.

A drizzle.

The rain was mild and quiet.

Bathed in the rain, Feng Jin Huang slowed down subconsciously as she walked.

The air was fresh with the smell of grass, all around her was a faint field of greenery.

This rain did not feel cold, it was like jade, mild and calm.

Feng Jin Huang knew that this was called quiet rain. When it rains, all sounds would be absorbed and the surroundings would be silent. Heaven and earth would be soundless, one would be able to hear their own heartbeats and breathing.

Quiet rain was a rank six immortal material, this valley was the resource point that created quiet rain, this was why it was named Quiet Rain Valley.

After Feng Jiu Ge betrayed Heavenly Court and went missing, his wife, the mother of Feng Jin Huang, Fairy Bai Qing, requested to be transferred to Quiet Rain Valley to collect quiet rain, she said she would not leave this place.

Whenever there was quiet rain, the valley would have music that sounded like zither and flute, it was akin to Fairy Bai Qing's anguished cries of sadness.

Feng Jin Huang had heard of this rumor and felt worried, she came to the valley to visit her mother.

The quiet rain was drizzling, there was indeed the music of zither and flute being emitted.

The sound of the zither spread out all around, like white clouds in the sky, ancient, melodious and pleasant to the ear. The sound of the flute, however, was high pitched, fluctuating almost abruptly, like a fierce hawk flying across the sky, sharply piercing the wind, tearing the sky.

At first, the sound of the zither resounded and the sound of the flute reverberated, alternating with each other, as if both sides were speaking, one sentence after the other.

Then, the zither and the flute began to approach each other, and gradually merged into one another. The white clouds were misty, and the eagles were flying across the clouds. The two abrupt sounds of music merged together, creating an indescribable beauty.

In the end, the sound of the zither and the flute become one and the same, forming a kind of mix, with the melodious sound of the zither and the clarity of the flute, it was unique and beautiful!

Feng Jin Huang was enchanted by the beautiful sound of the music. She went deeper into the valley and managed to meet her mother.

Fairy Bai Qing was sitting in a bamboo pavilion, with two Gu flying around her like white jade pearls. They were sound path mortal Gu, zither Gu and flute Gu.

When Feng Jin Huang entered the pavilion, the music slowly stopped.

Fairy Bai Qing had already known of Feng Jin Huang's arrival, she turned around slowly: "This demonic immortal unification song was composed by your father when we fell in love, it is the symbol of our relationship. I still remember the first time your father played it for me, he told me: Immortals and demons are one to begin with, initially, Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable was known as Primordial Origin Demon Venerable by the variant humans as well. This song contains deep meaning and your father has been treasuring and not using it, but he played it during the fate war."

Saying so, Fairy Bai Qing's tone changed as she looked at Feng Jin Huang fixedly: "The list of names has been announced already."

Feng Jin Huang nodded: "I know. The last time the sect recommended me, there was no reply from Heavenly Court. This time, the sect put Sun Yao's name and it was quickly approved by Heavenly Court."

Fairy Bai Qing said plainly: "Originally, the sect still wanted to recommend you to go there, but Li Jun Ying and Xu Hao got in the way, they ended up promoting Sun Yao instead. How do you feel about such an outcome, my dear daughter?"

"Hehe." Feng Jin Huang smiled slightly, her smile brilliant as a flower, bringing a bright sunshine to the bamboo pavilion for a moment.

"Mother, why do you have to test me on this? Ever since father betrayed and turned against Heavenly Court, I've already prepared myself. Right now, the situation is already not bad, my dream path Immortal Gu was not taken." Feng Jin Huang said.

Fairy Bai Qing also smiled slightly at her words: "It's not like there isn't any forceful seizure in the righteous path, but it's just that the act is often cloaked in a layer of righteousness and morality. It's already good that you have come to this level of understanding. However, don't worry too much, your father left Heavenly Court but created destiny song, his outstanding battle strength is evident to the world, Heavenly Court and Spirit Affinity House will not dare to touch you."

Feng Jin Huang revealed a look of displeasure: "Mother, you don't need to make an explanation for father. Although I can understand father, I will not forgive him. For him to suddenly turn his back on Heavenly Court and not even telling us beforehand is simply abandoning his wife and daughter! One day, I will settle the score with him."

"Hehehe." Fairy Bai Qing laughed and shook her head, walking up to Feng Jin Huang and holding her hand: "You misunderstand your father. That demonic immortal unification song, which he kept as a symbol of our love, has never been used for anything other than singing in front of me. But he used it during the fate war to tell me that righteous immortals and demons are the same, his feelings for me had never changed, and even when he left the righteous path and returned to the demonic path, it wouldn't end the relationship of our family."

"Do you believe me? As long as I give out the slightest hint of inclination to leave Spirit Affinity House, he will definitely take the initiative to bring me away. He understands me well and knows that I do not want to become a demonic path member. Therefore, he gave us both the opportunity to choose our side freely. He didn't want his ideals to become a burden on us."

Feng Jinhuang snorted coldly: "Father would rather help Fang Yuan, the great demon, than help my master. It's true that master was stubborn and was always nagging about fate and all that, but he was ultimately kind to us and truly had my best interests in mind. Father was simply too cold and heartless."

"Mother, since you are fine now, I'll be leaving."

"Oh you." Fairy Bai Qing sighed, but did not ask her daughter to stay.

When Feng Jin Huang left Quiet Rain Valley, she met with two female Gu Masters.

One was beautiful while the other was cute, they were acquaintances of Feng Jin Huang, they were anxiously waiting outside the valley.

After seeing Feng Jin Huang, they showed joy on their faces as they went to her.

"Senior sister, we heard you came here so we rushed over to find you!" The beautiful woman was Qin Juan.

"Senior sister, sorry, I... I did not want to snatch your opportunity..." Sun Yao had a cute and round face, she was very anxious now.

Qin Juan and Sun Yao were good friends with Feng Jin Huang, they had always followed behind her.

But in the recent years, Feng Jin Huang followed Duke Long and went away to cultivate dream path, they did not meet much during this period.

Feng Jin Huang laughed aloud and stretched out her hand to nudge Sun Yao's forehead: "Oh, you've done well this time, so why are you apologizing. The nomination quota is just a small matter, am I unable to become immortal without this funding? For me, becoming a Gu Immortal is by no means an obstacle. It's just that I have to consider the kind of Gu Immortal I want to become. But for you, this is a rare opportunity, so seize it well."

After speaking to Sun Yao, Feng Jin Huang looked at Qin Juan: "You've always been quite active and have good perseverance, but this time, when fusing with the dao marks, why did you faint? If not, the nomination would have been yours this time."

Qin Juan did not dare to retort: "Senior sister, you are right, I have slacked off on my cultivation."

"No, that is not so, senior sister. Sister Qin Juan was injured at that time, she could not endure the ordeal and fainted." Sun Yao quickly clarified.

"So that's how it was." Feng Jin Huang nodded her head and said regrettably: "It is indeed a great loss. Fang Yuan destroyed fate Gu and refined it into countless heaven path dao marks, which were dispersed to the people in the world. The more heaven path dao marks you absorb, the more beneficial it will be in the future. Be it cultivation or developing the immortal aperture, it will benefit with no harm. But there's no harm in not having any, at best it's just an opportunity. What determines your achievements in life will still depend on your own talents and efforts."

"Yes, Qin Juan will listen to senior sister's teachings." Qin Juan bowed.

Feng Jin Huang smiled again: "Let's go, I will give you two some guidance."

Qin Juan and Sun Yao revealed joyful expressions, the latter jumped around cheering: "That's great, we haven't been together for such a long time."

The three of them walked together, gradually leaving Quiet Rain Valley.

Within the valley, Fairy Bai Qing retracted her investigative method.

"Daughter, you've grown up." Fairy Bai Qing had a relieved expression.

Feng Jin Huang was very clear about her own circumstances, as well as Heavenly Court and the ten great ancient sects. Towards Feng Jiu Ge's actions, she had her own opinion, but she was able to put it aside and make a clear judgment, she had a solid foundation of skills.

"Maybe, your betrayal has hastened our daughter's maturity. We should let her walk on her own path."

"As a mother, all I can do is to wish the best for her."

"Of course, if some people in the sect do not know what is good for them and go overboard, I will not avoid conflict either." Fairy Bai Qing's expression turned cold.

At the same time, on another mountain, Affection Peak.

Spirit Affinity House's Li Jun Ying and Xu Hao went to visit Zhao Lian Yun.

Zhao Lian Yun had already become an immortal, she was assigned by Spirit Affinity House recently and became the Affection Peak Lord.

She was able to achieve what she had today thanks to the support of Xu Hao and Li Jun Ying, in addition to her own efforts. Zhao Lian Yun was also guided by the two immortals during her Gu Immortal cultivation journey and the management of her immortal aperture, so she was able to avoid many pitfalls.

Zhao Lian Yun remembered these debts in her heart, so when Xu Hao and Li Jun Ying visited her, she quickly came out of cultivation and attended to them personally.

But hearing their request, Zhao Lian Yun felt troubled.

"Seniors, you want me to use my status as the current generation fairy to deal with Feng Jin Huang and Fairy Bai Qing?"

"Indeed, now is the best opportunity! Feng Jiu Ge betrayed us and caused Heavenly Court to lose and Fate to be destroyed. If we target them now, we will definitely win." Xu Hao had a fierce expression.

The hatred between him and Feng Jiu Ge had a long history. In the past, he had hated Feng Jiu Ge so much that he held back key information and intelligence, almost causing him to die. Feng Jiu Ge had a very strong stance in his political manipulation, ostracizing the couple to the fringe of Spirit Affinity House in this power struggle. Most of the time, the two immortals were at a disadvantage against Feng Jiu Ge, they could only support each other with difficulty.

For them, Feng Jiu Ge's betrayal was great news, it was worth celebrating.

"This..." Zhao Lian Yun hesitated: "Feng Jiu Ge has already betrayed Heavenly Court, seniors, I know that you have grudges with him, but why do you want to implicate his family?"

"Oh Lian Yun, we cannot be too kindhearted sometimes. Think about it, think about the time you competed with Feng Jin Huang over the fairy position." Li Jun Ying urged: "If we do not use this chance, we will regret it in the future. You do not need to worry about it, I will tell you something, our sect's nominee was originally Feng Jin Huang but now she has been removed from the list."

"Seniors, people should let others off when possible." Zhao Lian Yun explained, she was not willing to do that. Conflicts should be resolved and not deepened, back then, when competing for the fairy position, both of them had used above board methods, Feng Jin Huang had a deep background but did not use any unscrupulous ways to deal with her as well.

Even though Zhao Lian Yun and Feng Jin Huang were competitors, Zhao Lian Yun admired Feng Jin Huang's personality, she had no ill feelings towards her.

Xu Hao did not listen to her words: "Back then, did the demon Feng Jiu Ge spare us?"

"You are too kind for your own good, Lian Yun." Li Jun Ying frowned.

Zhao Lian Yun sighed to herself, she changed her words and explained: "Seniors, we need to analyze this situation deeply. Even though the sect nominated someone else, Heavenly Court did not directly take away Feng Jin Huang's status. From that, we can see the attitude of Heavenly Court is still unclear towards her."

"Precisely because they are uncertain now, we need to deal the fatal blow and affirm their decision! The fight over authority will never cease, only when a true victor is decided can there be peace." Li Jun Ying said with deep meaning.

Zhao Lian Yun sighed again, she could only accept their request.

There was no choice, she owed them a big favor after all. Even though she was unwilling, people had to do some things that they did not want to in this world. They had helped her greatly, if she rejected them, what would others think?

Zhao Lian Yun was half an otherworldly demon, even though she was the current generation fairy, Spirit Affinity House still ostracized her. If she lost her relationship with Xu Hao and Li Jun Ying, she would truly become a loner.

The two immortals saw that Zhao Lian Yun agreed, they were overjoyed, they promised her a huge reward.

Zhao Lian Yun was not interested in the reward, after the two of them left, she continued her closed cultivation.

The destruction of Fate was actually great news to Zhao Lian Yun. With this, Ma Hong Yun's revival would be much easier and less troublesome.

But Ma Hong Yun's soul was still in Fang Yuan's hands.

Thus, Zhao Lian Yun had to cultivate and raise her strength, to make preparations to save her beloved.

In the secret room, Zhao Lian Yun calmed down and inspected her own immortal aperture.

Lian Yun blessed land had 5700km2 of land, the rate of time was one-to-thirteen. The terrain was mostly grassland and plains.

But after the heaven path dao marks were absorbed, Lian Yun blessed land started to change in many aspects.

Firstly, the ground cracked to form huge trenches, next, there was torrential rain as huge rivers were formed. The rivers overflowed and floods plagued the surroundings.

After three days and three nights, the floods receded, leaving behind vast expanses of fertile mud. Small ditches and rivers connected to the main channel of the giant river, forming an elaborate and dense network of rivers.

Zhao Lian Yun witnessed the transformation of her immortal aperture the entire time, she was dazed and greatly shocked internally.

"With heaven path dao marks, the immortal aperture will transform and become closer to a truly balanced environment. Even though there are temporary losses, the potential and prospects will rise by many times."

Zhao Lian Yun had divine concealment from Thieving Heaven's true inheritance. She did not face calamities and tribulations, this was beneficial and also detrimental, her immortal aperture development had always been a problem. But with the addition of heaven path dao marks, this problem was reduced greatly.

"If only I had more heaven path dao marks!"

"Sigh, what a pity that I only obtained six and a half heaven path dao marks, and they are all segmented too, I do not have a single complete heaven path dao mark."

"How many heaven path dao marks did Fang Yuan get? He was the person refining the Gu, he was the closest to these heaven path dao marks."

Zhao Lian Yun sighed.

She could not imagine it or find the answer, but she knew that the difference between her and Fang Yuan had been greatly increased again.

Chapter 1972: Fang Yuan's Disaster Relief

"Wake up, wake up, kid!"

Peng Da groaned and barely opened his eyes to see a bearded uncle, slapping him in the face with a rough palm.

Peng Da was in a trance, and it was only then that he recognized the man in front of him.

"Uncle Mo Li." He called out: "Wasn't I sleeping on the camel?"

Peng Da looked around, he could not help but be stunned once more.

There was sand everywhere, the caravan was nowhere to be seen, leaving only him and Mo Li, both were in a messy state.

"Ouch." Peng Da groaned as he realized he had bruises all over his body.

Uncle Mo Li looked at Peng Da and sighed: "You kid, I don't know what to say about you, you are so lucky! Many Gu Masters fled desperately, they all died. You were deeply asleep but survived. However, if I hadn't discovered your faint breath in time and dug you out, I'm afraid you would have been buried alive."

"Uncle Mo Li, you've saved me once again." Peng Da grabbed both of Mo Li's hands, saying gratefully: "But what in the world had happened?"

"It's a natural disaster, I've never seen it before." Uncle Mo Li let out a heavy sigh.

"So... what about our caravan?"

"Sigh, it's just the two of us now."

What?! Peng Da could not help but stare with wide eyes and scream in his heart: "How can this world be so vicious, there was a natural disaster with no warning! I just slept for a bit and almost died again! My lord, what kind of world have I come to. It is simply a brutal and terrible place to live!"

"At least we're still alive." Mo Li knocked Peng Da on the head: "Kid, you don't look satisfied? To be alive after a natural disaster like that is the greatest of all blessings!"

"Look at me." Mo Li pointed his finger at his chest: "I've worked hard most of my life to own such a caravan. And now it's all gone! Look on the bright side, otherwise we won't survive until tomorrow. Sigh, it would be great if I could become an immortal!"

"Immortal? There are immortals in this world?"

Mo Li looked at Peng Da: "Did you forget everything?! You forgot even immortals? Sigh, I'll explain in the future, let's leave first."

Peng Da followed Mo Li as they left, heading towards the closest oasis.

Peng Da followed behind Mo Li and asked with caution: "Are there many disasters like this?"

"Of course!" Mo Li said in a vicarious tone: "It's not easy for us to make a living in the desert. Sandstorms are the killers that visit often. Sometimes there are also flying blade hurricanes, and each gust of wind can condense into a huge wind blade that cuts everything wherever it goes. In addition to natural disasters, there are also vicious beasts. For example, we are in wolf desert, desert wolves are most plentiful here."

Howl—!

As Mo Li was saying that, a group of desert wolves suddenly emerged from under the desert.

"Wolves, wolves!" Peng Da jumped up in fright: "Oh heaven, they're coming out from under the sand! So many heads, what do we do, uncle?!"

Mo Li looked pale and cursed out loud: "Damn it! Why weren't these desert wolves wiped out by the natural disaster?"

It was not strange.

The qi tides were the phenomenon of fusing heaven and earth qi, it originated from the Heavenly Dao. But the Heavenly Dao would not wipe out all life, there was a chance of survival in every situation. Mo Li and Peng Da were able to survive, other lifeforms naturally had such an opportunity as well.

The desert wolves emerged from everywhere, but strangely enough, although they spotted Peng Da and Mo Li, they did not come to attack, instead they quickly assembled, howling and staring at the desert ground.

Rustle rustle....

With a series of moving sand sounds, golden scorpions emerged from the ground. These golden scorpions were all the size of a millstone, Peng Da watched with chills in his heart.

The golden scorpion group and the desert wolf group were engaged in a brutal fight.

Whenever a desert wolf was stung by a golden scorpion's needle, it would immediately foam saliva at the mouth, fall to the ground, and eventually die. On the other hand, the golden scorpions could not fight against the desert wolves' claws and teeth, and were often torn apart by the wolves' claws.

The two groups of beasts fought, because they were weak in intelligence, they paid no attention to Mo Li and Peng Da who were close by.

Peng Da looked frightened and pale. This world was too dangerous, no matter which beast group won, they would surely still end up attacking the humans.

"We must break out!" Mo Li gritted his teeth with a firm expression.

"But uncle, we're surrounded by golden scorpions and desert wolves." Peng Da wanted to cry.

"Do you want to wait to be eaten?" Mo Li said, about to move: "Kid, can you fight?"

"Huh? I, I can't, I have amnesia."

"These desert wolves and golden scorpions don't care if you have amnesia. Stay close to me and do your best to save yourself. There is at least hope for breaking out." Mo Li said and laughed, "If breaking out fails, you'll have to go fill the bellies of the beasts. But don't worry, you won't die alone, there's still me."

Peng Da could not help but roll his eyes, rather than dying like this, he would prefer to be buried alive!

Mo Li started to break out and Peng Da yelled: "Uncle, wait for me!"

He could only desperately follow behind Mo Li.

It was fine when they were still, but when they moved, they alerted the scorpion and wolf groups.

Almost at the same time, there were several golden scorpions and desert wolves, one left and one right, attacking them.

Mo Li grunted and activated his mortal Gu, but he only managed to repel two of the beasts before they got encircled by the groups.

"Breaking out has failed!" Mo Li sighed and gave up the fight.

Peng Da clutched his head and fell into despair, he stuttered: "Am... am I going to die?!"

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

At this moment, be they the mini five regions or the mini nine heavens, chaos was everywhere, the entire place was in a commotion.

Mini Southern Border's mountains collapsed, the terrain became disorganized, Mini Central Continent's river channels changed paths and caused torrential floods, Mini Western Desert had sandstorms everywhere that devoured cities and oases.

Mini Northern Plains.

An intense snowstorm was blowing, a pure white flame, fluttering in the blizzard, attached itself to wherever it burned.

This was the special fire immortal material — frost ice flame.

In places where the ice and snow path dao marks were dense, there would be a certain degree of probability that this special flame would be produced. Most of this flame was filled with ice and snow path dao marks, but the heart of the flame had dense fire path dao marks.

"We cannot let this frost ice flame spread everywhere!" Snowman Gu Immortal Xue Er was in charge of the situation, she tried to salvage it.

She was tasked by Fang Yuan to manage Triple Sacred Mountain, she controlled the snow crystal formation and focused on the growth of the snowman tribe's expansion.

Frost ice flames started to spread on triple sacred mountain, once the flames grew to a certain size, be they snowmen or snow monsters, they were burnt to death while crying in agony.

The snowmen were in chaos, they escaped and trampled on each other, causing unnecessary deaths.

Amidst the raging chaos, only a handful of snowman Gu Masters were trying to maintain order. But unfortunately, even with their cultivation, it was difficult to do anything against the immortal material frost ice flame.

"Oh no, the frost ice flame has reached the ice path crystal essence!" Xue Er's face turned pale, she became anxious.

She had just now tried to save more of the snowmen, and as a result, she had lost sight of this, allowing the frost ice flame to appear in the snow crystal formation.

The ice path crystal essence was the core of the snow crystal formation, Fang Yuan used the formation to spread out the frost energy created by the ice path crystal essence, that would constantly alter the environment inch by inch, creating a living habitat that suited the snowmen.

Xue Er felt deep regret as she watched the frost ice flame burn the ice path crystal essence, while being helpless against it.

Xue Er could not help but tear up and blame herself. The snow crystal formation was entrusted to her by Fang Yuan, it was the foundation for the snowman tribe's growth, but it was actually going to be destroyed because of her mistake.

She felt that she had let down the snowmen, she had let down Fang Yuan.

But at this moment, a figure suddenly appeared.

"Fang Yuan!" Xue Er was stunned before happiness appeared on her face.

Fang Yuan grabbed the empty space in front of him, all of the frost ice flames within the formation were drawn away.

Fang Yuan suddenly grunted as his body shook, pale white traces appeared around his body all of a sudden.

From these pale white traces, Xue Er felt a vast power that surged in heaven and earth!

"These are... heaven path dao marks! Oh heavens, there are so many heaven path dao marks, he must have at least a thousand!" Xue Er covered her mouth in surprise.

"I will leave the rest to you." Fang Yuan smiled at Xue Er as he brought the frost ice flame away with him and vanished on the spot.

Xue Er felt relaxed but worry soon appeared in her heart: "My dear fiance has so many heaven path dao marks, no wonder he went into seclusion after the fate war and rarely fought. Sigh, I am so useless, I could not help him at all. I could not even defend this snow crystal formation!"

Fang Yuan appeared to help Xue Er alleviate the crisis of the snowmen in Mini Northern Plains, he immediately went back to his secret room to continue his closed cultivation.

When he was refining fate Gu, Fang Yuan had the best position, because he was doing his best to absorb the heaven path dao marks, he had more than three thousand heaven path dao marks on his body, they were all complete and intact dao marks!

One could say that he was the biggest winner in this plan that Red Lotus created.

But this benefit was too great, he could not process it in the meantime. The sovereign immortal body had non-conflicting dao marks, with the addition of heaven path dao marks, that also meant that Sovereign grotto-heaven gained three thousand heaven path dao marks all of a sudden.

These heaven path dao marks created a huge impact on Sovereign grotto-heaven.

The impact was in many different aspects and had varying effects. They could be as large as mountains and rivers shifting, but also small like a changing tributary channel.

"The way of heaven is to take away surpluses while replenishing deficits. It focuses on the balance of living beings, they limit each other. Even in an extreme environment like the snow crystal formation, the Heavenly Dao could alter it and create fire path dao marks within the ice and snow path dao marks, once the frost ice flame spreads its destruction, Mini Northern Plains would be completely altered beyond recognition."

"Of course, if we ignore it, my Sovereign grotto-heaven will benefit from this, we will create a complete ecosystem that has balance and good prospects in the future.

"However, this method consumes too much of my foundation, it is also what Red Lotus Demon Venerable wants to see!"

Fang Yuan smiled coldly.

Fate Gu was destroyed, Red Lotus Demon Venerable's plan succeeded, Fang Yuan no longer had any value to him. Thus, Red Lotus Demon Venerable schemed and used the heaven path dao marks to restrict Fang Yuan, to limit his growth speed.

However, even though Fang Yuan saw through this, he had to take the bait. It was because Fang Yuan noticed that sovereign immortal fetus Gu was tampered by Spectral Soul, he needed the heaven path dao marks to counter Spectral Soul's arrangements.

Red Lotus Demon Venerable had been making use of Fang Yuan, it was evident from the rank seven future self killer move. But Fang Yuan also made use of Red Lotus, he used this Demon Venerable's plan to destroy fate Gu, which was his biggest problem, he used Red Lotus' million year plan to escape from the clutches of Spectral Soul's arrangement.

Zhao Lian Yun allowed the heaven path dao marks to make the alterations but Fang Yuan decided to interfere with them.

The heaven path dao marks altered the sovereign immortal aperture, he actively participated, resisting and cooperating with the alterations to preserve his immortal aperture's foundation.

This cooperation and resistance gave Fang Yuan a lot of insight.

Heaven path was merciless and impartial, human path was putting up a resistance, these two intertwined in Fang Yuan's heart, shining in different radiance.

"Time is about right." A while later, Fang Yuan moved again.

This time, he stored the sovereign immortal aperture, his main body arrived in the world of the five regions.

He stood in Western Desert as he looked at a tree in front of him.

This tree was not even eight feet tall, the branches were short, thin and twisted like monstrous claws, making it look extremely ugly. But the strange thing was, it had an enormous shadow of light. This shadow of light was extremely large, reaching five or six hundred feet. The shadow of light was like a flourishing tree with many branches and leaves. The tree branches were white as snow, the flowers were pink like cherries. There were clusters of small fruits among the floral leaves that had yet to ripen, with all sorts of colors.

It was the thousand wish tree.

Around the thousand wish tree was Fang Yuan's immortal formation.

Right now, he stored the immortal formation and took the thousand wish tree along with him, they were all sent into the sovereign immortal aperture.

This action caused a storm to surge, a vast air current spread out to the surroundings.

Fang Yuan did not care about this, he turned into a flash of light and flew into the sky.

The air currents rampaged in the surrounding deserts, causing loud sounds to be emitted.

Peng Da and Mo Li failed to breakout, they were surrounded by desert wolves, right when they were about to die, the air currents arrived.

The desert wolf group went into chaos as they scattered and escaped.

Peng Da jolted: "Another disaster!"

Mo Li stared with wide eyes as he looked and laughed: "Haha, we are saved! This is not a disaster, it is merely a normal hurricane. Let's go!"

Chapter 1973: Going After Fang Yuan

After the qi tide passed, clouds were sparse in the sky, it was a refreshing sight.

A yellow cloud flew high in the sky, sprinkling light sand behind it along the way.

There was a female immortal sitting on the yellow cloud. She had a corpulent body, her belly was bulging, her entire body resembled a water vat, she was a member of Mo clan, a super force in Western Desert. There was a title for her in Western Desert's Gu Immortal world — Plump Lady.

Plump Lady did not dislike this title at all. She felt beautiful for being fat, and upon learning of this title, she liked it so much that she publicly called herself this from then on. In time, even her original name was forgotten in place of this title.

"Huh?" As the yellow cloud flew, Plump Lady suddenly had a change of expression, sensing something unusual.

Thus, the yellow cloud slightly contracted and flew down diagonally, changing its course slightly before suspending in mid-air.

Plump Lady stood up from the yellow cloud and looked down at the giant pit beneath her feet.

This giant pit was partially hidden by the wind blowing yellow sand and covering it, but Plump Lady was a native of Western Desert, she was all too familiar with the landscape of the sand pit.

"This isn't a naturally formed sand pit, but rather an empty space left behind after something in it was drawn away."

"This aura... it's the aura of an ancient desolate plant!"

Plump Lady's eyes shined with bright light, she immediately understood: a Gu Immortal had secretly made a move to steal an ancient desolate plant from here.

Plump Lady snorted coldly as anger rose in her heart. Although she did not know what this ancient desolate plant was, this place was wolf desert, the territory of Mo clan. Stealing this ancient desolate plant was the same as stealing the Mo clan.

"This ancient desolate plant must be quite valuable since it is able to hide and conceal itself from the detection of our clan. I'm afraid that it has already been discovered by some people long ago but they just did not take it. Now that qi tides is causing disasters, this person who stole the ancient desolate plant must have been worried that they would endanger this ancient desolate plant, and that's why they took it."

Plump Lady secretly analyzed the scene and carefully examined it.

The thief's actions were very clean, no obvious clues were left behind. Feeling disappointed, she had to use an information path Gu worm to inform the Mo clan, hoping that the clan would send good investigators to track down and capture this damned thief!

And finally, Plump Lady used information path Gu worms to record the scene before leaving. She had a mission right now, she could not waste time here.

As she flew along, she saw an oasis. The oasis was vast, and there was a stone city at the center. The city walls were short, but the overall length was long, there were a huge number of mortals living in the city, it was Sand Wolf City.

Sand Wolf City was one of the main cities of Mo clan.

Plump Lady did not cover her tracks and flew directly from high in the sky to the City Lord Manor.

There were already people at the City Lord Manor who were ready to receive her, when they saw the arrival of Plump Lady, they all fell to their knees and shouted: "We pay our respects to revered immortal!"

"Get up." Plump Lady stored the yellow cloud and stepped on the ground in front of everyone.

"Revered immortal, the arrival banquet has been prepared. It contains the best wine and delicacies of Sand Wolf City, as well as fresh fruits that were just picked today." The city lord spoke.

Plump Lady, however, waved her hand, she was not interested, she only said: "Prepare a secret room for me to undergo closed cultivation. Also, I asked you to gather Gu Masters with aptitude and loyalty, how is it going?"

"It's almost done. The vast majority of the city's Gu Masters have already been screened." The city lord replied quickly.

"Very well. After three days, I will take them away. Now, you can go and attend to your own matters."

"Yes, I will do my best to complete this task to the best of my ability." The city lord promised in succession.

The door of the secret room closed slowly, Plump Lady activated the formation here with a wave of her hand.

She looked exhausted as her divine sense probed into her immortal aperture, when she saw the scene inside the immortal aperture, she inevitably let out another deep sigh.

Her immortal aperture was originally a land of yellow sand and it was flat. At the heart of the desert, Plump Lady had carefully laid out more than six thousand acres of sand farms.

Her sand farms mainly produced two types of immortal materials, they were light sand and cold-warm flowing sand. They were the main sources of goods that Plump Lady produced for a long time.

But after the fate war, Plump Lady absorbed five heaven path dao marks, her immortal aperture started to change. The landscape became uneven, more and more sand dunes were created. Furthermore, there was a trench, as if a knife had come straight down across the center of the desert, splitting the entire desert, thousands of acres of sand farms were lost.

"I don't have wisdom path methods to make deductions and restrain this kind of natural development. Unless I hire a wisdom path Gu Immortal to take action, but my assets are not enough, I can't afford it. I might as well save this expense in case of future mishaps." Plump Lady lamented in her heart.

Mo clan had Gu Immortals that cultivated wisdom path, but they were not close to Plump Lady. In fact, even if the relationship was close, the wisdom path deductions would still cost Immortal essence, they could not work for Plump Lady for nothing, right? Therefore, there had to be a reward.

"Furthermore, I recently absorbed heaven and earth qi, my immortal aperture is unstable."

Right now, the five regional walls were gone, the five regions' heaven and earth qi had no obstruction and started to fuse. Western Desert's heaven and earth qi was changing gradually, this caused the foundation of Western Desert Gu Immortals' immortal apertures to start differing from the heaven and earth qi of the outer world.

When Gu Immortals absorb this heaven and earth qi, their immortal aperture would be unstable, there would be tremors.

The best way to deal with it was to cooperate with the change and continue absorbing and releasing heaven and earth qi. If one keeps themselves in closed cultivation, after the heaven and earth qi changes drastically, when they open the immortal aperture entrance to absorb heaven and earth qi, the tremors would be huge, the immortal aperture would suffer even more damage.

"If I had qi path attainment, I would be able to reduce the losses caused by the heaven and earth qi to a great extent."

Wisdom path was a difficult path while qi path had been declining for years, there were few qi path Gu Immortals left.

Plump Lady was only having dreams that were not realistic. In the end, she consoled herself: Even though she did not have wisdom path or qi path methods, other Gu Immortals were like her. Thus, she was not left behind in the dust by the majority of them.

But Plump Lady still felt intense danger in her heart.

This was something that all of the five regions' Gu Immortals were feeling.

The five regions were unified, everyone knew that life was no longer going to be peaceful anymore. Be they lone cultivators or super forces, they were making preparations for the huge battles in the future.

This time, Plump Lady was tasked to go to Sand Wolf City and bring back Gu Immortal seeds for Mo clan to nurture.

In fact, Mo clan or Western Desert were not the only ones, all of the forces in the five regions and two heavens were making preparations now.

In the past, the five regions and two heavens were quite peaceful, super forces nurtured Gu Immortals while considering the provision of resources and their storage.

But now, everyone was preparing for war, they were going to mobilize these resources!

Thus, all of the forces focused on nurturing Gu Immortals than keeping resources. There was a common view: If they did not nurture enough Gu Immortals, their enemies would get all of their resources if they were wiped out in the future. If they did not use up those resources beforehand, that would be too wasteful.

Plump Lady looked at her sand farms in the immortal aperture while feeling heartache. She could not discard these farms, they were her only sources of revenue, they were her biggest financial support pillar.

Plump Lady had to preserve them.

The future was uncertain, she did not know how long the qi tides would continue, but she had to salvage them regardless.

"In the current world, I'm afraid only Fang Yuan will know how long these qi tides would last, he has Spring Autumn Cicada and can rebirth from the future after all." Plump Lady felt deep envy and admiration regarding this.

Plump Lady rebuilt the sand farms in her immortal aperture, fixing the Gu formations inside.

The area where the Earth Trench appeared could not be fixed. Thus, her six thousand acre sand farm was split into two.

"If only I had an immortal Gu formation." Plump Lady felt a bit of regret, Mo clan also had formation path Gu Immortals, when she created the sand farm, Mo clan's formation path Gu Immortal had asked her if she needed help.

But Plump Lady rejected him.

On one hand, she did not want to expose her immortal aperture, on the other hand, she wanted to save cost.

After all, creating an immortal formation would use one of her Immortal Gu as the core. Plump Lady only had two rank six Immortal Gu herself.

Also, the payment of hiring the formation path Gu Immortal was not cheap.

"If I had created an immortal formation back then, my losses would be much lower. Sigh, how can anyone expect their own immortal aperture to be unsafe?"

Plump Lady thought of this and felt some envy towards the formation path Gu Immortal. During this period of time, he had been extremely popular with everyone, they were looking for him to create immortal Gu formations around their immortal aperture's resource points to protect them.

Plump Lady felt a little bitterness towards the earth path she cultivated, earth path was skilled at changing terrain, but Western Desert had the most number of earth path Gu Immortals. Plump Lady's earth path inheritance was also quite ordinary.

As for cultivating a second path?

Plump Lady did not even dare to think about such an absurd idea.

She was already facing problems cultivating just earth path in terms of time and finances.

Trying to juggle another path was courting death!

Moreover, only those rare and exceptional inheritances could allow one to dual cultivate. For example, an inheritance left by Thunder Ghost True Monarch or Duke Long.

After repairing her immortal aperture's sand farm, Plump Lady still had to buy some fertile sand.

Sand farms nurtured sand using sand, without enough sand-type immortal materials, the production would fall greatly.

Plump Lady took out her Gu worms and connected to treasure yellow heaven.

Treasure yellow heaven had all sorts of news, a large number of wills were conversing as they interacted.

Because of the huge change in the world, Gu Immortals could not move around now, on one hand, they had to absorb and release heaven and earth qi continuously to adapt to the main world, on the other hand, they also had to take care of their immortal apertures and repair them continuously like Plump Lady. Cases like Zhao Lian Yun who ignored the damage caused were quite rare.

Thus, Gu Immortals needed immortal materials or the help of Gu Immortals of other paths, treasure yellow heaven became a very popular destination for them.

"Another qi tide happened over here, a lot of deaths occurred."

"When are these qi tides going to end! Damn it, my fisheries have all been destroyed."

"I hate the fact that we cannot move around, the stronger the immortal aperture foundation, the longer we need to adapt to the heaven and earth qi and keep up with the five regions' transformation."

The Gu Immortals sighed as they talked about the news of these qi tides.

Other than that, there was Fang Yuan's arrest warrant!

A mysterious force described Fang Yuan's circumstances, they were willing to pay a huge sum for his latest information.

Fang Yuan had the sovereign immortal aperture, his sovereign immortal body had non-conflicting dao marks. More terrifyingly, he could annex people's apertures to skip calamities and tribulations, increasing his cultivation level. But now, Fang Yuan obtained too many heaven path dao marks, his strength had hit an all-time low. Whoever discovered his location would get a huge reward!

The sovereign immortal fetus Gu's secret was completely exposed, this was not Heavenly Court's doing. Fairy Zi Wei and Old Man Zheng Yuan had released the arrest warrant due to Spectral Soul's orders.

"Too strong! This sovereign immortal body is too terrifying, it can cultivate all paths."

"I finally understand why Fang Yuan's cultivation level rose so quickly! In the blink of an eye, he became a rank eight great expert."

"Who can have such a great fortuitous encounter?"

"Why does heaven favor this otherworldly demon! If I had his fortuitous encounters, I could achieve such great accomplishments as well."

The Gu Immortals were filled with jealousy and hatred.

"We cannot let him grow further, he can annex apertures, he is the enemy of all Gu Immortals."

"Let those experts handle him. I am just a minor character, why would I ever encounter Fang Yuan?"

"The reward is a huge amount of immortal materials, I wonder which lucky person will get them."

"Lucky person? Exposing the great demon Fang Yuan's location would be offending him, you call that lucky? We have all seen Fang Yuan's battle strength ourselves, even if he is at his weakest, how weak can that be? No matter how weak a person is, killing an ant is extremely easy regardless. Even if I find his location, I will not dare to expose him."

Plump Lady heard these discussions, she felt conflicting emotions within her.

The information had been released in treasure yellow heaven several days ago. It had received huge attention, it was the hot topic currently, without showing signs of dying down.

Everyone in the world had seen the fate war. Fang Yuan's performance was shockingly terrifying. The world knew about his pseudo venerable battle strength, the title of the number one demon in the world belonged to him, nobody dared to contest this!

"Hopefully, I never meet such a person in my life. No matter how fat I am, my size cannot compare to such a huge demon. If I get involved in his matters, I will die without doubt."

Plump Lady was quite aware of her situation, she was only enjoying the show as a spectator.

But she did not know that she had once fought against Fang Yuan. In fact, the ancient desolate plant that was stolen earlier was taken by Fang Yuan!

While Plump Lady entered closed cultivation, two figures in sorry states supported each other as they moved towards Sand Wolf City step by step.

The city guards did not chase them away, they could tell that these two were Gu Masters.

The guard walked towards them and extended his hand: "Entry fee of one primeval stone per person."

"There's still an entry fee?" One of the downcast Gu Masters started with wide eyes, he was Peng Da.

The middle aged Gu Master that he was supporting was naturally Mo Li.

The two of them were saved by the air currents generated when Fang Yuan took the thousand wish tree, after exerting effort, they finally reached Sand Wolf City.

"I have them." Mo Li was already prepared, he took out two primeval stones and handed them to the guard.

Peng Da took a look at these two primeval stones.

Along the way, he was taught by Mo Li, he could now inspect his aperture, he found that he had three Gu worms. He even understood the value of primeval stones, it was used as currency but also as a way to replenish a Gu Master's precious primeval essence!

"Two primeval stones to enter a city." Peng Da sighed: "Uncle Mo Li, I will return this sum to you."

Mo Li patted his shoulder: "Let's go kid. No matter how poor I am, I can still afford this fee. During this period, you should stay at my home, you are penniless and have no memory of this city, how can you live alone?"

Mo Li had guided Peng Da along the way, after finding that he knew nothing about Gu Master cultivation, he believed the words that he was amnesiac.

"Uncle, thank you so much. You saved my life and even helped me this much..."

"Don't say that!" Mo Li interrupted Peng Da and brought him into the city.

Mo Li's house was at the central area of Sand Wolf City, it was a huge house with a garden that had flowers growing in it.

"I am back!" Mo Li knocked on the door as his wife opened the door.

"You are finally back!" Mo Li's wife was a rank two Gu Master, seeing her husband, she was happy and surprised: "I heard the qi tide appeared, I thought you..."

"I was lucky and lived, but my caravan is completely ruined, only the two of us survived. Sigh!" Mo Li sighed deeply.

"Being alive is the greatest blessing!" Mo Li's wife turned her eyes.

"Auntie." Peng Da greeted after their conversation.

Mo Li's wife chuckled: "Little lad, thank you for taking care of my husband along the way."

Peng Da's face turned red as he said: "I am ashamed, it was uncle who took care of me during this journey, without his help, I would have died in the desert."

"As travelers outside, helping each other is necessary. Quickly come in." Mo Li's wife was very welcoming.

Mo Li and Peng Da had a rough journey, but they were finally safe now.

After showering in Mo Li's house, the two of them went to bed and fell sound asleep.

After sleeping from noon to night time, Peng Da was woken up by Mo Li for a scrumptious dinner.

After dinner, Mo Li said to his wife: "We still have some money left, even though my caravan was destroyed, as long as I am alive, I can rebuild a new caravan!"

But his wife had a hesitant look: "I haven't told you this, I was hesitating, thankfully, you returned alive."

"What is it?" Mo Li was curious as he asked.

"After you left, the city lord sent orders that they would select Gu Masters that had A grade aptitude and were loyal to Mo clan. Supposedly, this is an order from the higher-ups, they want to nurture Gu Masters to become Gu Immortals."

"Oh? There is such a thing?" Mo Li hesitated: "The city lord put up a public notice? I went past the city gates quickly, I did not see it."

Mo Li's wife continued: "Our son heard the news and wanted to sign up."

Mo Li laughed unconsciously: "To think our son would have such aspirations, but he only has B grade aptitude."

Mo Li's wife laughed: "Aptitude is not too important, loyalty to Mo clan is most important. If we show enough loyalty, our son might be selected."

Mo Li realized at once, asking:" How much?"

Mo Li's wife said a number, Peng Da's mouth became wide open.

Mo Li's wife was very troubled: "Even if we use all our remaining savings, it will not be enough. Husband, the decision is up to you."

Mo Li was silent for a moment before he resolved himself: "I will borrow! It is rare that our son is no longer lazy and wants to improve himself, this is a good thing. I will go and borrow shamelessly, I am sure we will gather enough funds."

"Husband..." Mo Li's wife was touched but felt worried as well: "But our caravan was destroyed, I am afraid..."

Mo Li smiled as he patted his chest, feeling confident: "Don't worry, I am a rank three Gu Master, my body is strong and my strength is intact. Everyone knows that I only need time, as long as my luck is not bad, I can recover from this loss!"

Chapter 1974: Creating An Opening

The sky was light purple in color, gathered in mid-air was a large area of grey clouds resembling thick fog, making the view of Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven quite unclear.

But the layout of this place was good, even Spectral Soul could not help but praise it.

He had disguised as a soul beast, he successfully infiltrated the grotto-heaven, after many days, he finally found out a lot of information about Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven.

This was a soul path grotto-heaven, there were a lot of soul path cultivation resources here, it had at least ten giant resource points! In history, it had once produced two rank eight soul path immortals at the same point in time, it was a very rare situation.

The biggest trait of Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven was that it had a soul pacifying immortal killer move that influenced all lifeforms in this grotto-heaven. This killer move could pacify soul beasts and bring peace to Gu Immortals' souls, it had a huge supplementary effect in soul cultivation.

There were three aspects in soul path cultivation, strengthening, refining, and pacifying the soul.

The most effective method to pacify the soul was using the water of Bewitching Lake, it was known as pacifying soul soup, the most delicious wine in the world. This was recorded in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

The soul pacifying killer move in Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven was created by mimicking the pacifying soul soup. Even Spectral Soul thought that the effect of this move was good.

Within Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven, soul beasts were the most plentiful of beasts.

It had raised soul beasts to begin with, now that Fate was destroyed and the five regions unified, in order to prepare for war, the Gu Immortals of Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven went outside to hunt and store more soul beasts.

But the higher-ups with Lady Cold Ash as the leader still did not think this was enough, they sent even more Gu Immortals outside to search for even more soul beasts.

Thanks to the soul pacifying killer move, even if immemorial soul beasts went into Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven, they would remain peaceful and would not rampage.

After An Xun returned to the grotto-heaven to rest for a few days, he received orders to go out and hunt soul beasts again.

"I am letting you command three thousand soul beasts with one immemorial soul beast as the guardian, do your best." Before leaving, Lady Cold Ash called for him.

An Xun was the tall and skinny Gu Immortal from earlier, he was the nephew of Lady Cold Ash, and also the Gu Immortal with the best prospects to go beyond rank seven in Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven.

"Thank you for the concern, aunt." An Xun said with difficulty: "But such a huge soul beast group, I do not have the ability to command them."

Lady Cold Ash waved her hand: "My killer move can allow you to command this soul beast group with ease for twenty days."

An Xun was overjoyed, he quickly thanked her.

He understood that his aunt was helping in secret and taking care of him. Even though Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven did not lack resources and had deep foundation, when nurturing Gu Immortals, seniority mattered.

Lady Cold Ash helped An Xun secretly, hoping that he would emerge victorious in the contest against An Chong and become the rank seven Gu Immortal who received the most support.

She was his aunt after all!

An Xun led the soul beast army and left Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven, heading to black heaven for his hunt.

For the next few days, his gains were little, he became a little anxious.

"Logically speaking, after the qi tide passes, there would be many dead lifeforms, their souls would be left behind and form more soul beasts." An Xun could not understand why this was not happening.

Along the way, he did not meet many soul beasts, but he gathered a lot of qi path immortal materials, he did not know whether to laugh or cry.

Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven was a soul path grotto-heaven, these qi path immortal materials were almost unusable, they could only be traded away.

An Xun could not understand why, but Spectral Soul knew: "It seems that after the qi tide passes, qi path dao marks flood the area, causing other paths to be suppressed. Soul path is no exception, it is hard to form new soul beasts. In contrast, qi path immortal materials are going to increase in numbers, they will be at an absurd number in the future."

Spectral Soul saw the trend and felt a little strange internally: "To think that qi path would regain its former glory!"

Qi path had been declining, but with the current situation where qi path immortal materials get produced widely in the five regions and two heavens, the abundance of resources would lower the cost of cultivation. It would create a trend of numerous qi path cultivators.

Spectral Soul turned into an ancient soul beast and secretly followed An Xun, he left Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven for his own objectives.

He had already inspected Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven, but he could not take action inside. Outside, it was a different story.

However, Spectral Soul did not act immediately, he patiently waited for a chance.

As expected, after more than ten days, An Xun encountered a group of soul beasts that numbered to more than a thousand.

"I finally met some." An Xun was overjoyed, he quickly manipulated the soul beast army to attack.

A huge battle began.

Initially, An Xun had the advantage, but soon, he found that an immemorial soul beast appeared in the enemy's group.

He quickly let out his guardian, it was also an immemorial soul beast.

The two immemorial soul beasts fought intensely, creating a small battlefield for themselves.

The enemy immemorial soul beast was much stronger than An Xun had expected, his immemorial soul beast quickly fell into a disadvantage, about to be defeated.

An Xun was shocked, he quickly acted to help out his immemorial soul beast.

Eventually, An Xun paid a huge price of suffering injuries to exterminate the enemy immemorial soul beast.

An Xun felt regret that he could not capture the wild immemorial soul beast, he had tried many methods to subdue it but he failed, he had no choice but to kill it in the end.

After the battle, An Xun counted his gains and losses, despite his heavy injuries, he gained eight hundred soul beasts overall, among which were many ancient soul beasts.

"This should be enough." An Xun let out a sigh of relief, these gains were sufficient, he did not let down Lady Cold Ash and her expectations.

But right when An Xun relaxed his mind, Spectral Soul struck at lightning speed, flying into An Xun's body.

An Xun's face distorted as he shook intensely, after a while, he returned to normal.

Spectral Soul came out of his body as An Xun knelt down: "I pay respects to master!"

"Mm." Spectral Soul nodded with a tired expression.

He had an ability to enter a life form's soul and forcefully modify it so that they would obey Spectral Soul from the depths of their soul with absolute loyalty.

But there were many limitations to this, he could not use it casually.

Back then, Spectral Soul subdued Fairy Zi Wei and Old Man Zheng Yuan when they were at their weakest. Fairy Zi Wei and Old Man Zheng Yuan were in poor conditions then, while she had also been subconsciously influenced by him over time.

Thus, in order to deal with An Xun, Spectral Soul had to wait until he was at his weakest.

The reason he caused this huge soul beast battle instead of directly attacking because he needed to deceive Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven. An Xun was a rank seven Gu Immortal, it was not easy for him to explore black heaven, there were investigative methods used on him. If anything happened to him, Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven would react to it rapidly.

"After subduing An Xun, I have an opening in Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven, is Lady Cold Ash still far from my grasp? Hehe." Spectral Soul chuckled.

Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven had the most suitable cultivation resources for Spectral Soul, he could take control of it and use it to interfere in the world affairs to accomplish his goals.

"I have already created my opening here, it is far better than hunting soul beasts myself! I wonder what breakthrough Fairy Zi Wei has made already."

At the same time, in a certain Central Continent valley.

"Fang Yuan, you cannot escape." Fairy Zi Wei called out, using a purple meteor attack.

The purple meteor landed on Fang Yuan as it pierced his chest, creating a gaping hole.

Fang Yuan stared at Fairy Zi Wei, he fell with a loud sound and scattered into smoke.

"Another clone!" Even though Fairy Zi Wei was prepared for it, she still felt tired seeing this.

Fairy Zi Wei and Old Man Zheng Yuan had already killed hundreds of Fang Yuan's clones.

She immediately captured and stored the smoke that the myriad self clone turned into.

Next, she took out a sealed clone of Fang Yuan from her aperture.

She instilled the smoke of the destroyed myriad self clone into the sealed clone.

Soon, the white smoke was absorbed by the clone, its cultivation level rose again.

These myriad self clones were summoned by Fang Yuan during the battle in Heavenly Court, Fairy Zi Wei had used the transportation formation to send them all over Central Continent.

Fairy Zi Wei was ordered by Spectral Soul to find Fang Yuan, after putting up the arrest warrant, all the information she received involved these clones.

Fairy Zi Wei had no choice but to pay them the reward as they had provided information. But she also went around laboriously to capture the Fang Yuan myriad self clones all over the continent.

If she left them unattended to, these clones would be the best concealment for Fang Yuan's main body. Fairy Zi Wei also had another idea, what if Fang Yuan was hiding among these clones?

This was not impossible.

"Thankfully, these myriad self clones can sense each other, when I capture one, I can use the connection to find the next clone."

"But..."

Fairy Zi Wei watched as the sealed clone of Fang Yuan rose in cultivation level, she felt worried: "Fang Yuan's human path attainment level is so high. These clones can actually devour each other and show such autonomy..."

"Fang Yuan's strength is low because because of two reasons. Firstly, the heaven and earth qi are converging and forming qi tides, immortal apertures are becoming unstable, secondly, the heaven path dao marks he absorbed are also like a seal."

"Among the different paths, human path is the most suitable for dealing with heaven path. Who knows how many heaven path dao marks Fang Yuan gained, how long can they suppress him for?"

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

The thousand wish tree was planted in Mini Central Continent.

An immortal formation with the thousand wish tree as the core was already set up, it started to activate now.

Due to the influence of the heaven path dao marks, Sovereign grotto-heaven had been encountering disasters and calamities endlessly, but even in this situation, Fang Yuan still spent effort to create and defend this formation.

"Good." After observing for a while, Fang Yuan smiled as he saw the formation working normally.

This was a human path formation, the thousand wish tree was a human path ancient desolate plant, with his formation path and human path attainment levels, Fang Yuan finally made such progress.

The formation in Mini Central Continent was the main formation, there was going to be four more human path sub-formations created in the other mini regions.

"I am trying to use human path to restrict heaven path, let's see how well it works!" Fang Yuan held high expectations for this plan.

Chapter 1975: World Poetry Competition

Immemorial black heaven.

"They're here!" An Xun shouted excitedly.

Under his silent supervision, a soul beast army of a thousand charged towards his ambush.

Once they entered his range, An Xun activated his ambushing soul beasts, attacking all of the wild soul beasts from all sides.

While An Xun controlled the soul beast army, he activated Immortal Gu and unleashed all sorts of immortal killer moves.

As his killer moves landed on them, the soul beasts on his side gained a boost in battle strength, speed, and defense to some degree.

This battle lasted for several minutes, An Xun successfully killed four hundred wild soul beasts while the rest were captured.

"Master!" An Xun gathered a pile of soul cores and offered them to Spectral Soul.

Spectral Soul opened his mouth and absorbed all of these soul cores into his body, starting to digest them.

After last time when he secretly followed An Xun and enslaved him, Spectral Soul managed to get his plan started.

He secretly passed the profundities of soul path cultivation to An Xun, according to the soul path Immortal Gu that An Xun had, he personally created soul path killer moves for him.

An Xun's strength continued to rise, he took many missions to capture soul beasts.

For this purpose, Spectral Soul created two methods, one could find out the location of wild soul beasts, the other was a simplified immortal formation that could lure soul beasts after it was set up.

With these two methods, An Xun captured wild soul beasts with much higher efficiency, each mission was completed to a high degree.

Lady Cold Ash saw that her nephew did not let down her expectations but even went beyond that and shined brightly, she was very happy about it.

Within Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven, Lady Cold Ash was the only rank eight, she was naturally their leader.

Below her were An Chong and An Xun. Last time, when Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch opened his grotto-heaven and invited them, Lady Cold Ash brought the two of them with her, she wanted to let them gain some experience, and also let them meet up with others to become acquainted with other Gu Immortals.

When Lady Cold Ash was in the meeting in the grotto-heaven, An Chong and An Xun stayed outside the grotto-heaven and talked with the other rank seven elites of other grotto-heavens.

But Lady Cold Ash did not know that An Xun was already turned into Spectral Soul's slave. In fact, the entire Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven, including herself, was currently targeted by Spectral Soul, their future was bleak.

The more missions he completed, and the higher the completion rate, the more advantage An Xun would have in this competition.

Lady Cold Ash could see this, the other Gu Immortals in the grotto-heaven also noticed this.

One day, Lady Cold Ash summoned An Chong as she instructed: "Since the last time Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch called for us to have a meeting, he was very active in asking the grotto-heavens to work together. But in Central Continent's black heaven, there are many variant humans but only two rank eight humans including me. Thankfully, I have already contacted Granny Skeleton, she is a rank eight Gu Immortal of Eastern Sea's black heaven. In this journey to Eastern Sea, you are representing Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven, you will meet with Granny Skeleton and show our sincerity to cooperate."

"Yes." An Chong replied, feeling bitter inside.

He knew Lady Cold Ash's intention.

By sending him on this mission, she was helping An Xun to claim victory, he was going to become the nurturing target of Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven.

If An Xun performed similarly to himself, An Chong would feel unresigned and angry. But An Xun did really well, far better than him, even An Chong felt that he had no chance to win.

He accepted this mission, he took some immortal materials from Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven's inventory as a meeting gift.

After leaving Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven, he passed the heavenly wind qi wall and arrived in the five regions.

He concealed his traces and went from Central Continent to Eastern Sea. Next, he went through the heavenly wind qi wall in Eastern Sea and to Granny Skeleton's area.

When the regional walls existed, Gu Immortals had a lot of trouble crossing regions. Many strong Gu Immortals would choose to travel using the two heavens.

But now that the regional walls had vanished, even a black heaven Gu Immortal like An Chong could travel through the five regions.

Black heaven had a dangerous environment, it would be troublesome if one met an immemorial desolate beast. Even though An Chong had an immemorial soul beast hiding in his immortal aperture, he only had rank seven cultivation level after all. Especially now when the qi tides were rampaging, the five regions Gu Immortals had to recuperate, they rarely moved around. Thus, it was easy for An Chong to travel.

Along the way, An Chong found that the five regions were facing huge disasters, the qi tides had caused much destruction.

Regardless, he did not meet with any unexpected mishaps, he successfully arrived in Eastern Sea and went up to immemorial black heaven. According to the communication method left by Lady Cold Ash, he successfully went into Shattered Bone grotto-heaven and met with Granny Skeleton.

"Fate has been destroyed, the qi tides are surging. With the current changing world, if we do not cooperate, the future will be uncertain. We are all humans, we should work together and stay united." Granny Skeleton did not create problems for An Chong, she agreed immediately.

Granny Skeleton continued: "However, in Eastern Sea's black heaven, variant human forces are more dominant. Lady Cold Ash wants us to cooperate, why would Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch do nothing? He must be gathering the variant human forces of the other regions' black heaven as well."

An Chong knew that Granny Skeleton would not say unimportant things, he quickly asked: "Senior, what insight might you have?"

Granny Skeleton said: "Since we are uniting the humans of immemorial black heaven, why don't we include white heaven as well? I will not hide it from you, I have contacted many people already, the response is quite good. Among them, there is one key person, we need your help to persuade them."

Granny Skeleton paused and continued: "This person is a rank eight Gu Immortal, he is known as Old Immortal Hua Yu, he controls Profound Literature grotto-heaven. He has quite the reputation in Eastern Sea's white heaven, if we can ally with this person, it will definitely bring along a number of white heaven Gu Immortals, we will save a lot of effort."

An Chong heard this and thought: Going to meet Old Immortal Hua Yu was not part of his mission, but if he could accomplish this feat, he would have a chance to compete with An Xun again.

Thinking of this, An Chong made his decision, saying to Granny Skeleton: "Since senior has already planned this, junior will set out for Profound Literature grotto-heaven."

Granny Skeleton praised: "Good, as expected of a member of Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven. Old Immortal Hua Yu does not like to fight or kill, that is why he has little interest in an alliance. If you can succeed in this trip, I will reward you greatly!"

An Chong left Shattered Bone grotto-heaven and went to immemorial white heaven, meeting with Old Immortal Hua Yu.

Even though Old Immortal Hua Yu had little interest in an alliance, An Chong was representing Lady Cold Ash in this trip. The other party was also a rank eight Gu Immortal, Old Immortal Hua Yu did not dare to ignore them, he opened the door and invited An Chong in.

After seeing Old Immortal Hua Yu, An Chong gave the speech that he thought up along the way but Old Immortal Hua Yu was unmoved.

"My Profound Literature grotto-heaven does not involve itself in worldly affairs, we are a neutral party. Even though we do not want to make an alliance, the two of us can still exchange resources."

Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven produced soul path resources, it was quite useful for Profound Literature grotto-heaven.

Seeing that he could not convince Old Immortal Hua Yu, An Chong thought that this transaction was at least better than nothing. This was the first time they were interacting, after several transactions, wouldn't they get closer?

With a deeper relationship, requesting for an alliance would be much better hopes.

After saying goodbye to Old Immortal Hua Yu, An Chong was asked to stay by another Gu Immortal.

Gu Immortal Hua Song attended to him, he said: "You have traveled a long journey to come here, you should stay for a few days. During this period, the mortal imperial court is holding a world poetry competition, many beautiful poems will be created and recited then, it is quite interesting to watch."

An Chong had already heard from Granny Skeleton about the poetry culture of Profound Literature grotto-heaven. All of their Gu Immortals were scholarly and preferred literature works over beautiful women or wine.

An Chong wanted to improve his relationship with Profound Literature grotto-heaven, even though he had no interest in poetry or recital, he could not refuse their kind invitation, he agreed to stay.

The world poetry competition commenced.

This was an unprecedented event, Profound Literature grotto-heaven had never held such a huge competition before. Thus, all sorts of talents gathered from all over Profound Literature grotto-heaven.

Other than the talented scholars who wanted to display their abilities in the poetry competition, many people came here to watch the grand event.

Thus, the capital city that was holding the world poetry competition became filled with people since a month ago.

People moved on the bustling streets, Li Xiao Bai and Teacher Jiang walked side by side.

"The world poetry competition has eighteen rounds, Xiao Bai, if you want to change your circumstances, this is the best chance. I understand your talent, you can pass the first ten rounds, but the latter eight will depend on your luck. Sigh, teacher cannot help you this time, we might even end up as opponents." Teacher Jiang sighed.

This was a grand event, Teacher Jiang also wanted to participate and compete with the other talented scholars!

After Li Xiao Bai heard this, he held down the urge to roll his eyes as he thought: "I am almost certain now that you will end up as my opponent, dear teacher."

Li Xiao Bai was Fang Yuan's clone, he was sent into Profound Literature grotto-heaven as a pawn to take over this grotto-heaven.

Initially, Li Xiao Bai had a smooth sailing journey, he even received the affection of Su clan's young miss, Su Qi Han. As a result, Li Xiao Bai became one of the ten great scholars, he had a chance to become Su clan's son-in-law.

Next, while Li Xiao Bai was on his way to the capital city, the world shook as mountains collapsed and rivers flooded. The people in Li Xiao Bai's group got injured while some died, they were trapped in the valley for months before Li Xiao Bai managed to escape for his life.

Because of this, he missed the opportunity and did not meet with the emperor. Without the emperor's decree, his ten great scholar title was conferred to others.

Li Xiao Bai wanted to contact Su Qi Han but found that after hearing about his situation, she went to look for him and went missing as a result, even now, she had not returned yet.

After arriving in the capital city, Li Xiao Bai encountered many setbacks, people tried to target him secretly, he offended officials or royalty without knowing it, he had a tough time. If not for Teacher Jiang's help, he would have ended up on the streets as a beggar.

But he knew why.

"Even though my main body destroyed fate Gu, our strong luck was almost completely expended in this battle. The result is that I as a clone also became really unlucky."

"This world poetry competition is the event created by Profound Literature grotto-heaven to choose new Gu Immortal seeds. Even though teacher does not know the details, he still chose to join, he is going to become my obstacle."

"I am so unlucky now, I will definitely face him. If I defeat him, this teacher might hate me for life. But this chance is too rare, if I do not use it to deal with the difficulties ahead, I will meet with more problems in the future!"

Chapter 1976: Li Xiao Bai's Spring Poem

"Lord Gu Masters, please come in!" The waiter bent his back as he invited Hua Song and An Chong into the shop.

"This is a famous teahouse of the capital city, it is very crowded, I have come here many times in the past." Hua Song transmitted as he explained to An Chong.

The two had disguised as Gu Masters as they came to the capital city of Profound Literature grotto-heaven.

An Chong was more willing to observe the capital city from above the clouds. But since Hua Song had such interests, he could only accompany the person who invited him.

"I want a table on the fifth floor." Hua Song was very familiar with this place.

The two came to the fifth floor, they entered the room and saw through the windows that the streets were bustling with people outside, the street with the bronze gate where the first round of the competition was held was completely packed with people.

"These are the current generation scholars of my Profound Literature grotto-heaven, they are the hope of our future as well. Please observe." Hua Song sighed as he handed a rank five investigative Gu worm to An Chong, it could observe the target's talent qi.

An Chong took a look and used it immediately, his field of vision changing immediately. He could now see the talent qi above the heads of countless scholars. These talent qi had all sorts of colors, some were taller than others, they all had different forms, it was an eye-opener.

"Since you have such a Gu worm to observe talent qi, what is the point of holding this competition?" An Chong asked.

Hua Song chuckled: "You might not know, talent qi is like cultivation level, even if one possesses a larger talent qi, they might not be able to use it properly in actual competition. Furthermore, this competition requires them to make poems on the spot, they cannot cheat. We want to test the upbringing of these scholars, some who have abundant talent qi might not have sufficient inspiration to create the highest quality poems."

An Chong nodded: "I see that the formations here are interlinked, they are able to amplify the creative thinking of the scholars?"

Hua Song nodded: "Indeed, you are very perceptive! Within the immortal formation, scholars are able to display greater abilities than usual, they will make full use of their talents."

As they spoke, the door was knocked.

After getting Hua Song's permission, the waiter brought over an array of dishes and wine.

"Eight treasure duck, golden thread crispy sparrow, panda crab meat, they are all signature dishes of our teahouse, please enjoy the food." The waiter said.

Hua Song gave the waiter one primeval stone as a tip before he left the room.

Hua Song explained to An Chong: "Envoy, even though the tea here is mortal tea, it was created by Lord Hua Yu in his youth, when he was still a rank four Gu Master, he became the top scholar and thus this tea was named by him as the top scholar tea."

"Oh?" An Chong became interested now, this was the creation of a rank eight Gu Immortal in his youth.

"Then I will have to savor this well." An Chong drank it, he shut his eyes as he tasted the tea, in a daze, he felt a rush of excitement in his heart, it was as if he had attained success after decades of hard work, he finally gained the reputation and fame that he deserved, life was at its peak!

"Good tea, good tea." An Chong praised sincerely: "Even though this is a mortal tea, it has a trace of human path ingenuity within it!"

During the fate war, Central Continent's Heavenly Court used multiple human path killer moves with shocking power, the entire world knew about it. Thus, human path became renowned in the world, everyone knew about it.

While the two immortals were enjoying their tea, the bronze gate of the first competition ground opened slowly.

The crowd of people waiting before the gate erupted into a huge commotion.

"It's opening, it's opening!"

"Don't squeeze."

"Quickly let me in."

The crowds charged through the gate.

Li Xiao Bai was among them, but he was at the back instead.

He moved along with the people as he analyzed the rules of this competition.

"The world poetry competition has eighteen rounds, each one has a question, everyone has to answer it, regardless of how many people, their final product will be assessed and only half will be able to pass."

"Towards the later rounds, the numbers will continue being halved. Like this, once someone passes all eighteen rounds, they will fulfill the condition."

"If someone fails once, they will have to return to the previous round. If they keep losing and fall out of the first round, they will be out."

"However, this poetry competition will last for seven days. Everyone has three opportunities to try even if they get kicked out of the first round."

"This way, Profound Literature grotto-heaven will be able to pick the most eligible Gu Immortal seeds. Even if someone makes a mistake, they will have a chance to try again. But if any scholar fails to perform throughout the seven days, it will mean that they are not up to standard, they are not qualified to receive the grotto-heaven's help to become an immortal."

Li Xiao Bai retracted his thoughts, he had already arrived at the first arena.

The arena was large but packed with scholars.

There were males and females, young and old, the number of people exceeded the thousands.

This was just the first day.

Li Xiao Bai waited for another fifteen minutes in the arena before all of the scholars had joined the first round.

There was truly a sea of people, the liveliness was overwhelming.

Thankfully, the first arena was an immortal formation space, it could expand casually and hold so many scholars without problems.

Bang... bang... bang!

As the drums rolled, a voice was transmitted into the scholars' minds: "World poetry competition, first question — Spring, the time limit is five minutes."

After saying that, the voice vanished.

"The first question is spring?"

Many scholars frowned while many scholars showed happy expressions.

Li Xiao Bai thought to himself: "There are simply too many spring poems in existence, this question seems really easy. After all, most scholars would have some sort of verses related to this theme. Even though the world poetry competition requires the creation of poems on the spot, a person can easily modify existing verses to create their own new poems."

"But in reality, this question is quite the tough one." Li Xiao Bai had an expression of deep thought.

He knew that his poem was going to compete against the surrounding people. As long as he was stronger than half of them, he would progress to the next stage.

Many scholars noticed this as well.

Many people started to think, some sat down on the ground while others paced around with their arms behind their backs, some lowered their heads, muttering softly to themselves.

Li Xiao Bai's thought was: "Which poem do I use, or steal?"

There were many spring related poems in his memory, they were all amazing classics.

But using a legendary classic from the start was not good, this would not allow Li Xiao Bai to explain himself in the future. He did not have top tier talent qi, if he took out a shocking poem now, he would attract suspicion.

If his luck was good now, Li Xiao Bai might take slight risks. But now that he was having bad luck, Li Xiao Bai decided to play safe.

While Li Xiao Bai was thinking about it, many scholars already started to make their poems.

Thus, all kinds of lights shining in all colors, weak or strong, appeared. Whenever the light fades from a scholar's body, they would have some gains.

Some gained Gu worms, some gained a rise in cultivation level, some recovered primeval essence, while others recovered from fatigue.

This was the killer move known as assisting literary talents.

Profound Literature grotto-heaven's creator, its original owner, had used this move before his death. Because of assisting literary talents, more and more scholars were encouraged to study, it eventually created the environment of Profound Literature grotto-heaven where most people were scholars.

Li Xiao Bai decided on his poem.

He coughed lightly before starting his recital.

"A moonlit night[1]."

"Deep into the night the moon shines on half a cottage, across the sky the Big Dipper lies, the Little Dipper tilts an incline."

"The warmth of spring is readily felt tonight, through the green window screen, insects buzz and hum."

After Li Xiao Bai finished his recital, a light buzzing noise could be heard around him, his entire body shined in an intense green light.

Whoosh.

The scholars around Li Xiao Bai felt an invisible pressure as the green light forced them to move aside, a huge empty space was created with Li Xiao Bai at the center.

"Such, such a strong light!"

"A famed poem has appeared!"

"To think that a famed poem would appear so quickly. I wonder who created it?"

Many scholars lost their train of thought, they all looked towards Li Xiao Bai with admiration and suspicion.

Li Xiao Bai had a calm expression but he was a little conflicted inside: "Sigh, I went overboard a little, the effect was so eye-catching, I gained too much attention."

He looked around, hoping someone would step up and take the attention away from him.

As the green light entered his aperture, his cultivation level rose.

"Oh! A famed poem has appeared, let me go read it." At the teahouse, Hua Song had a sensation.

After reading Li Xiao Bai's work, Hua Song nodded in satisfaction: "Brilliant, brilliant! This Li Xiao Bai is very young but his poems are very mature."

"Normally, spring poems would use verses involving greenery or peach blossoms. But this poem uses another train of thought, using the night scene to conceal the spring light, it is quite interesting."

"The final verse must be created using Li Xiao Bai's personal experiences. It has a refreshing, happy, and lively feeling."

"Poems take after the creator, this Li Xiao Bai has a superb mindset!"

Hua Song praised it for a while, as if he had just eaten a delicacy of the world. He looked at An Chong as he smiled: "I wonder what envoy thinks of this poem?"

An Chong felt a headache as he thought: "If you didn't tell me, I wouldn't know what's so good about this poem. Sigh, he wants me to critique it, what should I say?"

[1] Poem by Liu Fangping. Back

Chapter 1977: Li Xiao Bai's Inner Conflict

Li Xiao Bai's expectations were not disappointed.

After his recital, three more people stepped up.

One was a strong man wearing a golden mask, he was shining in a glaring golden light.

There was an old man wearing a cone hat, he was holding a cane as a green light moved around him.

There was also a woman, she had a slim body and wore a pink dress, her face was covered by a veil, after her recital, butterflies flew around her, it was a beautiful sight.

These three had created famed poems on the same level as Li Xiao Bai's moonlit night.

Li Xiao Bai let out a sigh of relief: "This world has Gu worms to assist with poem creation. Gu Masters are also able to extend their lifespan and gain more experience in life. Thus, famed poems are more likely to appear than on Earth."

On Earth, moonlit night was a rare creation. But in Profound Literature grotto-heaven, it would not be unmatched.

Including Li Xiao Bai, the four of them had their own territory as they looked at each other.

The strong man, old man, and woman placed their gazes on Li Xiao Bai.

They knew each other, they had some sort of understanding towards their works, but Li Xiao Bai was a newcomer.

"Who is this young man?"

"His talent qi is not dense, how can he create such a famed poem?"

"Hehe, interesting guy."

Li Xiao Bai's teacher, Teacher Jiang, also saw his student's performance. He nodded in satisfaction: "Very good, Li Xiao Bai, it seems you are performing well today. Continue working hard."

In the end, no accidents happened, Li Xiao Bai moved to the next round and was teleported away.

After he regained his senses, he arrived in another arena.

"This is the fifth round, scholars, please wait patiently." Li Xiao Bai heard a voice in his mind.

Li Xiao Bai understood at once: "So the advancement has differences as well. The poem I made is enough to pass three rounds and directly reach the fifth round."

"This is quite a logical rule."

"But this means that the Gu Masters who reached this round are all people who created famed poems. Only half of these people can pass, the pressure has intensified now."

Li Xiao Bai looked around, he found two familiar faces.

It was the strong man and the woman from earlier.

After noticing Li Xiao Bai's gaze, the woman nodded at him, she seemed to be smiling under the veil. Meanwhile, the strong man had an air of arrogance, after giving Li Xiao Bai a glance, he started to shut his eyes and meditate.

In the fifth round, there was only the three of them now.

"I wonder which round that old man went to."

"I should pretend to rest now."

When scholars made poems, they had to think with all their effort, but he only had to select a suitable poem for his use. This was too easy, he had to conceal the fact.

After waiting for several minutes in the fifth round arena, the second competition began.

He had more than twenty competitors, Li Xiao Bai felt a certain level of pressure in his heart.

The theme of the second competition was out — Travel, the time limit was the same as before.

"Travel? This question is the same as spring, it is so broad and easy to write, but creating a famed poem will be very hard!" The strong man sighed to himself.

The woman was thinking: "I am not well versed in this, what should I do?"

Li Xiao Bai was also contemplating: "Which poem do I copy?"

After thinking for a while, he felt that he could not use a classic poem, the effect would be too overwhelming, but he could not use a bad poem. Otherwise, he would fail to advance and be kicked back to the previous round.

Li Xiao Bai was a little troubled, it was not easy to gauge this situation.

He knew his own ability, but he did not know about others, he did not know what sort of poem to use to win but not gain too much attention.

"In the first round, I went overboard. I should not try for first place now." Li Xiao Bai told himself.

He waited patiently.

After a few minutes, some scholars already created their poems. After that, a few more started to recite their poems, colorful lights appeared.

Li Xiao Bai sighed to himself, thinking: "It seems that famed poems are not easy to create, these people did well in the first round but currently, they are only performing at an average level."

Li Xiao Bai soon had an idea of the situation but he did not start working, he was still waiting.

As the time limit was about to be up, he finally saw some famed poems.

One from the strong man.

He recited a poem with great battle intent, resembling the march of horses and spears, his entire body was flickering with golden light, one could hear the clash of spears and blades.

The second famed poem came from the woman.

She created a gentle poem, describing a young lady looking outside her room's window, listening to the stories of travelers outside, imagining her own travel journey, it was quite impressive.

"Alright, it is my turn now." Li Xiao Bai coughed as he recited:

Date flowers fall on the villagers' clothes,

The sound of reeling carts heard from every household,

Old men dressed in simple clothes sell cucumbers under the willow tree.

Feeling drunk and drowsy from the long journey,

The bright sun makes my throat dry, I thirst for a refreshing drink,

I knock on the door of a mortal house, hoping to request for some tea.

He had copied Su Shi's Silk-washing Stream.

After the recital, be it the strong man or the woman, they were evidently moved as they analyzed the poem.

"Good poem! This poem starts with description of the scenery and actions at the back, with the fusion of both, one can feel interested in the event."

"Even though he is writing about a scenery, he uses his voice to create an image, compared to normal descriptions, this is very vivid. The emotional part is also very interesting. This kid might be a Gu Master but he is very polite and courteous, he does not barge into a mortal's house, he is truly a gentleman and has incomparable elegance."

"Reading his poem shows his nature. This young scholar is really promising!"

The surrounding scholars looked at Li Xiao Bai with a different gaze now.

Li Xiao Bai let out a breath of air, pretending that he was extremely exhausted.

"After this round, I should be able to advance. Not just that, my performance was really good, I did not gain too much attention but I also did not show inability."

Li Xiao Bai was quite satisfied with himself, after waiting for a while, the time limit was up.

He became stunned.

Most scholars failed to create a poem.

"This is the world poetry competition, I need to display my best abilities. If I use any inferior work, it will be too shameful."

"I did my best but could not create a satisfactory poem, even if I fail, I will not regret it!"

"This trip was worth my time, I got to hear three famed poems."

"Haha, in the worst case scenario, I might fall to the first round, so what? Goodbye!"

Those scholars that did not create a poem left in a carefree manner, while those scholars who made inferior poems showed shameful expressions.

Li Xiao Bai was calm on the outside but internally flummoxed: "How can you guys act so graciously?"

Even though he advanced, he had gained too much attention again. Earlier, he was quite satisfied with the situation, but to think these scholars would be so useless.

"Hmph, I had overestimated them." Li Xiao Bai thought.

There was nothing to say, he successfully advanced to the ninth round.

After patiently waiting for a while, the people gathered. This time, there was less than ten of them.

Many of them were famous scholars, they knew each other and greeted politely, they were calm and elegant on the outside, but were all feeling nervous internally.

At this point, the pressure of these competitors intensified again.

"I need to be stable, I cannot create a commotion again!" Li Xiao Bai clenched his fists, he kept reminding himself.

But this time, his opponents all performed well, more than half of the Gu Masters created famed poems.

Li Xiao Bai was the last one left.

Li Xiao Bai had a nervous expression but he was calm internally, he recited the poem that he had already prepared in advance.

With some flickering light, his cultivation level rose to rank four, he gained a new Gu worm.

This time, he planned meticulously, the poem he created was just borderline in the middle, he managed to advance successfully but he was at the bottom of the batch.

Right when Li Xiao Bai was feeling happy.

Cough!

Someone coughed out a mouthful of blood.

Ugh.

Someone fainted on the ground.

The strong man shook as he sat down with difficulty. The woman coughed for a long time with a pale expression.

Only Li Xiao Bai was left standing on the spot, unaffected.

At once, everyone's gazes were on him again.

"This young man is very strong! Currently speaking, he has already created three famed poems."

"He did not get injured at all, it seems that he had not gone all out when he made his poem earlier."

"Impressive! After this competition, I need to befriend him!"

Li Xiao Bai: "..."

He was speechless.

Oh heavens, why did everyone overexert themselves?!

Wasn't it just a poem competition, why were they risking their lives?

He wanted to pretend to cough blood too but it was too late now, he could not disguise himself anymore.

Li Xiao Bai had to continue moving to the next round with a plain expression.

Chapter 1978: Human Path, Changing Luck

Sovereign immortal aperture, Mini Central Continent.

Fang Yuan stood under the thousand wish tree, looking up only to see a blazing light in the sky, there were specks and lumps, fading and flickering, it was truly a dazzling sight.

Looking at the ground, sand and dust rumbled as wind was blowing wildly.

Fang Yuan's eyes flickered with cold light.

His heaven path dao marks were increasing in number!

He had originally gained three thousand or so dao marks from the Gu refinement, but now, he was approaching three thousand five hundred dao marks.

With the increase in heaven path dao marks, the number of other dao marks in Fang Yuan's immortal aperture was reducing in number.

This scene reminded Fang Yuan of his time in Crazed Demon Cave.

At the second lowest floor of Crazed Demon Cave, Fang Yuan saw the development of worlds. Countless worlds were destroyed as heaven path dao marks formed. The heaven path dao marks interlinked with each other or spread out themselves, forming new worlds.

At this moment, even though the sovereign immortal aperture was not destroyed and turned into heaven path dao marks, they were still modifying the various dao marks within this immortal aperture.

Of course, the heaven path dao marks were not just increasing. Sometimes, they fell in numbers, one heaven path dao mark turned into many dao marks of other paths, spreading throughout the world.

Using the transformation of these dao marks, in accordance with the Heavenly Dao, the environment of the entire sovereign immortal aperture was modified.

Like the scene that Fang Yuan was observing now, light was appearing in the sky, it meant that light path dao marks were increasing in numbers. There was also wind and rumbling sand on the ground, it meant that wind path and earth path dao marks were also increasing in numbers.

"If this goes on for a long time, the surroundings of the thousand wish tree would turn into a barren desert." The trend was too obvious, Fang Yuan smiled coldly to himself.

He had originally thought that the thousand wish tree was meant to be planted in a desert, but now, even though he was not wrong, his understanding was distorted.

The thousand wish tree was a human path ancient desolate plant, it used human will to create fruits. It was most suited to be grown in a bustling environment like a large city or market filled with people, the more human will the better.

However, the Heavenly Dao did not want the thousand wish tree to grow properly, it changed the heaven path dao marks to create a blazing sun and a vast area of sand, to isolate it from the living people.

In order to survive, the thousand wish tree had to change its own traits to adapt to this difficult environment and live.

But now that it was placed in Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture, the immortal formation created its own desert environment for it to slowly adapt and change, it would not be destroyed because of an unsuitable environment.

But outside the immortal formation was a fertile land with lush greenery and warm sunlight.

The immortal formation was not isolated, the thousand wish tree's human path aura could be sensed by the Heavenly Dao. But these heaven path dao marks were not under Fang Yuan's control, they could not change according to the environment within the immortal formation, they modified the environment outside the formation to stop the thousand wish tree's growth.

Thus, Fang Yuan learned about some things.

"The thousand wish tree will finish growing in three hundred years, flower at its six hundredth year and bear fruit at the nine hundredth year. It will create exactly a thousand fruits at that time."

"This is something that everyone knows as a fact, but now it seems, this is not true."

"The thousand wish tree is restricted by the Heavenly Dao, its actual potential is much larger!"

"From now on, I will water it with human will, I will gradually change its habitat, its production will definitely rise greatly!"

This was a future plan, Fang Yuan came to the thousand wish tree today for another matter.

At his will, Cooking Luck Pot revealed itself above him.

Rank seven Cooking Luck Pot was large as a basin, it was shining in golden and white light, sacred and royal.

The pot had thick sides, about the thickness of a thumb, there were eight dragons at the base of the pot, coiling around each other and extending their claws to become the legs of this pot. At the top of the pot, one could see Fang Yuan's exposed luck, it looked grey and damaged.

Even though Cooking Luck Pot was only rank seven, unable to contain all of Fang Yuan's luck in this one pot, it was still possible to observe something from it.

Fang Yuan's colossal luck was almost fully consumed in the fate war, after the fight, his luck became very low. This was his third hidden threat, aside from the qi tide and heaven path dao marks.

Fate was constant while luck was variable.

When one's luck was poor, it meant that unfavorable developments might happen.

But now, Fang Yuan's main body had immense battle strength that was pseudo venerable level, no matter how bad his luck was, he had the power to resist problems.

This was not a big issue for the main body, but he was worried about the luck of his clones.

Outside of Cooking Luck Pot were the luck of his respective clones.

The time path clone's luck still resembled the River of Time, but the water was no longer flowing smoothly, it was chaotic and the front of the river was cut off, it looked quite worrying.

Zhan Bu Du's luck was originally a mature eagle spreading its wings and flying, but now the eagle had fallen into water, it was covered by flowing water that made things difficult for him.

Li Xiao Bai's luck was like a bright blooming flower. The flower was bright red and burning intensely in a red color. Within the flame, the petals bloomed, it might look like good luck but the hidden threat was huge. He was basically playing with fire, he would die if he could not control the flames.

Wu Shuai's luck was like a coiling dragon, three of its dragon claws were holding onto a dragon pearl each. One had the silhouette of Dragon Palace, one had countless ants in it, while the third pearl had the image of Di Zang Sheng. Wu Shuai had the strongest luck among them, but he was surrounded by blade and sword qi, approaching from all directions.

Fang Yuan's main body had poor luck, his clones were in even worse states.

Fang Yuan had sensed his clones' problem long ago, it was not that he did not try to resolve it but his methods failed.

The heaven path dao marks restricted him, whenever he tried to use a killer move, they would interfere and cause his killer move activation to fail. Even if he succeeded, the power of the move would be greatly lowered.

"But this time, it should be different." Bright light flashed in Fang Yuan's eyes.

Fang Yuan multitasked, manipulating the formation around the thousand wish tree while also activating Cooking Luck Pot.

The thousand wish tree's branches continued to shake, bright rainbow light shot out of the formation, entering Cooking Luck Pot.

Cooking Luck Pot started to modify the luck of his clones.

The surrounding world started to rage with intense winds and fierce lightning. Heaven path dao marks appeared one by one, some were all over the place while others appeared on Fang Yuan's body.

The way of heaven was to take away surpluses while replenishing deficits.

The way of humans was to take away deficits while magnifying surpluses!

With the help of the human path immortal formation, Fang Yuan forcefully made modifications of certain degrees to the luck of his clones.

The time path clone's river luck stabilized and became smoother.

Zhan Bu Du's eagle luck started to shed its feathers in the water, it seemed like it was turning into a fish, adapting to the environment.

Li Xiao Bai's flower luck started to crystallize under the intense flames, it no longer had a threat of turning to ashes.

Meanwhile, Wu Shuai's dragon luck still remained in a coiling state, there was no change to the luck. The surrounding blade and sword qi, however, became much weaker, turning from dense smoke to light smoke. This meant that there would still be a fight but the scale of the battle would be much smaller than before.

"The problem of the clones is settled. The truly troublesome thing is the heaven path dao marks." Fang Yuan could increasingly understand the deeper intentions of Red Lotus as time passed.

Chapter 1979: Merman Court's Vicious Guest

Eastern Sea, Merman Imperial Court.

The sound of instruments was complemented with delicious wine and food.

At the grand banquet, the three female immortals leading the Merman Imperial Court sat on the main seats as they entertained an unexpected guest.

"Good wine, good music, and even better dance!" The guest drank his wine in one gulp as he slammed the cup on the table, laughing loudly.

He had a square face, he was muscular and strong, his skin was snow white, his eyes and hair were icy blue in color.

Rank eight aura permeated from his body.

He was a snowman Gu Immortal from black heaven's Ice Crystal grotto-heaven, it was the current generation Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch.

Ever since the last meeting of the black heaven forces, Night Heavenly Wolf Lord secretly contacted Central Continent's Heavenly Court, while Lady Cold Ash contacted the human experts like Granny Skeleton. Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch did not stay motionless, his target was not white heaven or black heaven, but the five regions instead. Thus, he went to Eastern Sea and approached the merman force.

Eastern Sea's merman force had three leaders, they were all mermaid immortals, they were called Lian Ke Xin, Yu Zi, and Xie Ning Si.

Even though this was the first time the three female immortals were seeing Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch, seeing that he was a variant human rank eight Gu Immortal, they held this banquet to welcome him.

Upon hearing Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's praise, Lian Ke Xin smiled and replied: "Thank you for the praise. These dancing Gu Masters all are the hope of our merman tribe, our Gu Immortal seeds. It is their honor to be praised by you, Immortal Monarch."

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch laughed again: "Pardon my insolence, but if these merfolk are the hope of your tribe, I'm afraid you are going to be wiped from existence soon."

These words made many of the merfolk's expressions change.

The dancing merfolk even became disorganized for a moment.

Lian Ke Xin remained smiling: "We already understand your intention in coming here. We are not going to be provoked by your words. For countless years, mermen have lived in Eastern Sea peacefully and harmoniously, we have been neutral all along, we will not participate in any conflict outside."

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch shook his head: "Preposterous! Who does not want to live in peace? But in history, such peace can only be gained through conflict and war. The merman race received the help of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable back then, that is why you could live like this until now. In the entire five regions, only you are still a super force among the variant humans."

"But we have all seen the fate war already. Fate has been destroyed, the five regions have merged, the world is changing right in front of our very eyes. With disasters and calamities, conflict will ensue and last for a long time."

"Your Merman Imperial Court wants to stay out of this? Hehehe, how long has it been since Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable died? How much influence does he still have to protect you?"

Lian Ke Xin had a grim expression, she could not rebuke him.

Yu Zi snorted coldly beside her: "We have more than ten Gu Immortals and Immortal Gu House Floating Reputation Boat, how is it completely Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's credit that we are able to develop to today's scale?"

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch nodded: "I have heard of your Floating Reputation Boat long ago, but so what? It is just a rank seven Immortal Gu House. You have many Gu Immortals, but do you have a single rank eight Gu Immortal? Not a single one! Hehehe, forget about everything else, if I want to attack you now, can anyone stop me?"

The three mermaids had cold expressions, Xie Ning Si said: "Immortal Monarch, if you want to fight, you can attack now, we will show you the power of our merman race!"

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch quickly waved his hand: "Don't misunderstand, I am not trying to become enemies with you. We are all variant humans, in the current world where humans dominate, I want us to cooperate. Variant humans are friends, not enemies. I am here to seek an alliance, how can I possibly fight you?"

"I understand why you do not want to cooperate. But think about this, as long as I spread the word that the three of you have invited me here and show signs of wanting to join up with black heaven's variant human forces to resist the humans, what will happen? Hehe."

The three mermaids looked at each other, they all had grim expressions.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch spoke gently but he had a tough tone, it was a forceful cooperation. If they rejected him, he would spread rumors and lie that the merfolk want to join him.

At this time, the fate war was known to everyone.

The things that Duke Long said to Fang Yuan exposed to the world that variant humans were going to rise up!

Once this news was spread out regarding the Merman Imperial Court and the variant humans, it would raise the paranoia of the humans, they would become a public enemy.

By then, with the usual behavior of humans, they would form into an allied army and eliminate the Merman Imperial Court first!

The human forces had been wanting to take down the Merman Imperial Court long ago, they were only restricted by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's influence. If the mermen wanted to harm the humans, regardless of whether anyone believed this lie, they would use it to deal with the Merman Imperial Court.

The Merman Imperial Court would be forced to resist, they would only be able to survive if they worked with Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch or other equally powerful alliances.

Thus, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's objective had already been fulfilled.

The three mermaids were troubled, they knew about the trend of the world, they were actively choosing Gu Immortal seeds and nurturing them.

They were mermen, they were variant humans, this status placed them in an awkward spot all along throughout the eras. During the five regions chaotic war, they would be in an even worse position when everyone was paranoid.

Thus, the merman tribe felt a strong sense of danger.

The three mermaids did not have much ambition, they only wanted to preserve their members during this new era. Thus, they did not want to antagonize Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch, but they did not want to side with this ambitious leader and wage war on the humans either.

Seeing that the mermaids were silent, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch smiled again: "How about this, we are all variant humans, I do not want to force you. Let's make a bet."

The three mermaids looked at each other, Yu Zi asked: "What bet?"

"We will have a three round competition, no matter what methods your tribe uses, as long as you can defeat me in one round, I will forget about the suggestion to make an alliance, I will leave without exposing anything about your tribe or spreading any rumors. But if I win all three rounds, it will mean that your merman tribe is just too weak, unable to even defeat a rank eight Gu Immortal like me, you will be in great danger anyway, you should work with me to ensure that your tribe survives the tides of time." Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch said slowly.

The three mermaids had no choice, they nodded and agreed to this bet.

In the first round, the three mermaids went all out, gathering the Gu Immortals of the tribe and creating the battle formation, merman wave sacred spiritual formation.

"Good formation, it can actually trap enemies." Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch took a look and praised it.

"Immortal Monarch, do you dare to enter?"

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch laughed loudly, he went into the formation and attacked several times, the tides turned into ice and shattered, allowing him to escape easily.

The merman Gu Immortals suffered backlash, they were either lightly or heavily injured, they all had grim expressions.

"It is a pity you do not have any rank eight expert controlling the formation." Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch critiqued.

During the second round, the Merman Imperial Court used their Immortal Gu House Floating Reputation Boat.

After a hundred rounds of fighting, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch claimed victory again.

The three female mermen went into anxious discussions.

"Only the third round is left, what do we do?"

"If we lose again, we will need to cooperate with Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch, what do we do?"

"Why don't we use that?" Xie Ning Si suggested.

Lian Ke Xin and Yu Zi were stunned, they shook their heads: "No, we cannot use that, the influence is too large. Even without Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's rumor, we will become the target of everyone, our tribe will be exterminated!"

"If we do not use that, what will we do? Do we request help from Eastern Sea's human forces?"

"No, we are all affected by the qi tides now, why would those humans come here to help us? Even if they come, the price will be too large."

"Oh? I thought of someone. Why don't we ask Gu tribe's leader for help?" Xie Ning Si asked.

Lian Ke Xin sighed, denying this possibility: "He is Gu tribe's leader, even though he has rank eight cultivation level, he is a beastman that is in seclusion. We have a good relationship with him but if we ask him for help, that will be making things difficult for him. Furthermore, he might not defeat this Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch."

Yu Zi's eyes suddenly brightened: "I thought of someone, this person might be able to help us, he might even win against Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch."

"Who?"

"Indeed, at this point in time, who can help us?"

Yu Zi blinked as she said: "Did you forget, there is currently a great expert at Gu tribe's headquarters."

"Oh, him." Lian Ke Xin suddenly realized.

"Brilliant, I will contact Gu tribe's leader now, we will ask Lord Wu Shuai for help!" Xie Ning Si said that as she rapidly got to action.

Chapter 1980: Admitting Defeat

Eastern Sea, Gu tribe's blessed land.

A grand palace was stationed here.

The whole palace shined with slight orange-gold light and was richly decorated, the pavilions and terraces were all grand and beautiful. It was the rank eight Immortal Gu House — Dragon Palace.

Within Dragon Palace, dream realms were spread out. In other Immortal Gu Houses, nobody would dare to do this. But although Dragon Palace was an enslavement path Immortal Gu House, it had dream path Immortal Gu and was not at risk of the dream realm corroding it.

In front of the dream realm, Fang Yuan's clone, Wu Shuai, had his eyes shut.

His body was here, but his soul was inside the dream realm, continuously exploring it.

Within the dream realm, Wu Shuai was the disciple of a medical clinic, he was trying to learn their skill.

A young man with broad shoulders and a thin waist stepped into the clinic with a valiant aura.

The young man had quite the status, the old doctor who owned the clinic had to attend to him personally.

"Doctor, ever since I won the fight last time, I have been feeling that my body has some lingering issues." The young man said.

The old doctor chuckled: "Come, I will check your pulse."

"Check my pulse?" The young man frowned, having a perplexed expression.

The old doctor said slowly: "This is a unique investigative method from my hometown, it can inspect illnesses. As a person's heart continues to beat, their blood will flow through their veins and create pulses. Through my specially created healing Gu worm, I can inspect your pulse and find out the cause of your illness."

The young man had a surge of admiration: "Worthy of an experienced doctor. I've heard that heaven has heaven veins, earth has earth veins, and humans have human veins. Does this method to inspect the pulse make use of a human vein to target the cause of the problem?"

"Hahaha, that is precisely so, extend your hand." The old doctor smiled.

The young man extended his hand, the old doctor placed his finger on his wrist, closing his eyes to inspect it.

A moment later, the old doctor opened his eyes: "This is indeed an illness but it is not obvious on the outside, this is quite vicious. You were hit by a phantom path method."

The young man nodded: "Senior is completely right, my opponent was a Gu Master specializing in phantom path. I was hit by his attack and although I did not suffer injuries, it still felt weird. Usually at night, I could undergo activities with more than ten of my concubines, but now, I get extremely tired after engaging with one. Also, my waist often aches and my body feels hot, I perspire a lot when I sleep, I even feel dizziness at times."

The old doctor nodded: "This phantom path method is quite wicked, it targets your kidney. In other words, you have kidney deficiency[1]."

"Phantom path is troublesome indeed, what should I do now?" The young man asked.

The old doctor replied: "I will prescribe you some medicine, take it for a month, during this month, you should not engage in bedroom activities."

The young man had a difficult expression: "Senior, can you use Gu worms to heal me directly? If I have to hold it for a month, I'll go crazy."

The old doctor shook his head: "Phantom path methods alternate between reality and illusion, we need ample time to deal with it. Even though my medicine is not a healing Gu worm, it is not far from an actual Gu recipe, it can definitely treat your problem. Other than this method, it will be hard to cure you. Unless you can find a doctor who has greater skill than me, he might be able to resolve your issue."

The young man sighed: "Senior is the greatest healer I know, I will follow your prescription."

The dream faded away, the exploration was successful.

"Human vein..." Wu Shuai's soul returned to his body, he was still savoring the true meaning in this dream.

This dream realm gave him the true meaning of two paths, phantom path and human path.

Fang Yuan's human path attainment level was at grandmaster but phantom path was only at ordinary. His main body still had the corpses of many Heavenly Court Gu Immortals, they had phantom apertures. But earlier, his phantom path attainment level was too low, even with wisdom Gu, he could not deduce the profundity of phantom path.

After the fate war, all of the dream realms were given to Wu Shuai to explore.

These dreams were all obtained from Yi Tian Mountain by Fang Yuan, even though a portion were used in the fate war, a large amount was still left.

After Wu Shuai left Heavenly Court, he returned to Eastern Sea and stayed in Gu tribe's blessed land. Other than opening his immortal aperture's entrance to draw in heaven and earth qi, he kept in closed cultivation, exploring dream realms to gain more true meaning, to raise the attainment levels of his main body's many paths.

"Currently, my main body needs human path attainment level. After this exploration, even though we did not gain much human path attainment level and are still at grandmaster, it should be of some help to my main body."

Wu Shuai started to rest, preparing for his next dream realm exploration.

"Hmm?" He saw that there was an information path mortal Gu from Gu tribe's leader in the hall.

"Gu tribe's leader would not bother me with trivial matters, something important must have happened." Wu Shuai retrieved the information path mortal Gu and checked it.

"Oh, a rank eight snowman Gu Immortal called Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch is finding problems with the Merman Imperial Court?"

In the letter, the three mermaids promised that as long as Wu Shuai taught this evil visitor a lesson and forced him away, they would thank him with rewards. Gu tribe's leader also used a polite tone to subtly request for Wu Shuai's help.

"Of course I will help." Wu Shuai smiled lightly.

He had a portion of Fang Yuan's five hundred years of memories.

Wu Shuai learned that in the previous life, when the regional walls vanished and the five regions united, there were qi tides too.

The five regions' Gu Immortals were forced to recuperate, during this period, the forces in the two heavens came out and acted arrogantly for some time.

"To think that I would have a chance to interact with these grotto-heaven forces. This is a great opportunity! For my main body's plans, I should do my best."

Bam.

The door of Dragon Palace opened, Wu Shuai came out of his closed cultivation.

At the banquet, the fragrance of wine spread but the atmosphere was very grim.

The three mermaids had cold expressions while Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch smiled at them.

The song and dance had ended, the hall was silent.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch drank a mouthful of wine as he asked: "I wonder if you have already decided on who to send for the final round?"

The three mermaids' expressions turned darker but at this time, they received a letter, their faces glowed with joy.

Xie Ning Si said: "Since Immortal Monarch is eager, let's start the third fight."

"Good." Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch placed down his wine cup: "How will we do this final fight, do tell me."

"We have invited someone to go against Immortal Monarch." Lian Ke Xin said.

"This lord has arrived already, prepare yourself, Immortal Monarch!" Yu Zi smiled coldly.

After a few breaths of time, following the mermaid immortals, Wu Shuai stepped into the hall.

"Who wants to fight me?" Wu Shuai asked, his voice reverberating in the hall.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch saw Wu Shuai and his expression changed, his casual and carefree attitude was no more, he said in shock: "You?"

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch had gained a lot of information about the fate war, Wu Shuai was one of the stars that shined, everyone in the world knew about him now.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch understood at once why the three mermaids had such confidence.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's heart sank, he knew about Wu Shuai's strength, there was little hope in beating him.

But in this situation, he had no choice but to ask: "Greetings, Wu Shuai, to think that you are in the Merman Imperial Court. I wonder where Fang Yuan is?"

Fang Yuan snorted coldly: "I gained Fang Yuan's help to revive, we were merely working together to resist Heavenly Court earlier. You are my opponent? Go ahead and attack."

Wu Shuai had a lofty expression, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch was angry, his expression turned cold: "Wu Shuai, you have rank seven cultivation level, but your tone is very arrogant."

Wu Shuai smiled: "Whose tone is more arrogant? In terms of seniority, I am someone from Red Lotus Demon Venerable's era! When I died of old age, your grandfather was not even born yet."

"You..." Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch stared with wide eyes.

"What? You came to look for problems with the mermen, let's not waste time." Wu Shuai stared: "Not attacking? Then I will make my move!"

Saying so, he waved his hand, an Immortal Gu House flew out.

"Dragon Palace!" Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's pupils shrunk, he watched as the Immortal Gu House came crashing towards him.

He was not a transformation path great expert, he could not resist this famous Immortal Gu House head-on, he quickly dodged.

The three mermaids did not expect Wu Shuai to act so quickly, he attacked with no warning.

Xie Ning Si quickly urged: "Senior Wu Shuai, this is the merman hall, if you are going to fight, it would be better to do it outside..."

Boom!

Dragon Palace expanded again, the entire merman hall was blown apart.

As dust clouds rumbled, the mermaids and Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch flew out pitifully.

Dragon Palace rose to the sky as Wu Shuai stood at the door, looking down at Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch: "Don't run, little fellow."

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's heart was pounding from the sudden assault, his throat felt dry: "Wu Shuai, you are a senior! Don't rely on the power of the Immortal Gu House if you have guts."

"Oh, is that so?" Wu Shuai snickered.

The three mermaids felt something amiss, Yu Zi quickly shouted: "Senior Wu Shuai! These are the headquarters of merfolk, if you are going to fight, please do it outside..."

Before she ended her sentence, with a loud sound, Di Zang Sheng was released from Dragon Palace by Wu Shuai.

Roar——!

The Evil Dragon roared, creating colossal waves. Its body was like a huge mountain, squeezed within the blessed land. Its dragon tail waved as several mountains and valleys were flattened.

Countless merfolk scrambled and ran away, screaming in chaos.

The three mermaids were stunned, they did not know what to do.

"Come, fight." Wu Shuai crossed his arms as he said to Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch with a plain tone.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch looked at the grand palace and the huge vicious Evil Dragon, he felt that he was very insignificant.

Even as a snowman who was extremely resistant to cold, at this moment, he felt a deep chill flowing down his spine.

After being quiet for some time, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch cupped his fists and said: "Senior, you are very powerful, junior admits defeat. Senior has won this battle."

The three mermaids were silent.

Wu Shuai only had rank seven cultivation level now, but nobody felt strange that Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch was admitting defeat to him.

Even without Dragon Palace, just the Evil Dragon alone could slaughter Heavenly Court's two transformation path experts and survive the attack of countless Gu Immortals.

During the fate war, Di Zang Sheng had only lost to Feng Jiu Ge and Duke Long!

"Hmph, little fellow, you are quite smart." Wu Shuai chuckled as he stored away Di Zang Sheng and Dragon Palace.

"Next, let's talk about the alliance." Wu Shuai descended and said this.

"Senior Wu Shuai!" The three mermaids were shocked.

"What? You still think you can isolate yourselves from everything?" Wu Shuai's eyebrows were raised, he spoke in displeasure.

The three immortals did not dare to rebuke him.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch was overjoyed, to think that there would be a turn of events, he stammered: "Se... senior, you mean to say?"

Wu Shuai patted his shoulder: "Come, let's talk in the hall."

[1] The character for deficiency here is the same as phantom. Back

Chapter 1981: I Will Be The Alliance Leader!

Because of Wu Shuai's interference, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch had to admit defeat. He had originally thought that his plan to ally with the mermen had failed, but to think that Wu Shuai had the same intention as him.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and the Merman Imperial Court made a bet, the loser won while the winner lost.

After the battle, Wu Shuai used the Merman Imperial Court to hold a talk with Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch, their discussion got more animated, the three mermaids' expressions turned grimmer.

Wu Shuai heard that Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch had already gathered the grotto-heavens for a meeting, he immediately requested to join them and even urged Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch to gather the remaining forces for a second meeting.

In Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's plan, the second meeting was going to happen much later, but Wu Shuai was urging him, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch thought: "With Wu Shuai's reputation, I can use it to my advantage, it is possible to push the meeting forward without issues."

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch knew that even if they gathered the grotto-heaven forces in black and white heaven, there would still be a huge internal threat. Among these forces, there was a small group of human forces.

He wanted variant humans to lead the alliance, thus, he had been looking for allies aggressively during this period. He had already contacted all of the variant human forces that he knew. Even the Merman Imperial Court in Eastern Sea was visited after all.

If he knew that Gu tribe was at the bottom of the sea, he would visit them too.

"But with this dragonman great expert Wu Shuai that everyone knows, even if the human faction gathers more people, they cannot match his influence, right?"

Wu Shuai attacked Heavenly Court as a dragonman and ended up as the victor, this result gave him huge prestige and reputation.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch thus held the second meeting in Ice Crystal grotto-heaven, the group was even bigger now.

"Golden Fur Immortal Monarch has arrived!"

"Blitz Cloud Heavenly Immortal has arrived!"

"Great Wisdom Immortal Mother has arrived!"

"Green Forest Great Sage has arrived!"

Many rank eight great experts of the variant humans came.

Golden Fur Immortal Monarch was a hairy man, he was covered in thick golden fur. Blitz Cloud Heavenly Immortal was a featherman, he had the appearance of a handsome young man. Great Wisdom Immortal Mother was an old female inkman. Green Forest Great Sage was a miniman, his entire body was covered in a green light.

This was the first time these four variant human Gu Immortals had attended the meeting.

As for the human rank eight Gu Immortals, other than Night Heavenly Wolf Lord and Lady Cold Ash, there were also newcomers, light path cultivator Crossing Heaven Immortal Monarch, wood path cultivator Black Locust and earth path female immortal Rainbow Rock Immortal Concubine.

There were only five human rank eights but almost ten variant human rank eights. Even though Lady Cold Ash tried to get more people to join, they were still unable to match the variant humans, in fact this gap was widening.

After a long discussion, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch announced: "We invited everyone here today, other than to discuss the matters of the world, there is also another important matter. Let me introduce you to a senior great expert!"

Everyone followed Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's hand gesture and looked towards the person.

Wu Shuai walked out from behind the veil, under everyone's supervision, he sat down on the main seat.

"This is?" The immortals were shocked.

"So it is Wu Shuai." A variant human rank eight who was close with Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch quickly said.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch showed a look of displeasure: "Call him Senior Wu Shuai!"

The variant human rank eight had an embarrassed expression, under Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's gaze, he changed his sentence: "Junior greets senior."

With this adjustment, all the other immortals had to call Wu Shuai senior.

"Good." Wu Shuai nodded in satisfaction: "Seniority is important, but I would rather everyone call me Alliance Leader instead!"

"Alliance Leader?" The immortals looked at each other.

Wu Shuai laughed: "Indeed, now that grotto-heavens are exposed, the five regions' Gu Immortals will attack us. They have not done anything now because of the qi tide, they cannot move around yet. We need to strengthen and help ourselves, we can only form an alliance to have any hopes of resisting the five regions!"

"Since ancient times, the most capable person will become the alliance leader. I have observed that nobody here can match me, if anyone does not agree, you can challenge me."

Before anyone could respond to Wu Shuai's words, they heard a dragon roar.

Di Zang Sheng's colossal body was exposed to everyone, blocking out the sun.

Next, an Immortal Gu House flew out of Wu Shuai's immortal aperture, it was small and delicate, it floated in his palm while shining with radiance.

It was a miniature Dragon Palace!

Wu Shuai looked at the Dragon Palace in his palm before turning to the immortals, threat was clearly shown in his eyes.

The immortals' expressions turned ugly, some went silent, they were furious but did not dare to say anything.

Even though Wu Shuai had rank seven cultivation level, everyone knew about the might of Dragon Palace and Evil Dragon. If everyone cooperated, they might have a chance against him. But the grotto-heavens were not close with each other, this was unlike the five regions where super forces interacted and conflicted with each other, they were familiar with one another. The black and white heavens were huge and dangerous, forces rarely met with each other, not to mention any cooperation.

"Hahaha!" Seeing no objection, Wu Shuai laughed loudly as he called out: "You are still not accepting your alliance leader?"

The immortals were silent, the atmosphere was heavy.

A moment later, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch stood up and cupped his fist at Wu Shuai: "Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch greets Alliance Leader!"

"Good, good." Wu Shuai pointed at him: "You will be the vice alliance leader."

Next, he looked at the other Gu Immortals with a vicious gaze.

The Evil Dragon shook its body outside, causing winds to form and clouds to scatter.

Seeing this, and with Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's initiative, all the immortals had to acknowledge Wu Shuai's status with a cold tone.

Wu Shuai sat at the main seat and looked at the Gu Immortals: "I know what you think, your acknowledge my alliance leader position because of the situation, but I am really not trying to force you."

"This is a very rare opportunity for us all, it is likely our only chance to resist the five regions. If we do not use this chance, when the five regions go after us and our grotto-heavens get encircled, regret will do us no good."

"However, at the rate your discussion is going, when can you take action? By the time you come to an agreement, the qi tides will be over already. Without a strong leader like myself to unify the grotto-heavens, how can we take action swiftly?"

Wu Shuai spoke with a harsh tone but he made good sense, the Gu Immortals' expressions became less hostile.

"Alright, enough of the useless talk, let's discuss our next target to attack." Wu Shuai continued.

This time, even Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch felt surprised: "Lord Alliance Leader, isn't it too early to attack now? Black and white heaven are too huge, there are still many grotto-heaven forces that we have not gathered yet."

"We can't wait anymore. As long as we succeed in our attack and create a commotion, these people will approach us themselves. This is how the hearts of the people work." Wu Shuai waved his hand and said.

The immortals fell into silence.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch had to continue asking: "Then in Lord Alliance Leader's opinion, which place is most suitable for us to attack?"

"Heavenly Court of course!" Wu Shuai answered without hesitation.

"Heavenly Court?!" The Gu Immortals shouted in astonishment.

"Heavenly Court is weak now, we did not retreat of our own accord earlier. As long as we take down Heavenly Court, the five regions will be shaken, who would dare to target us?" Wu Shuai laughed loudly.

"This is not wise!"

"Heavenly Court has immense foundations, it is not a place we can target."

"Lord Alliance Leader, please reconsider."

The immortals shook their heads, nobody agreed.

"Hmph, cowards!" Wu Shuai smiled coldly in displeasure: "Then we will go after Divine Emperor City."

"This Immortal Gu House is known as the largest Immortal Gu House, it is made from combining Divine Bean Palace and Emperor City. It has a huge significance to Heavenly Court, it is the gathering spot of the human vein, it is the land-based Heavenly Court. If we can obtain it, it will be a huge blow to Central Continent, we can even gain a rank eight Immortal Gu House, and also Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's true inheritance."

Lady Cold Ash pondered: "Since Divine Emperor City is so important, if we attack it, we will infuriate Heavenly Court, the whole of Central Continent will resist and attack us. Since we are going after them as well, what difference is there compared to attacking Heavenly Court directly?"

"Of course there is a difference! If these people are all lured to Divine Emperor City, we can send another group to attack Heavenly Court." Wu Shuai raised his eyebrows.

The immortals heard this and broke out in cold sweat.

"He still wants to attack Heavenly Court after all."

"Doesn't this mean that the group attacking Divine Emperor City will end up as cannon fodder?"

"Senior Wu Shuai is too aggressive, he wants to go against Heavenly Court no matter what!"

Wu Shuai had a look of displeasure: "What? You do not dare to attack Divine Emperor City?"

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch had an ugly expression, he spoke like he had constipation: "Please reconsider, Lord Alliance Leader, we..."

Wu Shuai waved his hand, saying unhappily: "Enough, I don't want to hear more excuses. How about this, let's get rid of Eastern Sea's Xia clan first."

Wu Shuai finally exposed his true motive.

Southern Border had Xia clan, Eastern Sea also had Xia clan, these Xia clans were not the same but they were similarly super forces.

Wu Shuai had a huge appetite, his first target was a super force.

If he mentioned this earlier, he would face the objection of the immortals. But his first two targets were Heavenly Court and Divine Emperor City, the immortals found that compared to them, they could accept this target, Eastern Sea's Xia clan, more easily!

Wu Shuai continued to analyze: "Eastern Sea's Xia clan has the weakest foundation of all the super forces, they are at the bottom of Eastern Sea's righteous path forces. Not just that, Xia clan is at the eastern most part of Eastern Sea, the location is remote, it suits our needs as a base."

"And even better, the territories of Xia clan and the Merman Imperial Court border each other, the Merman Imperial Court is our ally now, they can provide us a lot of help."

Saying this, Wu Shuai did not give anyone the chance to speak: "I have decided! Our target will be Xia clan."

Faced with such a domineering alliance leader, the immortals were quite displeased. But under the pressure of the Evil Dragon and Dragon Palace, they had no choice.

And most importantly, they were forced by the situation, they knew that if they did not use this opportunity well, if they did not gain an advantage now, the five regions would not let them off in the future.

"Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch, this alliance leader position should have been yours. Are you really going to let him have it?" After this meeting, some Gu Immortals were not satisfied, they hinted towards Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch smiled coldly to himself, he replied: "The nail that sticks out gets hammered down, the winds howl around the highest peaks. This Lord Wu Shuai is helping us charge forward as the vanguard, so what if I give him the alliance leader position? We have now gained the help of both the Evil Dragon and Dragon Palace."

"If our plan fails in the future and the five regions' Gu Immortals come after us, we can put the blame on Wu Shuai and get away ourselves."

Chapter 1982: Xia Clan's Catastrophe

Eastern Sea.

Reflecting shadow sea area.

The surface of the sea was like a smooth mirror without waves. Even when winds howled, the seawater remained unmoving.

Xia clan Gu Immortal Xia Zheng Qing was stationed here.

Reflecting shadow sea area was a giant resource point, it produced dark path and rule path cultivation resources in large quantities. Even though Xia clan primarily cultivated water path, these resources could be traded for huge profits.

Xia Zheng Qing was in closed cultivation now, suddenly, alarms rang in the formation around him.

"Is there an ancient desolate fish attacking the territory again?" Xia Zheng Qing initially thought that the sea beasts were causing chaos, he flew out of the formation.

But next, his entire body shook as he realized: "Enemies are attacking!"

Three rank seven Gu Immortals charged towards him together.

Xia Zheng Qing quickly activated the defensive formation.

At this time, there was a loud explosion as the formation shattered, a hairy man Gu Immortal carrying a huge hammer was covered in golden light as he charged into the formation, causing destruction!

Xia Zheng Qing spat out a mouthful of blood, looking fearful.

He immediately realized that the three immortals earlier were a distraction, this person was their main force.

"A rank eight hairy man Gu Immortal?" Xia Zheng Qing knew that he was not their match, he quickly transmitted to the clan as he activated the inner immortal formation, teleporting himself away.

At the next moment, he was transported to somewhere a thousand li away from the formation.

"Hahaha, he was transported here after all. Great Wisdom, very impressive." Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch praised.

Great Wisdom Immortal Mother shook her head: "If not for Lord Alliance Leader's precise information, how could I have made such accurate deductions?"

Xia Zheng Qing took a look and felt despair!

There were two variant human Gu Immortals here, they both had rank eight cultivation level.

"Since when did rank eight Gu Immortals become so common?"

"Three variant human rank eights!"

Xia Zheng Qing could not believe it, he gritted his teeth: "Who are you people? Why are you going against our Eastern Sea's Xia clan?"

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch could not be bothered to talk with him, he waved his hand, his killer move was unleashed.

Xia Zheng Qing only had rank seven cultivation level, how could he resist a rank eight killer move, he was instantly frozen in ice.

Eastern Sea Xia clan's headquarters, Hot Springs blessed land.

"Oh no! A strong group of enemies attacked, reflecting shadow sea is lost, even though Xia Zheng Qing used the immortal formation to escape, we have lost all contact with him!"

Xia Zheng Qing's call for help had reached Xia clan.

Most of Xia clan's Gu Immortals were gathered in the headquarters, they did not expect such bad news to appear out of nowhere.

"As the saying goes, while a person stays in their house, calamity descends from the sky!"

"Xia Zheng Qing sent information that there are both human and variant human Gu Immortals among the enemies, among them is a rank eight hairy man."

"Where did these people come from?"

"I'm afraid they are forces from black and white heaven. During the qi tide rampage, grotto-heavens are all exposed. To think there are still so many variant humans left, they even came to create trouble for us!"

"This is somewhat understandable. If they do not grasp onto this chance, when the qi tides subside, the five regions will investigate the grotto-heavens of black and white heaven. If we find any variant human force with rank eight Gu Immortals, we will exterminate them."

"Hehe, back then, even Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable and Star Constellation Immortal Venerable could not find all of the hidden variant human grotto-heavens. But now that the world has changed, these variant humans are forced to expose themselves."

Xia clan's Gu Immortals were not flustered, even though the information said that there was a rank eight variant human Gu Immortal, they still had an Immortal Gu Houses to resist the enemy.

But soon, more bad news came.

Light ripple sea and shooting fish sea were also taken down by these variant human Gu Immortals! The Xia clan Gu Immortals defending the two resource points were even weaker, they did not even manage to send any information over before losing contact.

Xia clan's Gu Immortals were furious.

"We need to teach these variant human Gu Immortals a lesson!"

"Mere variant humans dare to bully us human super forces."

"Hmph, Whom the heavens would destroy, they first make mad. These variant humans have gone insane."

"First supreme elder, let use mobilize both Immortal Gu Houses and kill them all!"

"Yes, our clan's three Gu Immortals have fallen into their hands. We need to save our clansmen and take revenge for this humiliation!!"

The Gu Immortals were filled with fighting spirit, they requested to fight.

Xia clan's first supreme elder was Xia Rui Zhi, hearing the Gu Immortals' words, his face was dark.

He shook his head: "It is not wise to attack now! We lost three resource points at once, these are all important places, we have powerful immortal formations protecting them. It is not normal that we lost them so quickly."

"Our clan does not have rank eight Gu Immortals defending us. If we mobilize both Immortal Gu Houses, our headquarters will be severely weakened. Right now, we are close to completing the Human Sea, we cannot be complacent!"

"In my opinion, we should defend ourselves fully until we complete Human Sea. By then, our foundation will rise greatly, we will be one of the top Eastern Sea forces. By then, dealing with the variant humans will have much greater effect."

Even though Xia Rui Zhi only had rank seven cultivation level, he had high reputation, after hearing his words, Xia clan's Gu Immortals felt that it was logical, they no longer had such a strong desire to fight.

But at the next moment, a thunderous sound erupted as an Immortal Gu House broke through the defensive barrier, entering Xia clan's public blessed land.

"Eastern Sea's Xia clan, today, you will face extermination!" The door of the Immortal Gu House opened as Wu Shuai and the other grotto-heaven Gu Immortals appeared.

Xia clan saw this group of enemies, fear and shock became plastered on their faces.

"Dragon Palace!"

"Wu Shuai!!"

"So many variant human rank eights, oh heavens!"

Xia clan's Gu Immortals turned pale, they were immensely fearful.

But Wu Shuai did not give them time to accept reality, he waved his hand: "Attack!"

Thus, at the next moment, the rank eights around him charged down and attacked.

Seeing this terrifying scene, Xia clan's Gu Immortals felt their vision turning dark, some almost fainted on the spot.

Such a group completely overwhelmed and dominated Xia clan's Gu Immortals.

Xia clan did not have a single rank eight while Wu Shuai had more than ten, how could they fight?

"My Xia clan's blessed land is not Heavenly Court, why are there so many rank eight Gu Immortals attacking us?!" Xia Rui Zhi mumbled, facing such a strong foe, he felt despair.

"The enemies are too strong, we must retreat!" At this time, female immortal Xia Ying shouted at the Xia clan immortals.

Xia Rui Zhi shook as he gritted his teeth: "Go, we will leave, let's get into the Immortal Gu Houses!"

Xia clan had two Immortal Gu Houses, they were both rank seven.

One was Whale Fishing Boat, the other was Golden Star Tower.

"You want to leave? Not so easy!"

"None of you will escape."

The variant human Gu Immortals attacked quickly, unleashing a myriad of attacks, the explosions resounded heaven and earth.

At the crucial moment, Xia Ying dodged an attack, managing to enter Golden Star Tower.

But she did not escape, she steered Golden Star Tower and went in front: "Everyone, leave, I will block them!"

Golden Star Tower charged relentlessly, using killer moves, golden stars shot out everywhere, the variant humans quickly dodged them.

The remaining Xia clan Gu Immortals found the chance and went into Whale Fishing Boat, escaping their headquarters.

Chapter 1983: You Have A Problem With Me?

"Even though these variant human Gu Immortals have rank eight cultivation level, their battle strength is not high. Only Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch is passable."

"As for Eastern Sea's Xia clan, even without a rank eight, they can rely on rank seven Immortal Gu Houses to put up a fight."

Wu Shuai stood near the door of Dragon Palace, he looked at the battlefield and observed the fight, he did not make a move.

Earlier, when attacking the three resource points, due to the difference in cultivation level, he could not tell. But in the current deadlock, he sensed many details.

Wu Shuai analyzed, he quickly realized the reason.

The variant humans were able to survive until today and develop well because of the help of heaven's will.

Heaven's will was disrupted by Star Constellation's will, it could not make fate Gu show the sign of variant human supremacy. But heaven's will could still influence calamities and tribulations.

Tribulations were the biggest obstacles in the rise of a Gu Immortal's cultivation level.

The more prosperous humanity was, the more help heaven's will would provide to the variant human grotto-heaven forces.

The difficulty of tribulations that these variant humans faced was many times simpler than normal human Gu Immortals! In fact, even for the human Gu Immortals in black and white heaven, because they were at odds with the five regions human forces, they were also given some special treatment. This was thanks to heaven's will.

There were clear historical records about this.

Back then, variant humans ruled the world as overlords. Heaven's will thus affected fate Gu and showed the revelation of humanity reigning supreme. On one hand, heaven's will aided Primordial Origin and helped him to become an Immortal Venerable, it also took care of the humans, helping humanity develop and grow. On the other hand, heaven's will also influenced the variant humans, dividing them and causing them to undergo intense internal conflict, they greatly weakened themselves.

"And because the two heavens are too huge, with each heaven having the total area of all five regions, there are so many rank eight Gu Immortals in black and white heaven. Other than the group I brought here, a small group are still left in the two heavens."

Wu Shuai thought about this as he started to move.

Dragon Palace slowly activated.

Xia Ying, who was inside Golden Star Tower, became anxious. It was very tough to deal with these rank eights now, she seemed to have the upper hand but she could not last long. Even if the battle tilted in the enemy's favor at the next second, it would not be surprising.

"Good, Lord Wu Shuai is making his move!"

"I'm looking forward to it."

"It is a pity that our grotto-heavens have no Immortal Gu Houses. Only after fighting can we see that they really are the foundation of a super force."

The rank eight Gu Immortals had excited expressions, they were anticipating his action.

But under everyone's gaze, Dragon Palace flew away from the battlefield.

The rank eight Gu Immortals were stunned.

What was going on?

At the next moment, Wu Shuai's icy voice could be heard: "If more than ten rank eights cannot deal with one rank seven immortal and a rank seven Immortal Gu House, what is the point of your existence?"

The rank eight Gu Immortals were tongue-tied, they could not respond.

Eventually, they could only watch as Dragon Palace flew away.

"Oh no, he is flying towards Human Sea!" Xia Ying saw this, her heart jumped.

Xia clan felt very suspicious: "How does Wu Shuai know that our Xia clan's base contains Human Sea? No, Human Sea is very deeply hidden, maybe he just wants to find some resources."

Wu Shuai left the battlefield, he went to the top of a certain lake, he stopped Dragon Palace's movement.

"Human Sea should be here." Wu Shuai's eyes shined with bright light, he activated his method.

A mystical light shot out from his palm, piercing hundreds of feet of lake water, reaching the bottom.

Next, the mystical light spread out towards the entire lake surface.

The water evaporated, turning into mist and dispersing, one could hear countless human voices from the dense white fog.

The voices of people became louder, the white fog turned into human silhouettes as they flew around in the sky.

At once, Dragon Palace was surrounded by white fog, countless silhouettes moved around Dragon Palace like ghost phantoms, there were tens of thousands of them.

"Come." Wu Shuai willed, the fog quickly gathered and condensed into white lake water that flowed into Dragon Palace.

The commotion created was huge, the two parties fighting in the battlefield could see it clearly.

"Wu Shuai actually went to collect loot while we are fighting with our full effort!"

"The fog is very special, it emitted dense human path aura. It must be a great treasure for Wu Shuai to retrieve it personally!"

"Don't fear, as the alliance leader, how can Wu Shuai not lead by example? How can he gain our acceptance otherwise? He will definitely give a portion of the white fog to us later."

The rank eight Gu Immortals conversed with each other.

Xia Ying's heart sank to rock bottom: "Wu Shuai actually knows about the existence of Human Sea! In fact, he has a method to take Human Sea away, how can this be possible?"

"The plan of constructing Human Sea was only known to us Xia clan Gu Immortals, we kept it as a secret all along. Even if Xia Zheng Qing and the rest were captured by Wu Shuai, only our first supreme elder knows how to retrieve Human Sea. How can he find an alternate method so quickly?"

"To think that the current Human Sea is still incomplete." Wu Shuai looked at the white fog in Dragon Palace, it was still showing human figures and shadows from time to time, it was creepy but quite amazing as well. Two different types of images had fused together in a natural way.

Wu Shuai smiled, he did not mind it.

To replenish Human Sea, he only needed to kill enough humans.

Because of the main body's information, Wu Shuai knew that Human Sea was the work of Xia clan for many years, they were attempting to create a human path secluded domain in secret.

In the five hundred years of his previous life, during the five regions chaotic war, Human Sea was dazzling and impressive, it helped Eastern Sea's Xia clan to rise up to the top.

But it was still far from an actual secluded domain after all.

In the future, Southern Border's Chai clan gained some key comprehension from Human Sea, they started to create a similar artificial secluded domain — Human Mountain.

Wisdom path Gu Immortals of that time had deduced that if Human Sea and Human Mountain were fused together into one, they could form an actual secluded domain of heaven and earth!

"Human Mountain and Sea is too far away, but just Human Sea alone is sufficiently helpful to my main body." Wu Shuai was quite happy.

The most important thing was Fang Yuan's main body after all.

The current biggest obstacle of Fang Yuan's main body was the restriction of heaven path. This was Red Lotus' scheme, Fang Yuan was trying to find a way to break out of this predicament.

He found that human path was a countermeasure, even though the thousand wish tree was a human path ancient desolate plant, it could not match the numerous heaven path dao marks.

Thus, Fang Yuan placed his sight on the Human Sea of Eastern Sea's Xia clan.

Because of Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch, Fang Yuan did not need to go personally, his clone Wu Shuai was able to head there and retrieve Human Sea easily.

After Wu Shuai stored Human Sea away, the battle had also concluded at the other side.

Xia Ying was unable to escape in the end, but many of the rank eights were injured as well. The one who defeated Golden Star Tower was Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch.

"Lord Alliance Leader, you took the chance to take the human path treasure, that's not fair, right?" As the immortals gathered at the door of Dragon Palace, an anxious rank eight Gu Immortal questioned.

Wu Shuai glanced at him as Dragon Palace used its killer move — Dreamy Light Smoke!

The rank eight Gu Immortal who spoke was unguarded, the smoke easily swept him away into Dragon Palace before he was even able to say another word.

The immortals were stunned and fearful.

"Who else has a problem with me?" Wu Shuai crossed his arms, looking at the immortals.

He only had rank seven cultivation level, he was surrounded by a group of rank eights.

But the rank eight Gu Immortals looked at each other, they were pale and chose to keep silent, they did not dare to say a thing.

Chapter 1984: Wu Shuai's Political Skills

Facing Wu Shuai's aggressive stance, the Gu Immortals of the two heavens lowered their heads, they did not dare to look at him directly.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch saw this, he cheered internally, Wu Shuai's actions would cause him to lose the support of everyone. However, he also felt envious, when would he gain such huge battle strength to make everyone lower their heads in front of him?

After a while of silence, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch stood up at an appropriate timing, saying respectfully: "Lord Alliance Leader, dear allies, the most important thing now is to go after the remaining Xia clan members. Most of Xia clan's Gu Immortals have escaped using Whale Fishing Boat, if we do not chase them now, it will be too late."

"Yes, yes." The immortals nodded, they started discussing this topic.

Many people casted gazes of gratitude towards Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch, his words had undeniably given them a way to escape the embarrassment.

"Haha." Wu Shuai laughed loudly: "Chase? Why must we chase them?"

Wu Shuai continued: "We were able to take down the headquarters of Eastern Sea's Xia clan, it was because we acted quickly and caught them off guard. From now, it will be difficult if we want to expand our territory. The whole of Eastern Sea and even the righteous paths of the five regions will become very cautious now."

"But if we allow this group of Xia clan Gu Immortals to escape, they will invite members of Eastern Sea's righteous path to try to recover their territory."

"This way, those Eastern Sea righteous path members will need to leave their territories and come here to seek death. Isn't that great?"

The immortals were stunned, they nodded in unison, agreeing that Wu Shuai's analysis was sound.

"Lord Alliance Leader is very knowledgeable, it is natural that we cannot compare to him." Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch ingratiated.

But Wu Shuai had a grim expression: "I don't care about all of these Eastern Sea super forces! There is only one person I am wary about, Qi Sea Ancestor."

"This old man can fight evenly with Duke Long, he had once held the qi sea banquet, he also did not help Fang Yuan nor Heavenly Court during the fate war. His stance is very important now!"

"It is likely that the righteous path will convince him now to fight against us. Of course, it is not strange if he chooses to continue staying in seclusion and not face us."

"I let these Xia clan members go, I am also trying to probe Qi Sea Ancestor's intentions."

The Gu Immortals of the two heavens heard Wu Shuai's words, they nodded as their expressions turned dark.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch took a glance at Wu Shuai, he thought: "Wu Shuai is Wu Shuai after all, he cannot be underestimated. He has both wisdom and political skills, it is just that he does not feel the need to use tricks against us."

But he quickly thought: "Qi Sea Ancestor's attitude is very ambiguous. He had once worked with Fang Yuan and went against Duke Long, but later they reconciled. On the other hand, he also held the qi sea banquet, he welcomed Heavenly Court's Gu Immortal Jun Shen Guang, while also letting a demonic Gu Immortal sell blood path Immortal Gu in public."

"Alright." Wu Shuai waved his hand, breaking the immortals' train of thought: "We chased Xia clan away, it is time to split the loot."

Thus, the atmosphere changed instantly, everyone got excited.

Eastern Sea was the richest of the five regions, as an Eastern Sea super force, Xia clan had ownership of many resource points, their inventory was filled.

These assets of Xia clan were split up by Fang Yuan and given to the Gu Immortals, each of them gained a considerable sum of wealth.

The Gu Immortals of the two heavens smiled, they felt extremely happy.

"The five regions are so rich!"

"This is merely the foundation of one Eastern Sea super force, it is already so much."

"Xia clan is useless! If my grotto-heaven had such resources, we would be far stronger than now."

And what surprised the Gu Immortals of the two heavens was that Wu Shuai took a much smaller portion of the gains that they had expected.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch had a change of thought, he quickly said to the surrounding Gu Immortals: "Everyone, listen to me. We gained so much loot because of Lord Alliance Leader. He was the one who guided us towards victory. Without his information and plan, how could we take down Xia clan so easily? But currently, Lord Alliance Leader is taking the smallest portion of loot, this is not fair to him."

The Gu Immortals were stunned, they looked at Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch had a look of sincerity and admiration.

Wu Shuai looked at Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch deeply in the eye: "I am a lone person, I do not need much in cultivation resources, nor do these resources suit me. If I need anything in the future, I will definitely take them. Since I have distributed this loot already, I will not take them back, but Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch, your words reminded me of something."

"Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch." Wu Shuai spoke.

"This subordinate is here." Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch cupped his fists, showing a respectful attitude.

Wu Shuai smiled: "You are quite good."

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch quickly bowed: "To receive such compliments from Lord Alliance Leader, it is my greatest blessing!"

Wu Shuai nodded: "Of course, my leadership is the greatest blessing that all of you have. As for you, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch, as the vice alliance leader, you should not get the same amount of loot as the rest of the allies. I will make the decision, shooting fish sea will belong to you now."

"Lord Alliance Leader?" Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch quickly raised his head, feeling shocked.

Wu Shuai laughed: "I said you'll get it, just take ownership of it. Don't worry! I am here to back you up. If anyone dares to make problems for you, if you dislike anyone, just tell me, I will take care of them!"

Wu Shuai said this as he looked around, his dragon eyes emitting an aggressive light. The Gu Immortals all turned away, not daring to meet his gaze.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch obtained a giant resource point but he felt no joy internally.

He looked at Wu Shuai, seeing that seemingly smiling face, he could not help but shudder in a chill.

"As expected of the dragonman who once ruled his race, I underestimated him! This old monster must have realized my intentions." Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch noticed this, his back was covered in cold sweat.

He wanted to cause Wu Shuai to lose even more support from the rest of the people. But Wu Shuai had made use of his action and acted this way, it made all the other Gu Immortals feel that Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch was not happy with his gains, he wanted to use his status and the alliance leader's dominance to gain more benefits.

After all, if the alliance leader gets more benefits, wouldn't it be logical if the vice alliance leader also got more loot?

"Hmm? Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch, you are not thanking me?" Wu Shuai stared at Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch, showing a smile filled with deep meaning.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch shuddered in his heart as he gritted his teeth and said with a hoarse voice: "This subordinate thanks Lord Alliance Leader."

Seeing that he had submitted, Wu Shuai did not feel any happiness, he was actually quite disappointed.

The Gu Immortals of the two heavens had been in seclusion for too long, due to their identities, they did not dare to move around or compete against each other.

Without competition, they could not be trained well. Even if heaven's will helped them, Gu Immortal elites could not be nurtured.

Wu Shuai looked at the Gu Immortals of the two heavens, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch was the only one with passable battle strength and attitude. The rest of the rank eights were simply a disgrace to other rank eight Gu Immortals!

It was no wonder that in Fang Yuan's previous life, these people did not manage to create any big commotions.

Chapter 1985: Truly Incredible

While Wu Shuai and the rest were splitting up the fortune of Xia clan, the atmosphere inside Whale Fishing Boat was grim and sad.

"First supreme elder, what do we do now?"

"The enemies are too powerful, there are more than ten rank eights, there was no way we could defend our headquarters!"

"Especially their leader Wu Shuai! If we retaliate, there is little hope of success."

"Sigh, it is a pity that Xia Ying and the rest sacrificed themselves."

Xia clan's Gu Immortals were furious and helpless, they felt that the future was bleak.

Xia clan's first supreme elder Xia Rui Zhi snorted coldly: "I don't care who the enemy is, be it Wu Shuai or the rank eight Gu Immortals of the two heavens, they should not have taken our Xia clan's territory. They will not stay arrogant for long! We are going to get help from Eastern Sea's righteous path."

"Hmph, so be it if they are human Gu Immortals. But they are mostly variant human Gu Immortals with Wu Shuai leading them, we have already kept a copy of the battle scene, it is the best evidence against them. Eastern Sea's righteous path and even the five regions' righteous path will not allow this group of variant humans to grow stronger and larger!"

Xia clan's Gu Immortals heard this, they recovered a bit of their morale.

Seeking reinforcements was the only way out, but the important thing to consider was which clan to approach.

Xia clan was situated at the eastern most area of Eastern Sea, towards their west was the Merman Imperial Court, towards the southeast was Tang clan, and towards the northeast was Xie clan. These three were not good targets to request for help.

The three of them were directly connected to Xia clan in territory, Xia clan's relationship with the Merman Imperial Court was best but they were variant humans. Even though there were no mermen in the battle earlier, Xia clan did not dare to take the risk.

As for Tang clan and Xie clan, these two clans had conflict with Xia clan during normal times, if they went to ask these two clans for help, Xia clan's Gu Immortals would not want to face their mockery.

After a round of discussion, Xia clan's Gu Immortals moved in Whale Fishing Boat, they carefully went past the Merman Imperial Court, approaching Shen clan, which was further west, for help.

But because of this, their journey became much longer.

During Xia clan's journey to seek help, information that they were invaded by Gu Immortals of the two heavens spread like wildfire in treasure yellow heaven, it shook the world.

"There are so many rank eight Gu Immortals among the variant humans! Is this information reliable?"

"It is nothing strange. Be it black heaven or white heaven, each of them is as large as the five regions together."

"These damned variant humans are hidden too deeply!"

"They are too daring, they dared to wage war on our human forces, they are courting death!"

"The thing that makes me angrier is that among these people, there are human Gu Immortals. What are they thinking? They are betraying their own race!"

At once, all of the Gu Immortals in the world discussed this matter.

Shen clan was no exception.

The letter requesting help from Xia clan had already reached Shen clan.

This was an important matter, Shen clan's first supreme elder, Shen Cong Sheng, called all the Gu Immortals for a meeting.

"The reason why Xia clan is asking our Shen clan for help is obvious, there is no need to explain it. But should our Shen clan help them? Everyone, tell me your view." Shen Cong Sheng said.

"The enemy is too strong, why must our Shan clan face such a strong foe alone? Remember that Wu Shuai has Dragon Palace and Di Zang Sheng, he even possesses dream path methods, their battle strength is too overwhelming."

"That's right, and even more worrying is that Wu Shuai has a relationship with Fang Yuan. Nobody knows how good their relationship is, but we know that they are close. If we target Wu Shuai, we might cause the great demon Fang Yuan to come after us!"

Shen Cong Sheng nodded: "You are correct."

He did not show any change of expression.

During the blue dragon whale trip, he had cooperated with Fang Yuan. But because they worked in secrecy, even Shen clan's Gu Immortals did not know about it, Shen Cong Sheng could preserve his clan's reputation as a result.

"I feel that we cannot refuse to help Xia clan! Xia clan is also a member of the righteous path, they came all this way to ask us for help, if we do not agree, what would Xia clan think of us? What would Eastern Sea think of us? What would the whole five regions think of us?"

"I agree, this is not just a conflict between us humans, this is the battle between humans and variant humans! If Shen clan does not show a clear stance, the people of the world will accuse us of our inaction."

Shen Cong Sheng nodded: "This is correct too. But the enemy is too strong, they have more than ten rank eights and even Wu Shuai leading them. Even if we have Ancestor Shen Shang here, we cannot resist such a group of enemies."

After the fate war, Shen Shang went missing after going insane. Even though Shen clan wanted to find their Ancestor Shen Shang, they did not succeed.

The entire world was watching now, it was likely that news in treasure yellow heaven had spread from Xia clan themselves.

Xia clan was using this method to force Eastern Sea's righteous path forces to help them.

With the entire world watching, Shen clan had to help Xia clan. But Wu Shuai's group was simply too powerful, they were too terrifying.

Even though Shen clan was a super force, against the allied forces of two heavens, it still felt very wary and unsure.

"Elders, I have a plan to resolve this problem." Ren Xiu Ping spoke.

After returning from the blue dragon whale trip, Ren Xiu Ping became Shen clan's external supreme elder. Ren Xiu Ping was a person who followed the rules and kept a low profile, but now that they were in this situation, if Shen clan falls and chaos descends, he would also be implicated.

Ren Xiu Ping continued: "Wu Shuai has very high strength, but in this current Eastern Sea, there is another ancestor capable of resisting the Evil Dragon."

"You mean to say that person in qi sea?" Someone's eyes brightened up.

"Indeed, Qi Sea Ancestor." Ren Xiu Ping nodded.

"Good plan, let's do that." Shen Cong Sheng laughed and clapped, deciding on the spot.

For the next few days, Xia clan arrived in Shen clan, they wanted to borrow strength to reclaim their territory. Shen Cong Sheng came out to speak to them, they attended to Xia clan's members warmly.

But when asked to fight against Wu Shuai, Shen Cong Sheng said that he had too little strength, he suggested that they should gather more righteous path forces.

Currently, qi tides were surging everywhere, almost all the five regions' Gu Immortals were recuperating and resting, they did not dare to move abruptly.

Thus, Eastern Sea's righteous path could not use much of its strength now.

But Shen Cong Sheng suggested that Xia clan should inform Qi Sea Ancestor of this situation, they should request for the ancestor to uphold justice for them.

Shen Cong Sheng copied Xia clan, before they asked Qi Sea Ancestor for help, they already published the news in treasure yellow heaven.

Thus, the entire world's attention went to qi sea.

Almost all the Gu Immortals were waiting to see Qi Sea Ancestor's response.

All the human Gu Immortals were hoping that Qi Sea Ancestor would step up as the senior of the rank eights, the person who resisted Duke Long on equal footing, he had the responsibility to lead them.

But many people were pessimistic about it. Because Qi Sea Ancestor was a secluded cultivator, he had an ambiguous relationship with the righteous path and demonic path, he had even worked with Fang Yuan before. From this aspect, there was quite a chance that Qi Sea Ancestor would not entertain these worldly affairs.

Qi Sea Ancestor's response was rapid.

He announced in treasure yellow heaven: "There are those of other races having such motives, first there was Primordial Origin, now there is Qi Sea, we will not let these variant humans with ulterior motives bear roots here on our soil!"

Once he said that, the world world resounded with praises.

Qi Sea Ancestor, you are truly incredible!

Chapter 1986: Heavenly Court's Tactic

Heavenly Court.

The damage caused during the fate war was starting to recover. Having collated their losses, they really had suffered a huge setback.

Discussion hall.

Qin Ding Ling sat at the main seat as she looked around, observing the Gu Immortals and their wills.

Most of the Heavenly Court members had gone back to hibernating in the immortal graveyard. More than half of the immortal graveyard was destroyed by Fang Yuan, but Heavenly Court still had sufficient members left.

These members had little lifespan remaining, rather than dying of old age, they could display greater value by hibernating in the immortal graveyard.

What worried Qin Ding Ling was that even though these Gu Immortals went back into slumber, she did not receive any sort of message from Star Constellation's will.

It was as if the fate war caused Star Constellation's will to suffer a huge loss.

This made already become Qin Ding Ling's greatest worry. Star Constellation's will could interfere with heaven's will but heaven's will was also able to assimilate Star Constellation's will. If she lacked support and got assimilated by heaven's will, it would be a huge nightmare to humanity and Heavenly Court.

But Qin Ding Ling came here and gathered the immortals for a meeting, it was not because of Star Constellation's will.

"Qi tides are rampaging, the two heavens are making a move. Wu Shuai is leading an allied army of the two heavens and has already taken down Eastern Sea's Xia clan. Now, Xia clan has requested for Qi Sea Ancestor's help, the two sides are opposing each other. What do you think we should do at this key moment?"

Qin Ding Ling asked.

She was a luck path Gu Immortal, she did not cultivate wisdom path like Fairy Zi Wei. Thus, when faced with this matter, Qin Ding Ling could not make a resolute decision, she needed to discuss it with the other Gu Immortals.

"Undeniably, the allied army of the two heavens is made up of variant humans, enemies of our Heavenly Court, we need to exterminate them!"

"In this aspect, Qi Sea Ancestor is quite a responsible person."

"Right now, the conflict between Wu Shuai and Qi Sea Ancestor is akin to the conflict between humans and variant humans. But the truth is, whoever wins between them is not the key, the most important element is someone else — Fang Yuan!"

"Indeed, be it Wu Shuai or Qi Sea Ancestor, they are both related to Fang Yuan. Wu Shuai claims that he has only cooperated with Fang Yuan, he has revived after a million years, aspiring to grow the dragonman race once again. As for Qi Sea Ancestor, he had once made an agreement with Fang Yuan, he went against Heavenly Court but changed his mind later when Lord Duke Long gave him half of the qi path true inheritance. During the fate war, Qi Sea Ancestor did not show up at all, it showed that Lord Duke Long had made a wise decision."

"I have a different opinion! Qi Sea Ancestor can likely be Fang Yuan's disguise. In the past, we did not think of this because Fang Yuan only had rank seven cultivation level, but now that we know about the secret of the sovereign immortal body, it is likely that Fang Yuan had rank eight cultivation level then and disguised himself as Qi Sea Ancestor. Don't forget that during the fate war, Fang Yuan destroyed the qi wall with a qi path method."

"His qi path method is called unlimited qi sea, it is the signature method of Qi Xiang of the Heaven Surveying Five Xiangs in the past. But the qi path methods that Qi Sea Ancestor used against Duke Long were very different from unlimited qi sea. It is quite unlikely that the two of them are the same person."

"But we cannot rule out this possibility."

"Speaking of which, Wu Shuai is much more suspicious than Qi Sea Ancestor. He might not be a disguised Fang Yuan, he could simply be Fang Yuan's clone. As the leader of Shadow Sect, Fang Yuan definitely has a portion of Spectral Soul's foundation. And a method Spectral Soul excels in is creating split souls. That was how he created Shadow Sect singlehandedly."

The immortals discussed among themselves.

Qin Ding Ling was hesitant, she felt a huge headache.

The immortals had their own viewpoints, nobody could convince the other. In the end, Qin Ding Ling had to make the decision after all.

Qin Ding Ling thought about it for a while before sighing: "Everyone, listen to me. Fang Yuan has familiar face, he can disguise as different people. Even though we need to be wary of this, we cannot ignore other possibilities just because of our suspicions. Wu Shuai might be Fang Yuan's clone, Qi Sea Ancestor might be Fang Yuan's disguise, these are possible truths."

"But at the same time, there is also the possibility that they are not that closely related to Fang Yuan. We cannot create enemies everywhere just because of this, forget about Wu Shuai, but for Qi Sea Ancestor, we cannot give up on winning over Qi Sea Ancestor just because of this possibility, can't we try to make him an ally of Heavenly Court?"

Fang Zheng heard this as he hesitated and asked: "Senior Qin wants to recruit Qi Sea Ancestor?"

Qin Ding Ling nodded: "Lord Duke Long has passed away while Feng Jiu Ge betrayed us, our Heavenly Court desperately needs a pseudo venerable capable of holding the situation. In the past, Senior Duke Long used Primordial Origin's true inheritance to gain Qi Sea Ancestor's friendship. Even though he did not agree to join us, he had not shown up during the fate war either."

The immortals fell into silence.

Qin Ding Ling's current plan was Duke Long's former plan.

In the past, in order to repair fate Gu, Duke Long wanted Qi Sea Ancestor to stay out of the conflict. But now?

Heavenly Court needed someone with pseudo venerable battle strength to support them!

Currently, even though there was peace, the truth was that the rampaging qi tides and heaven path dao marks were forcing most Gu Immortals to stay inactive and recuperate from the damages caused, they could not take action.

But once the qi tides subside and Fang Yuan manages to refine the heaven path dao marks?

By then, the strongest person in Heavenly Court would be Qin Ding Ling, could she resist the Gu Immortals of the other four regions with ill intentions? Could she block Di Zang Sheng? Could she block Fang Yuan?

Heavenly Court knew about this threat, in history, they had also recruited Gu Immortals of the other four regions.

The obvious example was Wan Zi Hong, this female immortal was once a demoness of Western Desert, Heavenly Court had recruited her to join them. As long as one was a human, Heavenly Court could be magnanimous towards them.

"I am not against winning Qi Sea Ancestor over. But before that, we need to clarify his true relationship with Fang Yuan!"

"That's what you say, but right now, Qi Sea Ancestor might not even feel any threat from our Heavenly Court."

"Haha, I think that for him, the attraction of Primordial Origin's true inheritance surpasses everything."

Fang Zheng volunteered: "Currently, the conflict between Qi Sea Ancestor and Wu Shuai is our greatest opportunity. We can investigate and find out the truth from this. Of course, no matter the outcome, we cannot spare the Gu Immortals of the two heavens. Since we already have Night Heavenly Wolf Lord as our insider, I am willing to lead a group to Eastern Sea and exterminate these variant human Gu Immortals!"

Fang Zheng was the current owner of Demon Judgment Board, even though he had rank seven cultivation level, with this board, he could fight against most rank eight Gu Immortals.

Due to the influence of qi tides, the five regions' Gu Immortals could not move around. But Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were different.

Most of them had phantom apertures, they were not restricted by this.

Right as Fang Zheng spoke, another Gu Immortal volunteered to join the group and head to Eastern Sea, in order to kill these variant human Gu Immortals.

Even though Heavenly Court lost, their motives and actions still followed the basis of defending humanity.

Qin Ding Ling smiled: "I got it! Why must we go to Eastern Sea? Wu Shuai is there right now, we can use him to probe Qi Sea Ancestor's background. Let's go to the two heavens and exterminate those grotto-heaven forces, we will uproot the allied army of the two heavens from their bases!"

Chapter 1987: Qi Harvest Fruit

"Heavenly Court is Heavenly Court after all..." Night Heavenly Wolf Lord looked at the information path Gu worm in his hand as he sighed to himself.

As he had expected, Heavenly Court really went ahead to deal with the two heavens alliance.

Earlier, he had predicted that such a situation would occur.

Those who live in a society have to follow its rules, Night Heavenly Wolf Lord had to join the two heavens alliance. Otherwise, his grotto-heaven would be attacked until it was destroyed.

But joining this force only helped to delay their own destruction.

When the five regions counterattack, the two heavens alliance would break apart, there would be huge casualties. None of these allies would be spared, Night Wolf grotto-heaven would also face a calamity by then.

From the start, Night Heavenly Wolf Lord had made up his mind to defect to the five regions. This was for his own sake, and also the future of the entire Night Wolf grotto-heaven.

Thus, he took a risk and went to approach Heavenly Court.

As the situation progressed, Qi Sea Ancestor went against Wu Shuai and Heavenly Court sent a secret group to attack the headquarters of the two heavens' variant humans!

Since Night Heavenly Wolf Lord decided to defect, Heavenly Court's Qin Ding Ling sent him a secret letter, asking him to be their spy and cooperate with Heavenly Court in this battle.

"Heavenly Court did not disappoint me after all!"

"Even though they lost in the fate war, despite everything, they still uphold the righteousness of humanity. They think for the whole of the human race without caring about sacrifices or benefits."

Such grandness resonated with Night Heavenly Wolf Lord.

Because he was a human Gu Immortal!

Compared to Heavenly Court's magnanimity, be they Qi Sea Ancestor or Wu Yong, they were simply too petty. Even Northern Plains' Longevity Heaven was the same.

What was the mindset that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable left behind?

Hereditary monarchy!

Even if Night Heavenly Wolf Lord and Longevity Heaven had no grudges, he would not go to and attempt to join them.

Night Heavenly Wolf Lord did not hesitate, he immediately replied that he was willing to cooperate with Heavenly Court.

According to their agreement, the moment Wu Shuai and Qi Sea Ancestor collide, Heavenly Court would use the chance to attack! If these two do not fight, then a month later, Heavenly Court would still take action.

"It will depend on Wu Shuai and Qi Sea Ancestor now." Night Heavenly Wolf Lord waited in anticipation.

Other than Night Heavenly Wolf Lord, countless forces and Gu Immortals were also paying attention to the situation in Eastern Sea.

Southern Border's Wu Yong was one of them.

"If Qi Sea Ancestor loses, the variant human forces will definitely expand their territory, they will develop rapidly like a growing snowball, they will become a huge threat to the five regions!"

"If Wu Shuai loses, the variant human forces will gather together in a defensive manner, this will be good news to the humans of the five regions. But that is not what I want to see."

Wu Yong was an ambitious person.

He wanted the world to be chaotic, the more conflicts there were, the more opportunities he had to try to reap benefits from the situation, to strengthen himself until he reached the top of the world!

Thus, he felt deep hatred towards the qi tides.

Because of the qi tides, the five regions' Gu Immortals had to forcefully recuperate, he lost the chance to completely take down Heavenly Court.

It was a real pity.

"Lord, Empress Wu Ji and the others have revived. What do we do now?" At this time, Wu Ba Chong came to report the news.

He was the second supreme elder of Wu clan, he was an old and experienced man.

After fate Gu was destroyed, the most evident change was that revival methods became very easy to use. Earlier, Gu Immortal seeds like Empress Wu Ji had died on Yi Tian Mountain. But now, Wu clan's Gu Immortals revived them all.

Wu Yong nodded: "These people are the hope of our future, they have experienced ample setbacks and training as Gu Masters. When they become Gu Immortals, they will definitely be elites among their peers. Impart them the method of immortal ascension and make ample preparations, ensure there are enough resources. I want Wu clan to gain more than ten Gu Immortals in the next few years!"

"Yes lord." Wu Ba Chong did not question this decision.

In the future, during the five regions chaotic war, there would be a long lasting struggle, it would not be settled quickly. By then, all of the different forces would need to compete using their foundation and long term planning.

"There is another matter regarding qi path." Wu Ba Chong said as he handed Wu Yong an information path mortal Gu.

Wu Yong looked into it and quickly browsed through the content.

This information path mortal Gu contained the information of all sorts of qi path immortal materials, they had all appeared as a result of the qi tides.

"It seems that qi path is about to flourish again. Does this qi harvest fruit really have such great effects?" Wu Yong sighed as he asked at the end.

Wu Ba Chong nodded: "Currently, many Gu Immortals have used it already, it is precisely so. This fruit is the essence of qi path and the fusion of the five regions' qi, it is not normal. By placing it into one's immortal aperture, it can turn into turbulent qi flows that can hasten the transformation of the heaven and earth qi. Whoever can get more qi harvest fruits will be able to get through this period of inactivity more quickly."

"Then collect more of this immortal material. Also, sort out and make a list of the clan's inventory, collate a qi path inheritance. We are going to use it and try to cultivate qi path Gu Immortals." Wu Yong instructed.

"Yes." Wu Ba Chong answered.

Wu clan was specialized in wind path, they did not have much foundation in qi path. But such a huge force would naturally have accumulation in qi path to some extent, if they could put together many incomplete inheritances into a proper inheritance, they might be able to nurture one or two qi path Gu Immortals.

Of course, even if these Gu Masters became qi path Gu Immortals, they would not be promising in terms of future achievements.

But since Wu clan had to make up for their deficiency in this aspect, these Gu Masters could only sacrifice their future potential and become qi path Gu Immortals.

Southern Border, Luo clan.

Three Gu Immortals went deeply into Qi Jue grotto heaven.

"I broke through!" Luo Ran was excited.

His skin tone was white and he had a cold expression, he was a Luo clan general famous in Southern Border, having peak rank seven battle strength.

When the entire world was resting and recuperating, Luo Ran secretly brought two Gu Immortals from Luo clan and explored Qi Jue grotto heaven, he did not care about the changes in his own immortal aperture.

His hard work and efforts were not in vain, they finally broke through the difficulties and had a smooth journey ahead.

As they explored deeper, they arrived at the center of Qi Jue grotto heaven.

"To think that the qi tides would cause a change in Qi Jue grotto heaven, allowing us to progress more smoothly in here." Luo Mu Zi felt deep emotions about this.

"Let's hurry up, the qi tides are rampaging in the world now, Qi Jue grotto heaven will only stay concealed for a short period of time. We need to find Qi Jue's true inheritance before anyone else finds us. With this true inheritance, our Luo clan will be able to adapt to this great era and obtain the initiative!" Luo Hao Ze's eyes shined with bright light.

Several days later.

Eastern Sea.

Qi Sea Ancestor suddenly appeared, creating countless qi waves that moved towards the headquarters of Eastern Sea's Xia clan openly.

"Come!" Wu Shuai sensed it from far away, he smiled as Dragon Palace moved, he controlled Di Zang Sheng and fought bravely against the enemy.

A huge battle that concerned the whole world erupted all of a sudden.

Chapter 1988: Wu Shuai Fights Qi Sea Ancestor

Rumble!

With a thunderous sound, intense tremors filled heaven and earth. Endless qi waves surged out, Dragon Palace shined with radiant lights as it retreated continuously.

Qi Sea Ancestor did not pursue it, many layers of qi waves stacked around his body, like an impenetrable fortress.

Both sides fought for an entire day and night, they exchanged blows but neither party could do anything to the other.

All around the battlefield, countless eyes were watching. Eastern Sea's righteous path, demonic path, and even lone immortals came here to watch the fight, naturally, there were also Gu Immortals of the two heavens.

"Senior Qi Sea Ancestor is truly powerful, his methods are grand and imposing, Wu Shuai's attacks all ended up useless." Hua clan first supreme elder Hua Cai Yun sighed to herself.

Beside her, Qing Yue An said: "But Wu Shuai is not to be underestimated, he merely has rank seven cultivation level but is able to evenly match Qi Sea Ancestor."

Hua Cai Yun sighed: "Wu Shuai was reborn, he is also an old monster. The Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace that he controls is really powerful, if not for it, he would not be Qi Sea Ancestor's match."

While the two conversed, a loud dragon roar resounded.

A huge demonic dragon that seemed like a mountain range appeared on the battlefield, it could be seen from a gigantic distance away.

"Oh heavens, such a terrifying giant dragon, this must be the number one immemorial desolate beast in the world?"

"This is Di Zang Sheng! I am shocked just by simply watching it fight, I cannot muster any battle intent against it. I can't imagine how the Gu Immortals fighting against it felt."

"Wu Shuai finally let out the Evil Dragon, this proves that Qi Sea Ancestor has forced him to his limit. The following fight is the crucial part."

All of the Gu Immortals watching this fight were shocked. Many of them had not participated in the fate war, they only watched it through the killer move everybody's vision. They saw the battle but did not experience it personally.

Their personal experience now was naturally creating a different feeling.

The Evil Dragon roared as it charged towards Qi Sea Ancestor.

Qi Sea Ancestor snorted coldly, his voice reverberating over the surroundings. He clapped both hands as an immortal killer move was unleashed, qi currents surged like a tsunami.

Di Zang Sheng charged forward but as it crashed into the qi currents, its movement halted.

Di Zang Sheng twisted its body and wanted to progress but the qi currents were endless, the great power could not be defied, it was forcefully suppressed on the ground!

Seeing this, the observing Gu Immortals gasped.

Qing Yue An, Hua Cai Yun, and Shen Cong Sheng cheered as expressions of joy appeared on their faces.

As for Zhou Xiong Xin and Jun Shen Guang who were sent here by Heavenly Court, they became stunned, quickly looking at each other.

"Thinking about the fate war, the two transformation path great experts of our Heavenly Court could not stop the rampaging Evil Dragon, they were suppressed by it. To think that Qi Sea Ancestor is able to stop it!" Jun Shen Guang was stunned.

Zhou Xiong Xin squinted, he assessed Qi Sea Ancestor from afar. His information path methods had been used already, seeking to collect information from the entire battlefield as the fight progressed.

Zhou Xiong Xin analyzed: "Qi Sea Ancestor is an expert who fought evenly with Lord Duke Long, it is not strange that he can resist Evil Dragon Di Zang Sheng. But his new killer move seems to have some elements of the primordial qi wall in it."

"Lord Duke Long once gave half of Primordial Origin's true inheritance to Qi Sea Ancestor. To think that he has already innovated upon it after the fate war had just ended to create a brand new qi wall killer move."

Jun Shen Guang blinked: "Does this mean that during the fate war, Qi Sea Ancestor was in closed cultivation to comprehend this new killer move?"

Zhou Xiong Xin could not deny it: "We cannot be sure yet. But at least for now, Qi Sea Ancestor's methods are very different from the qi path methods that Fang Yuan possesses."

Saying this, Zhou Xiong Xin sighed: "Qi Sea Ancestor's origin is too mysterious, he is too deeply concealed. We have not even found any past details about him. Beforehand, we could use the River of Time to trace his origin and find out his past identity. But after fate Gu's destruction, the River of Time has become extremely dangerous, it is filled with vicious waves, even if a time path great expert enters, they will be in great danger, we cannot enter it anymore."

Other than time path, there was still wisdom path.

But regrettably, Fang Yuan destroyed the majority of the immortal graveyard while Fairy Zi Wei defected to Spectral Soul, Heavenly Court faced an unprecedented lack of wisdom path experts.

Boom—!

An overwhelming amount of qi waves crashed down with heaven shaking might.

The Evil Dragon roared, it tried to move its mountain-like body, but Qi Sea Ancestor continued to suppress it from above.

Qi Sea Ancestor's moves gave an unrivaled atmosphere, his every action contained the power to overturn mountains and seas, the great Evil Dragon was not his match.

The human Gu Immortals cheered to themselves.

At this moment, Qi Sea Ancestor's reputation rose greatly in the five regions.

When the five regions' Gu Immortals could not fight, when humanity was at its weakest, Qi Sea Ancestor had emerged to resist and defeat the variant humans, this was really satisfying to all the human Gu Immortals.

"This is the action of a true man!" Even though Xi clan's first supreme elder did not come personally, he had sent a Xi clan Gu Immortal to witness this battle themselves.

Wu Yong was in Southern Border, upon seeing this, his heart sank as he pondered: "When we attack Eastern Sea in the future, this Qi Sea Ancestor will be a huge obstacle."

Qin Ding Ling was guarding Heavenly Court with a complex emotion. In the past, Heavenly Court would be the one standing up during such situations, fighting on the front lines, but this time, Qi Sea Ancestor took Heavenly Court's place and shouldered the expectations of the human race.

Even though Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were still suspicious about Qi Sea Ancestor's identity and his connection to Fang Yuan, after this battle, their impression towards him had undoubtedly improved greatly.

While the human Gu Immortals were feeling happy, the two heavens alliance felt solemn, all the Gu Immortals were fearful.

"How can this be! Even after using Di Zang Sheng, we cannot turn the situation around?"

"The humans are really strong! This is the foundation of the five regions, we chose to invade them so abruptly, we were simply too hasty."

"Hmph, even if we do not take action, these humans will still go after us. For the last few million years, they have been treating us variant humans like so."

"Indeed, we can only have any hope of surviving by taking the initiative."

"We cannot interfere in a battle of such a level, sigh, we can only hope that Lord Wu Shuai can claim victory!"

The variant human Gu Immortals continued to converse, their expressions were grim as their gazes turned uncertain.

There were many rank eight Gu Immortals among them, they had high cultivation and generally were characters of ancestor level in their respective grotto-heavens. But after witnessing this terrifying battle, nobody dared to participate.

"Qi Sea Ancestor, you have been arrogant for too long!" Right at this moment, Dragon Palace rose up, Wu Shuai's voice came from within.

The immortals watched as Dragon Palace flew towards Qi Sea Ancestor like an orange-gold meteor.

Qi Sea Ancestor's qi currents surged and blocked it but the effect was mild.

Dragon Palace rode the waves and advanced further, charging with great momentum. A dream path killer move was used, a trace of smoke shot towards Qi Sea Ancestor.

"Be careful!" Seeing this, many human Gu Immortals shouted while feeling very anxious, despite knowing their voices could not reach the battlefield.

Right now, dream path was invincible in the world. Qi Sea Ancestor had to dodge the attack as he retreated.

This time, Wu Shuai gained the upper hand.

The variant humans quickly became overjoyed while the human Gu Immortals let out sighs of relief, Qi Sea Ancestor was not hit by the dream path killer move, that was an ideal outcome!

The battle between Qi Sea Ancestor and Wu Shuai concerned all of the Gu Immortals in the world. Each clash shook people's souls, it would directly affect the future of the five regions.

As the two sides continued to fight, the immortals heard loud noises from the west.

The loud sound came imposingly, with an unstoppable aura like a torrential flood.

The Gu Immortals heard this and quickly shifted their gazes, they saw that qi tides were approaching the battlefield from far in the horizons.

"During this crucial battle, the qi tides actually came to wreak havoc!"

"Quickly retreat, if we get hit by the qi tides, our immortal apertures will tremor and result in lots of losses."

"What about this battle?"

The Gu Immortals were stunned, this was an unexpected development.

Jun Shen Guang's expression sank: "Oh no! Qi Sea Ancestor is an Eastern Sea Gu Immortal, he is restricted by the qi tides, the situation will be severe. But Wu Shuai is a new dragonman Gu Immortal, after the refinement path modification, he is less affected."

This information came from Duke Long.

During the fate war, Duke Long secretly used dragonman extermination but could not end Wu Shuai's life. Back then, he specially told them about this.

Humans alike dragons was the Gu refinement method created by Duke Long, it could turn humans into dragonmen. The first generation dragonmen were created by this method.

Heavenly Court had Duke Long's information and also the method humans alike dragons, they could easily deduce a portion of Wu Shuai's foundation. Thus, when they learned that Wu Shuai was leading the two heavens alliance to invade Eastern Sea, they were not surprised that he could fight.

Zhou Xiong Xin gritted his teeth: "Qi tides are a qi tide catastrophe, Qi Sea Ancestor is a qi path great expert, he definitely has an advantage in dealing with it compared to us! Now, let's see how he deals with this change, it will be the turning point of this battle."

"Qi Sea Ancestor, even heaven is not helping you. Let's see how long you can last in the qi tide!" Wu Shuai shouted excitedly, he moved Dragon Palace to assist the Evil Dragon as they attacked ferociously.

This sight made the human Gu Immortals grit their teeth as they retreated, many prayed in their hearts: "Senior Qi Sea Ancestor, you must persevere."

At the next moment, Qi Sea Ancestor laughed loudly: "Wu Shuai, you fell for it, I was waiting for you to fall for the bait."

As he said that, the qi waves turned around, like a blossoming flower returning to a bud, they encased Qi Sea Ancestor and Dragon Palace before condensing into a dot, vanishing.

In the battlefield, only Evil Dragon Di Zang Sheng was left growling and roaring.

"What battlefield killer move is this?"

"At the crucial moment, Senior Qi Sea Ancestor actually trapped Wu Shuai in a battlefield killer move. This is too amazing!"

"So Qi Sea Ancestor had been plotting all along."

"Wu Shuai is trapped in a qi path battlefield, isolated from the Evil Dragon, he is at a disadvantage now."

"That might not be true, Qi Sea Ancestor's qi path battlefield is going to face the rushing qi tides, if the battlefield is destroyed, Qi Sea Ancestor will suffer backlash, he might end up in a disadvantage too."

"Now, it will depend on whether Qi Sea Ancestor is able to break into Dragon Palace first. If not, when his qi path battlefield is destroyed, Wu Shuai will gather with the Evil Dragon, Qi Sea Ancestor will be in huge danger."

The Gu Immortals on both sides were very worried.

They could not personally watch such a crucial battle. Not only that, they had to retreat away from the qi tides, otherwise, their losses in the immortal aperture would be huge.

Right as everyone was thinking about the qi path battlefield and how intense the battle would be, Wu Shuai and Qi Sea Ancestor were relaxing and drinking wine in Dragon Palace.

Other than wine, there was also food.

Fang Yuan's clone and his main body were in harmony, the atmosphere was relaxed.

Wu Shuai clone gave the incomplete Human Sea to Fang Yuan's main body.

After receiving it, Fang Yuan's main body and Wu Shuai clone started to discuss their plans for the future.

Chapter 1989: Demon Judgment Board Lord

"To think that the qi tide would come at such a crucial moment." Prince Feng Xian wore a golden cape, he sighed in pity.

Beside him was a female immortal of Heavenly Court, she was Bai Cang Shui, she said with deep meaning: "Isn't that a good thing?"

Besides them, Gu Yue Fang Zheng was also here.

These three Gu Immortals were currently inside rank eight Immortal Gu House Demon Judgment Board, they were not in Central Continent, they had entered immemorial black heaven.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng's expression changed slightly, he knew the deeper meaning that Bai Cang Shui was pointing out.

He could not help but think back to the instructions and arrangements that Qin Ding Ling gave him before leaving Heavenly Court.

"You and Gu Yue Fang Yuan were born together and counter each other, you are the arrangement of the Heavenly Dao. Even if Fang Yuan changes his body, this relationship will not change. Precisely so, you will lead the expedition this time, bring Prince Feng Xian and Bai Cang Shui to launch a sneak attack on the headquarters of the variant human grotto-heavens in the two heavens!"

Qin Ding Ling cultivated luck path, she placed great importance on Gu Yue Fang Zheng, knowing that the lucks of Gu Yue Fang Zheng and Fang Yuan were tightly connected, she could sense that they countered each other.

And facts proved this.

Qin Ding Ling's awakening, the discovery of the dragonman blessed land, they were all variables that suppressed Fang Yuan.

Right now, Heavenly Court lost in the fate war, Duke Long died, Feng Jiu Ge betrayed them, the immortal graveyard was destroyed, while Star Constellation's will had no response. The great Heavenly Court was at its weakest moment for the last million years.

Qin Ding Ling temporarily led Heavenly Court, she naturally had to make use of all the available strength to defend themselves and resist enemies.

Thus, the stronger Fang Yuan was, the more focus Qin Ding Ling placed on Fang Zheng.

In order to nurture Fang Zheng, Qin Ding Ling spared no expense on immortal materials, she even let him lead this expedition to train his leadership skill.

Fang Zheng was not a youngster anymore, he knew that this was an unprecedented opportunity that was rarely seen in thousands of years. Even though Heavenly Court lost, their foundation was still unfathomable, with such a huge organization supporting him, he had to grasp it.

Fang Zheng still had rank seven cultivation level now, he had not reached the condition to join Heavenly Court, thus, his rank seven blessed land was not handed over to them. The truth was, Qin Ding Ling needed him to grow stronger, thus, even when he becomes a rank eight Gu Immortal in the future, as long as he still had room for improvement, Qin Ding Ling would not make him give up his immortal aperture. After all, the Gu Immortal's growth would almost completely halt after getting a phantom aperture.

"Senior Bai is right! Currently, with Qi Sea Ancestor and Wu Shuai stuck in battle, it is our best opportunity to launch an attack. Let's go now."

Gu Yue Fang Zheng spoke as he acted swiftly.

Rank eight Immortal Gu House Demon Judgment Board was immediately activated, it turned into a blood colored meteor that pierced through the grotto-heaven wall with a loud sound, entering Great Wisdom grotto-heaven directly!

The three immortals in Demon Judgment Board looked at Great Wisdom grotto-heaven, it had a beautiful scenery of lush mountains and flowing rivers. Inkmen lived here harmoniously, they had peaceful lives, there were many people here, it was a flourishing habitat.

A thick blood red light spread out rapidly from Demon Judgment Board, spreading throughout the world.

The essence of an Immortal Gu House was immortal killer moves, it was constructed using Immortal Gu and mortal Gu. According to the different Gu worms used, with different structures, Immortal Gu Houses had their own specialties.

Demon Judgment Board had great might, it showed a solid performance during the fate war. It was able to fight directly and managed to survive the war, this showed that Demon Judgment Board was one of the top rank eight Immortal Gu Houses in the world.

At this moment, Demon Judgment Board was unleashing an information path ability that had not been used in the fate war.

Wherever the blood red light went, all sorts of information gathered into Demon Judgment Board like a waterfall, before entering the minds of the three immortals.

Prince Feng Xian frowned, showing a look of hatred and disgust: "The inkmen here actually captured humans secretly and exploited them as slaves, they truly deserve death. These variant humans should all die! Let's kill these ones here and soul search them first."

But Bai Cang Shui shook her head: "These are just mortals, even if we soul search them, they would not know many secrets of the higher-ups. We should give them a taste of their own medicine, let's enslave them all and sell them as slaves in treasure yellow heaven, not only can we replenish Heavenly Court's reserves with this, it can also display the authority of our Heavenly Court."

Fang Zheng frowned on the inside.

He had once lived for many years in Lang Ya blessed land with the hairy men due to Fang Yuan, he experienced the culture of the variant humans.

Even though these inkmen treated humans as slaves, he was still unwilling to kill the innocent.

But Fang Zheng did not rebuke the two immortals, instead he said: "These mortal inkmen are not important, the key now is to rapidly kill the inkman Gu Immortals here. Let's take a look at this list of the Demon Judgment Board!"

A new list on the Demon Judgment Board appeared, the names of the inkman Gu Immortals inside Great Wisdom grotto-heaven were clearly written on it.

"Let's go!" Fang Zheng shouted resolutely, activating Demon Judgment Board, they followed the connection to rapidly find the closest inkman Gu Immortal.

This inkman Gu Immortal had already sensed something amiss, he secretly went to gather with the other inkman Gu Immortals.

Seeing the approaching Demon Judgment Board, he flew desperately, but how could his speed match a rank eight Immortal Gu House?

"Ahhh!"

With a pitiful cry, this inkman Gu Immortal was directly killed by the charging Immortal Gu House. Blood red light captured his soul, it was brought to the three immortals.

The three immortals quickled used soul search to gain lots of precious information.

Within this Great Wisdom grotto-heaven, there were many inkmen and cities. The biggest city was at the center of the grotto-heaven, it had the largest number of inkman Gu Immortals gathered there.

Of course, at this moment, there were still a few inkman Gu Immortals scattered outside.

"Demon Judgment Board Lord, what do we do now?" Bai Cang Shui asked Fang Zheng.

Fang Zheng did not hesitate: "We will immediately attack that immortal city!"

Demon Judgment Board tore through the sky with outstanding speed, reaching the immortal city in a moment's time.

During this period, the inkman Gu Immortals of the grotto-heaven had already gathered.

"Heavenly Court! We have no grudges with each other but you launched a sneak attack on us, can you still consider yourself righteous?" Within the immortal city, an inkman Gu Immortal shouted.

Prince Feng Xian laughed heartily: "Heavenly Court upholds the justice of humanity, your entire inkman group is full of evil demons, you deserve to be purged by everyone."

"What's the point of arguing with them?" Fang Zheng acted more directly than Prince Feng Xian, he sent Demon Judgment Board to crash down on them.

The inkman Gu Immortals gritted their teeth and shouted: "Then you will have a taste of our Great Wisdom grotto-heaven's main formation!"

At once, fog appeared and dyed the sky pitch-black.

Demon Judgment Board entered the fog and could not find its directions, it was completely trapped.

Not only that, the dense black fog was seeking to infiltrate the Immortal Gu House Demon Judgment Board.

Fang Zheng did not fluster, he first tried to use killer moves to probe it.

Lumps and lumps of blood flames spread out, wherever they went, black fog dispersed, but soon, the black fog seemed to have adapted, it devoured the blood flames aggressively.

Fang Zheng tried to attack several times but he failed each time.

Demon Judgment Board flew around the place but could not find any opening, it could not fly out of the black fog.

After thinking for a while, Fang Zheng used the strongest method in Demon Judgment Board, causing wanton destruction everywhere.

After a few minutes, a large amount of immortal essence was expended, Fang Zheng saw the black fog dispersing as they saw daylight again.

But the immortal city was already blown to bits, the surrounding thousand li were in ruins, countless lifeforms died from Demon Judgment Board's attacks.

The defending inkman Gu Immortals were mostly dead, only one was still alive, holding his final breath.

He looked at Demon Judgment Board with a gaze of deep hatred, he gritted his teeth: "How laughable, the great Heavenly Court is actually using blood path methods! You slaughtered these innocent people with no sense of guilt in your heart, you are truly the most vile demons of the demonic path!"

Prince Feng Xian snorted coldly, replying in disdain: "Blood path is only a method, when used on you, it shows humanity's righteousness."

"The owner of our Great Wisdom grotto-heaven will not let you off!" The inkman Gu Immortal said before dying.

"It's over?" The person who caused this situation and claimed victory, Fang Zheng, stared with wide eyes in disbelief.

Bai Cang Shui knew how he felt, she smiled: "Board Lord, you think this is the fate war, where intense fighting would happen that persists for months?"

Fang Zheng heard this and had a realization, he sighed: "So that's it."

The fate war was at the peak of the world in terms of battle strength. After Fang Zheng participated in it personally, his impression of fights between Gu Immortals was elevated to a great degree.

Right now, he was fighting against rank six and seven inkman Gu Immortals using the rank eight Immortal Gu House Demon Judgment Board, he realized it was so easy! It was too simple!

"Then, what do we do now, Board Lord?" Prince Feng Xian asked.

Fang Zheng pondered before answering: "Right now, the owners of these variant human grotto-heavens are with Wu Shuai in Eastern Sea. Since we already won this fight here, we still have time to attack the other grotto-heavens. This assault is a great chance, we need to make good use of it. Senior Bai Cang Shui, stay here, guard the place and collect our loot."

For the sake of the ordinary inkmen, Fang Zheng did not let the more racist and violent Prince Feng Xian stay here, he chose Bai Cang Shui.

Bai Cang Shui and Prince Feng Xian looked at each other, seeing satisfaction in each other's eyes.

Fang Zheng's performance as the leader of this trip was quite commendable. Be it his decisions or mindset, he was dependable and had the aura of a great general.

"Then I will stay here. Please be careful yourselves." Bai Cang Shui expressed.

Fang Zheng nodded with a solemn expression: "Senior, don't worry, I will not underestimate the enemies. I have not forgotten the most important point, that is the actions of Wu Shuai's force."

Bai Cang Shui felt relieved upon hearing these words, they took their leave.

Eastern Sea.

The qi tide had just subsided, the Dragon Palace with a damaged appearance crashed into Xia clan's headquarters.

"Oh, Lord Wu Shuai is back!"

"What was the result of the battle?"

"Lord Alliance Leader, you got injured?!"

The variant human Gu Immortals entered Dragon Palace, they saw Wu Shuai, who had a pale expression and was covered in bloodstains.

"Qi Sea Ancestor is formidable! I need to recuperate in closed cultivation." Wu Shuai coughed out mouthfuls of blood.

The variant human Gu Immortals were pale, overwhelmed by fear and panic.

Wu Shuai snorted coldly: "Don't worry, I used up a major portion of Human Sea and unleashed human path methods, that Qi Sea Ancestor is also severely injured."

The variant human Gu Immortals let out sighs of relief, it turned out the battle had ended in a draw.

Right at this time, Great Wisdom Immortal Mother's expression changed as she cried out in alarm: "Oh no! My Great Wisdom grotto-heaven was attacked, it is in imminent peril!"

Chapter 1990: Wu Shuai's Healing

Great Wisdom Immortal Mother's words shocked all of the present variant human Gu Immortals.

Soon, they reacted to the news.

"We need to save them, these are our headquarters."

"Great Wisdom, do you know who invaded your grotto-heaven?"

"Heavenly Court!" Great Wisdom Immortal Mother had a dark expression, gritting her teeth in hatred: "The invading Gu Immortals used Demon Judgment Board, it is a Heavenly Court rank eight Immortal Gu House, this cannot be faked."

"Hmph, so it is Heavenly Court!"

"Heavenly Court is simply too shameless, they actually attacked without a proper declaration of war."

"Heavenly Court is an organization made by demons to begin with. The past Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable was the biggest demon in the world, far beyond Fang Yuan in fact. These are the records that our races have clearly left behind."

While the immortals berated Heavenly Court, there was a sudden sound as Great Wisdom Immortal Mother directly knelt on the ground, kowtowing to Wu Shuai as she called: "Lord Alliance Leader, please help us uphold justice."

Great Wisdom Immortal Mother knew in her heart that she had no ability to save it. Just that rank eight Immortal Gu House Demon Judgment Board alone was an obstacle. That was not including the hidden Heavenly Court rank eight Gu Immortals in Demon Judgment Board.

Wu Shuai acknowledged her words: "Great Wisdom, no need to worry, stand up first!"

He seemed to have a livid expression but he did not find this strange at all. Heavenly Court's actions were within his expectations, during the five hundred years of his previous life, Heavenly Court had similarly done such an invasion.

Wu Shuai said resolutely and solemnly: "Great Wisdom is one of us, now that Great Wisdom grotto-heaven is attacked by Heavenly Court, we need to save it. Not only that, we need to take revenge for the damage that Heavenly Court has caused to Great Wisdom grotto-heaven, we will not let this go!"

"Thank you Lord Alliance Leader!" Great Wisdom Immortal Mother felt relieved, she stood up shakily, she already had the appearance of an old woman, at this moment, she looked even more pitiful as she asked: "When will we set off?"

Wu Shuai pondered: "This is a huge matter, we need to make plans first, we cannot panic and lose our rationality. We need to save Great Wisdom grotto-heaven, but we also need to defend our Eastern Sea Xia clan territory. Even though I fought evenly against Qi Sea Ancestor this time, Eastern Sea's righteous path will not let this go, they will retaliate. We worked hard to gain this territory, we must defend the fruits of our labor. Thankfully, we did not use any mermen earlier, in the following battle, the Merman Imperial Court can support us secretly as spies."

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch stood up from the crowd at this moment: "Reporting to Lord Alliance Leader, I am willing to defend Xia clan's headquarters. If the Eastern Sea righteous path attacks, I will do my best to defend this place, they will not pass until I die!"

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's words were very heroic and grand, but in his heart, he was trying to avoid conflicting with Heavenly Court. There were many variant human Gu Immortals with similar thoughts, they all sighed now, they had been too slow, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch made a move before them.

Among them, some of the variant human Gu Immortals who were close to Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch felt happy internally, if Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch defended the base, they would definitely be chosen to stay with him, after all, he could not defend the location alone.

"Very good." Wu Shuai nodded, he looked at Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch with admiration: "Ice Crystal, you are very strong and have a vigilant nature, you are a powerful general in our alliance, I will be assured if you are defending it. After I recover from my injuries, you will defend Xia clan's territory for me."

Great Wisdom Immortal Mother heard this and became anxious, you all are talking so much but why is nobody talking about the departure timing?

She started to urge again: "Lord Alliance Leader, fellow allies, there is no time, Great Wisdom grotto-heaven's crisis is at hand, we need to save it immediately!"

Wu Shuai sighed: "After this battle against Qi Sea Ancestor, not only are my injuries severe, the healing is very troublesome. I need a lot of immortal materials to heal my physical body. The reason is because my dragonman body is different from Duke Long, I modified it and innovated upon the original version. When refining this body, I used a lot of rare immortal materials and paid a huge price. My healing will also require the same cost, regrettably, I lack a lot of immortal materials now, I need to make purchases in treasure yellow heaven."

Great Wisdom Immortal Mother had also heard rumors regarding the humans alike dragons method, she did not suspect his words as she asked: "May I ask Lord Alliance Leader how many immortal materials you require to heal your injuries? We can provide it."

Wu Shuai listed out the materials for her.

After hearing his words, all the variant human Gu Immortals took in sharp breaths.

The price was too huge!

Great Wisdom Immortal Mother was tongue tied as she gasped: "To think that Lord Alliance Leader's body is so valuable and expensive!"

Wu Shuai smiled but did not speak, he only glanced towards Gu tribe's leader.

Gu tribe's leader immediately said: "I can testify for this, many of my people have turned into dragonmen, we expended far more immortal materials than this!"

This was a lie, but Gu tribe's leader and Wu Shuai were very close, because he was an Eastern Sea rank eight, his words carried huge trustworthiness.

Great Wisdom Immortal Mother had naturally suspected that Wu Shuai was extorting them, but she did not dare to question him, the situation was not within her control.

After hesitating for a while, Great Wisdom Immortal Mother gritted her teeth as she said with difficulty: "Lord Alliance Leader, I am willing to fund and contribute the immortal materials to help you recover quickly."

The variant human Gu Immortals quickly took action, gathering the immortal materials.

Wu Shuai accepted the immortal materials but shook his head: "Even with all the immortal materials I need at least three days and two nights to heal."

Great Wisdom Immortal Mother heard his words and almost fainted on the spot.

She was extremely anxious, she was about to speak but Wu Shuai waved his hand, she could not say anything.

Because at the next moment, Wu Shuai added: "As the alliance leader, no matter which of your headquarters get attacked, I will definitely save them. Heavenly Court is our common enemy! But the situation is indeed tough now, how about this... Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch, as the vice alliance leader, lead a group of people to save them in black heaven first. Try your best to preserve the foundation of Great Wisdom grotto-heaven."

"What?" Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch stared with wide eyes, showing a difficult expression. to think that this matter still ended up being delegated to him, he quickly thought about it but found that he could not refuse, he gritted his teeth: "I... will go. But I am too weak and powerless, I do not want to ruin the expedition, I would like to borrow Lord Alliance Leader's Dragon Palace. With it, I can definitely complete my mission!"

But Wu Shuai shook his head: "I cannot lend Dragon Palace, I need it to heal my injuries."

"Is that so..." Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch wanted to speak.

But Wu Shuai's expression changed as he said grimly: "Everyone, the situation is urgent now, we cannot talk about it further. Great Wisdom grotto-heaven is only the first target, will your grotto-heavens remain untouched? You need to save yourselves! Were I not the alliance leader, when faced with this situation, would you surrender to them? Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch, I order you to go save them immediately, you can choose five people here to go with you."

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch felt a strong pressure pressing down on him. He could only lower his head and accept the order.

He chose five Gu Immortals from among the people here, they were all rank eight Gu Immortals.

These were all leaders of forces close to him, there was no choice, resisting Heavenly Court to save Great Wisdom grotto-heaven was too dangerous, he did not want to get into trouble from internal strife.

However, right when they were about to move out, Great Wisdom Immortal Mother suddenly froze as she said dejectedly: "It's too late, my Great Wisdom grotto-heaven has been completely taken down by Heavenly Court!"

The Gu Immortals gasped in unison.

Great Wisdom Immortal Mother fell to the ground as she knelt before Wu Shuai, sobbing: "Please take revenge for me, Lord Alliance Leader. My tribe has been doing its best to collect the fragments of the Qian Kun Crystal Wall, we have more than fifty percent now! If we can find another ten percent, we will be able to excavate the racial inheritance of our inkman race!"

Great Wisdom Immortal Mother directly exposed the racial inheritance of her tribe, the intention was obvious, she was trying to use benefits to lure Wu Shuai!

After hearing about the racial inheritance, the other Gu Immortals' eyes started to shine.

At this moment, another Gu Immortal shouted in panic: "Oh no, my grotto-heaven is being attacked by Heavenly Court. Quick, quick! Go and save it!"

Wu Shuai looked at Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch imposingly: "This is an urgent matter, aren't you setting off?"

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch gritted his teeth, he brought a number of Gu Immortals to return to immemorial black heaven.

Great Wisdom Immortal Mother and another pitiful Gu Immortal went back to reinforce the invaded grotto-heaven, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and the rest also went there, within Dragon Palace, less than half the Gu Immortals were left.

The remaining Gu Immortals had ugly expressions, most of them were shell shocked, after all, they could be the next target at any time.

Wu Shuai ignored them, he ordered them to defend Xia clan's base as he shut the door of Dragon Palace, attending to his 'injuries'.

"These variant human Gu Immortals are truly not our match, hehe." Night Heavenly Wolf Lord was among the Gu Immortals, he was the only person here who had peace of mind.

"All these grotto-heaven Gu Immortals don't have any interaction during normal times, they even guard against each other and think that they should keep more secrets to themselves! With such precaution against each other, how can they make any change? Even if they work together, they are still a disunited bunch! My decision to join Heavenly Court was right after all."

After this matter, Night Heavenly Wolf Lord was even more sure of his intention to work for Heavenly Court.

After parting with the immortals, he secretly informed Heavenly Court of this expedition.

Wu Shuai had created the two heavens alliance agreement, there were restrictions upon it naturally. But the information path dao marks on Night Heavenly Wolf Lord had already been removed by Zhou Xiong Xin and the others, thus, even though he was a traitor, no backlash had occurred.

In Heavenly Court's Central Great Hall, Qin Ding Ling soon received news of this.

She thought about it but did not inform Eastern Sea's righteous path, instead she told Fang Zheng.

Fang Zheng was already about to take down the second grotto-heaven, the remaining Gu Immortals in the grotto-heaven were still well hidden, Fang Zheng was anxious to find them.

After thinking about it, he decided to ask Prince Feng Xian to stay here and clean up the situation. He would bring Demon Judgment Board to the third grotto-heaven and assault it!

At the same time.

Eastern Sea, qi sea.

Qi Sea Ancestor had a pale expression, he sat at the main seat as he looked at Xia Rui Zhi and the rest.

The representatives of Eastern Sea's righteous path forces were all here.

Qi Sea Ancestor looked at Xia Rui Zhi as he asked: "In this battle, I had the upper hand at first, but that Wu Shuai actually managed to use a human path method. This method was very powerful, it could create countless flying human figures. According to Wu Shuai, this is the foundation of your Xia clan, is it an artificial secluded domain of heaven and earth?"

Chapter 1991: Ancestor is Righteous and Mighty

After Xia clan first supreme elder Xia Rui Zhi heard Qi Sea Ancestor's question, he became shocked.

After a while, he answered vigilantly: "Reporting to ancestor, my Xia clan was indeed creating an artificial human path secluded domain, it is called Human Sea. But this secluded domain does not have any offensive power. The reason why we created it was to deal with the future chaos and have a method to revive our Xia clan Gu Immortals."

Xia Rui Zhi spoke vaguely but he did not lie. The reason why Xia clan was creating Human Sea was to revive their Gu Immortals.

In the five hundred years of his previous life, Fang Yuan remembered that when Xia clan's Gu Immortals died outside, they were not truly dead, they could revive from Human Sea. Although their Immortal Gu and immortal aperture's accumulations would be lost, they would still retain their cultivation level and immortal aperture itself.

Eastern Sea's Xia clan gained a huge reputation because of this, for the following period of time, they invaded Southern Border. Southern Border's Gu Immortals fought against Xia clan, over time, they learned about Xia clan's background and foundation, eventually, Chai clan mimicked Human Sea and created their own Human Mountain secluded domain.

Qi Sea Ancestor stroked his beard: "It seems that the reason why Wu Shuai led the two heavens' Gu Immortals to invade your Xia clan was because of this Human Sea secluded domain."

All of the present Xia clan Gu Immortals looked at each other.

Xia Rui Zhi frowned as he muttered: "Was my Xia clan invaded because information got leaked and the allure of the Human Sea secluded domain caused enemies to attack? But this Human Sea secluded domain has not been completed yet."

Qi Sea Ancestor had a grim expression: "If Wu Shuai did not have a complete Human Sea secluded domain, does that mean that after he completes it, he will have an actual Human Sea and his human path killer move will be even stronger?"

Xia Rui Zhi smiled: "Ancestor, don't worry, the creation of Human Sea originated from an ancestor of my clan, it was refined by generations of descendants. Wu Shuai does not know of its profundity, if he tries to complete it, Human Sea will only dwindle and shrink."

Qi Sea Ancestor shook his head: "Wu Shuai is an old monster of the past, he made use of Fang Yuan's power to revive successfully, this person is too scheming and crafty, he takes action with certainty. Each time he strikes, he is resolute and will always make great gains. Since he knew about your Xia clan's Human Sea secluded domain, he might also know a way to complete it."

Xia Rui Zhi's smile became more forced: "This possibility... is not likely. Only the top three supreme elders of my clan know about the creation method of Human Sea. Right now, they are all here, don't tell me we have a traitor among us?"

Qi Sea Ancestor sighed: "It might not be a traitor. Don't forget that Wu Shuai controls Dragon Palace which has dream path killer moves, he might have targeted you in your dreams."

"This..." Xia Rui Zhi's smiling expression froze entirely.

If it were any other path, Xia Rui Zhi would still feel some confidence. But against dream path methods, he could not be certain.

"Lord Xia Rui Zhi, friends from Xia clan." At this time, a Tang clan Gu Immortal spoke: "Should you still be hiding it? You should tell us the creation method of Human Sea, let us refer to it and find out a weakness of Wu Shuai's human path method."

Xia clan's Gu Immortals were stunned.

The creation method of Human Sea was the deepest foundation of Eastern Sea's Xia clan, how could they expose it like this?

Tang clan's Gu Immortal was merely after Human Sea himself.

Tang clan's member chuckled: "Pardon my words, but friends from Xia clan, what are you still waiting for? Your territory has been lost, you want to create a brand new Human Sea secluded domain from scratch? Do you know what the most important thing is now? When ancestor and Wu Shuai fought, it ended in a draw because of that human path killer move. As long as we can deduce this human path killer move, would we have to fear Wu Shuai and his army? By then, wouldn't you get back your homeland?"

Xia clan's Gu Immortals gritted their teeth in anger.

Tang clan was an Eastern Sea super force, they bordered Xia clan and had much conflict in usual times. Thus, they decided to make things difficult for Xia clan at this moment.

However, even though they were causing problems intentionally, their words made sense.

This was something even Xia clan's Gu Immortals had to admit.

Xia Rui Zhi thought about it before making up his mind: "The method to create Human Sea is our Xia clan's secret, we will not announce it publicly. I am only willing to contribute this human path essence to ancestor alone!"

Qi Sea Ancestor got injured from fighting Wu Shuai, Xia clan's hopes were all on Qi Sea Ancestor now. Because the two heavens were led by Wu Shuai, Eastern Sea only had Qi Sea Ancestor able to resist the Evil Dragon and Dragon Palace collectively.

Xia Rui Zhi was trying to gain Qi Sea Ancestor's favor now, he was making plans for his own clan.

But Qi Sea Ancestor shook his head: "I am only asking this to confirm the situation. Your Xia clan can keep this Human Sea creation method. I have no foundation in human path, even if I get it, I cannot deduce Wu Shuai's methods."

Xia Rui Zhi became anxious and wanted to speak but Qi Sea Ancestor waved his hand to interrupt: "Xia clan does not have to worry. Wu Shuai is a dragonman, the two heavens alliance is also made up of mostly variant humans, they are public enemies of the five regions! If they invaded the other four regions, so be it, but they chose Eastern Sea after all, so as a human, I will resist these variant humans with all my effort."

"Ancestor is righteous and mighty!" The Gu Immortals present called out in unison.

Qi Sea Ancestor added: "But now, I have injuries from the battle, I need to recuperate in closed cultivation. As for Wu Shuai, his injuries are more severe, he will not take action during this period of time, there is no need to worry."

Qi Sea Ancestor paused before continuing: "When I recover, I will need you all to cooperate and gather an army to fight against the two heavens alliance."

"We will listen to ancestor."

"With ancestor leading us, Eastern Sea has nothing to worry!"

"Without ancestor, Eastern Sea would have suffered great losses already. It is truly Eastern Sea's blessing to have ancestor defending it, this is the blessing of the people."

The Eastern Sea Gu Immortals continued to flatter him without stopping.

But Xia Rui Zhi had a worried expression, he and Xia clan's members were currently homeless. During this period, they could not reclaim Xia clan's territory, where were they going to go now?

Qi Sea Ancestor smiled lightly: "Before we attack, friends from Xia clan, you may stay in qi sea as guests."

Xia clan's Gu Immortals instantly became overjoyed.

Xia Rui Zhi cupped his fists and thanked: "Xia clan will remember ancestor's warm hospitality, we will definitely repay you in the future."

The other clans' Gu Immortals looked at Xia clan's Gu Immortals with different expressions now. Other than disdain and sympathy, they also felt envious and jealous.

Was this Xia clan's fortune after a disaster? They were able to stay closely with Qi Sea Ancestor, as time passes, their relationship would deepen, they would be able to gain the backing of a great expert!

If they knew the truth, who knew what expression they would show.

After finishing their discussion, Qi Sea Ancestor went to recuperate in closed cultivation, the other Eastern Sea Gu Immortals also went back to their bases to make preparations for the upcoming battle.

Mermaid Lian Ke Xin was feeling nervous at the moment. The Merman Imperial Court had already joined the two heavens alliance, but Wu Shuai did not expose their identity, they were currently spies sent to gather information.

Feeling the cold breeze in the sky, Lian Ke Xin calmed down slowly as sorrow emerged in her heart: "Now it seems that Eastern Sea will be peaceful for this period of time without any fighting. But this is the calm before the storm, sigh, during the battle in the future, I wonder what action my Merman Imperial Court should take?"

Lian Ke Xin was one of the three immortals in charge of the Merman Imperial Court, she had high status and authority, but now she felt helpless and fearful.

The five regional walls vanished, everyone knew that the five regions were going to become chaotic and turbulent.

But the chaos had just started, Lian Ke Xin already felt like she was in treacherous waters, her future was bleak and dark, she could not see the light or hope of survival. If she was careless, then the entire Merman Imperial Court would even get completely devoured!

After hearing the report, Shen Cong Sheng learned of Qi Sea Ancestor's decision.

"It seems that Eastern Sea is currently led by Qi Sea Ancestor after all." Shen Cong Sheng sighed: "If Ancestor Shen Shang returned, it would be different. Letting a secluded cultivator lead the entire righteous path..."

Shen Cong Sheng shook his head.

He had ambition, he wanted Shen clan to be the overlord of Eastern Sea, as the number one force.

Different from the other righteous path clans, Shen clan had Shen Shang, he was someone who could compete with Qi Sea Ancestor.

But Shen Shang's whereabouts were unknown.

Shen clan had searched for him with full effort but they made no discoveries.

Shen Cong Sheng felt a huge headache regarding this: "Oh ancestor, where in the world are you?"

At the same time.

Divine Emperor City, painting path world.

Hong Yi and Ye Fan walked side by side on the bustling street.

At the corner of an alley, a group of muscular men surrounded a person as they kicked and punched.

"Stop!" Hong Yi could not watch anymore, he quickly stopped them.

After seeing the situation, Ye Fan was also furious: "Are you guys really hitting him? So many of you are bullying one beggar?"

The group of muscular men turned around: "Stupid kids, don't meddle in others' affairs! This lunatic is courting death, he scared my young master's precious horse to death, my clan's young master also fell to the ground. We will not rest until we beat him to death."

Hong Yi sighed: "You went overboard."

Boom boom boom.

Hong Yi and Ye Fan made their move, the group of muscular men were sent scrambling and escaping.

The beggar was curled up on the ground, he was covered in bruises, his body shivered as he muttered nonsensical phrases.

"He really is insane." Hong Yi sighed.

"Sigh, even if he is crazy, he is still human. He did not mean to scare the horse, right?" Ye Fan also felt some pity: "Come, let's help him, we can't leave him here like this."

The two brought the beggar into a secluded alley as they got him a few buns, placing it beside him.

After that, they left.

What they did not know was, after they left, the beggar regained his sanity.

"Where am I?"

"Damn it, the black fire wreaked havoc, I went mad again!"

This beggar was the person that Shen clan had been desperately trying to find, Shen Shang.

Chapter 1992: Foundational Pillar of Human Path

People on the streets moved continuously, shops on both sides had bright signs and attractive banners.

"Wow! This is the world inside the painting. It is incredible! Everything seems so real!" Sun Yao's body shook as her vision widened, after entering the painting, she could not help but shout in amazement.

The surrounding people looked towards this young lady with perplexed gazes.

But Sun Yao did not notice it, her eyes were wide open and shining as she looked around, filled with curiosity and excitement.

Sun Yao was a Spirit Affinity House Gu Master, she was chosen as a Gu Immortal seed by the sect and was given much assistance.

Spirit Affinity House's original nominee was Feng Jin Huang, but because of Feng Jiu Ge's betrayal, Qin Ding Ling hesitated.

Spirit Affinity House thus changed their nominee, Sun Yao took over Feng Jin Huang's position.

However, the sect's nurturing was different from what she expected. Spirit Affinity House only told Sun Yao about the background of this painting before sending her in.

Sun Yao moved around the different shops on the streets, having a lot of fun.

She had grown up in Spirit Affinity House, she only had senior brothers or sisters around her, they were all cultivators and according to the rules of the sect, they did not interact with the outside world very much.

Everything that happened here was very exciting and interesting to her.

She spent primeval stones to buy many sticks of candy, she ate them as she looked around.

She saw paper-cutting artists in the alleys, where pieces of red paper were quickly transformed with scissors into life-like butterflies and flowers.

She went into the theater to enjoy the opera, she saw the people with their painted faces, their exaggerated dresses, and their long, high-pitched singing.

She stopped at a corner of the street and saw two strong men putting up a performance of smashing rocks on their chest.

Suddenly, she was tapped on the shoulder.

Sun Yao turned around and saw a young man, with a squarish face and an honest appearance.

Before Sun Yao could open her mouth, this young man with an honest and righteous air smiled sheepishly and said: "Are you from the ten great ancient sects?"

Sun Yao suddenly stared with wide eyes and exclaimed in surprise: "Senior brother, you too?"

The young man then nodded his head and introduced himself with cupped fists: "I am Chen Da Jiang of Wind Cloud Manor."

"So it's Senior Brother Chen!" Sun Yao was shocked, she returned the greeting in succession. Chen Da Jiang was the current generation number one disciple of Wind Cloud Manor, Sun Yao had already learned of his name before this.

Sun Yao had the feeling of seeing a celebrity. When Chen Da Jiang had first gained fame, she was nothing more than a follower of Feng Jin Huang.

Like Sun Yao, Chen Da Jiang was a recommended candidate from Wind Cloud Manor and was sent to the world of the painting.

The two of them met in a strange place, and even though it was only the first time they met, there was a natural closeness between them.

"Senior Brother Chen, I wonder what other arrangements the sect has made by sending us here for training." Sun Yao inquired.

Chen Da Jiang shook his head: "I don't know anything about that either. I originally thought that by entering here, I would be able to get guidance on the next step of my cultivation. I didn't expect that the sect would not have any arrangements."

The two of them had a fruitless conversation and decided to travel in companionship.

"Give me some food, please, our mother hasn't eaten for three days."

"Please give some money, please help us."

"My father is gone, I am selling myself to raise money for his funeral, I beg for your help!"

The two wandered aimlessly into a street, but all they saw were starving people, there were many yellow-skinned people leaning on the corner wall. Many people were begging, cupping their hands or holding up broken bowls.

Pedestrians on the street, on the other hand, were in a hurry and avoided them, rarely stopping to give alms to anyone.

"How is this happening? They are just two streets apart." Sun Yao was greatly surprised when she saw this scene.

Chen Da Jiang analyzed: "This is the painting world of Divine Emperor City. Every major scene that happened in the history of Emperor City is merged into one painting. It looks like this is what happened in Emperor City during one of the famine disasters of history."

Sun Yao couldn't help but overflow with sympathy: "Senior Brother Chen, even though they are only people in the painting and not real existences, they are so pitiful, I still want to help them."

Chen Da Jiang was impressed by Sun Yao's words, he smiled readily: "This might sound funny, but I also have the same idea. Why don't the two of us act together?"

"Awesome!" Sun Yao jumped at the chance and agreed to do so.

The two of them contributed money and effort, not only giving out primeval stones, but also purchasing porridge, buns, and other food to deliver to these beggars.

"Kind people!"

"Thank you, benefactors, we will never forget your act of kindness."

"Benefactors, please allow me to follow you two in return for your kindness!"

The people in distress were grateful and appreciative.

Just then, a shrill voice cut in: "What are you guys doing?"

When Sun Yao and Chen Da Jiang turned their heads, they saw a Gu Master wearing a white robe with a jade belt at his waist, his posture was as straight as a sword, an air of arrogance could be felt between his brows as he walked towards them.

"So it's Brother Xiao Qi Xing of Spirit Butterfly Valley!" Chen Da Jiang greeted with cupped fists.

Sun Yao gasped, Xiao Qi Xing was also a well-known figure, she said in a panic: "Spirit Affinity House's Sun Yao greets Brother Xiao."

Xiao Qi Xing sized up Sun Yao: "Are you the candidate of Spirit Affinity House this time? It seems that Feng Jin Huang has indeed been suppressed, this is not surprising at all, her father has openly betrayed Heavenly Court, this outcome is only natural."

As soon as this was said, Sun Yao frowned: "Senior Sister Feng wouldn't care about these things."

"Hehe, she is indeed arrogant. Pity, what a pity, a fallen phoenix is worse than a chicken." Xiao Qi Xing revealed a mocking smile: "You guys are actually helping these beggars again? They're not real people, why are you doing this for?"

"No reason, we just feel like helping them." Chen Da Jiang smiled.

"Hehe, sympathy..." Xiao Qi Xing shook his head in disdain: "That means you don't know the importance of this journey, you're wasting your time here!"

"Oh?" Chen Da Jiang's eyes lit up: "What does Brother Xiao know?"

Xiao Qi Xing looked at Chen Da Jiang: "There is no harm in telling you, this painting world is so vivid because it is the effect of Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's contented lifestyle killer move. We were all nominated by our sects to be trained by Heavenly Court and sent here for further nurturing. As I'm sure you've noticed, there are also Gu Masters cultivating here, but they cultivate mainly human path."

"What the sect wants is for us to cultivate human path. We will strive to ascend to become immortal using human path as our main path. Although this world is not real, the cultivation of human path is not fake. All the human path Gu worms we get from here can also be taken outside and used."

"So that's how it is!" Sun Yao's eyes widened but soon she expressed some doubt: "But why didn't the sect tell me?"

Chen Da Jiang, on the other hand, simply asked: "Where did Brother Xiao learn about this inside information?"

Xiao Qi Xing smiled slightly, he puffed out his chest and said proudly: "Even Spirit Butterfly Valley has not informed me of this inside information, I had gone to ask my great grandfather to find out."

Chen Da Jiang nodded understandingly, seeing that Sun Yao was still puzzled, he explained: "Brother Xiao has a noble status and a wealth of knowledge, his great grandfather is Lord Gu Immortal Xiao Bai Hong."

"Oh, so that's how it is." Sun Yao's gaze towards Xiao Qi Xing changed again.

"Alright, I have to head to the military base now and join the city guards. I've already investigated it, only city guards can get soldier Gu, sergeant Gu, lieutenant Gu, captain Gu, and others. These human path Gu worms are very useful, they can build a strong foundation in our human path cultivation. We should go together, we can take care of each other." Xiao Qi Xing suggested again.

But Chen Da Jiang shook his head, "Brother Xiao, go first, I'm not done helping the beggars here."

Xiao Qi Xing looked at Chen Da Jiang and nodded: "You're still the same as before, so what about you?"

He looked at Sun Yao.

Sun Yao hesitated and shook her head as well: "No, Senior Brother Xiao, I... I plan to help Senior Brother Chen."

"Haha." Xiao Qi Xing laughed as he showed a smile with deep meaning: "Then I will not disturb the two of you in your good work."

He left straight away, laughing coldly in his heart: "These two idiots have no idea what kind of opportunities they are missing out on!"

Xiao Qi Xing could not help but recall the words that his great grandfather had instructed him: "Oh Qi Xing, this trip into the painting world is an unimaginably great opportunity. If possible, you can even inherit Genesis Lotus' true inheritance and become the Lord of Divine Emperor City. You must do your best to grasp this opportunity! Remember, you must hurry up. You are only the first batch of candidates, Heavenly Court will also arrange for some rank six Gu Immortals to enter next. These people are also elites that Heavenly Court is focusing on nurturing, but the qi tides have not settled yet and they are all still resting and recuperating."

"After you enter the painting world, you will have to race against time and try to establish an early advantage so that you can deal with those Gu Immortal opponents in the future. Don't be afraid, these Gu Immortals can only follow the rules in the painting world. Inside it, immortals and mortals are basically equals."

Xiao Qi Xing's heart beat rapidly every time he recalled these words.

This was an unparalleled opportunity, of course he wanted to grasp it!

Sun Yao and Chen Da Jiang did not know the inside story, so Xiao Qi Xing wanted to coax them to help himself out. It was a pity that these two actually wanted to do good deeds, they were really not qualified to work with him. Xiao Qi Xing saw through this and was unwilling to waste precious time and energy on them.

"We brought steamed buns and porridge, eat slowly and don't choke." Sun Yao placed a bowl of porridge and steamed buns in front of Shen Shang.

Shen Shang was still covered in injuries and resembled a beggar, sitting in the shade at the corner like a stone statue.

Sun Yao also did not pay attention to it, after all, there were many such silent beggars. She did this to help others, not for the sake of listening to some words of gratitude and praise.

Shen Shang's eyes contained bright light as he looked at Sun Yao who was close to him, and also at the back of Xiao Qi Xing, who was about to disappear in the distance of the street.

"These people are all Heavenly Court's Gu Immortal seeds. In order to face the tides of the great era, Heavenly Court has made long-term plans."

"Xiao Bai Hong is too shortsighted and doesn't even know that he has harmed his own great-grandson. Sun Yao and Chen Da Jiang were previously kept in the dark, but now, although they learned some of the inside story, they still upheld their nature and acted according to their desires. These two will definitely benefit greatly if they continue."

Shen Shang thought to himself. Although these three people were transmitting their conversations, they could not hide it from a character like Shen Shang.

Shen Shang sighed in his heart.

"Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's arrangement is truly vast and grand, I really admire him."

"In history, the greatest human path true inheritance is \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>. Even though this book seems shallow, it is profound to the limit, only a small group of people can actually comprehend its true essence and create human path killer moves."

"However, to establish a path, these killer moves are too few and rare, they are like the moon beyond the clouds, normal people cannot reach them. Even though human path has such great potential, it has no foundations set upon it, it is unable to develop until now."

"But Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable created this painting world, he used the scenes of the mortal world for the past million years to derive the foundations of human path. He is making an immense contribution towards the development of human path! He is truly the foundational pillar of human path."

"The human path developments here are also very helpful to me. I wonder what happened when I was in a state of madness, how did I end up in here?"

"It is a pity I cannot contact Fang Yuan's Fang Di Chang clone. What is happening over on his end?"

Shen Shang was the one who had previously collaborated with Fang Di Chang and successfully unraveled the venerables' human path methods, adding a significant weight to tilt the balance of the battle in the fate war.

Shen Shang knew that Fang Di Chang had refined Divine Bean Palace before, he had a large level of authority over it. If they could collaborate once again, it would benefit both of them!

Chapter 1993: Fang Yuan Within The Mist

Sovereign immortal aperture, Mini Southern Border.

In a valley, Shi Shi Cheng leaned over to check out the stone mushrooms within the valley.

If these stone mushrooms were in good condition, they would be five feet tall, shaped like a small tree with a cover like an umbrella. However, these stone mushrooms were short, just like stumps left behind after a tree was cut down. And instead of a healthy gray stone color, their bodies were covered in a distorted multicolored color, and one could tell at a glance that they were not normal.

"These stone mushrooms are ruined!" After Shi Shi Cheng finished his inspection and confirmed this, his expression was quite ugly.

Although his cultivation was only rank six, he was valued by Fang Yuan and arranged to lead the rockman tribe in Mini Southern Border. Shi Shi Cheng held Fang Yuan in high esteem and was dedicated to developing the rockman tribe, in order to live up to Fang Yuan's expectations.

This stone mushroom field was a medium-sized resource point that he had personally constructed for the sake of the rockman tribe. In order to build this resource point, Shi Shi Cheng had specifically requested many immortal materials from Fang Yuan's time path clone as the initial investment. At that time, he even vowed and guaranteed that there would be desirable returns!

As a result, reality was like a slap in the face of Shi Shi Cheng.

"What is happening?"

"I clearly followed the records of the tribe to carefully cultivate the stone mushrooms without any mistakes."

Shi Shi Cheng was very confused. A few days ago, these stone mushrooms were all growing normally and everything was fine. But after a few days had passed, these stone mushrooms had become like this.

"How can I explain this to Lord Fang Yuan?!" Shi Shi Cheng furrowed his brows and sighed.

At this moment, light flashed and Fang Yuan's will was transmitted over in mid-air.

The will was solid and lifelike.

Shi Shi Cheng gasped and immediately bowed: "Subordinate pays respect to lord."

"Mm." Fang Yuan's will waved his hand: "I already know about your situation here, the stone mushroom field was destroyed, no one can blame you, it was a natural disaster. You should go back for now, another batch of immortal materials will arrive in a while, and you can just build a second stone mushroom valley."

Shi Shi Cheng was overjoyed and thanked him, but also wanted to say something.

Fang Yuan's will revealed an understanding smile: "Are you thinking of asking what caused these stone mushrooms to be destroyed?"

Shi Shi Cheng nodded: "Lord is perceptive, I would like to ask if these stone mushrooms can still be recycled in some way? It would be a pity to just throw them away."

The initial investment in building the stone mushroom valley was huge, it was certainly nothing in Fang Yuan's eyes, but in Shi Shi Cheng's opinion, it was an astronomical investment. Together with the effort and time he had invested in this place, he did not want to see all his efforts go up in smoke.

But Fang Yuan shook his head: "You don't need to think about the details, if I can solve it, you will have no worries. If I can't solve it, it's useless for you to know. As for these stone mushrooms, none of them can be used, even if they are used as materials to refine Gu, they will only cause more harm instead. You can leave now."

"Yes, my lord!" Shi Shi Cheng took his leave respectfully, he was worried in his heart: "Why do we have such a big problem? According to his tone, it may not be possible to resolve the matter?"

Shi Shi Cheng left, only Fang Yuan's will remained in this valley.

Fang Yuan's expression was grim.

He scanned the entire valley first, the countless stone mushrooms in the valley had become twisted objects, the originally smooth surface forming countless creases. The colors were bright, like a gathering of poisonous creatures, giving people a sense of terror.

This was of course just the appearance.

In Fang Yuan's eyes, he could see that the original earth path dao marks in these stone mushrooms had been disrupted and washed away, many different dao marks from other paths, including wind path, lightning path, poison path, dark path, fire path, and so on, were added instead.

Because of this, these stone mushrooms could only be discarded as waste material. At least currently, Fang Yuan had no means to utilize them.

"Heaven's will!" Fang Yuan's will suddenly sneered and discovered heaven's will lurking in the valley.

With a loud sound, he transformed into a field of clouds and mist that covered the entire valley, pursuing and intercepting heaven's will.

A confrontation between wills soon came to an end. Fang Yuan was victorious, he had managed to completely clear the heaven's will lurking in this place, but of course, the price paid was not small.

After his will had gathered again, it was no longer as lifelike as before, but illusory as a shadow, giving the impression like it was going to fade away at any moment.

Fang Yuan sighed.

This victory only resolved the problem but not its fundamental cause, a new problem would occur again!

The stone mushroom valley was not just an isolated case, recently, there had been heaven's will lurking all over the sovereign immortal aperture, many resource points had been destroyed.

Fang Yuan's main body had obtained more than three thousand heaven path dao marks as he was the person refining Gu, managing to destroy fate Gu for good.

These dao marks did not belong to him and were imposed on him. The heaven path dao marks transformed on their own, causing the various environments of the sovereign immortal aperture to change, becoming more and more balanced and stable.

In the long run, this change would naturally do more good than harm, greatly increasing the development potential of the sovereign immortal aperture. However, if one looked at the immediate future, it would cause Fang Yuan to suffer heavy losses.

Fang Yuan was not a super force, all his possessions were in the sovereign immortal aperture. A great loss in this foundation of his would definitely affect his battle performance. Fang Yuan did not want to fall into the trap of Red Lotus Demon Venerable, he had been working hard to command the humans and variant humans in the grotto-heaven, constantly fighting against natural disasters. At the same time, he had successively retrieved the thousand wish tree and the incomplete Human Sea, using human path to restrict the heaven path effects.

With such a two-pronged approach, the situation of sovereign immortal aperture was greatly improved. However, Fang Yuan did not expect that the natural development of the heaven path dao marks would produce heaven's will after some point.

The Heavenly Dao was impartial, it had no malicious intent against Fang Yuan, changing the environment was just a natural step of development. But this was not the case for heaven's will.

Heaven's will was produced from the Heavenly Dao, it was more flexible and resourceful. The Heavenly Dao was unable to eliminate Fang Yuan, the otherworldly demon that affected the balance of the world, so heaven's will went one step further and began deliberately destroying the various resource points in the sovereign immortal aperture.

Heaven path dao marks could transform into other paths, so heaven's will used this ability to completely disrupt the dao marks of the various resource points, turning them from orderly to a complete mess.

Stone mushroom valley was just one of them.

"I have the killer move heaven's will dissipation, but the sovereign immortal aperture is too huge, the Heavenly Dao is constantly deriving new changes, it can produce heaven's will anywhere in the entire grotto-heaven. It is too difficult for me to clear out all this heaven's will! Even if I do my best, the efficiency is low."

Fang Yuan was clear that the way to settle the fundamental cause was to directly refine these heaven path dao marks, so that they truly belonged to the sovereign immortal aperture and himself.

But what the method to go about it was, he had no idea.

He had never heard of anyone cultivating heaven path before! The only known way was to use human path methods to suppress heaven path.

Fang Yuan thought for a long time and found two possible ways out.

The first one was Emperor City.

"Emperor City was carefully arranged by Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable, it has now become the sacred land of human path. If I can obtain it, I will definitely be able to greatly restrain the Heavenly Dao."

The second way was in Crazed Demon Cave.

"Crazed Demon Cave was set up by Limitless Demon Venerable in his later years, the eighth layer contains the derivations of the Heavenly Dao. In Crazed Demon Cave, the demonic sounds are rampant, driving lifeforms mad, all kinds of immortal materials turn into trash as dao marks are messed up. The situation is exactly the same as the stone mushrooms and other resources. If I can grasp all the secrets of Crazed Demon Cave, I should be able to improve my situation."

But these were two dangerous options.

Emperor City was located in the center of Central Continent, if Fang Yuan were to go there, he would definitely have to fight Heavenly Court. With his current strength, he would be able to defeat Heavenly Court. However! Fang Yuan's fear was Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable and Red Lotus Demon Venerable.

Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable had schemed against him, causing him to lose his clone Fang Di Chang. When using luck inspection earlier, he did not find Fang Di Chang's luck, it was likely that he had perished, the likelihood of his death was great.

Red Lotus Demon Venerable also schemed against him, if not for the heaven path dao marks, how could heaven's will be produced in Fang Yuan's immortal aperture? Of course, Red Lotus was also plotting against Spectral Soul. The heaven path dao marks were both dangerous and also a fortuitous encounter for Fang Yuan, it was also his protection. At the least, Spectral Soul could not use his hidden methods because of these dao marks.

If Fang Yuan wanted to take Emperor City, he would have to face the methods of Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable and Red Lotus Demon Venerable.

As for Crazed Demon Cave?

It was also filled with danger.

The Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics had promised to join the fate war to Fang Yuan, but during the battle, none of them had shown up. Fang Yuan had tried to contact them, but they had completely vanished.

What happened in Crazed Demon Cave that caused the Three Crazed Demon Eccentrics to mysteriously disappear?

Fang Yuan guessed that Longevity Heaven might have taken action. Fang Yuan realized that the consumption of wisdom Gu was part of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's scheme. Giant Sun's single attack also made Fang Yuan realize that he was keeping some trump cards after all.

Now that fate Gu was destroyed, it was possible for venerables to revive. If Fang Yuan went to Crazed Demon Cave, it was likely that he would need to face the methods of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Limitless Demon Venerable.

There was one more thing that worried Fang Yuan, there were changes happening in the River of Time.

Ever since the destruction of fate Gu, the water of the River of Time had become extremely violent, vicious and dangerous. Even if Fang Yuan used Myriad Year Flying Warship, he could only barely enter the river and last for a moment before having to return to the five regions, he was unable to explore it for long.

Fang Yuan understood the reason.

In the past, the River of Time could move forward smoothly because everything was fixed, everything moved according to the path set by fate, no matter what existed, they had a specific trajectory of life experiences. This was why time path Gu Immortals could often "predict" things by watching the downstream segments. Red Lotus Demon Venerable was able to plot the destruction of fate Gu by observing the downstream events and learning many secrets of the future.

But now, once fate Gu was destroyed, everything no longer had a fixed path and could change at will. As a result, the River of Time has become extremely violent, everything has become turbid and chaotic.

With such a change in the River of Time, Spring Autumn Cicada could no longer be used for the time being.

Before, Spring Autumn Cicada could move through the river because the water was gentle. Now that the river had become violent and chaotic, once Spring Autumn Cicada was activated and entered the river, it would definitely be smashed to pieces by the river water. Unless Fang Yuan developed some other killer move that could use Spring Autumn Cicada.

"Although the river water is troublesome, it's actually not a big problem. What I'm really worried about is still Red Lotus Demon Venerable. He's the one who had built the stone lotus islands in the River of Time. I don't know what other arrangements he has in the River of Time."

Fate Gu was destroyed at long last, Fang Yuan had finally gotten free of the Sword of Damocles hanging above his head.

However, the journey ahead of him was filled with mist, he was walking in a dangerous valley. Within the mist, which area could be explored, which area would lead to a cliff?

Would his path to eternal life, his lifelong ambition, be hidden within the mist?

If it existed, where would it be?

Chapter 1994: Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch Fights Fang Zheng

In immemorial black heaven, a group of Gu Immortals were traveling stealthily as they flew continuously.

These Gu Immortals had outstanding cultivation level, they were all rank eight variant human Gu Immortals. The leader was a Gu Immortal with pale skin and blue hair, he had a grim expression, it was Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch had received orders from Wu Shuai to reinforce the headquarters of the grotto-heavens, to resist the invasion of Heavenly Court.

Along the way, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's heart was filled with worry: "This is not the same as my expectations… I made Wu Shuai the alliance leader so that he would be the vanguard. But in the end, to deal with Heavenly Court, I was the one sent out instead."

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch had the intention to reject this order, but the situation back then did not allow him to use any excuses.

"Wu Shuai suffered injuries against Qi Sea Ancestor, in a way, he was indeed used by us to resist Qi Sea Ancestor."

"As the vice alliance leader, I need to put in some effort too. It makes logical sense for me to reinforce them in black heaven."

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch did not want to face Heavenly Court directly.

Regardless of win or loss, he would become an eyesore from Heavenly Court's perspective.

Currently, he wanted Wu Shuai to attract the attention of the enemies. But the world was not as simple as he thought, society was vicious to everyone, right now, he was pushed forward as the vanguard.

"I am truly unable to go against the tides!" Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch sighed deeply to himself.

He definitely had to go save them, but the way to go about it was something that he could determine himself.

"Vice alliance leader, we found a large number of Gu Immortals ahead." The investigative Gu Immortal suddenly spoke: "They are our allies."

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch nodded in response, unsurprised: "Go meet with them."

Even though Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch regretted his vice alliance leader position, it was already too late now, he could only take full advantage of the authority he had.

Before setting off, he had already used his status as vice alliance leader to order the remaining grotto-heaven forces to help each other out, in order to chase away Heavenly Court, they had to contribute their strength.

The two groups of Gu Immortals gathered, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch looked at the reinforcements, he felt rage building internally.

Chaotic Rock grotto-heaven sent an immemorial rock monster, Rotten Egg grotto-heaven sent six eggman Gu Immortals, they could form the ancient battle formation, Rotting Smell Vicious Cloud formation, while Strange Hair grotto-heaven brought an incomplete Immortal Gu House, Black Emperor Building. These three grotto-heaven forces that were close to Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch brought their trump cards along with them, but other than them, the other forces were simply not putting in effort. Especially those human forces, they only dispatched several rank seven Gu Immortals without much sincerity.

"The enemy is right ahead but these grotto-heaven forces are still trying to preserve their strength! Sigh, grotto-heavens are too far apart, we do not have much interaction normally, even if we cooperate, it is only due to external pressure."

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's anger soon turned into helplessness and dejectedness.

"In that case, I should conceal my own strength too, let's just put up a superficial show. After all, the people I brought amount to quite a force already."

Heavenly Court was powerful, if possible, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch did not want to face them head-on. He knew his own limits, if he really charged forward fearlessly, he might not return alive.

While Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch was thinking about this, his expression changed as his eyes widened, almost spewing fires of rage!

The other Gu Immortals saw Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's expression and turned around.

Someone asked: "Vice alliance leader, what happened? Have Xia clan's headquarters fallen?"

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch gritted his teeth: "Xia clan's headquarters have Lord Alliance Leader, how can they fall! My grotto-heaven has been invaded by Demon Judgment Board, my tribe's Gu Immortals are currently fighting them to the death, we need to reinforce them now!"

"This…" Great Wisdom Immortal Mother was still thinking of saving her grotto-heaven, she was hesitant.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch stared at her: "Your grotto-heavens have already fallen into the enemy's hands, the outcome has been decided. But my Ice Crystal grotto-heaven is still resisting them, there is hope. We need to return to reinforce them immediately, if anyone does not help, I will report it to Lord Alliance Leader Wu Shuai!"

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch made use of Wu Shuai's name, and because the variant human Gu Immortals close to Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch expressed their support, Great Wisdom Immortal Mother and the rest had to follow this order.

The immortals did not conceal their traces anymore, they flew towards Ice Crystal grotto-heaven with their fastest speed.

The grotto-heaven entrance opened as Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch flew in anxiously, while the rest followed.

Ice Crystal grotto-heaven was already in chaotic battle, Demon Judgment Board flew around like a meteor, slaughtering everything in its path, totally unstoppable.

The rank six and seven snowman Gu Immortals in Ice Crystal grotto-heaven were nowhere to be seen, they were controlling the formation to unleash a blizzard on Demon Judgment Board, but the effect was very minimal.

Suddenly, Demon Judgment Board shot out a sharp blood red light that landed on the control area of the formation.

The snowman Gu Immortals quickly put up their defenses, the blood red light seemed to be reflected by a mirror as it changed directions and shot elsewhere.

Boom!

There was a loud sound as heaven and earth shook, the blood red light exploded as the sky turned red. For the radius of several thousand li, the snowy and icy plain got completely obliterated.

"Ah, my blizzard icy plain!" Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch saw this and became overwhelmed with anger.

This icy plain was the largest gathering spot of the snowman race in Ice Crystal grotto-heaven, now that it was destroyed, nearly ten million ordinary snowmen died a terrible death.

The blizzard icy plain carried special significance to Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch personally.

His coming-of-age ceremony was held in this blizzard icy plain.

Back then, his father had brought the young Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch to the periphery of the icy plain.

"You are an adult now, my son. The icy plain you see here is the location of your trial. You need to survive seven days here to pass the trial, you will be qualified to become a Gu Master and awaken your aperture."

The young Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch looked at this vast plain and felt lost, fear appeared in his eyes.

His father observed his expression and said: "Fear is normal because you might likely die here. The trial is fair, you need to experience the danger of death in order to be qualified to become a Gu Master. Even as a Gu Immortal, I cannot protect you from this, I can only give you a suggestion."

"What is that?" The young Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch asked.

"It is too difficult to live alone in the icy plain for seven days, there is barely any hope." His father shook his head: "But there are many snowman tribes in this icy plain, if you can follow the traces to find them, they will protect you."

"But I don't know these people." The young Ice Crystal was worried.

His father explained meticulously: "Don't worry, the snowman tribes will protect every person who is stranded, because these people will end up protecting the entire race in the end. They will definitely help you, my son, if you succeed the trial, regardless of your achievements, you will need to protect our entire race. This is how a snowman lives!"

As expected, the young Ice Crystal survived for three days and nights in the icy plain, chasing after the traces of snowmen tribes.

At the moment of life and death, he crawled his way to a hunter's tribe near the periphery and was discovered, managing to survive.

The tribe took him in and healed him for free, welcoming him to become a member of their tribe.

Even though the young Ice Crystal left in the end, his experiences in that tribe were deeply etched into his heart, it affected him for the rest of his life until now.

After he became rank eight and inherited the title of Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch, becoming the owner of the grotto-heaven, he developed the blizzard icy plain and made the sparse icy plain grow abundant with resources, the lives of the snowmen living in it improved greatly, their numbers increased gradually.

But now, it was all ruined!

All ruined.

By a killer move of a strong foe that affected the entire blizzard icy plain.

Not only were Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's efforts ruined entirely, his memories also became just memories now, he could no longer find them in real life.

Anger and hatred rose in his heart, burning intensely.

For a moment, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch became silent, he took in a deep breath.

The air in Ice Crystal grotto-heaven was always so cold, it was still extremely cold now.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch suddenly remembered his father's teachings: "The tribe will definitely help you, my son, if you succeed in the trial, regardless of your achievements, you will need to protect our entire race. This is how a snowman lives!" "

Indeed.

It is time for me to protect my race.

Rumble!

At the next moment, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's aura erupted, creating an intense blizzard as he charged towards Demon Judgment Board.

All of the Gu Immortals behind him were shocked.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch was actually so courageous!

"Reinforcements from the two heavens are here." Inside Demon Judgment Board, Gu Yue Fang Zheng took in a deep breath as his expression turned grim.

Many people had arrived, among which were various rank eight Gu Immortals.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng was only rank seven but he was not flustered, all of his battles before this had tempered his own confidence and determination.

But the bigger reason was also the fact that he had absolute confidence in the rank eight Immortal Gu House, Demon Judgment Board!

"You created a grand commotion, but can you fight Demon Judgment Board?" Gu Yue Fang Zheng smiled coldly, instead of using any killer move, he directly used Demon Judgment Board to charge ahead.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch gritted his teeth, he was forced to retreat.

He was an ice and snow path Gu Immortal, he did not cultivate transformation path or strength path, how could he resist an Immortal Gu House with his body?

"Let's join the battle too!"

"Quick, work together and help vice alliance leader."

The two heavens alliance shouted and attacked at once.

Seeing this, Gu Yue Fang Zheng moved Demon Judgment Board away to retreat from them, pulling some distance agilely.

Blood red light flickered in Demon Judgment Board, killer moves were unleashed. The immemorial rock monster became slower, the eggman Gu Immortals were covered in blood, they had to save themselves instead of assembling the ancient battle formation. The incomplete Black Emperor Building from Strange Hair grotto-heaven was also waiting at the back, not daring to contest Demon Judgment Board directly.

The other Gu Immortals were even less useful, even though there were many rank eight Gu Immortals, they were all scared about losing their lives, only using long ranged killer moves instead. Once the enemy got close, they would prioritize escaping first.

It was a disunited bunch!

This phrase appeared in Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's mind, he felt angry and anxious.

Ice Crystal grotto-heaven had nothing to do with them, they would not risk their lives for it. The only person that Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch could rely on now was himself.

"I can only use that move now!" Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch made up his mind.

"Master, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's group is about to lose, should we help them?" Soul path Gu Immortal An Xun asked Spectral Soul secretly.

On this occasion, Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven sent him here, Spectral Soul came along and lurked in secret.

"Hehehe, they fought like this despite having so many rank eight Gu Immortals. The two heavens alliance is a joke." Spectral Soul laughed: "No need to be anxious, that Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch has other tricks up his sleeve, let's wait for now."

Chapter 1995: Extreme Ice Crystal Light Immortal Suppression Coffin

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch floated in the sky, his aura surged continuously as his clothes fluttered with the wind.

Around him, countless traces of frost energy gathered, whipping up a storm.

Such power surpassed ordinary rank eight killer moves, once Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch succeeded in activating it, the power would definitely shake heaven and earth. Fang Zheng sensed this, he wanted to use Demon Judgment Board to obstruct it.

"Let's lend Ice Crystal a hand!"

"Stop Demon Judgment Board!"

The Gu Immortals of the two heavens were not that useless after all, they quickly went ahead to block Demon Judgment Board.

At once, all sorts of killer moves were unleashed, it was like a display of fireworks.

Demon Judgment Board was obstructed by the bombarding killer moves, but at the crucial moment, a flash of blood red light shot out, about to land on Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch was still activating his killer move, he did not move.

At the crucial moment, An Xun opened his immortal aperture's entrance and let out an immemorial soul beast.

The immemorial soul beast moved quickly, standing in front of Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and blocking the blood red light entirely.

With a loud sound, an explosion occurred.

The immemorial soul beast growled in pain, half of its body was destroyed, it fell towards the ground.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch immediately looked towards An Xun with gratitude. The aura on his body was calming down, he had evidently passed the most dangerous moment, his killer move preparation was already done.

"Immemorial soul beasts have no blood, Demon Judgment Board's blood path killer move had little effect." An Xun was very excited as he said: "Master, if not for your reminder, I would not have been able to block this blood red light, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch would have been in trouble."

"No." Spectral Soul analyzed: "The killer move that Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch is using contains deep profundity, during the activation process, he gains an increased level of defense, even if he was hit, he would only be injured, the killer move activation would not fail."

"Heavenly Court! I'll let you have a taste of my race's unique killer move — Extreme Ice Crystal Light Immortal Suppression Coffin!" Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch shouted as all of the aura surging around him became completely concealed.

At the next moment, his entire body exploded and spread out into countless frost lights.

The frost lights shot out with extreme coldness! Everywhere they went, air would freeze into ice crystals before falling to the ground.

Fang Zheng felt something amiss, he wanted to activate Demon Judgment Board but how could his speed match the frost lights?

Almost at the same moment, Demon Judgment Board got hit by countless extreme ice crystal lights.

Crack crack.

Every crystal light that hit Demon Judgment Board turned into a small piece of ice attached to Demon Judgment Board.

Countless crystal lights shot towards it from all directions, Demon Judgment Board had nowhere to dodge, instantly, layers of ice started to form all over it.

Fang Zheng's heart sank, he activated Demon Judgment Board and used a killer move to melt the ice layers.

But his speed could not match the rate at which the freezing was occurring, very soon, ice that was five feet thick formed all over Demon Judgment Board.

"Oh no, the thicker this ice layer is, the greater the effect of the frost lights that land!" Discovering this, Fang Zheng turned pale with shock.

This move was unavoidable from the start, it was quite powerful, but its true strength came much later. The longer it dragged on, the stronger this move would be!

Fang Zheng quickly tried to move Demon Judgment Board, expending the remaining rank eight immortal essence to activate Demon Judgment Board's strongest killer move.

Blood red light spread out, a layer of ice quickly melted.

Next, the frost lights seemed to react, they quickly went towards the area that Fang Zheng was trying to break out from and made Demon Judgment Board's ability much weaker.

The Gu Immortals were all stunned.

"Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch is actually so powerful!"

"He actually sealed Heavenly Court's rank eight Immortal Gu House Demon Judgment Board with his own strength!"

"This is incredible, what is the name of the move?"

"Extreme ice crystal light immortal suppression coffin!"

At once, all of the immortals muttered the name of this killer move, engraving it to their heart.

"This is the unique killer move of the snowmen from ancient times, hehe, to think that they have actually obtained a racial inheritance already." Spectral Soul who was inside An Xun laughed lightly.

An Xun understood after hearing this: "So this is a move from the snowman racial inheritance, no wonder it is so strong! Wait, no, can ancient killer moves still be used in the current era? The world now is very different from the past, wouldn't such antique moves be outdated already?"

"Hehehe." Spectral Soul chuckled: "Back then when variant humans ruled the world, they had countless killer moves, those moves that were specially chosen to be kept in their racial inheritances are naturally more outstanding in many ways. Taking this extreme ice crystal light immortal suppression coffin for example, its core is not an Immortal Gu but the variant human using it."

Spectral Soul's depth of knowledge was not ordinary, he had once searched countless souls in the Door of Life and Death. Many of these souls came from the Olden Antiquity or Remote Antiquity Era, some were even from the Immemorial Antiquity Era.

Thus, Spectral Soul had a lot of information about these eras.

Even though his attainment levels had all fallen to rock bottom, his memories were still intact.

Like what Spectral Soul said, extreme ice crystal light immortal suppression coffin was somewhat similar to Wu Yong's unlimited wind killer move. When using unlimited wind, Wu Yong would expend his own wind path dao marks. As for extreme ice crystal light immortal suppression coffin, not only would it consume Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's ice and snow path dao marks, it would also cost him his lifespan.

As the core killer move of the snowman Gu Immortals, extreme ice crystal light immortal suppression coffin was not very affected by the progression of eras. At the same time, any other races' Gu Immortals could not use this move even if they had it.

Fang Zheng's forehead was already covered in sweat.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch displayed battle strength that far surpassed Fang Zheng's expectations. The great Demon Judgment Board was actually sealed in ice, there was little hope of escaping.

Even if Fang Zheng wanted to fight Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch, he had no way to do so.

Because Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch had already turned into countless frost lights, this was the superiority of extreme ice crystal light immortal suppression coffin killer move.

Seeing as Demon Judgment Board was about to be completely sealed in ice, at this time, a phoenix cry could be heard.

Following a loud sound of crashing waves, Prince Feng Xian and Bai Cang Shui arrived.

It turned out that while fighting Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch, Fang Zheng had already informed Heavenly Court's Prince Feng Xian and Bai Cang Shui.

Bai Cang Shui was originally cleaning up the battlefield, she could leave immediately. As for Prince Feng Xian, he gave up some gains there and rapidly came to reinforce Fang Zheng.

The two rank eight Gu Immortals saw Demon Judgment Board which was trapped, they shouted as one unleashed torrents of golden flames, while the other sent out huge waves.

The ice was attacked from the inside and outside, it could not last any longer as the external layer of ice quickly cracked, Demon Judgment Board which was inside got ready to retaliate.

The two heavens' Gu Immortals saw this and wanted to attack but Prince Feng Xian and Bai Cang Shui suppressed them instead.

Even though they had many more rank eights than Heavenly Court, it did not matter.

In Gu Immortal battles, numbers were not the most crucial. Even though the two heavens had many people, they could not cooperate, their killer moves often interfered with each other. About half of their strength was limited because of this, even before they hit any enemies.

But if they were to fight alone, they would be fearful and cowardly, they would focus on preserving their own lives, unwilling to take any risk or get into danger.

Of course, the other reason was that Prince Feng Xian and Bai Cang Shui were elite rank eights with excellent battle strength. They were able to become Heavenly Court members, they naturally surpassed other rank eights.

The situation was in a deadlock, Spectral Soul acutely sensed that the ice layer was weakening, he instructed An Xun: "Quickly let out the soul beast army, lend your Immortal Gu to me now."

"Yes master!" An Xun did not hesitate, he quickly followed the instructions.

The soul beast army came out and attacked.

Prince Feng Xian and Bai Cang Shui did not care about them at first, they used two killer moves in succession, but the soul beast army split up and moved fluidly like water, dodging most of the killer moves' effects.

Next, from the soul beast army, three immemorial soul beasts flew out to attack Prince Feng Xian and Bai Cang Shui.

As the two sides fought, the immemorial soul beasts were naturally unable to resist the two Heavenly Court immortals, but the immemorial soul beasts had the army to support them, at crucial moments, killer moves would help them out as well.

Even though Bai Cang Shui and Prince Feng Xian had the upper hand, the soul beast army successfully restrained them. They could not help Demon Judgment Board like before, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's frost lights began to regain their footing.

"This soul path rank seven immortal is quite talented!"

"I will go kill him!"

Prince Feng Xian and Bai Cang Shui communicated, the former moved as he spit fire, creating a path within the soul beast army as he charged towards An Xun.

An Xun 'turned pale with fright', shouting: "He is coming, protect me!"

The two heavens' Gu Immortals knew that enslavement Gu Immortals were most vulnerable to direct attack, they quickly responded.

Prince Feng Xian charged without stopping, he broke through all of the obstacles, but because of these obstruction, An Xun managed to pull some distance between them.

"You cannot escape." Prince Feng Xian smiled coldly as he charged again.

Spectral Soul would not personally take action in this public environment, he controlled An Xun's body to retreat while using the other Gu Immortals to obstruct Prince Feng Xian.

Prince Feng Xian's advancement was ferocious, the two heavens' immortals were all shocked by his aggressiveness.

But Bai Cang Shui shouted: "Feng Xian, quickly kill him."

Prince Feng Xian gritted his teeth, he did not expect An Xun to be so hard to catch.

At this time, the frost light successfully trapped Demon Judgment Board again, the thick ice coffin sealed the rank eight Immortal Gu House at its center.

"Oh no!" Seeing this, Bai Cang Shui and Prince Feng Xian's hearts sank.

Seeing that Heavenly Court's side was in danger, at this time, heaven and earth shook, qi currents surged as the world roared.

"Qi tide again!" Spectral Soul snorted coldly.

Ice Crystal grotto-heaven had already been broken through when Prince Feng Xian and Bai Cang Shui attacked, it was connected to the outside world.

At this moment, qi tides surged in the outside world, instilling into the grotto-heaven harshly.

The qi tides implicated the battlefield, wherever it reached, people fell to the ground.

Ice Crystal grotto-heaven's defensive immortal formation could not last any longer, it shattered, many snowman Gu Immortals fell into mortal danger.

The frost light around Demon Judgment Board flickered as it hesitated for a moment. But immediately, the ice crystal lights shot towards the snowman Gu Immortals as they turned into countless ice tubes that protected them.

But this way, Demon Judgment Board's pressure lifted greatly. Prince Feng Xian and Bai Cang Shui saw this and quickly made their move, breaking the remaining ice layers and saving Demon Judgment Board.

The two immortals went into the Immortal Gu House, Demon Judgment Board left the battlefield rapidly while resisting the turbulent qi tides.

Chapter 1996: Big or Small, Qi Harvest Fruit

The grand qi tide soon filled up the whole of Ice Crystal grotto-heaven.

Spectral Soul sighed deeply, this was really a pity. he wanted the two sides to fight to their deaths before he reaped the rewards, devouring Gu Immortal souls was much more helpful than absorbing soul cores after all.

But his scheme was ruined by this qi tide.

"I do not have Dang Hun Mountain, I lack guts Gu, I can only devour soul beasts and soul cores. But this takes time to digest, it is not like guts Gu which can directly raise my soul foundation."

"Why the coincidence? Not long ago, when Qi Sea Ancestor and Wu Shuai fought, a qi tide appeared. This time, another qi tide showed up."

Thinking about this, Spectral Soul had a realization: "Don't tell me that fighting between Gu Immortals will attract qi tides?"

Spectral Soul was only making a guess, he was not certain.

"It is a pity that my qi path attainment level is just ordinary. Otherwise, I will be able to come to a conclusion."

He had soul search and soul devouring methods, but these methods could not directly raise attainment levels. The only way to instantly raise one's attainment level was through absorbing true meaning. The attainment levels that Spectral Soul had at his peak were all gained through actual cultivation from the memories he had soul searched, it was not easy to reach that level.

"Forget it."

"An Xun performed well this time, with such achievements, he might likely receive Wu Shuai's audience."

"By staying in his body, I can get closer to Wu Shuai. There might even be a chance to enslave Wu Shuai and take Dragon Palace!"

Spectral Soul's current plan failed, he quickly came up with a new plan.

He had a deep desire towards Dragon Palace which contained dream path Immortal Gu!

Amidst the surging qi tides, frost lights gathered into Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's aura was weak, his face was pale, the price to activate extreme ice crystal light immortal suppression coffin was very high.

But he had almost singlehandedly sealed Demon Judgment Board, he was the biggest contributor to this victory.

The two heavens' Gu Immortals came to visit him, their gaze was different from before.

Strength was the determining factor towards one's status. Undeniably, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch who had extreme ice crystal light immortal suppression coffin killer move far surpassed the other rank eight Gu Immortals of the two heavens in battle strength.

"Even though I saved Ice Crystal grotto-heaven, our race's unique killer move was exposed." Even though he forced Heavenly Court to retreat, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch was not happy.

Right now, he could only console himself that this move was very hard to counter, it could still be his trump card for the time being.

"Friends, I am not injured, I only need to rest. I hope everyone can help to protect my grotto-heaven." Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch said.

"Sure, sure."

"We are all part of the two heavens alliance, this is not a problem."

"Everyone, we will do our best to defend Ice Crystal grotto-heaven!"

The Gu Immortals of the two heavens resisted the surging qi tides in the grotto-heaven while Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch focused on repairing the hole created in the grotto-heaven's aperture wall.

Even though the qi tides were powerful, with the cooperation of all the Gu Immortals, they soon settled down.

Because they had taken action swiftly, the qi tides did not cause much losses to Ice Crystal grotto-heaven.

"Vice alliance leader, take a look, we found something!" Great Wisdom Immortal Mother flew over to Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch with some unexpected news.

A moment later, the immortals of the two heavens also arrived at the area.

They saw a fruit that was the size of a hill floating in the air. This fruit was translucent, it was completely formed from heaven and earth qi, it was shaped like a gourd, or a peanut.

"This is a qi harvest fruit?"

"After the qi tides appeared, people often found these qi harvest fruits produced. If Gu Immortals get them and use them in the immortal aperture, they can rapidly soothe the heaven and earth qi and hasten the progress of the heaven and earth qi fusion."

"But ordinary qi harvest fruits are just as large as a horse carriage. Why is this qi harvesting fruit so huge?"

The two heavens' immortals discussed but could not come up with an answer.

"Master, is this really a qi harvest fruit?" An Xun asked Spectral Soul: "If it is, isn't this Ice Crystal grotto-heaven benefiting from a disaster? As long as it absorbs this huge qi harvest fruit, will Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's immortal aperture be modified completely, he will no longer be affected by the qi tides?"

"This is a qi harvest fruit indeed, but whether it is a blessing or a disaster is unknown for now." Spectral Soul chuckled to himself.

As expected, when Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch tried to take this qi harvest fruit, he was shocked to find a deeper secret.

"Oh no!" Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's expression turned even more pale: "This qi harvest fruit is still growing, it is absorbing my grotto-heaven's heaven and earth qi to grow further. If I take it away now, it will cause a huge commotion in the grotto-heaven, living beings will die, and an even more turbulent qi tide will appear."

The immortals gasped, after getting Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's permission, they quickly used investigative methods.

"We cannot let this qi harvest fruit continue to grow, who can help me get rid of this hidden threat? I will not be stingy on rewards." Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch had a solemn expression.

But the Gu Immortals looked at each other, they were all helpless.

Almost everyone could pull out the qi harvest fruit by force, but that was harmful to Ice Crystal grotto-heaven, its foundation would be affected.

And according to their deductions, directly destroying the qi harvest fruit would create a new qi tide that would create a second qi harvest fruit later.

This way, to get rid of this threat permanently without harming Ice Crystal grotto-heaven, the difficulty was very high.

Great Wisdom Immortal Mother suggested: "We can't do it because we do not cultivate qi path, but what about Lord Alliance Leader?"

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch had a look of worry, he sighed deeply: "Right now, we can only ask Lord Alliance Leader for help."

Wu Shuai soon received Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's request for help.

"My memories are limited, I did not know that the qi harvest fruit would become like this. Maybe the main body knows more things."

Wu Shuai quickly reported the information that Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch gave him to Fang Yuan's main body.

"Oh? The hidden threat of the two heavens' grotto-heavens have been found, this is much earlier than in my previous life." Fang Yuan's main body naturally knew about this.

In the five hundred years of his previous life, the two heavens' Gu Immortals had also worked together, they attacked many places and caused a lot of trouble for the five regions.

Due to the qi tides, the five regions' Gu Immortals were greatly restricted. But the two heavens' Gu Immortals were able to move around, they were less affected by the qi tides.

Furthermore, when Gu Immortal battles reach a certain level, qi tides would occur.

Even though the two heavens' Gu Immortals had low battle strength, with the help of the qi tides, they could defeat the five regions' Gu Immortals.

But good times did not last long, soon, the two heaven's Gu Immortals found that qi harvest fruits started to appear in their own grotto-heaven headquarters.

These qi harvest fruits used the grotto-heaven's heaven and earth qi to grow, they were like stubborn pests, if left unattended, they would grow endlessly and eventually destroy the entire grotto-heaven world.

"Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch fought against Heavenly Court and caused the qi tides to appear in his grotto-heaven, that is the reason why qi harvest fruits appeared earlier than the previous life."

Fang Yuan sent the information to Wu Shuai, suddenly, he had a thought as he gained a burst of inspiration.

"Wait!"

"Maybe I can use these qi tides to deal with heaven's will."

His situation was really bad now.

The main problem was the heaven path dao marks, he could not refine them in the short time, while these dao marks generated heaven's will.

The heaven path dao marks had no ill intentions towards Fang Yuan but heaven's will wanted to kill him, it tried all sorts of ways to destroy his sovereign immortal aperture.

And worse was that if Fang Yuan did not get rid of the heaven's will, after accumulating to a certain level, even if the sovereign immortal aperture remained shut, the grotto-heaven's heaven's will could resonate with the five regions' heaven's will and expose his identity.

Once Fang Yuan's location was exposed, if he stayed in qi sea, his cover as Qi Sea Ancestor would be blown.

However, it was difficult for Fang Yuan to get rid of heaven's will.

The sovereign immortal aperture was too huge, Fang Yuan did not know where to start. He could not predict the natural developments of the Heavenly Dao, he could not know where heaven's will would be created.

"I should try to let the qi tides rampage in my sovereign immortal aperture. Like a washing machine, they might be able to cleanse all of the heaven's will away."

As Fang Yuan thought about it, he found that this was a very possible idea to execute.

It seemed dangerous but it was possible to use the two threats against each other, with his qi path and wisdom path foundation, it was a realistic solution.

Of course, whether this method could succeed or not, until it was used, Fang Yuan could not know for sure.

"If only I still had wisdom Gu, that would be great."

Wisdom Gu provided unlimited inspiration, with the light of wisdom, Fang Yuan could quickly and efficiently develop a killer move that could make use of the qi tides.

At the same time, in Qi Jue grotto-heaven.

"This is the center of the grotto-heaven!" Luo clan's three Gu Immortals were all injured, they reached this place after much difficulty.

"What... what an incredible qi harvest fruit..." Luo Mu Zi was lost for words, the other two immortals were filled with shock.

According to the three immortals' deductions, the center of Qi Jue grotto-heaven should contain the most valuable thing in the entire grotto-heaven.

At this moment, the three immortals saw that there was a tiny and exquisite qi harvest fruit here, it was extremely vivid, the surface had flowing lights that flickered dazzlingly.

It was the size of a gourd but it contained genuine rank nine immortal material aura. It had surging waves of vitality resembling the ocean, it pressed down on the hearts of the Luo clan Gu Immortals.

"This qi harvest fruit is not ordinary at all, it contains deep secrets, we need to research upon it."

"Strange, qi harvest fruits are produced by the qi tides, why is it hidden by Demon Immortal Qi Jue and kept here?"

"Unless he predicted that in the future, there would be disasters like the qi tides?"

"Take action!" Luo clan's three immortals were talking when suddenly, they heard a shout, several variant human Gu Immortals showed up and attacked.

Luo clan's three immortals were caught off guard, they were swept into a battlefield killer move instantly.

"Oh no, an ambush!"

"Someone else found Qi Jue grotto-heaven?"

"Who are you?"

Luo clan's three immortals shouted.

The leader of the variant human Gu Immortals was about the size of a thumb, there were translucent wings behind him, this was a miniman Gu Immortal.

"Hmph, Luo clan immortals, I, Xiao He Jian, found this place twenty years before any of you." The miniman Gu Immortal smiled coldly as he said: "Attack, kill them all!"

Chapter 1997: Both Sides Seek Reinforcements

Days later, in the headquarters of Southern Border's Wu clan.

Wu Yong stood at the peak of a mountain, he slowly opened his eyes.

In front of him were three mortals. They were all tied on a wooden pole, they were all unconscious.

Immortal killer move — Farewell Friend Wind!

Wu Yong breathed in deeply, his preparations were completed, he unleashed this peculiar killer move.

Without the emergence of any unique wind, the three mortals in front of him started to disintegrate, their skin, flesh, and bones scattered with the natural breeze. In an instant, even the clothes of these mortals vanished, nothing was left.

Wu Yong showed a satisfied smile at last.

During this period, he had modified farewell friend wind, the results were quite good.

Farewell friend wind was a wind path killer move with human path effect, it originally needed the user to touch the target's body and say some parting words.

But now, these limitations were all modified by Wu Yong and removed successfully.

Even though the current farewell friend wind still needed the user to become friends with the target before usage, the range had greatly increased, it was much more usable now.

Wu Yong had lost a lot of his wind path dao marks during the fate war from using the killer move unlimited wind and his foundation fell.

But during this period of recuperation, he made some gains instead in terms of comprehension, his wind path attainment level rose to a new level. Because of that, he could modify farewell friend wind.

Wu Yong was not just satisfied with modifying farewell friend wind, the rise in his attainment level also meant a comprehensive rise in power.

Farewell friend wind was just one of the aspects.

"Next, I will modify the other killer moves, and even Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building! After modification, my battle strength will rise back to normal, it can even surpass my former level."

Right when Wu Yong thought about his future, an information path Gu worm flew towards him.

Wu Yong took it and read the information, his brows rose as he showed a surprised expression.

He was originally going to stay in closed cultivation for some time, but after receiving this information, he halted his plan.

Returning to his guest hall, he met with the two Gu Immortals that were looking for him.

These two Gu Immortals had the same clothing, they wore deep green short sleeve shirts and long black pants, they also had jade colored leg bindings.

Any Gu Immortal familiar with Southern Border's Gu Immortal world would know that this was Luo clan's signature attire.

Of the two Luo clan Gu Immortals who came, one was an old man with a bitter expression, another was a middle aged Gu Immortal with a pale face, he was evidently injured.

"Luo Zu (Luo Ran) pays respects to Lord Alliance Leader." Luo clan's two Gu Immortals saw Wu Yong and immediately paid respects.

The Southern Alliance was created long ago, Wu Yong was the leader of this alliance.

Of the two Luo clan immortals, Luo Ran was a general of Luo clan, he was a space path expert with peak rank seven battle strength, he was an arrogant person. As for Luo Zu, he was a person of authority, he was the current first supreme elder of Luo clan. These two were so respectful to Wu Yong now, it was clear that they needed his help.

Wu Yong nodded: "We can sit and talk."

After the two Luo clan Gu Immortals sat down, Wu Yong asked directly: "What is the matter with Qi Jue grotto-heaven?"

Luo Zu breathed in deeply before explaining the entire situation. In summary, when a Gu Immortal of Luo clan explored white heaven using an Immortal Gu House, he discovered Qi Jue grotto-heaven by chance. Luo clan had been exploring it for many years, finally, with the help of the qi tides, they made a breakthrough and entered the central area of Qi Jue grotto-heaven.

But when they were about to obtain Qi Jue's true inheritance, they were ambushed by variant human Gu Immortals. The three Luo clan Gu Immortals exploring it were caught off guard, the situation did not look good.

Thankfully, their leader was the space path expert Luo Ran, he used his trump card and escaped with the other two immortals.

The variant human Gu Immortals did not let them go, they pursued these three Luo clan immortals.

After Luo clan was informed, they immediately sent their Immortal Gu House to reinforce them, the two sides fought intensely at the heavenly wind qi wall. Even though those variant human Gu Immortals did not have high battle strength, their leader, the miniman Gu Immortal Xiao He Jian, was very outstanding. At the same time, the variant human Gu Immortals had an Immortal Gu House too, Luo clan was forced to escape back to Southern Border pitifully.

After passing the heavenly wind qi wall, the variant human Gu Immortals were afraid that Southern Border's Gu Immortal world would gang up on them, they gave up on the pursuit.

Luo clan's immortals were defeated, they returned to recuperate in their headquarters, feeling angry and helpless. After discussing for some time, they felt that they could not obtain Qi Jue grotto-heaven themselves, they should get the help of other forces.

After hearing their explanation, Wu Yong understood the situation.

"Due to the rampant qi tides, the grotto-heavens in the two heavens are exposed, this created the two heavens alliance. The alliance mainly comprises variant humans, they have Wu Shuai as their leader."

"This group of variant human Gu Immortals that defeated Luo clan must have a close relationship with the two heavens alliance."

"The two heavens alliance first occupied an area in Eastern Sea, Wu Shuai fought with Qi Sea Ancestor. After that, Heavenly Court attacked them, their vice alliance leader Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch forced Demon Judgment Board to retreat, creating a huge commotion."

"If Luo clan looks for Hou clan or Yao clan, even though they are super forces, they cannot deal with the colossal two heavens alliance. When the situation aggravates, they will still have to look for me in the end. Thus, they came to me from the start."

Thinking so, Wu Yong smiled, promising them: "Our Southern Border's righteous path is united, now that Luo clan has faced a setback, as long as you are part of the Southern Alliance, we will help you out. As the leader of the Southern Alliance, I, Wu Yong, will lend my strength as well!"

Luo clan's immortals quickly responded: "Alliance Leader is righteous and mighty."

But there was no joy on their faces.

This concerned a huge treasure like Qi Jue's true inheritance, Wu Yong was sure to agree to help without doubt.

The important things were how to get true inheritance of Qi Jue, how would Luo clan and Wu clan cooperate, if they obtained the true inheritance, how would they split it?

Those were the true details to discuss.

While Luo clan's immortals and Wu Yong were negotiating, Wu Shuai also received the audience of a Gu Immortal.

"The one asking to see me is a miniman Gu Immortal named Xiao He Jian?" Wu Shuai squinted.

"Yes." The reporting Gu Immortal explained: "This immortal has extraordinary strength, his reputation is long established, even though the Gu Immortals of the two heavens do not interact much with each other, we have all heard of this Xiao He Jian. His strength is likely on par with vice alliance leader."

The vice alliance leader was naturally Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch.

This time, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch used his immortal sealing coffin killer move to defeat Heavenly Court, his reputation surged, everyone in the two heavens alliance knew about it.

"What is the reason for his request to meet me?" Wu Shuai asked purposely.

"This subordinate... does not know." The reporting Gu Immortal lowered his head: "He says that he has a huge fortune to give to Lord Alliance Leader, he wants to join our two heavens alliance."

Wu Shuai smiled.

In the past, he did not know, but after the main body sent him some information of the previous life, he learned about this person.

This Xiao He Jian was quite a formidable figure in the five hundred years of his previous life, he was indeed an expert among the variant human rank eight Gu Immortals, he was able to contest Heavenly Court's members evenly.

Speaking of which, in the five hundred years of his previous life, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch did not have much reputation.

In terms of battle strength, Xiao He Jian and Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch were on the same level. Even though the two heaven's Gu Immortals were not very outstanding, they still had several incredible experts. If not for this, they would not have caused problems to the five regions in the previous life.

"Xiao He Jian explored Qi Jue grotto-heaven, he probably got into a conflict with Luo clan. Now that the Southern Alliance was created in advance and Luo clan suffered a loss, they would definitely find their allies, they might approach Wu Yong."

"Xiao He Jian has several grotto-heaven forces allied with him, but how can he resist the great Southern Alliance? Thus, he came to me, by joining my two heavens alliance, not only can he protect himself, he can also use my strength to resist the Southern Alliance and obtain Qi Jue's true inheritance."

"But this Qi Jue grotto-heaven is a dangerous area, in my previous life, Qi Jue grotto-heaven self-detonated, killing countless Gu Immortals in the process. The two heavens alliance also suffered a huge setback from this, the losses were so severe they never recovered."

Wu Shuai guessed that Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch died during this Qi Jue grotto-heaven explosion, otherwise, with his strength, he would not have stayed so low profile the entire time.

Considering this, Wu Shuai smiled coldly, thinking: "This Xiao He Jian is crafty, he wants to borrow our strength and use us to kill his enemies, since he wants my help, let's have a good negotiation with him."

"Go." Wu Shuai stopped thinking about it as he sat on his main seat, telling the Gu Immortal: "Tell Xiao He Jian to come in."

Chapter 1998: Exploring Qi Jue Grotto-Heaven

The sky had a unified color, it was a sight of bluish jade.

Great winds howled, killing intent gathered.

Two Immortal Gu Houses faced each other.

One was a majestic palace shining in golden light, it was elegant and grand, this was Dragon Palace. The other was a two storey bamboo building, it was filled with vitality and looked delicate but exquisite, this was Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building.

The two rank eight Immortal Gu Houses contained many Gu Immortals inside them.

Wu Shuai sat at the main seat with two rows of Gu Immortals from the two heavens below him. On his left was Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and others, while on his right was the recently joined wood path great expert, miniman Gu Immortal Xiao He Jian. As for Lady Cold Ash, Night Heavenly Wolf Lord, and others, they were mixed among these two groups.

Not long ago, Wu Shuai met with Xiao He Jian, after some negotiation, they set off for Qi Jue grotto-heaven.

On the other side, Southern Alliance's Wu Yong also knew the importance of speed, he quickly mobilized Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building, bringing Wu clan's and Luo clan's immortals to immemorial white heaven.

Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building was much faster than Dragon Palace, Wu Yong left later but arrived earlier, yet Qi Jue grotto-heaven could not be easily entered. While Wu Yong and the rest waited, Wu Shuai arrived with Dragon Palace.

The two sides met in white heaven, they immediately got into a deadlock.

"Wu Yong." Wu Shuai spoke within Dragon Palace, his voice resounding in the battlefield: "Qi Jue's true inheritance is in front of us, why don't we each send three people out to fight, the winner will be the side which has two victories, they will get the true inheritance, while the loser gets the grotto-heaven, how is that?"

"Wu Shuai, why are you being so cowardly now?" Wu Yong snickered from within Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building: "Let the person fortunate enough under the circumstances get Qi Jue's true inheritance, let's fight for it using our respective abilities!"

As he said this, Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building shot out like a rainbow, piercing into a certain opening within Qi Jue grotto-heaven.

Wu Yong had waited for a long time, he finally found an opportunity to get inside.

Even though Wu Yong brought Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building with him, and had Wu clan's and Luo clan's elites around him, in terms of scale, he could not match Wu Shuai. Not just in quantity, but the quality of their high end battle strength also differed greatly.

If they really used the rules Wu Shuai set to determine a victor, in one-on-one combat, Wu Yong's side would be disadvantaged.

Furthermore, when Gu Immortals fight, heaven and earth qi would be disrupted, qi tides would appear. By then, the two heaven's Gu Immortals would be less affected, their advantage would rise again.

Wu Yong was a formidable leader, how could he let his side fall into a disadvantage from the start?

"Lord Alliance Leader, there is no time to waste, let's set out!" Xiao He Jian urged anxiously.

Wu Shuai looked at the openings in Qi Jue grotto-heaven, even though these openings varied in size, they were all milky white in color, formed from moving qi currents.

Earlier, Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building had gone through the largest opening to get inside Qi Jue grotto-heaven.

After looking at it for a while, Wu Shuai understood some of its profundity.

"These openings vary in size, they are increasing in numbers, I'm afraid this is the immortal aperture entrance of Qi Jue grotto-heaven."

Fang Yuan's main body and clones had varying amounts of memories but they shared the same attainment levels. Wu Shuai also had the main body's qi path attainment level, he could see it more clearly than others.

Just these holes alone made Wu Shuai's eyes brighten as he felt some comprehension.

"Normally, immortal aperture entrances are closed, only used to connect the inside world and the outside. Qi Jue grotto-heaven's entrance is unique, it is the most efficient way of maximizing the effect of that connection between worlds using the immortal aperture's entrance. I wonder what gains I can make inside?"

Thinking so, Wu Shuai's curiosity rose as he moved Dragon Palace towards the openings.

In the five hundred years of his previous life, this Qi Jue grotto-heaven was destroyed by self-detonation, it greatly affected the two heavens alliance and caused it to falter in the future. Many rank eight Gu Immortals died during this event.

Qi Jue grotto-heaven was dangerous, this was also why Fang Yuan did not take the initiative to explore it before the fate war.

But now that Qi Jue grotto-heaven was exposed, with an alluring true inheritance of Qi Jue inside and Dragon Palace's protection, Wu Shuai also had nothing urgent to attend to, he could put effort into this now.

Dragon Palace got past the narrow opening, rapidly arriving inside Qi Jue grotto-heaven.

The immortals saw that all around them, there were white colored qi currents that surged and moved.

"Qi Jue grotto-heaven's structure is quite special, it is not like ordinary grotto-heavens, there are white qi currents everywhere. These qi currents form into tunnels and countless tunnels turn this grotto-heaven into a maze, it is like the intestines of a giant. We need to get through these tunnels quickly and find the correct path to the central area. Qi Jue's true inheritance is hidden there!" Xiao He Jian explained when they got in.

All the immortals inside the palace listened attentively.

Xiao He Jian did not say everything he knew earlier, to prevent Wu Shuai from leaving to snatch the true inheritance alone after getting the information, he had kept many secrets, he promised Wu Shuai that he would explain the situation after they arrived.

Dragon Palace moved around in the white qi current tunnels, quickly reaching a crossroad. On the left and right were two paths, they were identical in size and shape.

"How do we determine the correct route?" Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch asked.

Xiao He Jian replied: "I cannot be sure about it either, we need to test the paths. The only rule here is that the closer we get to the center, the more valuable the monsters and resources within the qi current tunnels. At the most central area, the qi harvest fruit has reached rank nine level!"

"What about Luo clan?" Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch asked another crucial question.

"Luo clan does not have a more accurate method either. In fact, their exploration speed was far slower than us. It was because of the qi tides that they gained an opportunity to get past many difficulties and reach the central area rapidly. Looking at our previous progress, my tribe was extremely close to Qi Jue's true inheritance, we were just two obstacles away." Xiao He Jian sighed, he felt somewhat of a pity regarding it.

The immortals heard this and relaxed slightly.

"In that case, even though they came inside first, in terms of advantage, we have the upper hand." Great Wisdom Immortal Mother analyzed.

"Don't be careless, Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building is much faster than us." Wu Shuai said plainly.

He chose a random path and moved Dragon Palace along it.

Along the way, the qi current tunnels became wider and taller, many qi path living beings were in them, creating special living environments that were isolated from each other.

Roar!

Suddenly, a group of qi monsters emerged from the thick tunnel walls, surrounding Dragon Palace.

These qi monsters had all sorts of strange forms, resembling bulls, goats, fish, or birds. However, their colors were similar, being close to orange-yellow.

"These are qi monsters created from luck qi." Xiao He Jian said: "Even though there are no immemorial qi monsters, they are quite troublesome to deal with. Without luck path methods to protect us, if we kill them, our luck will fall."

Immortal killer move — Dreamy Light Smoke!

At the next moment, a gush of smoke flew out from Dragon Palace, wherever it went, all of the luck qi monsters were swept away, suppressed within Dragon Palace.

"Uh." Xiao He Jian was stunned but he soon reacted as he said respectfully: "A dream path killer move, truly worthy of Dragon Palace!"

As they continued, they saw an immemorial qi monster, it was pitch-black like a whale, its body was colossal.

Xiao He Jian had a grim expression: "Be careful, this is an immemorial qi monster created from hard qi, thankfully it is sleeping now. I'd suggest that we detour around it, let's not..."

Boom!

At the next moment, Dragon Palace accelerated and crashed into the immemorial qi monster.

Dragon Palace shook intensely but the immemorial qi monster was pierced through, it retaliated in anger.

Dragon Palace charged and crashed into it again, and again!

The immemorial qi monster broke apart, turning into lumps of black hard qi. Next, Wu Shuai stored the hard qi in his palace.

"You can all split the spoils." Wu Shuai kept most of the gains and passed the rest to the Gu Immortals.

"Alliance Leader is mighty!"

"All hail Dragon Palace!"

"Subordinate thanks Lord Alliance Leader."

"With Lord Alliance Leader here, so what if they have Wu Yong?"

At once, the immortals expressed their gratitude as all sorts of praises erupted.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch smiled as he looked at Xiao He Jian, saying with deep meaning: "Try not to be shocked at these minor situations, it will cause us to lose face."

Xiao He Jian had to nod in acknowledgment but he still felt deep shock internally: "Even though I saw the fate war, I can only see how powerful Dragon Palace is after witnessing it in action personally. If Dragon Palace is so strong, what about Duke Long, Fang Yuan, and Feng Jiu Ge?"

At once, Xiao He Jian's emotions became rather complex.

On one hand, the stronger Dragon Palace was, the more hopeful he was. But on the other hand, as a great expert, seeing such a difference between them and seeing such a powerful existence made him feel some dejectedness.

Along the way, wherever they went, Wu Shuai took all of the loot that they could gather.

Qi Jue grotto-heaven was really the land of treasures for qi path, it was like the qi sea of ancient times. Not only were the qi path resources here in huge quantities, they also varied greatly in variety, there was basically anything one needed here.

Wu Shuai purposely displayed his might to intimidate Xiao He Jian. As a result, he exposed more secrets, according to him, when exploring this place, he found a Qi Breath Peak! Qi Jue grotto-heaven actually had such an extinct qi path resource, but regrettably, Xiao He Jian only took a glance at it, he did not have the ability to take it.

"This is the center of Qi Jue grotto-heaven?" Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building had just arrived at the destination, before Wu Yong could rejoice, his pupils shrunk: "Hmph, they weren't slow at all."

Behind Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building, Dragon Palace arrived.

At the center of Qi Jue grotto-heaven was a huge hollow sphere. The sphere had many qi pillars that interweaved with each other, creating countless tunnels.

Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building and Dragon Palace entered this area, it was like two flies had entered a beehive.

The qi pillars continued to move around, some were fast while others were slow, they even affected each other. Under Wu Yong's control, Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building moved carefully and avoided the qi pillars, taking sharp turns along the way.

"These qi pillars are special, they are at least rank eight immortal materials. We cannot touch them easily or unnecessary problems will occur." Xiao He Jian quickly said.

This place was not suited for fighting, thus, in order to kill the three Luo clan immortals, Xiao He Jian had arranged a battlefield killer move.

But in the end, Luo clan's Luo Ran was a space path Gu Immortal, he brought the other two immortals away by piercing through the battlefield, using this special terrain to get free from Xiao He Jian and the rest, escaping.

"No need for such trouble." Wu Shuai waved his hand.

At the next moment, a dragon roar was heard, the Evil Dragon descended.

Boom boom boom!

The Evil Dragon charged ferociously, wherever it went, qi pillars broke and shattered, it created a path for Dragon Palace to move along from behind it.

"Hmm?" Wu Yong frowned.

Xiao He Jian's mouth was open, he became dumbstruck.

Chapter 1999: Qi Jue, Xi

"Great!"

"Lord Alliance Leader is so powerful!"

"This is the power of our two heavens alliance!"

The morale of the immortals within Dragon Palace surged, they quickly cheered.

Evil Dragon charged ahead with an unstoppable might, Dragon Palace followed behind it casually.

"This dragonman brute!" The eyelids of Luo clan's first supreme elder Luo Zu were twitching as he gritted his teeth.

The two clans' Gu Immortals within Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building felt immense pressure. Evil Dragon was charging relentlessly like a mobile mountain range, in comparison, Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building was very delicate and small.

And most importantly, Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building had to dodge the qi pillars, its advancement route was long and winding. But Evil Dragon moved forward in a straight line without obstruction, the distance between them was shortening.

"What do we do now?" The Southern Alliance's Gu Immortals turned pale.

Wu Yong smiled lightly: "Wu Shuai uses strength to suppress others, he is making full use of his advantage. If I were him, I would do the same. Everyone, after the fate war, not only was Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building fully repaired, I even strengthened it further, we can block Di Zang Sheng for a period of time. Even though they are strong, we do not need to bother with them, we just need to get Qi Jue's true inheritance before them."

"Lord Alliance Leader is right!" The immortals nodded in agreement.

Any sort of conflict had its goal, Wu Yong could clearly see that their objective was Qi Jue's true inheritance. Whoever gets it would be the winner, even if they suffer some losses while competing, so what?

But the Evil Dragon was really too strong.

It was the immemorial desolate beast with the strongest battle strength!

In the five regions and two heavens, there were less than five people who could fight this Evil Dragon head-on!

While Wu Shuai and Wu Yong were chasing after their goals, a third rank eight Immortal Gu House stealthily arrived outside Qi Jue grotto-heaven.

It was Demon Judgment Board!

Demon Judgment Board was controlled by Fang Zheng, not only did Prince Feng Xian and Bai Cang Shui come along, even Che Wei, who had recovered from his injuries, and information path great expert Zhou Xiong Xin were here.

Fang Zheng took the initiative to attack the two heavens previously, even though Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch forced them away, their gains were still huge. Prince Feng Xian and Bai Cang Shui obtained abundant loot from plundering the two grotto-heavens.

Even though Fang Zheng lost in battle, he had only lost some reputation of Heavenly Court, they did not lose benefits.

Heavenly Court was originally not sure of Qi Jue grotto-heaven's event, after all, immemorial white heaven was huge, even during the qi tides when Qi Jue grotto-heaven exposed itself, Heavenly Court could not find it immediately.

But don't forget that Night Heavenly Wolf Lord under Wu Shuai had submitted to Heavenly Court. The fact that Xiao He Jian joined the two heavens alliance was not concealable, Night Heavenly Wolf Lord learned of Qi Jue grotto-heaven's secret and informed Heavenly Court as a result.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue was very famous in history, he was a terrifying great expert who opposed Limitless Demon Venerable!

Especially when he cultivated qi path, in the current environment where qi tide surged, all new qi path resources were emerging in huge quantities continuously. The five regions' forces wanted to research more into qi path.

Heavenly Court was no exception!

Even though they had Primordial Origin's true inheritance, if Heavenly Court could gain Qi Jue's true inheritance, it would mean that other forces could not get it. With this difference, Heavenly Court would have a great advantage against others.

Thus, Fang Zheng did not rest for long, he received Qin Ding Ling's orders and brought four rank eight Gu Immortals to move to white heaven using Demon Judgment Board, arriving at this place.

"This should be Qi Jue grotto-heaven, but what is going on?" Fang Zheng had just arrived but he saw a shocking change.

He saw countless holes appearing, milky white qi currents surged endlessly as they moved around, the many new openings started to connect the grotto-heaven to the outside world.

These openings increased in numbers and continued to surface, there were too many of them, this would be a fearsome sight to others.

After more than ten breaths, a huge silhouette of Qi Jue grotto-heaven appeared. On the surface, there were countless white qi currents surrounding it, within the qi currents, there were countless holes breathing in and out.

The surrounding air was sucked into the grotto-heaven by a terrifying formless force. As for the loud noise that it created, the Heavenly Court immortals felt deafened all of a sudden.

"A huge change is occurring in Qi Jue grotto-heaven!"

"Wu Shuai and Wu Yong might have fought in the grotto-heaven."

"What to do?"

Prince Feng Xian and the rest looked towards Fang Zheng, he was still their leader in this expedition.

Fang Zheng felt pressured, the choice in front of him was a difficult one. At this moment, he fell into hesitation, what should he choose?

At the center of Qi Jue grotto-heaven.

Boom boom boom!

Qi pillars continued to break and shatter as noise erupted endlessly.

The Evil Dragon destroyed everything in its path, but such a sight did not last long, after the qi pillars were destroyed, they turned into strong qi currents that intertwined together, surrounding the body of the Evil Dragon as they pressured it, trying to attack and kill it from all directions.

The Evil Dragon roared but its speed continued to fall, it was facing an unprecedented pressure from ahead.

Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building and Dragon Palace were not having an easy time either.

These qi currents were like tsunami waves that constantly attacked, these two rank eight Immortal Gu Houses were like small rafts trying to float in this treacherous storm.

Huge qi currents collided and caused the two Immortal Gu Houses to shake, sometimes, the Immortal Gu Houses even spun around on the spot.

There was a shot of deep blue qi current, Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building quickly tried to dodge it. But the deep blue qi current was too large and fast, Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building exerted all of its strength before leaving and escaping after three breaths of time.

"Lightning qi!" Southern Border's Gu Immortal gasped: "I've never seen such colossal lightning qi, this quality is on par with rank eight immortal materials."

Lightning qi could only be collected during stormy weather.

It was not hard to collect lightning qi, but high ranked lightning qi immortal materials were very rare.

Rank eight lightning qi was even rarer.

If the situation were not so urgent, Southern Border's Gu Immortals would want to collect the lightning qi.

"This is all Wu Shuai's fault! By causing rampant destruction, Qi Jue grotto-heaven has gone into a berserk state." Luo Zu gritted his teeth.

Wu Yong's expression turned dark: "Qi Jue's true inheritance is our primary goal!"

The lightning qi from earlier caused Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building to lose some Gu worms, Wu Yong quickly replenished them.

These immortal materials had incredible dense dao marks, this environment was very dangerous. If there were wind path qi current immortal materials, Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building would have an incredibly good time here.

The change in Qi Jue grotto-heaven's situation made the environment much more dangerous, but on the whole, Wu Yong's situation had actually improved.

Because Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building suffered much less obstruction compared to Wu Shuai's side.

Dragon Palace was much slower than Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building.

There were sharp blade qi, black hard qi, dark death qi... all sorts of qi currents were all at rank eight level. Wu Shuai gritted his teeth as he drove Dragon Palace forward, resisting them by force.

The Evil Dragon was left in the dust already.

Its body was too big, it was resisted by at least ten air currents or more, it could no longer be of use here.

"This is the foundation of Qi Jue grotto-heaven..." Wu Shuai had a solemn expression, his gaze flickered with uncertainty.

He had the disadvantage now but the situation had not been decided.

The two heaven's Gu Immortals were also speechless at the moment. If not for Dragon Palace's protection, who would dare to travel in this dangerous place? Many rank eight Gu Immortals felt their own weakness and insignificance at this moment.

"Demon Immortal Qi Jue is truly worthy of being the person who rivaled Limitless Demon Venerable in the past!"

The two rank eight Immortal Gu Houses did not give up, they moved towards the center with much difficulty, trying to obtain Qi Jue's true inheritance.

But outside the grotto-heaven, Fang Zheng no longer had to hesitate.

"Let's retreat first and observe the situation." Fang Zheng ordered, Demon Judgment Board quickly retreated.

Prince Feng Xian and the rest were silent, they agreed with this decision.

Because right now, a change occurred again, raging qi currents appeared all over the place, a new qi tide had begun!

Fighting during a qi tide would cause the Gu Immortals to suffer backlash, even Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were no exception.

"It seems our earlier deduction was right."

"The heaven and earth qi in our immortal apertures differ from the outside world, thus be it opening the immortal aperture entrance or fighting intensely, when it hits a certain level, a new qi tide will occur."

"Demon Immortal Qi Jue is a five regions Gu Immortal, because of his foundation, now that his immortal aperture's entrance is basically wide open, along with the fight between Wu Shuai and the Southern Alliance inside, they created a gigantic qi tide."

"Let's watch by the side and try to reap some benefits from the outcome."

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals conversed as they kept a close eye on Qi Jue grotto-heaven.

The powerful qi tide went through the openings and rapidly entered Qi Jue grotto-heaven.

Wu Shuai and Wu Yong instantly felt huge pressure as the wild qi currents became even stronger. Even though the rank eight Immortal Gu Houses were powerful, these qi currents made them helpless, they were often blown away to random places.

Bang... bang... bang!

As the two Immortal Gu Houses approached the center, they started to hear loud thumping sounds.

"What is going on?"

"What qi currents are causing these sounds?"

"No, this is someone's heartbeat! Quickly look!"

The two Immortal Gu Houses arrived at the center of Qi Jue grotto-heaven, all of the Gu Immortals saw this sight —

At the point where all the countless qi currents merged was the eye of the storm, this place was completely tranquil and safe.

In this tranquil environment, there was a tiny and delicate qi harvest fruit, it continued to absorb the surrounding qi currents.

Countless qi currents of all types got absorbed into the qi harvest fruit and their traits were assimilated, becoming a part of the fruit.

Different from the previous situation, there was the form of a baby inside the qi harvest fruit!

The qi harvest fruit was like a woman's womb, a human baby was curled up inside, growing and getting larger by the second.

"What is happening?"

"What in the world is going on?"

"This is a monster! It is actually absorbing rank eight immortal materials endlessly to strengthen itself!"

"It is about to be born, quickly stop it!"

The immortals' expressions changed, Wu Shuai wanted to unleash the killer move dreamy light smoke, but the qi harvest fruit seemed to have sensed it, it shook and self-detonated.

The baby was successfully born, he had tiny arms and legs like he was malnourished.

At this time, the silhouette of a concave land appeared above his head. This concave land contained deep profundities, it gave off a rank nine aura. But this aura was far more perfect and refined than the incomplete Human Sea that Wu Shuai had previously.

This was a secluded domain of heaven and earth!

The baby raised his arms, he seemed to be using both arms to carry the silhouette of this secluded domain of heaven and earth.

"Xi—" He shouted out in a long tone.

At the next moment, all of the surrounding qi currents moved into the silhouette of the secluded domain of heaven and earth like river tributaries returning to the ocean.

The qi currents moved with incredibly shocking speed, within a few breaths of time, all of them went into the mysterious secluded domain of heaven and earth. Wu Shuai and Wu Yong could not even sense a single qi current around them anymore.

In the sky, only the baby and the two rank eight Immortal Gu Houses were left.

"We're outside again." Luo Zu found himself in the outside world.

"No, the whole of Qi Jue grotto-heaven turned into qi currents and got absorbed by him." Wu Yong was unable to conceal his shock, everything was unexpected in this situation, he felt like he was used.

This was someone's scheme!

"Who are you?" Wu Shuai shouted from within Dragon Palace.

The baby had grown into a boy, he breathed in deeply, the silhouette of the secluded domain of heaven and earth above his head went into his nose.

Next, he looked around and saw Dragon Palace and Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building, he also found the hidden Demon Judgment Board.

The boy smiled as he started to recite: (Chapter 1319)

"Climbed mountains to seek immortality, danger present in every step.

Dust specks float like light, dark Gu lurk in heart.

A dream like golden jade, thousands of years of loneliness.

Five regions and nine heavens, everything is in one breath[1]."

As he recited, his voice was young but his tone was aged: "Who else can I be? Yours truly, Demon Immortal Qi Jue."

"Demon Immortal Qi Jue?!" The immortals were all shaken.

"Wait, if he is Demon Immortal Qi Jue, then the secluded domain of heaven and earth from earlier, it is 'Xi' from \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>?" Within Demon Judgment Board, Zhou Xiong Xin suddenly had a thought.

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> had two very mysterious secluded domains of heaven and earth, there was little description regarding them.

One was 'Hu', the other was 'Xi'.

[1] Breath written as qi in Chinese. Back

Chapter 2000: Might of the Demon Immortal

Demon Immortal Qi Jue!

The mysterious Gu Immortal stated his own identity, the entire place went silent.

The three sides' Gu Immortals were shaken. According to history, Demon Immortal Qi Jue was someone who had been evenly matched with Limitless Demon Venerable in battle at some point!

Wu Shuai, who was inside Dragon Palace, frowned, he realized many things: "It seems that in my previous life, Demon Immortal Qi Jue failed to revive. Otherwise, there would not have been zero information about Demon Immortal Qi Jue's revival. There are two possible reasons, one is that fate Gu was not destroyed then, the second is that Spectral Soul succeeded in refining sovereign immortal fetus Gu, from all the signs known, he had already infiltrated Heavenly Court and gained complete control of the situation. He would not allow someone like Demon Immortal Qi Jue to revive."

Thinking of this, Wu Shuai snorted coldly as he willed.

Roar—!

At the next moment, the Evil Dragon moved.

Earlier, because of the countless qi currents obstructing it, the Evil Dragon was covered in injuries. But now that the whole of Qi Jue grotto-heaven was absorbed by Demon Immortal Qi Jue using an unthinkable method, the Evil Dragon regained freedom, it charged towards Demon Immortal Qi Jue with imposing aura again.

Once it moved, wild winds started blowing.

The Evil Dragon's colossal body was like a moving mountain range, engulfing heaven and earth.

Forget about Demon Immortal Qi Jue's tiny child body, even the great Dragon Palace could not match the Evil Dragon's body.

"Hehehe, come." Demon Immortal Qi Jue's vision was filled by Di Zang Sheng.

He was not flustered, instead he smiled calmly.

He did not dodge, he directly extended his small hand towards Di Zang Sheng.

Immortal killer move — Great Qi Grasp!

With a loud sound, endless white qi currents shot out of Demon Immortal Qi Jue's body, forming a giant hand with five fingers.

The hand was only the size of an Immortal Gu House at first, but it slowly inflated to the size of a hill. Three breaths of time later, the entire qi current hand had expanded to the size of the Evil Dragon's head.

But the milky white qi current hand continued to grow!

Di Zang Sheng had already reached it.

Bam.

The two sides collided, but out of everyone's expectations, Demon Immortal Qi Jue's qi current hand was easily destroyed in one move.

Di Zang Sheng did not slow down, continuing to pursue Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue did not dodge, he continued to face Di Zang Sheng casually.

Di Zang Sheng only charged for a few seconds before slowing down, it growled loudly like it was in great pain.

"My great qi grasp can form and scatter at will. It can grab mountains and seas if it takes form, but it can also invade organs when it scatters. How will you deal with it?" Demon Immortal Qi Jue stood arrogantly and said.

The immortals were shocked.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue used one move to subdue Di Zang Sheng, he had true pseudo venerable battle strength!

"Another demonic path expert!"

"Sigh, with the destruction of fate Gu, the world will go into chaos."

"Demon Immortal Qi Jue had died more than a million years ago, that source of chaos Fang Yuan gave him the chance to revive!"

Inside Demon Judgment Board, Heavenly Court's immortals gritted their teeth, they had ugly expressions.

After the fate war, the righteous path fell while the demonic path surged!

Duke Long, who was the pillar that held up Heavenly Court, died, Feng Jiu Ge, whom they entrusted their hopes to, betrayed them, while Fang Yuan, who was the culprit behind the destruction of Fate, still remained scot-free!

And now, there was this Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

There were sad cries as Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals realized that the future of the five regions and two heavens became much bleaker now.

They did not even think of recruiting Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

Although in history, he had opposed Limitless Demon Venerable, there was also no possibility that he would ever join the righteous path.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue, just the demon in his name stated the obvious. After all, the saying goes: There are only wrong names, not wrong titles.

"Xiao He Jian, what are you really up to? You created such a huge enemy for our two heavens alliance!" Within Dragon Palace, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch suddenly shouted.

Xiao He Jian could not rebuke him, his face turned pale.

He felt a lot of lingering fear but also relief. He was relieved that he joined the two heavens alliance, otherwise, with just himself, he would have become the sacrificial lamb of Demon Immortal Qi Jue's revival already.

"This is a scheme, I am a victim too." Xiao He Jian voiced his innocence.

"This is a scheme, Demon Immortal Qi Jue's scheme." At the same time, Wu Yong sighed within Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building.

Luo Zu sighed deeply: "Demon Immortal Qi Jue is a qi path cultivator, but he actually predicted the events a million years into the future? What sort of level did he reach?!"

Wu Yong frowned slightly, he looked through Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building towards Dragon Palace.

He could understand Demon Immortal Qi Jue's arrangements, but he had some doubt in his mind, did Wu Shuai know about this secret?

Now that Wu Yong recalled it, Wu Shuai had been controlling the Evil Dragon to create destruction all over the place, was it because he was straightforward and wanted to use brute force, or was he purposely trying to destroy Demon Immortal Qi Jue's arrangements?

Evidently, it was because of the Evil Dragon's rampant destruction that Demon Immortal Qi Jue was revived ahead of time.

Wu Yong was a formidable person with a sharp mind, the more he thought about it, the more he suspected Wu Shuai's actions.

"It is possible that Wu Shuai knows about Demon Immortal Qi Jue's existence. After all, he has some sort of relationship with Fang Yuan, and Fang Yuan possesses Spring Autumn Cicada, it is not strange that he knows some secrets." Wu Yong thought of Fang Yuan.

"Did Fang Yuan come here?" Inside Demon Judgment Board, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were guessing.

Fang Yuan was a person who had been reborn, if he knew about the secret of Demon Immortal Qi Jue's revival, he might likely hide somewhere to make his move!

Precisely because of this concern, Demon Judgment Board did not take action. Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building was also waiting for something to happen.

But Demon Immortal Qi Jue did not want to let them off.

"Today is the wonderful day I revived, come, come, let me see what methods the Gu Immortals of this current era have!"

Demon Immortal Qi Jue had the appearance of a boy but his tone was that of a man proud of his experience, he actually attacked again.

At once, milky white qi currents gushed out, filling the world with a tsunami, Heavenly Court, the Southern Alliance, and Wu Shuai's side were all enveloped.

"Hmph! Old scoundrel Qi Jue, don't be too arrogant, we are not afraid of you, we are just wary that Fang Yuan might be hiding somewhere." Wu Yong spoke, using Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building to retreat immediately.

Fang Zheng's voice resounded from Demon Judgment Board: "Precisely! Demonic path senior, even though you are famous in history, you cannot compare to the number one demon in the current world, Gu Yue Fang Yuan! This person destroyed my Heavenly Court's fate Gu, without him, you would not have revived."

"Fang Yuan? I will remember this name." Demon Immortal Qi Jue stretched his arms, qi currents shooting out rapidly: "But none of you will escape!"

He was like a bottomless hole, constantly shooting out milky white qi currents.

These qi currents were unique, ordinary immortal killer moves could not destroy them. At once, three rank eight Immortal Gu Houses fell into a predicament, their speeds fell drastically.

Wu Shuai snorted, he controlled Dragon Palace to advance instead of retreating, attacking Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue laughed loudly: "Good, someone with actual guts."

A trace of smoke flew out of Dragon Palace.

Immortal killer move — Dreamy Light Smoke!

Demon Immortal Qi Jue did not dodge it, he was hit by the smoke, instantly disappearing.

Wu Shuai had a perplexed expression, he was like a fisherman spreading his web, he used all his strength to cast the web but in the end, he only caught some bubbles without any fish.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue's body appeared again, this time, he was far away.

He looked at Dragon Palace deeply with an expression of wariness: "Good, I'll remember this."

He gave up on Dragon Palace, he went to attack Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building and Demon Judgment Board instead.

Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building emitted wild winds while Demon Judgment Board shot out powerful blood red lights, they both displayed their might.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue's moves were mostly grand and wide ranged, he managed to suppress the two Immortal Gu Houses.

After more than ten rounds, bright light shined in his eyes as he shouted: "Good, good, good, to think that people have already created wind path and blood path, this is truly exciting. I did not waste my effort in arranging for my revival in this great era!"

"Other than you people, who else is there in this world?" Demon Immortal Qi Jue asked.

Wu Yong smiled coldly: "Ignoring anyone else, Eastern Sea has quite the formidable person. He also cultivates qi path, his battle strength is definitely higher than yours. He stays in qi sea, he calls himself Qi Sea Ancestor, he is the undisputed leader of the current Eastern Sea righteous path!"

"Oh? There is a qi path cultivator? Back in my day, qi path was already declining, to think that it would still linger until today! Very good, it seems I will need to meet him." Demon Immortal Qi Jue laughed loudly in joy.

Wu Yong continued: "Other than Qi Sea Ancestor, there is also a sound path demonic immortal named Feng Jiu Ge. He has also defeated the Evil Dragon in one move with much greater ease than you. In the battle earlier, he betrayed Heavenly Court openly and now his whereabouts are unknown, but Heavenly Court does not dare to release an arrest warrant for him."

"Feng Jiu Ge? Good, I'll remember him. Anyone else?" Demon Immortal Qi Jue's eyes shined.

Wu Shuai interrupted at this moment: "Get past us first, old man."

As he said that, Dragon Palace flew over again.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue smiled lightly as he pointed: "Lower qi."

Milky white qi currents gushed out and caused Dragon Palace to fall in altitude.

At this time, Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building carried a storm with it as it charged towards Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue pointed another finger: "Upper qi."

Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building was swept away by the qi currents, flying upwards uncontrollably.

Demon Judgment Board arrived in front of him.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue stretched out two fingers as he pointed at this house: "Upper-lower breathless qi."

Demon Judgment Board erupted with a loud sound as it stayed stationary in midair. The Gu Immortals inside had changes of expressions, the immortal essence that they tried to instill became choppy, this rank eight Immortal Gu House was like a dying old man who could not take proper breaths at this moment.

"Juniors, I'm not going to play with you anymore. Go and spread the word, tell Fang Yuan, Qi Sea Ancestor, and Feng Jiu Ge that I will visit them soon. They can't hide from me."

Demon Immortal Qi Jue had just said this when his figure vanished, he did not appear anymore.

All of the immortals were wary now, after getting rid of the remaining milky white qi currents, they confirmed that Demon Immortal Qi Jue had truly left the scene.

"Do we pursue him?" Someone within Dragon Palace asked.

Wu Shuai snorted coldly: "Where did he go? Why don't you tell me?"

The Gu Immortal who asked turned pale, he lowered his head, not daring to say another word.

"Let's retreat." Wu Yong smiled, not forgetting to salvage the morale: "Even though we did not have much gains this time, fighting against someone like Demon Immortal Qi Jue is worth the trip after all."

"Sigh! After Fang Yuan comes Demon Immortal Qi Jue, I really do not know which great expert will revive next!" Fang Zheng was filled with worries, he mobilized Demon Judgment Board to quickly leave the battlefield.

Chapter 2001: Recruiting Qi Sea Ancestor

Demon Immortal Qi Jue revived, he suppressed Heavenly Court, Southern Border, and the two heavens. News of this battle soon spread in the entire Gu Immortal world, everyone in the world was shocked.

"To think that Demon Immortal Qi Jue revived!"

"The world is really going into chaos, I wonder how many great experts will revive next?"

"Demon Immortal Qi Jue was able to revive, there's no reason the venerables cannot, right? Oh heavens!"

"No wonder they said Great Dream Immortal Venerable would be the strongest venerable in history. Being able to emerge as a venerable in this terrifying era means they have to be incredibly strong."

While countless Gu Immortals made their guesses, the three parties involved were actively recuperating.

Dragon Palace.

"Sigh, I thought that I would be able to obtain Qi Jue's true inheritance, to think that it was a trap!"

"Now that Demon Immortal Qi Jue has revived and we actually offended him, what do we do now?"

"It is all Xiao He Jian's fault, he caused our two heavens alliance to fall into this awkward position."

Most of the variant human Gu Immortals looked towards Xiao He Jian with animosity.

Xiao He Jian smiled coldly, he knew that this was the act of Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch, attempting to suppress him.

He had just joined the two heavens alliance but because of his great strength and reputation, he was already threatening Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's status, this was the cause of the animosity from the opposing faction.

"Have you all said enough?" At the main seat, Wu Shuai snorted coldly in displeasure.

Instantly, Dragon Palace became silent, all the immortals shut up.

At this point, Xiao He Jian showed a shameful expression, he bowed to Wu Shuai, saying in a tone of sincerity: "Lord Alliance Leader, I am at fault..."

But before he continued, Wu Shuai interrupted: "Enough, keep quiet. Even if Demon Immortal Qi Jue comes, we have the Evil Dragon and Dragon Palace, what is there to fear? The most urgent matter now is the qi harvest fruits in your grotto-heavens."

"Demon Immortal Qi Jue revived using a qi harvest fruit, this thing clearly contains secrets and profundities, we have not explored it sufficiently. How are we going to get rid of the qi harvest fruits in your grotto-heavens? If we do not act quickly, your grotto-heavens will be in danger."

"Indeed, indeed."

"Lord Alliance Leader is right!"

"My grotto-heaven has already started producing a qi harvest fruit, this fruit is absorbing the heaven and earth qi of my grotto-heaven, it cannot be removed by force."

"The same situation is happening in my grotto-heaven."

"Right now is not the time to take revenge on Heavenly Court or defend against Demon Immortal Qi Jue, the most important thing is to get rid of the qi harvest fruits in our grotto-heavens."

At once, all the immortals in the palace changed expressions as the topic was shifted to the qi harvest fruit.

However, this talk bore no fruit, the palace soon became shrouded in an atmosphere of panic and fear.

Even Xiao He Jian was the same.

Even though his grotto-heaven had not produced any qi harvest fruits yet, at this rate of development, it was only a matter of time.

Even Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch did not have the mood to compete with Xiao He Jian.

His Ice Crystal grotto-heaven's qi harvest fruit was the largest, he was in the greatest danger.

Night Heavenly Wolf Lord also showed a bitter expression.

His grotto-heaven was not spared either, a qi harvest fruit was growing in it. Even though it was still small now, it was growing at a terrifying speed.

But Night Heavenly Wolf Lord was much less anxious than the rest.

"If the two heavens alliance cannot resolve it, I can get help from Heavenly Court."

At this crucial juncture, Night Heavenly Wolf Lord felt that his decision to join Heavenly Court was extremely wise!

Night Heavenly Wolf Lord had a lot of expectations towards Heavenly Court.

After all, the first generation Heavenly Court Immortal King was Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, he was a qi path cultivator.

Night Heavenly Wolf Lord secretly informed Heavenly Court about this as he sought help from them.

Heavenly Court had sent Fang Zheng and the rest to Qi Jue grotto-heaven but Demon Judgment Board did not enter it at all, he did not know what happened inside.

After getting Night Heavenly Wolf Lord's information, Heavenly Court learned the truth.

Qin Ding Ling placed huge emphasis on Demon Immortal Qi Jue's revival using the qi harvest fruit, as well as the disaster occurring in the two heavens' grotto-heavens! This was because Heavenly Court was not exempted, a qi harvest fruit was also growing in it.

She immediately summoned the immortals to research and think of countermeasures.

Heavenly Court had deep foundations, even after the fate war, it was still the number one super force in the world.

Especially when they had Primordial Origin's qi path true inheritance, they had a huge advantage in qi path, they were at the peak compared to all others.

And most importantly, Heavenly Court's research into heaven path was quite extensive, they had great results. Back then, even Limitless Demon Venerable was after their heaven path findings, he made the bet with Star Constellation.

"Heaven, earth, and humans all have veins, humans have human veins, the earth has earth veins, and heaven has heaven veins."

"The two heavens' grotto-heavens are all situated on the heaven veins, thus they benefit greatly and the grotto-heavens are nourished by the heaven veins, producing even more resources."

"However, the world is changing now as qi tides are produced. Qi tides appeared because of the unification of the five regions, the earth veins are becoming one. But the truth is, heaven veins are also merging into one, although the change is not very apparent now."

Heavenly Court's immortals found that the whole of heaven and earth was fusing into one. The five regions were just the start, the two immemorial heavens would start fusing together later as well. The five regions and two heavens were all separated originally, their heaven and earth qi were not the same. But with the fusing of the heaven and earth qi across all regions, qi tides would emerge as the places where they merge.

Wherever the qi tides go, abundant qi path immortal materials would be produced, qi harvest fruits were the quintessence of them.

The reason why the two heavens' grotto-heavens produced qi harvest fruits was because they were situated on the heaven veins, they were facing the brunt of the initial impact.

"That is to say, as long as these grotto-heavens relocate away from the heaven veins, they will resolve the problem of the qi harvest fruit?" Qin Ding Ling asked.

"Theoretically yes, or at least, once they move away from the heaven veins, the growth of the qi harvest fruits in the grotto-heavens will stop." Heavenly Court's immortals answered.

Qin Ding Ling frowned: "Once grotto-heavens are placed, they are hard to relocate, unless one has some special method to move them around. Our Heavenly Court is too big, it has the foundation of Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable's immortal aperture along with the future generations of venerables, and countless immortal apertures of Heavenly Court members, how can we relocate Heavenly Court?"

Heavenly Court became silent, they fell into deathly silence.

"Maybe... Demon Immortal Qi Jue has a method?" Breaking the silence, Fang Zheng spoke.

Qin Ding Ling's eyes shined with bright light.

That was true, the possibility of this was high!

Since Demon Immortal Qi Jue was able to revive using a qi harvest fruit, his understanding regarding qi harvest fruits should surpass everyone else. But to get him to cooperate with Heavenly Court, how hard would it be?!

"According to historical records, Demon Immortal Qi Jue will definitely not cooperate with Heavenly Court. Rather than him, we have a higher chance of getting Qi Sea Ancestor's cooperation."

"Indeed, we cannot resolve Heavenly Court's crisis alone. To get rid of this qi harvest fruit calamity, we need a qi path great expert."

"Duke Long had once given Qi Sea Ancestor half a portion of Primordial Origin's true inheritance. During the fate war, Qi Sea Ancestor did not show up, he kept his promise. There is still hope of our cooperation now."

"But Qi Sea Ancestor has some relationship with Fang Yuan..."

"In my opinion, this is a small matter. Ever since Qi Sea Ancestor appeared, all his actions state one motive. He wants to be the leader of Eastern Sea's righteous path, be it the qi sea banquet or the resistance of the two heavens alliance, they show it clearly. His actions do not align with Fang Yuan's interests, even if they cooperated before, it is not our problem."

"Can't our Heavenly Court settle this ourselves?"

"It will be too difficult, ever since the immortal graveyard was destroyed, Star Constellation's will has not shown up once..."

"If we can cooperate with Qi Sea Ancestor, we might even be able to get him to join Heavenly Court. We really lack someone with pseudo venerable battle strength now."

Qin Ding Ling sighed as she made her decision: "Let's try it then."

Chapter 2002: Fragment of Xi

Immemorial white heaven.

Aurora lights moved in the air dazzlingly.

Eastern Sea rank seven Gu Immortal Qing Hui Zi flew around in the sky of aurora lights, unleashing immortal killer moves to continuously retrieve these aurora lights.

After gathering the rainbow lights in his hands, he turned them into balls.

The balls were then sent into his immortal aperture and buried in cloud soil. After some time, these aurora light balls would grow and sprout, becoming seedlings. By using lightning water and magnetic sound to water them, flowing light fruits would grow on them.

Flowing light fruits were a rank six immortal material, formed from extremely dense lights, having all kinds of color like red, brown, yellow, green, black, blue, purple.

Qing Hui Zi did not only pluck the flowing light fruits, he had his unique plantation methods. Precisely so, he was one of the three main sellers of flowing light fruits in treasure yellow heaven.

"With the qi tides weakening the heavenly wind qi wall, I can also get past them and explore immemorial white heaven for immortal materials. This is my fortuitous encounter."

Qing Hui Zi sighed to himself.

Aurora lights were very common in the two heavens, they were produced abundantly.

Qing Hui Zi collected these aurora lights personally, it caused the cost of producing flowing light fruits to fall greatly, he could earn a huge profit.

As Qing Hui Zi collected the aurora lights, he paid attention to the heavenly wind qi wall below him.

He did not have the strength to survive long in immemorial white heaven, he could not even break the heavenly wind qi wall. Thus, he needed to pay attention to it constantly, once the hole created by the qi tides start to close up, he would need to return to Eastern Sea.

It was no joke.

If Qing Hui Zi got distracted and got trapped in immemorial white heaven, with his strength, he would not last until the next qi tide, he would die in this dangerous immemorial white heaven.

One could say that Qing Hui Zi was risking his life to get these aurora lights.

But Gu Immortal cultivation was not easy, even as a rank seven Gu Immortal, Qing Hui Zi needed to take risks to support his livelihood.

"Xi—!"

Right at this time, Qing Hui Zi heard a voice.

Next, winds blew and clouds shook, Qing Hui Zi was shocked to find out that the heavenly wind qi wall below him was being pulled away by a terrifying formless force.

In a few breaths of time, the surrounding tens of li of heavenly wind qi wall got sucked into the whirlpool at the center.

"What is going on?!" Qing Hui Zi was overwhelmed by fear and shock: "Is that an immemorial desolate beast? But I've never heard of any immemorial desolate beast with such strength!"

The heavenly wind qi wall vanished entirely, a secluded domain of heaven and earth that had a concave appearance could be seen.

Next, this silhouette of the secluded domain of heaven and earth went into the nose of a Gu Immortal who resembled a boy.

Qing Hui Zi saw this boyish Gu Immortal, his entire body and mind shook, he felt like cold water was poured on him, into the depths of his despairing heart.

"Ah, Demon Immortal Qi Jue!" Qing Hui Zi fell into deep despair: "Why am I so unlucky? I only wanted to collect aurora lights but I ended up encountering Demon Immortal Qi Jue!!"

The battle of Qi Jue grotto-heaven had happened recently but it could not be hidden, the world knew about it already.

Even though the killer move everybody's vision wasn't around for all the Gu Immortals to witness the battle themselves, Demon Immortal Qi Jue's appearance and methods were widely spread already.

In the Gu Immortal world, there were a few people publicly recognized as terrifying beings that had to be avoided at all costs.

The number one person was Fang Yuan.

This demon had countless methods and outstanding strength, he did things without any regard or concern, he was ruthless and cruel, even Heavenly Court had no choice against him.

Wu Shuai was also on the list, he was the leader of the dragonmen, owner of Dragon Palace which enslaved Di Zang Sheng, he bore deep grudges towards humanity.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue was a newly added person.

As for Heavenly Court and Qi Sea Ancestor, because of their factions, they would not bully the weak, thus they were not on this list.

After Qing Hui Zi saw Demon Immortal Qi Jue, he recognized the demon, he stared in shock, frozen on the spot like a statue.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue frowned as he looked at his palm.

His palm was tiny and smooth, his body was still small like a boy.

Thinking about his revival, Demon Immortal Qi Jue felt angry and annoyed.

If he had some more time, he would revive perfectly and have the body of an adult. But the Evil Dragon caused great destruction in its movement, he had to revive in advance, it caused his body's growth to be halted, his potential was limited.

After absorbing this heavenly wind qi wall, he finally recovered some losses from the intense battle earlier.

After resting, he was going to set off again.

"Junior, come here." Demon Immortal Qi Jue looked towards Qing Hui Zi and called out.

Qing Hui Zi shivered, he went towards Demon Immortal Qi Jue with a bitter expression, fearing for his life.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue smiled lightly, he stretched out his finger as an eerie qi current flew out.

The qi current quickly surrounded Qing Hui Zi's body, he wanted to resist subconsciously but Demon Immortal Qi Jue shouted: "Don't move!"

Qing Hui Zi gritted his teeth, not daring to move at all.

He gave up on struggling, he let the qi currents enter his body and move around his soul.

After some time, Demon Immortal Qi Jue absorbed all of the qi currents that entered Qing Hui Zi back into his own body.

Instantly, he received a vast amount of information, he gained a much deeper understanding of the current era.

"This is truly a wonderful era filled with great excitement, interesting!" Demon Immortal Qi Jue's eyes shined as he spoke in amazement.

Next, he instructed Qing Hui Zi: "Hand over your Gu worms."

Qing Hui Zi's lips twitched, for an instance, he wanted to resist but soon, logic took over his mind, he obediently handed over all of his Gu worms to Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

This action made Demon Immortal Qi Jue reassess him.

After taking away these Gu worms, Demon Immortal Qi Jue inspected all of them, he only took a few glances at Qing Hui Zi's light path Immortal Gu before he placed his focus on those exceptional mortal Gu.

Especially Gu worms like soul search Gu, Demon Immortal Qi Jue was very interested in them.

At the end, he even returned the light path Immortal Gu to Qing Hui Zi.

Qing Hui Zi was very surprised.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue smiled: "Junior, you are not stupid enough to resist me. Who do you think I am? Why would I be greedy and take your trifling Immortal Gu? Scram now."

Qing Hui Zi was in disbelief before it turned into deep joy: "Junior will never forget Senior Qi Jue's magnanimity."

"Hahaha, I searched your soul, why is there a need to thank me?" Demon Immortal Qi Jue laughed: "Go ahead and hate me, I don't care. Even though this era is great, in the entire world, in the absence of the venerables, there are few people who I can take interest in. Even though I lack Immortal Gu, I have not sunk down to the level of snatching light path Immortal Gu. I want to take some qi path Immortal Gu!"

Qing Hui Zi instantly had a thought: "Senior, you want to go to qi sea?"

But at the next moment, Demon Immortal Qi Jue waved his sleeves impatiently.

Qing Hui Zi was surrounded by qi currents and could not move, he was sent flying by the movement of the qi currents.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue snorted, he did not look at Qing Hui Zi, he flew towards the direction of qi sea instead.

"I wonder how powerful this Qi Sea Ancestor is, hehe, I hope his qi path Immortal Gu will not disappoint me." Demon Immortal Qi Jue carried great confidence as he went towards qi sea.

He flew in the sky of Eastern Sea, he was surrounded by qi currents as he moved rapidly across various sea areas.

He did not conceal his traces, causing huge waves along the way, the commotion shook the surroundings, his demonic might was exposed in full view. Along the way, he met several Eastern Sea Gu Immortals, these people scrambled in panic as they escaped.

"Oh?" Halfway through his journey, Demon Immortal Qi Jue's expression turned to shock as he stopped his movement.

He felt a movement in his secluded domain of heaven and earth.

"Don't tell me?" Demon Immortal Qi Jue was slightly stunned, he thought of something as joy appeared on his face.

He temporarily put aside the plan to head to qi sea, he changed directions and went southwest instead.

After some time, he arrived at a sea area.

The sky here had many white clouds, shrouding his vision, he could not see any starlight. Even when the sun was blazing, the sunlight could not penetrate the cloud layers, it only made the place brighter.

The surface of the sea was calm but inside it were countless currents. These currents were of all types and forms. They interlinked with one another, they moved in this sea area with absolutely no rhythm or pattern. Without the defensive methods of a Gu Immortal, mortal corpses would be torn to shreds in the currents instantly.

It was the turbulent flow sea area.

After inspecting it closely, Demon Immortal Qi Jue became quite happy: "Wonderful, wonderful. This sea area must have a fragment of Xi, that is the reason why it can create such turbulent currents."

"To think that my luck would be strong after reviving."

"I'll retrieve this fragment first and absorb it before going to find that Qi Sea Ancestor."

Thinking of this, Demon Immortal Qi Jue plunged into the sea, vanishing from plain sight.

Chapter 2003: Qi Jue Suppresses Qi Sea

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

The disasters were still ongoing, the situation was slowly moving towards the abyss of doom.

Fang Yuan's losses were severe. In order to save his resource points, he had already deployed the variant human and human Gu Immortals in his immortal aperture to different areas, they were tasked to take care of the resources and they were even given mortal Gu that could be used to detect heaven's will.

Along with Fang Yuan's time path clone and main body working together to get rid of the newly created heaven's will, he managed to save all the large resource points in the sovereign immortal aperture.

However, as long as the heaven path dao marks were not refined by Fang Yuan, they would continue to produce endless heaven's will in increasing quantity.

Even though Fang Yuan was using his full strength, he could not stop the situation from aggravating further.

He could only barely protect his resource points now, but the sovereign immortal aperture was too huge, resource points were only a small part of it. In most areas, heaven's will was produced, moving towards the respective resource points like a huge army.

Fang Yuan knew that this situation was at its most crucial point now!

He could no longer cleanse all the heaven's will, in order to prevent the grotto-heaven's heaven's will from linking with the five regions, he had to create an isolated secret space in qi sea, to prevent heaven's will from detecting him.

As for the external situation, Demon Immortal Qi Jue's revival was out of Fang Yuan's expectations, Demon Immortal Qi Jue said that he would go and meet Qi Sea Ancestor, he was not joking.

There were both internal and external problems!

"Now, it will depend on the effectiveness of this immortal formation." Fang Yuan's concentration was invested into this rule path formation.

This formation was situated in Mini Blue Heaven, it floated on its own, it was a modified version of the five regional limit formation.

Fang Yuan had wisdom path attainment, he knew long ago that the situation would progress like this, he made preparations in advance and tried to come up with countermeasures early.

Not long ago, he gained some inspiration and decided to mimic the qi tides to deal with the heaven's will in his immortal aperture.

And this rule path formation was the fruit of his research.

Rank eight immortal essence was already piled up at the side, stored into the immortal formation. With Fang Yuan's thought, this huge formation that covered the range of more than ten li started to activate.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh...

The formation created huge winds, as the sounds of the wind resounded in heaven and earth, countless qi currents appeared from the formation, as if the entire sky was covered in steam, it was completely white, one could not see anything.

The formation suddenly emitted profound light. The profound light landed on the white qi and pushed it like a giant hand.

At the next moment, thirty percent of the white steam qi moved forward like a gushing fountain.

The profound light entered the white qi and modified it, causing the scattered white qi to become more concentrated.

Finally, the white qi that was pushed out turned into a qi tide as it swept towards the southeast direction firmly. Along the way, the qi tide was like a brush that cleaned up the surrounding heaven and earth qi in its path.

In terms of strength, the qi tide that Fang Yuan created could not compare to a true one. But its strength was quite amazing already, it could easily take the lives of mortal Gu Masters.

This was also why Fang Yuan set up the formation in Mini Blue Heaven, it was to prevent an accident from slaughtering countless lifeforms, it would cause him a huge loss.

After moving for an hour, this qi tide almost reached the aperture wall boundary of Mini Blue Heaven.

Fang Yuan inspected the results, he found that the heaven's will that he had specially arranged here was all cleanly removed, not a trace was left. Furthermore, along the path that the qi tide moved, heaven and earth qi were well blended, it was peaceful and calm.

Fang Yuan let out a breath of air, this was good news.

With this formation, he could finally get rid of the huge problem of heaven's will.

This carried huge significance to him!

If he could not get rid of heaven's will, he would be trapped inside qi sea's formation to prevent his location and identity from being exposed to heaven's will.

The pressure that was weighing down on Fang Yuan dissipated to some extent.

Now that he looked at the qi tide again, he felt that he had a deeper understanding of it.

"Qi tides are created because of the differences in heaven and earth qi. It is like how water flows down a cliff to create a waterfall. The qi tides are similar, because of the disappearance of the regional walls, with the unification of earth veins, the different heaven and earth qi of the five regions merge and cause qi tides to appear."

"In the future, when heaven and earth qi becomes the same in all five regions, there will no longer be any qi tides."

"As for the five regional walls? The truth is, they are all qi tides in essence."

The heaven and earth qi of the five regions were different, thus at the intersection points of these regions, there would be disparity in the heaven and earth qi. But because the earth veins were different back then, the heaven and earth qi could not fuse together like now, they eventually gathered and formed into dense regional walls.

Gu Immortals suffer backlash when using killer moves in the five regional walls, it was similar to being in the qi tides. The reason was that their own heaven and earth qi differed from those in the regional walls.

As for the five regional walls that Tao Zhu researched on for his entire life, they were simply just qi tides!

However, his research was focused on the aspect of rule path. His main result was five restriction profound light qi, from this name alone, it showed a connection to qi path.

Fang Yuan had Tao Zhu's true inheritance, he had half a portion of Primordial Origin's true inheritance, along with Qi Xiang's foundation and his own qi path attainment level, he had immense foundation, Fang Yuan quickly made some progress and obtained gains.

"Next, I will need to modify this formation slightly and scatter the sub-formations all over the aperture, I will send out qi tides to eliminate heaven's will."

"The problem of heaven's will has been settled, but the refinement of heaven path dao marks is still a huge problem."

But Fang Yuan had to put this problem aside for now, because he had to guard against Demon Immortal Qi Jue, who was coming for him.

The identity of Qi Sea Ancestor was very valuable. During the fate war, Fang Yuan tried his best to conceal it, he did not expose any clues that they were the same person.

In order to preserve his Qi Sea Ancestor identity, Fang Yuan's main obstacle now was Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

On one hand, Fang Yuan used the formation to settle his internal threat, on the other hand, he waited patiently for Demon Immortal Qi Jue to arrive.

According to Fang Yuan's deductions, Demon Immortal Qi Jue was going to come here for a fight during this period of time.

After waiting for some time, one day, a change occurred above qi sea.

White qi waves surged in the sky, they were grand and unceasing, pressing down on qi sea with immense force.

Within the qi waves, Demon Immortal Qi Jue's boyish figure could be vaguely seen, filled with demonic aura.

Soon, his young but confident voice resounded: "Junior Qi Sea, I, Demon Immortal Qi Jue, have come here for you."

"Qi Jue, what is the matter?" Fang Yuan appeared, activating qi sea's formation as he stood on the surface of the sea, looking up and speaking.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue chuckled: "I have just revived, I do not have my Immortal Gu now. I heard that you are the sole qi path great expert at the peak of rank eight, I have come here to borrow some Gu."

"Hahaha, borrow Gu indeed." Fang Yuan laughed loudly, he could feel the arrogance in Demon Immortal Qi Jue's words: "The Immortal Gu are with me, whether you can get them will depend on your abilities."

Demon Immortal Qi Jue laughed as his young face showed deep battle intent: "Good! Junior, I like your personality, face this move of mine."

Immortal killer move — Great Qi Grasp!

Instantly, a milky white qi current hand flew out like a small mountain, pressing down on Fang Yuan.

This was the move that made Di Zang Sheng cry out in pain, it was incredibly profound, able to scatter or take form, Gu Immortals could not deal with it easily.

Fang Yuan breathed in deeply, he had a calm expression that showed no anxiety. He extended his hand and he pushed forward.

Rumble!

A qi wall that was a hundred li long soared up into the sky, it was grand and magnificent.

The qi wall collided into the hand, the hand was forced to retreat, it could not stop the qi wall from flying up.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue smiled lightly, he pointed his finger as the qi current hand scattered, attempting to infiltrate the qi wall in the form of countless currents.

But the attempt failed to do anything.

Fang Yuan's qi wall was not only huge, it was densely packed, Demon Immortal Qi Jue had no way to penetrate it.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue's expression changed at this moment: "This is a powerful qi wall, what is the name of your move?"

Fang Yuan said frankly: "I created this move specially for you, Qi Jue, I have not named it yet. Do you have any good suggestions?"

Demon Immortal Qi Jue squinted uncontrollably as bright light shined in his eyes.

The fact that Qi Sea Ancestor had just created this move was scarier than him having this move for a long time. This meant that Qi Sea Ancestor had very high qi path attainment level, he could observe the battle situation and modify his own qi path killer move successfully to deal with his enemies!

Demon Immortal Qi Jue did not know that Fang Yuan was focused on modifying the five regional limit formation, this qi wall killer move was merely a small part of his effort.

Even though Fang Yuan lost wisdom Gu, he still had abundant wisdom path methods.

As the qi wall continued to rise into the sky, the milky white qi currents that filled the sky had to retreat further upwards.

By the time it reached Demon Immortal Qi Jue, the qi wall suddenly transformed, it turned into two hands, one black and one white, clapping together from the right and left directions.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue did not dodge, he allowed the black and white hands to grab him.

As the hands started to exert pressure, at the next moment, there was a loud voice coming from within the hands: "Xi—!"

Both hands were instantly absorbed into the silhouette of a concave secluded domain.

This time, it was Fang Yuan's turn to be shocked, he keenly sensed that the secluded domain of heaven and earth above Demon Immortal Qi Jue's head was more complete than the last time he saw it.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue knew that ordinary methods could not work against Qi Sea Ancestor, he directly used his trump card.

Secluded domain of heaven and earth — Xi.

Fang Yuan tried to use his methods, all sorts of qi path killer moves attacked Demon Immortal Qi Jue, but Xi Land would absorb them all. It was like a bottomless hole, Fang Yuan could not fill it up no matter what.

With Xi Land above his head, Demon Immortal Qi Jue had the advantage, he could not lose.

He even started to critique Fang Yuan's qi path killer moves casually.

"This pair of black and white hands is a nice concept, by including yin and yang qi, you can use the attraction force of the two to amplify the power of this move."

"Your qi path defenses are also quite impressive. Every single thread of your clothes is made of wind qi, are you trying to mimic the heavenly wind qi wall?"

"It is a true pity. If it were before, you would still be a threat to me. But regrettably, I have recently dismantled the turbulent flow sea area and also completely fixed Xi Land. With this, I can counter all qi path methods in the world, Junior Qi Sea, you are no exception!"

"How is it? May I borrow your Immortal Gu now?"

The reason why Demon Immortal Qi Jue gained his reputation was because of this, it countered all qi path methods in the world.

All qi path killer moves would be absorbed by Xi Land, unless the killer move could surpass the limits of Xi Land. But the problem was that Demon Immortal Qi Jue had already fully repaired Xi Land, it experienced a qualitative change in battle strength.

In a way, it was easier for him to deal with Qi Sea Ancestor than Wu Shuai, who controlled Dragon Palace.

Chapter 2004: Heavenly Court's Reinforcements

Turbulent white qi covered the sky above qi sea in a chaotic fashion.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue stared down at Qi Sea Ancestor while emitting a grand demonic aura. The phantom image of Xi Land appeared in its full glory above his head, placing him in a highly advantageous position.

"Junior Qi Sea, is my cultivation enough to borrow Gu from you?" Demon Immortal Qi Jue said again.

Fang Yuan felt heaviness.

The previous exchange of moves had already allowed him to understand many details about Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

There was no need to mention the various killer moves possessed by Demon Immortal Qi Jue, his trump card was clearly the secluded domain of heaven and earth, Xi Land. With this secluded domain of heaven and earth, he could counter all qi path Gu Immortals in the world.

If it were other paths, Demon Immortal Qi Jue would not have such huge dominance. But Qi Sea Ancestor's main cultivation happened to be qi path and was thus suppressed heavily.

This showed Demon Immortal Qi Jue's nature.

He might be domineering in his actions, but he was not stupid, he knew how to play to his advantage. Thus, after he revived, he did not continue fighting with the three sides and chose to retreat wisely. He then completed his Xi Land along the way and increased his battle strength. Now, he appeared in front of Qi Sea Ancestor and demanded to borrow Immortal Gu.

The moment he gains rank eight qi path Immortal Gu, his strength would definitely soar and firmly hold its position at the peak of the present age.

With just Qi Sea Ancestor's methods, Fang Yuan was indeed not Demon Immortal Qi Jue's match, but he was not panicked.

Fang Yuan always took action after planning first.

He had already known of Demon Immortal Qi Jue's threat and modified qi sea's formation. As long as he retreated into the formation, he would be able to resist for some time.

If Demon Immortal Qi Jue charged into the formation, Fang Yuan could detonate this large formation and create an opportunity to retreat.

Speaking of it, Fang Yuan had obtained this detonation method from Fang Di Chang. Back then, Fang Di Chang set a trap for Fang Yuan in Divine Bean Palace, he wanted to sacrifice wisdom path Gu Immortal Suan Bu Jin by detonating the Immortal Gu House inside Divine Bean Palace and thus break through the impasse and refine Divine Bean Palace in one move.

Fang Yuan saw through the scheme and captured Fang Di Chang. After soul searching, he obtained the method of Immortal Gu House self-detonation. He then modified the method and arranged it in qi sea's formation.

The self-detonation would be extremely powerful, even if it did not threaten Demon Immortal Qi Jue's life, it could obstruct him for a period of time.

Fang Yuan was very confident about this.

But...

If Fang Yuan used the formation's self-detonation to retreat, the value of this Qi Sea Ancestor identity would fall sharply.

To preserve this identity, Fang Yuan intentionally restrained himself from using many qi path methods during the fate war. Even unlimited qi sea was used just once.

Were Fang Yuan to retreat, it would mean Qi Sea Ancestor was defeated by Demon Immortal Qi Jue. From then on, Qi Sea Ancestor's reputation would fall greatly and his appeal to Eastern Sea would lower sharply.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue frowned slightly, he had spoken twice but Qi Sea Ancestor did not respond. His patience reached the limits.

He snorted and was about to continue attacking when a blood red ray of light suddenly pierced through the skies and shot right towards his face.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue dodged quickly and turned around to see Demon Judgment Board appear in the horizon.

"Heavenly Court, you again!" Demon Immortal Qi Jue sneered: "I am not looking for trouble with you but you are instead trying to provoke me. After such a heavy defeat in the fate war, what confidence do you have to act like this?"

"Heavenly Court defends humanity's righteous path, our actions are not because of confidence but because of our beliefs!" A reply came from inside Demon Judgment Board.

This was not Gu Yue Fang Zheng's voice, it was a female voice.

Fang Yuan's heart shook slightly when he heard the voice: "Qin Ding Ling came personally? So the reinforcement shown by my luck actually refers to her!"

Demon Immortal Qi Jue pointed his finger towards Demon Judgment Board.

Qi currents surged and transformed, rapidly gathering into a lump. In an instant, hundreds of milky white qi spheres shot towards Demon Judgment Board like meteors, creating a series of explosions.

Demon Judgment Board's momentum stopped and shook violently from the explosions.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue was about to say something when his expression changed suddenly. He quickly withdrew and moved away from his spot like lightning.

The previous blood red ray of light shot by Demon Judgment Board actually turned around to attack him.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue evaded the blood red light but he did not expect golden light to shoot out from this blood red light.

The golden light condensed rapidly into a huge golden scissors above Demon Immortal Qi Jue's head.

Crack, crack.

The golden scissors cut Demon Immortal Qi Jue's head repeatedly, but the attacks seemed to be in vain.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue, however, paled suddenly.

"This is a luck path method!"

He quickly activated investigative killer moves and immediately felt a loss: "Damn it, these golden scissors are cutting my luck!"

Demon Immortal Qi Jue put great emphasis on maintaining his luck, after his revival and later dismantling turbulent flow sea area to replenish Xi Land, he had already consumed a lot of his luck. The attacks of the giant scissors were making things worse.

"Qi Sea, Heavenly Court, I will remember this. If there is a chance in the future, I will settle it with both of you properly." Demon Immortal Qi Jue's voice resonated throughout the area.

After this sentence, he immediately entered milky white qi currents that filled the sky and left the battlefield rapidly.

"Retreating again?" Gu Yue Fang Zheng, who was inside Demon Judgment Board, was somewhat stunned.

On the contrary, other Heavenly Court members looked solemn.

Qin Ding Ling sighed and explained to Fang Zheng: "This is the terrifying thing about Demon Immortal Qi Jue. He always maintains his calm and has a clear judgment of the situation. We can only give him some trouble, but in the current situation, Qi Sea Ancestor would not just stay on the sidelines. With Demon Immortal Qi Jue's battle strength, it won't be difficult for him to oppose our joint attacks. But the battle will be intense and his plan to borrow qi path Immortal Gu has no chance to succeed. So he directly chose to retreat to preserve his strength."

Fang Zheng immediately realized: "I understand. Demon Immortal Qi Jue is a person from a million years ago after all, he has just revived and doesn't have much contact with new paths. Against Demon Judgment Board's blood path attack and your luck path golden scissors, he prioritized on dodging them. When he gets familiar with these paths and modifies his killer moves, it will be much more difficult for us to confront him."

"That is correct." Qin Ding Ling nodded: "Let's get out and have a talk with Qi Sea Ancestor."

Heavenly Court Gu Immortals filed out with Qin Ding Ling taking the lead and Gu Yue Fang Zheng following closely behind.

They put away Demon Judgment Board of their own initiative, demonstrating Heavenly Court's sincerity.

"Thank you for helping this old man get through this danger." Fang Yuan heaved a long sigh.

Qin Ding Ling was wearing a golden armor and a cape, and in combination with her tall body, wide shoulders and long legs, she emitted heroic aura. But this heroic aura was different from Feng Jin Huang's, it had a natural nobleness to it that felt like it was innately above others.

But right now, Qin Ding Ling had a smile on her face as she showed the initiative to get close to Fang Yuan.

She spoke: "Ancestor, if not for your injuries, how could Demon Immortal Qi Jue be so rampant? Moreover, I saw that you were calm throughout the battle, you definitely have some trump cards up your sleeves. We might even have to ask for your understanding and to not blame us for interfering."

These words were so polite that Fang Yuan felt like it was similar to a warm spring breeze.

Heavenly Court's attitude was different compared to his previous life. At that time, Heavenly Court was oppressive and gave no way out for others. But in this life, Heavenly Court's leader took the initiative to treat others warmly.

After the fate war, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals' attitude was completely different from before the war. Before the fate war, Heavenly Court had fate Gu and possessed huge advantages. But now that fate Gu was destroyed, Heavenly Court's strength had diminished sharply, on one hand, they were actively recuperating, while on the other hand, they took the initiative to make alliances.

Qi Sea Ancestor became a goal in Heavenly Court's eyes and was the best ally for them.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue wanted to find an expert to spar with, naturally, he would first look for Qi Sea Ancestor. After all, be they Fang Yuan or Feng Jiu Ge, their traces were vague and hard to find. However, Qi Sea Ancestor stayed in qi sea and could be found easily.

Since Heavenly Court wanted to ally with Qi Sea Ancestor, they naturally wanted to use Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

After all, adding icing on the cake cannot compare to offering help in times of need.

Heavenly Court helped Qi Sea Ancestor ward off Demon Immortal Qi Jue, it was not a casual action but was planned for a long time.

It was not only Fang Yuan who had been waiting patiently for Demon Immortal Qi Jue, Heavenly Court was also the same.

"Friends, please come in. Let this old man prepare a simple feast to express some gratitude." Fang Yuan led the Heavenly Court immortals into qi sea's formation.

He prepared a feast and hosted the Heavenly Court immortals.

During the banquet, the Xia clan immortals who were staying as guests were also invited to join.

The Xia clan immortals were grateful towards the Heavenly Court immortals, they had a very enthusiastic attitude.

They had seen Demon Immortal Qi Jue's fight with Qi Sea Ancestor, they felt very worried.

Their territory was already seized by Wu Shuai, so they could only put the hope of regaining their territory in Qi Sea Ancestor. If Qi Sea Ancestor was defeated or died, it would be a cruel blow to all the Xia clan members.

Thus, Heavenly Court helping Qi Sea Ancestor was like helping them.

When Qin Ding Ling saw the Xia clan immortals, she immediately expressed her sympathy and condemned the two heavens alliance. She even promised she would certainly fight against this large variant human alliance.

This attitude made Xia clan have an even better impression of them.

The face of Xia clan's first supreme elder even reddened with joy.

This was different from the empty words of the other Eastern Sea super forces, Heavenly Court had truly taken actions. Previously, Demon Judgment Board carried three immortals and attacked the two heavens' grotto-heavens, every Gu Immortal in the world knew of this.

Qin Ding Ling inquired about Xia clan's recent situation.

All the Xia clan Gu Immortals replied: They were hosted well by Qi Sea Ancestor and would always be grateful, it was just that they had a worry about when they could return to their home.

Qin Ding Ling realized Qi Sea Ancestor's intention.

"He is raising his reputation! His ambition is truly big."

Qin Ding Ling was happy to see this. As long as Qi Sea Ancestor had greed and ambition, they would have the foundation to cooperate.

Fang Yuan naturally did not invite the Xia clan Gu Immortals to join the banquet for no reason.

Through Qin Ding Ling's attitude towards the Xia clan Gu Immortals, Fang Yuan was even more certain of Heavenly Court's purpose in coming here. At the same time, he was also making this native force, Xia clan, serve as a witness. After all, as an Eastern Sea Gu Immortal, having close ties with Heavenly Court would lower Qi Sea Ancestor's authority in Eastern Sea.

After a few rounds of wine, Fang Yuan took the initiative to speak: "Friends from Heavenly Court, you helped me today, this old man shall remember this favor. If Heavenly Court has any trouble in the future, I am willing to contribute my strength to Heavenly Court."

This was a clear gesture.

Heavenly Court's immortals were spirited when they heard it.

Qin Ding Ling put down her cup slowly and looked at Qi Sea Ancestor with a smile as she finally got to the main topic: "To tell the truth, Heavenly Court is indeed facing some issues currently. We came to ask for Ancestor's help."

"Oh? Please explain." Fang Yuan asked straightforwardly.

Qin Ding Ling did not mention the matter of the qi harvest fruit emerging in Heavenly Court, instead she handed over an information path mortal Gu to Qi Sea Ancestor.

Fang Yuan probed with his consciousness and was immediately moved.

The content of this information path mortal Gu was the remaining half of Primordial Origin's true inheritance!

Chapter 2005: Cooperating with Heavenly Court

The moment Fang Yuan saw this remaining half of Primordial Origin's true inheritance, he had a thought, it was not related to the true inheritance.

"Should I use this chance to capture these Heavenly Court Gu Immortals in one fell swoop?"

This thought was very attractive.

Qin Ding Ling was currently the temporary leader of Heavenly Court, Heavenly Court would definitely receive a huge blow if they lost her. Gu Yue Fang Zheng was arranged by heaven's will and was a crucial character to restrain the otherworldly demon Fang Yuan. If Fang Yuan killed him, he would be free from this shackle. The accompanying Prince Feng Xian, Bai Cang Shui, and the rest were also pillars of Heavenly Court currently. If they were gone, it would be a great disaster to Heavenly Court and the whole of Central Continent's righteous path.

But thinking about it, Fang Yuan gave up on this idea.

His current strength was not complete and he could not maintain his battle strength because of the heaven path dao marks.

On the surface, the Heavenly Court immortals were conversing happily and looked relaxed, but how could they not be on guard in Qi Sea Ancestor's domain?

It was just that they pretended to be relaxed to show their sincerity and friendliness.

Even if Fang Yuan activated qi sea's formation, the Heavenly Court immortals would definitely take out Immortal Gu Houses immediately and defend.

Were he to attack the Heavenly Court immortals right now, whether it resulted in victory or defeat, Fang Yuan's Qi Sea Ancestor identity would be met with heavy scrutiny.

In truth, Fang Yuan was willing to cooperate with Heavenly Court.

Even though Heavenly Court tried all methods to create difficulties for Fang Yuan and attempted to kill him, even forcing him into near death situations, as long as there were enough benefits that were useful for him in pursuing eternal life, Fang Yuan was not conflicted over cooperating with Heavenly Court.

Heavenly Court wanted to cooperate with Qi Sea Ancestor for their own benefits.

Fang Yuan would also similarly receive huge gains from cooperating with Heavenly Court.

There was no need to mention the long term benefits, merely Fang Yuan forcing back Demon Immortal Qi Jue with the help of Heavenly Court was enough to guarantee the value of this Qi Sea Ancestor identity. At the same time, Heavenly Court also took the initiative to give the remaining half of Primordial Origin's true inheritance to him!

Fang Yuan was rather moved as he held the information path mortal Gu.

Back then, he had spent much thought and effort to scheme for this qi path true inheritance. Duke Long was shrewd, Thieving Heaven's method could reduce his lifespan but he pretended it did not work and used half of Primordial Origin's true inheritance to successfully stabilize Qi Sea Ancestor.

The remaining half was held firmly by Duke Long and Fang Yuan was unable to get it.

Fang Yuan did not hold any hope but who could have thought that after the fate war, he would actually obtain the remaining half of Primordial Origin's true inheritance through Qin Ding Ling.

In the remaining half of Primordial Origin's true inheritance, the triple qi retraction Fang Yuan coveted was recorded.

"Qin Ding Ling cannot be underestimated." Fang Yuan sighed in his head.

Without even mentioning any requests, Qin Ding Ling directly handed the remaining half of Primordial Origin's true inheritance to Qi Sea Ancestor, the courage needed for this move was truly immense. Qin Ding Ling's and Heavenly Court's sincerity was shown fully.

"If Qin Ding Ling knew I was Fang Yuan, I wonder what expression she would show?"

Duke Long helped the enemy previously and now Qin Ding Ling continued this trend. Were Qin Ding Ling to know the person in front of her was the greatest culprit of the fate war and she had personally handed the true inheritance to him, she might cough blood from anger.

"I genuinely feel your sincerity. What troubles do you have, I will use all my strength to help Heavenly Court!" Fang Yuan stored the information path mortal Gu in his aperture, he already guessed Heavenly Court's troubles.

Qin Ding Ling let out a sigh of relief as she saw Qi Sea Ancestor putting away the information path mortal Gu.

What she had been worried about was that possibility of Qi Sea Ancestor not agreeing to help. After all, Qi Sea Ancestor had been a secluded cultivator who did not care about things that did not concern him. Maybe the information given by the reborn Fang Yuan made Qi Sea Ancestor realize that if he were to continue his secluded cultivation, Heavenly Court would look for trouble with him, so he changed his way of doing things.

Qin Ding Ling did not know how Heavenly Court became enemies with Qi Sea Ancestor. But since Qi Sea Ancestor believed Fang Yuan's words, it was clear Fang Yuan had provided enough evidence.

This was a mess that they were not responsible for, with the destruction of fate Gu, the future had changed, Heavenly Court was unable to find out anything about it. Qin Ding Ling could only rely on the current situation to infer and deduce.

It was normal for Qin Ding Ling to have some worries.

After all, Qi Sea Ancestor had a hostile relationship with Heavenly Court before and had only turned neutral because of Duke Long's mediation. Right now, to recruit Qi Sea Ancestor, Qin Ding Ling had to take out something that Qi Sea Ancestor would not be able to refuse.

Qi Sea Ancestor accepted Primordial Origin's true inheritance and immediately showed a firm attitude of helping Heavenly Court.

Qin Ding Ling was very relieved. Her scheme did not end here. Primordial Origin's true inheritance was only bait, Qi Sea Ancestor would require suitable qi path Immortal Gu to activate the killer moves recorded in it.

And these qi path Immortal Gu were all in Heavenly Court's treasuries.

These were the chips to tempt Qi Sea Ancestor later on.

"Perhaps we can still use Demon Immortal Qi Jue's pressure to push Qi Sea Ancestor to join Heavenly Court." This inspiration emerged in Qin Ding Ling's mind but was temporarily suppressed.

She began to explain the issues Heavenly Court was facing.

Fang Yuan stroked his beard as he ascertained his guesses. Just like he predicted, the qi harvest fruit appeared in Heavenly Court as well.

With Duke Long's sacrifice and the immortal graveyard's destruction, Heavenly Court no longer had a qi path expert to stabilize the situation, thus it was very difficult for them to resolve the issue of the qi harvest fruit.

Qin Ding Ling handed Primordial Origin's true inheritance straightforwardly and also hoped this true inheritance could help Qi Sea Ancestor in dealing with the issue of the qi harvest fruit much more quickly.

Fang Yuan thought for a bit and nodded: "I will handle this matter of the qi harvest fruit. But I have no methods to deal with it now and need to be in closed cultivation for some time to research Primordial Origin's true inheritance."

At this moment, Xia clan's first supreme elder suddenly said: "Lord Ancestor, you are injured and have to recuperate first. Your safety not only concerns Eastern Sea but is also related to maintaining the overall situation of humanity and the variant humans."

He was worried and afraid that if Qi Sea Ancestor were to collaborate with Heavenly Court, Xia clan's matters would be pushed aside.

Qin Ding Ling smiled: "You don't have to worry, I am going to talk about the two heavens alliance now. Wu Shuai is currently a huge demon and also a sinner who invaded Heavenly Court, we absolutely won't let him develop. We came here to ask for Ancestor's help as well as to deal with this variant human force."

After a slight pause, she continued: "Heavenly Court is willing to take out immortal materials to finance Ancestor and Xia clan, to help you reclaim your lost land. In the future battles, if necessary, Heavenly Court will send reinforcements to lend a hand in fighting against the variant human races."

"Ah!" Xia clan's first supreme elder exclaimed in shock and bowed: "Heavenly Court is righteous and worthy of being the number one force of humanity. I am extremely grateful, the whole of Xia clan is immeasurably grateful!"

Qin Ding Ling chatted with Xia clan's first supreme elder for a while, deepening their relationship quickly.

Heavenly Court lost the fate war but it did not lack resources, it only lacked manpower.

In this trip to Eastern Sea, Heavenly Court wanted to entice Qi Sea Ancestor while also targeting Xia clan's Gu Immortals. Roping in a native force of Eastern Sea would establish their foundation in the future five regions chaotic war.

This was a long-term plan.

The unfortunate thing was that Heavenly Court and Xia clan's immortals did not know Wu Shuai and Qi Sea Ancestor were the same person in essence. This was truly a huge secret that would shock the world.

Fang Yuan nodded without hesitating: "I will never let the two heavens alliance exist in Eastern Sea, I will certainly drive them out and exterminate them thoroughly!"

Qin Ding Ling raised her hand: "In my view, the two heavens alliance has human forces as well, it is just that the two heavens alliance is being firmly controlled by variant humans currently. These human forces are not different from us, we are all humans. We should stick together and unite. So, there is no harm in splitting them first before we take action."

Fang Yuan immediately understood the meaning: "Could it be that some human forces in the two heavens alliance have already surrendered to you?"

Qin Ding Ling shook her head: "It is not like that. We were able to capture a rank eight Gu Immortal. She is called Granny Skeleton, the current owner of Shattered Bone grotto-heaven in the two heavens."

Granny Skeleton was persuaded by An Chong's words and wanted to join the two heavens alliance. But halfway in her journey, she was ambushed and captured by Heavenly Court.

Naturally, it was Night Heavenly Wolf Lord who provided this information.

Lady Cold Ash wanted to unite the human forces in the two heavens and fight for authority in the two heavens alliance. She had already made Night Heavenly Wolf Lord one of her helpers, but she could have never expected Night Heavenly Wolf Lord to have already sided with Heavenly Court.

"Granny Skeleton?" Fang Yuan paused a bit before asking: "Is this person here right now?"

Qin Ding Ling shook her head: "My Heavenly Court uses virtuous means, we let her go after persuading her for some time."

The eyes of Xia clan's first supreme elder opened wide at these words, he felt some worries regarding Heavenly Court's 'naivety' but did not speak up.

Fang Yuan, however, looked at Qin Ding Ling with deep meaning and smiled: "Looks like Granny Skeleton is a crucial character and the key to tempt her to join us should lie on the qi harvest fruit's matter."

Qin Ding Ling laughed and raised her cup in praise: "Ancestor, you have discerning vision. The issue of the qi harvest fruit appeared in Shattered Bone grotto-heaven as well, if we can solve this issue, we can rope in Granny Skeleton and other human forces."

"Good plan!"

"If we can rope in these human forces, it would be their loss and our gain, this will be a great blow to the two heavens alliance, and there is even a chance they will disintegrate."

"Those of other races have different motives, the human Gu Immortals in the two heavens are of the same race as us. As long as we show enthusiasm and sincerity, it should not be difficult to recruit them."

Xia clan's immortals smiled and conversed, some clapped and laughed, the atmosphere of the banquet became increasingly lively.

Fang Yuan had a smile as he observed the Gu Immortals' expressions from his seat.

If they knew their enemy had already known of their plan before they even implemented it, how would they feel?

Fang Yuan's gaze moved around before finally stopping on Qin Ding Ling's face.

"Although she only cultivates luck path, her leadership is up to standard."

"At her level, she should have reached the level of being proficient in mimicking other paths too. Ordinary wisdom path rank eights are also not superior to this."

'Of course, there is still a large gap between her and Fairy Zi Wei.'

Chapter 2006: Shadow Sect's True Members

Central Continent.

"This qi harvest fruit is mine!"

"Get lost."

"You wish."

The qi tide had just passed, a group of Central Continent lone immortals was fighting fiercely for around ten qi harvest fruits.

To grotto-heavens, the qi harvest fruits that emerged inside them were a huge calamity. But the qi harvest fruits that were left behind after the qi tides were precious treasures coveted by every Gu Immortal.

It had already been a while since qi tides appeared, the five regions' Gu Immortals were fully aware of the excellent effect of the qi harvest fruit.

Gu Immortals did not need any qi path attainment, as long as they obtained qi harvest fruits and crushed them in their aperture, they could greatly improve the harmonization of heaven and earth qi. Thereby, gaining freedom of action earlier than other Gu Immortals.

Just as the immortals were fighting, a snowy ray of light pierced through the skies, shooting towards them.

The ray of light was sharp and fierce, shooting right towards a Gu Immortal.

This Central Continent Gu Immortal was only rank six, he sneered when he saw that the ray of light looked fierce but only had rank six aura, he activated his defensive killer moves.

Bam.

The ray of light struck the Gu Immortal and pierced through him.

"How?!" The struck Gu Immortal's eyes were wide open, his expression filled with disbelief.

Both sides were rank six, so why was there such a huge gap!

"Who is it?"

"Ah, could it be Snow Demon!"

The remaining two Central Continent Gu Immortals were also rank six. They were pale with fright when they saw the Gu Immortal whom they had been fighting at a deadlock with die immediately.

The two immediately thought of a mysterious demonic immortal who had emerged recently, this person appeared often to fight for qi harvest fruits and was very vicious.

The two retreated quickly, not daring to fight.

That snow ray of light ignored them and moved straight towards its goal, looting the qi harvest fruits.

After the snow ray obtained them, it left immediately with extreme vigilance.

After moving for a few minutes and using various concealment methods, this snow ray of light stopped in a nameless valley.

The snow dissipated and the Gu Immortal's appearance was revealed, who else could it be but Bai Ning Bing?

After the fate war, Bai Ning Bing was left outside and was not recalled by Fang Yuan.

Bai Ning Bing temporarily obtained freedom and did not want to return to Fang Yuan's side, choosing to cultivate alone. Over this period of time, she was extremely active and had seized many qi harvest fruits, using them in her immortal aperture.

These qi harvest fruits she obtained would have negligible effects on Fang Yuan's rank eight grotto-heaven. But to Bai Ning Bing's rank six blessed land, the effects were conspicuous.

Bai Ning Bing originally possessed future self and could achieve peak rank seven battle strength. But after the fate war, the lower streams of the River of Time became violent, future self thus lost its effect, Bai Ning Bing's battle strength returned to its original rank six level.

"After I get a few hundred more qi harvest fruits, I can battle with all my strength for two hours." Bai Ning Bing used the seized qi harvest fruits while estimating inwardly.

Suddenly, her heart jolted as she sensed something wrong, she immediately shot out of the valley.

But it was already late.

A purple light barrier trapped her rapidly, directly creating an independent space that was isolated from the outside world.

"This is an immortal battlefield killer move!" Bai Ning Bing frowned: "Who is it, come out!"

Clap clap clap.

Following resounding claps, Fairy Zi Wei revealed herself.

She looked at Bai Ning Bing with a smile: "You actually sensed me activating this battlefield killer move. Worthy of a genius chosen by Fang Yuan."

"It's you!" Bai Ning Bing immediately recognized Fairy Zi Wei and her heart sank.

The enemy was a rank eight Gu Immortal, while her strength was only at rank six. She might still have some hope to resist if she had future self, but the current difference in strength was too big, it made her helpless.

Fairy Zi Wei fixed her eyes on Bai Ning Bing, asking with interest: "How did you sense it? I did not see you using any special investigative methods."

Bai Ning Bing's expression was cold as ice as she replied: "It was only an instinct. You already put an ambush beforehand and waited for me to take the bait?"

Fairy Zi Wei chuckled: "You took action too many times recently, the clues are all with me, so it is not a difficult thing to deduce when you will make a move and where you will retreat to. Did you actually discover the danger with only your intuition? My immortal battlefield killer move did not leak any aura when it was activated."

At this time, another figure appeared not far behind Bai Ning Bing, it was Old Man Zheng Yuan.

Old Man Zheng Yuan coughed: "Lady Zi Wei, this is caused by human qi. Although Bai Ning Bing did not use any special investigative method, she has robust human qi. We must have agitated her human qi when we tried to trap her, which made her sense it intuitively."

Bai Ning Bing snorted and took on a combat stance: "You talk too much, let's fight, Heavenly Court!"

Fairy Zi Wei's smile became even brighter: "You are wrong, Bai Ning Bing, we are not representing Heavenly Court, but Shadow Sect. We did not come to kill you."

"What?" Bai Ning Bing was astonished: "You sided with Fang Yuan?!"

Old Man Zheng Yuan chuckled: "This junior Fang Yuan stole the position of Shadow Sect's leader. We are representing the true Shadow Sect!"

Bai Ning Bing's mind shook as she guessed the truth: "Spectral Soul has revived? You want to find trouble with Fang Yuan through me!"

"What do you think? Join us, don't you want to get rid of Fang Yuan and free yourself from all the shackles?" Fairy Zi Wei enticed.

Bai Ning Bing sneered and stared deeply at Fairy Zi Wei: "Of course I want freedom. But what is the difference between joining you and siding with Fang Yuan? I will be even more restricted with you people than with Fang Yuan!"

She noticed what was wrong with Fairy Zi Wei and Old Man Zheng Yuan, they were clearly enslaved by Spectral Soul.

Standing with Fang Yuan, Bai Ning Bing had the feeling of being an ally at least. But if she joined the Shadow Sect in front of her, then she would only be Spectral Soul's slave.

Fairy Zi Wei nodded: "But you don't have a choice, do you?"

Old Man Zheng Yuan added: "Surrender or die, choose."

Bai Ning Bing's silence did not last long, after a few breaths of time, she nodded: "I will join you."

Old Man Zheng Yuan approached and patted Bai Ning Bing's shoulder: "This is a wise choice. Relax, we will deal with your information path alliance agreements. But your dragonman status is somewhat troublesome, it was Fang Yuan who helped you change that. The dragonman method he used probably went through many changes, it will be very difficult to get rid of this within a short period of time."

"No worries, I am already used to it." Bai Ning Bing said indifferently.

She was restricted by Fang Yuan first, then she entered Shadow Sect and was controlled by Old Man Yan Shi; later, she returned to Fang Yuan's side again, transforming into the new dragonman. Now, she was clamped down by Fairy Zi Wei.

Bai Ning Bing was right, she was already used to it.

Almost at the same time, Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven.

"Aunt, this is the soul core I obtained recently, it is extremely strange, please appraise it." An Xun respectfully bowed and handed over a soul core.

Lady Cold Ash took this soul core and observed it carefully, her expression becoming increasingly strange.

She had seen countless soul cores, but this soul core gave her a feeling which she had never felt before. Just the dark light circulating on the soul core's surface was beyond ordinary.

Suddenly!

The soul core transformed into dark lightning that struck Lady Cold Ash's face, it quickly infiltrated her body and imprisoned her soul.

Lady Cold Ash's body was tense, and when she reacted, she had already fallen to her own relative's trap.

"An Xun, you!" Lady Cold Ash had been concerned with her nephew An Xun and nurtured him wholeheartedly, she had never expected to be betrayed.

Lady Cold Ash struggled before she stood up abruptly.

An Xun was given a great fright as he stepped back quickly.

But at the next moment, Lady Cold Ash's energy dissipated and sat down again.

She groaned as dark light filled her eyes.

Soon, she could not struggle anymore and stood up silently.

An Xun prostrated on the ground: "Subordinate pays respect to master."

Spectral Soul's voice came out from Lady Cold Ash's mouth: "This body is quite good, I shall use this for now to get close to Wu Shuai."

Spectral Soul did not have guts Gu, so he could only devour soul cores and digest them slowly.

Over this period of time, he had already recovered some strength and immediately made a move on Lady Cold Ash.

After he had succeeded, it meant the whole of Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven had fallen into his hands!

Chapter 2007: Target — Profound Literature Grotto-heaven

Roar—!

A huge, mountain-like immemorial soul beast with two horns on its head was howling.

But it was not showing its might and dominance, but madly struggling to flee.

Its tail was grabbed by an ordinary hand.

Then, an extremely terrifying absorption force spread out from the palm. There was a whirring sound resembling a wild hurricane as the immemorial soul beast was absorbed completely by the hand within a few breaths of time.

The owner of that hand let out a burp.

It was the rank eight soul path expert, owner of Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven — Lady Cold Ash.

Her eyes were pitch-black and threads of black smoke coiled around her body. After a while, she stopped the killer move, the black smoke around her whole body were restrained, and nothing looked out of place from the outside.

But in fact, her body was already possessed by Spectral Soul and her soul had been devoured.

Spectral Soul sighed: "I am full again."

He got much more freedom with Lady Cold Ash's identity. Over these days, he was actively devouring immemorial soul beasts, increasing and recovering his strength rapidly.

But Spectral Soul was not satisfied.

Devouring immemorial soul beasts was not like consuming guts Gu after all, Spectral Soul needed to digest them. Otherwise, the immemorial soul beasts would corrode his soul, make him lose his rationality and finally turn into a deformed soul monster.

The first choice in strengthening the soul was of course the guts Gu from Dang Hun Mountain, there was no need to digest them and they could be absorbed almost instantly.

The more Spectral Soul yearned for Dang Hun Mountain, the more he wanted to find Fang Yuan and kill him!

"Where exactly did this rascal Fang Yuan go to?" Spectral Soul thought of Fang Yuan and could not help but narrow his eyes.

Fairy Zi Wei had already informed Spectral Soul of the information she had gained from Bai Ning Bing.

This was great news to Spectral Soul.

Fairy Zi Wei had found clues of Ying Wu Xie, as long as they got hold of Fang Yuan's subordinates, they would have enough clues to deduce Fang Yuan's location.

"Fang Yuan obtained so many heaven path dao marks and has been missing since the fate war, his situation must be dismal. This is the best chance to capture him."

Spectral Soul had been a venerable, he queried himself and got the conclusion that even when he was at his peak, it would have been a difficult task to refine so many heaven path dao marks. Let alone the current Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was strong, but he was not a venerable after all and had a limited understanding of the heaven path dao marks.

"But I can no longer count on the arrangements I left in the sovereign immortal aperture."

Spectral Soul understood that heaven path dao marks developed naturally, the hidden arrangements he left behind were essentially dao marks and were certain to be transformed by the heaven path dao marks.

His methods would not be effective after they were transformed.

If they were effective, why would Spectral Soul have to go through such trouble to search and capture Fang Yuan's subordinates, he would have already gone to kill Fang Yuan.

"After half a month, I can devour an immemorial soul beast again to recover my strength... hmm?" Just as Spectral Soul was planning, he suddenly received a message.

Spectral Soul immediately revealed joy: "Wu Shuai is convening rank eight Gu Immortals of the two heavens alliance to discuss an important event, Lady Cold Ash is also summoned. Great, Wu Shuai is acquainted with Fang Yuan, he might even be Fang Yuan's clone. I might be able to lure out Fang Yuan's main body if I enslave him."

Spectral Soul immediately moved out of Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven under Lady Cold Ash's identity and rushed towards the headquarters of Eastern Sea's Xia clan.

In the public blessed land, he smoothly entered Dragon Palace and saw Wu Shuai.

Wu Shuai was sitting on the main seat while the other people were divided into two rows. On his immediate left was vice alliance leader Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch; on his right was the recent addition, rank eight expert Xiao He Jian.

Below them were leaders of various variant human forces.

The human grotto-heaven owners were arranged further back. For instance, Lady Cold Ash's position was almost close to Dragon Palace's door.

The political state of the two heavens alliance was clear from these seating arrangements. Variant humans were dominant and had most of the authority, while human Gu Immortals were firmly at a disadvantage. It was not that they did not resist, but they were helpless. After all, Wu Shuai had a dragonman identity and it was natural for him to be closer to other variant humans.

'If I kill all of them, how much of my strength can I recover?' Spectral Soul looked around with killing intent surging in his heart.

Sensing her gaze, Night Heavenly Wolf Lord who was standing opposite her nodded slightly, showing goodwill.

Spectral Soul had already obtained all of Lady Cold Ash's memories: "This Night Heavenly Wolf Lord, maybe I can make a move against him first. This human rank eight Gu Immortal's soul is much more suitable for my recovery."

Night Heavenly Wolf Lord thought: "This Lady Cold Ash can be used. My contribution regarding Granny Skeleton came from her. After this discussion, I should find her to drink tea and probe her intention. If I can rope her into Heavenly Court's side, my contribution will be even bigger."

Night Heavenly Wolf Lord's thoughts were normal.

In his opinion, the previous Lady Cold Ash did not lose hope and wanted to unite other human forces to counter the current alliance situation, raising the human forces' position in the alliance. But right now, her plan was already useless, Granny Skeleton did not come at all. And with Heavenly Court already proceeding to the next plan, that was, to split up the whole two heavens alliance, Night Heavenly Wolf Lord saw his chance to make much more contributions!

Just as Night Heavenly Wolf Lord and Lady Cold Ash were scheming, Wu Shuai spoke: "I think you should all know why I convened everyone this time. That's right, it is about the qi harvest fruit disaster."

"Qi harvest fruits have appeared in most of your grotto-heavens. These qi harvest fruits absorb the heaven and earth qi in the grotto-heaven to strengthen themselves, directly harming the grotto-heaven's foundation. But ordinary methods cannot get rid of these qi harvest fruits, a rash move will only harm the grotto-heaven's foundation."

"Today, I gathered everyone to try to collectively think of a good solution."

After Wu Shuai spoke, the immortals began to offer their suggestions.

Over this period of time, most of them had racked their minds and were completely focused on this problem.

These immortals might lack combat proficiency, but their foundations were instead stable and solid. Thus, they suggested many methods.

However, although there were many methods suggested, which were truly effective?

No one could guarantee or be certain!

None of them cultivated qi path as their main path, there were a few who cultivated qi path on the side but their attainment was low and could not be counted upon.

"There are many methods, let's try them one by one, there should be a way to resolve this issue. So, what we need to do is to try these methods continuously. Who is willing to try it first?" Wu Shuai summarized and asked.

Dragon Palace immediately fell into silence.

No one wanted to be the guinea pig!

It was extremely crucial to clear up the qi harvest fruits. It was like a heart surgery, a slight mistake and it would be the end of the grotto-heaven. Even if they were fortunate and the grotto-heaven survived, its foundation would be heavily damaged and there would be massive losses.

"These Gu Immortals are really pitiful, fortunately I have already sided with Heavenly Court." Although Night Heavenly Wolf Lord showed a worried expression, he was calm.

He had been informed by Heavenly Court that they had already found the solution to the qi harvest fruit issue. So he was not the least bit worried.

But in fact, Qin Ding Ling only said that to stabilize Night Heavenly Wolf Lord and make him more loyal.

"It is both hard and easy to resolve the qi harvest fruit." Spectral Soul naturally knew some methods but he did not mention them.

His current thoughts were filled with how to attack Wu Shuai.

He could not make a move now with so many people present.

But how could he find a chance to be alone with Wu Shuai?

"The biggest obstacle is still this Dragon Palace." Spectral Soul was somewhat wary. Dragon Palace, in essence, was an enslavement path Immortal Gu House, Spectral Soul was not afraid about this. What he was worried about were the dream path methods of Dragon Palace.

Even Spectral Soul had to be vigilant regarding this, once he was captured by dreamy light smoke, he would immediately be defeated.

Wu Shuai saw the immortals becoming silent for a long while, he already knew their thoughts.

He smiled: "Since no one is willing to give it a try, we should find other people to try. There are many grotto-heavens in the two heavens, there are still people who have not joined us and are harboring unfathomable thoughts."

The Gu Immortals' eyes brightened, they felt the alliance leader's idea was simply too great!

Thereupon, the immortals resounded in agreement, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and others even boot-licked Wu Shuai.

"Which grotto-heaven do you think is suitable?" Wu Shuai asked.

At the next moment, various opinions emerged and a large number of targets were mentioned.

The one which was mentioned the most was Profound Literature grotto-heaven!

Old Immortal Hua Yu was a human with powerful strength as well as high prestige that allowed him to influence many of the surrounding grotto-heaven forces. If Wu Shuai could get rid of him and incorporate Profound Literature grotto-heaven into the two heavens alliance, there would be countless benefits.

Chapter 2008: All Destroyed!

Profound Literature grotto-heaven.

"Xiao Bai, here will do." In the small path between mountains, Teacher Jiang stopped and spoke to Li Xiao Bai.

Li Xiao Bai showed sadness and reluctance: "I was able to survive in the capital city all thanks to teacher's guidance and help. I will engrave this kindness in my heart and never forget it. But after this separation, I wonder when I can see teacher again!"

"You." Teacher Jiang sighed and patted Li Xiao Bai's shoulder, encouraging him: "Although you lost in this world poetry competition, your poems have already spread far and wide. Everyone knows your talent is worthy of the title of a great scholar. Moreover, Su Qi Han has already returned, the capital city is the arena for you to display your talents. Go back, teacher will look forward to your performance."

Li Xiao Bai bid farewell to Teacher Jiang with eyes full of tears.

Li Xiao Bai rode a horse through the mountain path that was covered with trees while pondering about his future.

He lost in the world poetry competition, although his earlier performances were exceptional.

Like he had expected, he ran into Teacher Jiang in the later stage. This made Li Xiao Bai fall into an awkward situation — if he won against his teacher, his morals and character would be criticized and there would definitely be a tide of hateful remarks.

Li Xiao Bai had wanted to use his next chance to continue passing through the stages. But he kept on running into his teacher again and again.

Teacher Jiang was also helpless, in fact, he also did not want to succeed by stepping on his own student. But he had to grab onto every chance because he had also probed the biggest meaning behind the world poetry competition.

Li Xiao Bai ran into Teacher Jiang time and again, his hands were tied and he eventually lost the competition.

Although he felt pity about this, Li Xiao Bai felt thankful as well: "My previous performances were too exceptional and even excessive. If I were to succeed like this, there would definitely be a detailed investigation done on me. Even if I passed the investigation, because I don't have a good background and am not a renowned person, I am very likely to be schemed against. Many people are coveting this opportunity to become an immortal, how could they let it fall into a minor character's hand?"

The world poetry competition's selections looked extremely fair, but in fact, where there were people, there would be conflicts of interests and many deals going on behind the scenes.

Just look at the list of candidates that passed the world poetry competition's selection, they were either influential officials or renowned people, even the so-called dark horses have extraordinary roots and background.

"It doesn't matter that I am not selected in this world poetry competition, there will be a second selection in the future."

"Even if there is no second world poetry competition, don't tell me I cannot become an immortal by relying on myself?"

"Hmm, what smell is this, it is so fragrant!"

Just as Li Xiao Bai was thinking, a delicate fragrance broke his train of thoughts.

This fragrance was really pleasing and smelled like the inky fragrance of a book.

Li Xiao Bai was immediately curious, how could there be such a fragrance in this mountain's forest?

He rode the horse and followed the fragrance to its source.

After riding for a while, dense bush blocked the path ahead, Li Xiao Bai had no choice but to get off the horse and continue on his feet.

The fragrance became increasingly strong as Li Xiao Bai moved deep into the forest, he knew he was going in the right direction and was getting closer to the source of the fragrance.

Finally, he brushed aside some leaves and found a pine tree.

This pine tree was covered with pine cones and these pine cones were releasing the dense book fragrance. And on the branch of the tree, there was an exquisite and unique brown tree-house.

"Is someone living here? A mountain hermit?" Li Xiao Bai carefully approached and called out: "I am Student Li Xiao Bai, I accidentally passed through here and took the liberty to pay a visit. Please don't blame me, sage in the mountain."

But there was no sound from the treehouse.

Li Xiao Bai called out several times but there was still no reply. Seeing that there seemed to be no one in the treehouse, he walked towards the pine tree.

When he reached the pine tree, Li Xiao Bai made another discovery. The treehouse was not constructed on the tree, but was integrated into the tree, like it had directly grown from the tree.

Li Xiao Bai wanted to enter the treehouse to probe, but after circling around the tree, he found that the treehouse was completely integrated, with only windows but no doors.

"What do I do?" Li Xiao Bai thought and subconsciously placed his hand on the tree trunk.

Suddenly, the bark let out crisp sounds as it transformed. In an instant, a spiral staircase appeared around the tree trunk that moved towards the treehouse.

And a door appeared on the treehouse as well.

Li Xiao Bai only hesitated for a bit before stepping on the stairs and walking to the treehouse.

There were three rows of bookcases in the treehouse that were standing against the three walls. In the compartments of the bookcases were many Gu worms.

"Book fragrance spreads, talented scholars smell. Book house inheritance shall be left to the fated." At this time, information was transmitted to Li Xiao Bai's mind.

Li Xiao Bai inspected it and felt joyous.

"So this is an information path inheritance."

"Although it is only a Gu Master inheritance with no Immortal Gu, there are various rank four and many rank five Gu worms. There is also detailed cultivation instruction, forming a complete system which suits me."

"Speaking of which, my luck has been improving recently. Looks like my main body has already stabilized the situation."

This inheritance was a peak level Gu Master inheritance, not only did it have many Gu worms, the pine tree itself was an exceptional mortal Gu House — Book House.

Li Xiao Bai stored Book House and returned back the way he came. He smoothly found his horse and hurried back to the capital city.

At the peak of the mountain, two figures were standing.

One immortal and one mortal.

The immortal was Hua Song, the mortal was rank five Gu Master Teacher Jiang.

Teacher Jiang had witnessed the whole process of Li Xiao Bai obtaining the inheritance and was extremely grateful: "Teacher, many thanks for helping my student."

It turned out that Teacher Jiang's teacher was Hua Song.

Hua Song smiled: "He is your student, according to the relationship, he is my grand-disciple. He belongs to our faction, how can I ignore him? When the world poetry competition started, I already noticed him. He clearly had the strength to pass the stages, but because he ran into you, he chose to limit himself. I had been hoping for you two, teacher and disciple, to succeed in passing the competition, but his luck seems to be quite bad, he ran into you again and again during the crucial rounds and was finally eliminated."

"I am at fault." Teacher Jiang lowered his head.

"Hahaha." Hua Song patted Teacher Jiang's shoulder: "You are really outstanding for being able to teach such a superb student. If this Li Xiao Bai had disregarded his teacher for fame and defeated you in front of everyone, I would have punished this kid severely. But he prioritizes this teacher and student relationship, his character is excellent. Although he failed this time, there is no harm in it."

"It is this child's fortune to be noticed by teacher. Just that, teacher, why didn't you…." Teacher Jiang hesitated.

Hua Song sighed: "Although I am the host of the world poetry competition, if I were to act in favor of my personal gain, I would be criticized by other Gu Immortals and lose my reputation in front of Old Lord Hua Yu."

"Moreover, Li Xiao Bai is still too young, he lacks tempering. If he suddenly became an immortal, it might lead to misfortune because of this good fortune. He should still continue to accumulate experience in the mortal world, a jade stone is useless if it is not polished."

"Teacher is right, I was thinking too simplistically." Teacher Jiang wholeheartedly admired his teacher and said excitedly: "I understand teacher's effort. Teacher, you don't want me to bear the feeling of guilt, so you gave Li Xiao Bai such a great inheritance, right?"

"It is good that you know that." Hua Song smiled: "You are my student, you were selected this time and will be nurtured to become an immortal. You must concentrate wholeheartedly and not split your attention because of other matters. Concentrate on cultivation, don't ruin my reputation."

"Yes, teacher, I will definitely use all my strength!" Teacher Jiang cupped his hands and bowed solemnly.

Although Profound Literature grotto-heaven maintained neutrality and was not willing to participate in any fights, they understood chaotic times were coming so they did not hold back in cultivating Gu Immortals.

Teacher Jiang and others were handled and given plenty of resources with many Gu Immortals guiding them personally.

Teacher Jiang studied and practised hard everyday, using his time to the fullest.

Despite him using all his strength to study, his performance was still at low to mid level. This showed the talents of this batch's Gu Masters.

Even the teaching Gu Immortals were secretly pleased. This batch was indeed full of the elites of Profound Literature grotto-heaven and everyone was an excellent Gu Immortal seed.

Over half a month passed, Teacher Jiang and the rest welcomed the most crucial moment of their lives — immortal ascension.

"With several teachers protecting us, the success rate of immortal ascension is high. Once I become an immortal, my future will undergo a complete transformation and elevation!"

Teacher Jiang was looking forward to it and studied with even more effort.

However, just as the first among them was about to undergo tribulation, there was an explosion and the whole of Profound Literature grotto-heaven shook fiercely.

Following the explosion, an Evil Dragon with the length of mountain ranges descended, filling the sky of Profound Literature grotto-heaven.

Large numbers of enemy Gu Immortals appeared in all areas of Profound Literature grotto-heaven and attacked at the same time. The flames of war burned everywhere.

The place where Teacher Jiang's group was in was given considerable attention.

"Die!" Wu Shuai controlled Dragon Palace and slammed down.

"It is Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace, we can't block it! Retreat!" The Gu Immortals who were guarding this place were pale with fright as they retreated.

Rumble!

Earth quaked and mountains shook, dust and stones flew everywhere.

This learning palace that was arranged meticulously was completely destroyed. Teacher Jiang and the rest could not even dodge and were squashed into pulp, dying miserably.

The Gu Immortals who taught them felt their hearts bleeding at this scene. Their weeks of guidance were just about to show results, the greatest future potential of Profound Literature grotto-heaven was destroyed all at once by this attack.

Completely destroyed!

"Wu Shuai, my Profound Literature grotto-heaven has remained neutral and never created any difficulties for you. But you actually attacked my land and slaughtered innocents, you are too overbearing and sinful!" Old Immortal Hua Yu was alarmed and shouted in fury.

Wu Shuai laughed heartily inside Dragon Palace, suddenly, his laughter stopped: "Old Immortal Hua Yu, you don't know when to advance or retreat, you don't know what's good for you! I sent messages for you to join time and time again, but you actually made excuses to ignore them, you simply show no regard for me. Today, I will make you and the entire world realize what the outcome of defying my will is! Attack!"

Chapter 2009: Following Willingly

Attack—!

Wu Shuai's shout triggered boundless wind and clouds, resounding throughout the grotto-heaven.

Many Gu Immortals in Profound Literature grotto-heaven had a change in their expressions, feeling panicked and worried when they sensed Wu Shuai's ferocious might.

Profound Literature grotto-heaven had lived in peace for too long and had never experienced such an ordeal. Even the current grotto-heaven owner, Old Immortal Hua Yu, was extremely surprised.

Because Profound Literature grotto-heaven was an information path grotto-heaven and was most specialized in gathering all kinds of information and clues. They would definitely detect any invasion in advance.

However, Old Immortal Hua Yu and the rest were completely unaware of this invasion, and Wu Shuai's surprise invasion could even be considered a masterpiece, he was able to teleport his Gu Immortals to various areas of the grotto-heaven, launching violent attacks at the various important areas and Profound Literature grotto-heaven's Gu Immortals.

This ambush could be said to be extremely successful.

Profound Literature grotto-heaven suffered disastrous losses, not only did the meticulously selected future potentials like Teacher Jiang perish, even most of the Gu Immortals of Profound Literature grotto-heaven were killed.

"Persevere, this is our home, we cannot lose it. I have already requested for reinforcements, we cannot let these despicable thugs succeed!" Old Immortal Hua Yu shouted, slightly stabilizing the morale of the soldiers.

He then opened his mouth and moved his tongue, spitting out text characters.

These characters were like a storm as they shrouded Dragon Palace with dense frost energy.

Immortal killer move — Cold Words!

The moment Dragon Palace was struck by this move, layers of frost solidified on its surface which greatly slowed its speed. The frost continued to condense and spread, and in a blink of an eye, was already as tall as an adult's calf. If this went on, the whole of Dragon Palace would be sealed in ice.

Wu Shuai snorted as he activated his defensive killer move.

The frost on Dragon Palace's surface began to melt gradually, and Dragon Palace's power continued to rise, letting out rays of orange light.

The orange light shot towards Old Immortal Hua Yu, who immediately changed the words he recited and used a movement method.

Immortal killer move — Quick Words!

At the next moment, his speed surged and he perfectly dodged the orange light.

Immortal killer move — Vicious Words!

Old Immortal Hua Yu spat out tides of characters from his mouth, these purplish black words were like poison arrows that shot and detonated on Dragon Palace.

Rumble...

The series of explosions forced Dragon Palace to retreat constantly, at the same time, large amounts of toxic smoke infiltrated Dragon Palace.

Wu Shuai was seated on the main seat, he did not panic upon seeing this and immediately activated defensive methods to resolve this danger.

Old Immortal Hua Yu's reputation was not undeserving, he truly had some skills, to be able to confront Dragon Palace without losing his ground.

Naturally, this was because Dragon Palace was an enslavement path Immortal Gu House and was most proficient in the enslavement aspect. Moreover, Wu Shuai did not reveal the Four Dragon Generals although he had already gathered them. What he used normally was the Evil Dragon, which had already become a trump card of Dragon Palace.

The Evil Dragon was rampaging!

The two heavens alliance's Gu Immortals were killing and looting!

Wu Shuai was not in a hurry at all, because the situation was extremely favorable to him.

Old Immortal Hua Yu became increasingly anxious as the battle continued, he knew he was already tangled up with Dragon Palace and would have to rely on external force to save Profound Literature grotto-heaven from the danger.

But could the reinforcements arrive in time?

Old Immortal Hua Yu was awaiting the reinforcements, but he knew there was not much hope. Although he had a high reputation, and Profound Literature grotto-heaven's relationship with the surrounding grotto-heaven forces was also quite close, but asking these people to reinforce him in fighting against such strong enemies?

Old Immortal Hua Yu placed himself in their position and thought: if a surrounding grotto-heaven was attacked and asked him for reinforcements, and the enemy was the two heavens alliance, he would also hesitate.

The two heavens alliance's Gu Immortals continued to wreak havoc.

Flames of battle rose everywhere as living beings were exterminated.

"Old Immortal Hua Yu, use your trump cards if you have any left, if you don't use them now, you won't be able to save your grotto-heaven. Hahaha." Wu Shuai laughed wildly.

Old Immortal Hua Yu was silent, his expression grim.

The aftereffects of their fight harmed everything around them, causing holes to appear in the grotto-heaven aperture walls, linking the inside to the outside world.

Suddenly, Wu Shuai's laughter stopped as he shouted in fury: "Old geezer Qi Sea!"

The moment he finished speaking, boundless qi currents surged in from outside and gathered into a giant hand.

The hand was as large as a mountain as it slammed into Dragon Palace and sent it flying far away.

Following which, a tall and sturdy figure appeared in the grotto-heaven's sky, looking down at Dragon Palace.

"Qi Sea Ancestor!" Old Immortal Hua Yu looked up and said with surprise and joy.

Qi Sea Ancestor's appearance surprised him, but thinking about it carefully, he felt it was natural. Qi Sea Ancestor was the biggest enemy of Wu Shuai, he would not sit by and watch Wu Shuai leading the two heavens' forces to do whatever he pleased.

Roar—!

Dragon Palace moved back while the Evil Dragon took its place.

Qi Sea Ancestor, however, held his hands behind his back with no intention to attack: "Wu Shuai, stop now, I can let all of you retreat. If we truly fight, your two heavens alliance will cease to exist."

"You...." Wu Shuai's furious voice came from Dragon Palace: "Qi Sea Ancestor!"

The Evil Dragon stopped, Wu Shuai seemed to be thinking.

Old Immortal Hua Yu let out a sigh of relief, looking towards Qi Sea Ancestor with an extremely grateful look.

Qi Sea Ancestor did this to preserve Profound Literature grotto-heaven and not let it turn into ruins. This was not easy! The two heavens alliance's Gu Immortals were scattered everywhere, Qi Sea Ancestor could take the chance to attack them and deal heavy damage to the two heavens alliance.

But Qi Sea Ancestor did not do this, instead, he considered Profound Literature grotto-heaven. Moreover, prior to this, Old Immortal Hua Yu had never come into contact with Qi Sea Ancestor.

"Qi Sea Ancestor took such protective action for an outsider like me. He is truly worthy of being a famed expert and the leader of Eastern Sea's righteous path!" Old Immortal Hua Yu was extremely moved.

However, at the next moment, the Evil Dragon attacked and Dragon Palace followed closely behind.

"Qi Sea Ancestor, it has been too long since the battle that day. Face my move again!" Wu Shuai shouted.

"Despicable!" Old Immortal Hua Yu cursed when he saw Wu Shuai sneak attacking.

But Qi Sea Ancestor was smiling as if he was already prepared: "Come."

Boom!

At the next moment, the Evil Dragon and Dragon Palace crashed into a firm and solid qi wall.

The qi wall broke down but the Evil Dragon and Dragon Palace's momentum was also completely exhausted.

"Old geezer Qi Sea, I am relieved that you are so energetic. We shall battle later!" Wu Shuai saw he was unable to gain any progress and started to retreat slowly.

Dragon Palace and Evil Dragon left the battlefield and moved out of the grotto-heaven.

The two heavens alliance's Gu Immortals did not dare to stay any longer and started retreating, they were afraid of Dragon Palace leaving them behind in this dangerous place.

Wu Shuai's group arrived fast and left just as quickly, leaving behind flames of war and ruin.

Old Immortal Hua Yu did not rush to provide disaster relief and stabilize the situation, instead, he flew towards Qi Sea Ancestor and bowed deeply: "Ancestor, you helped us in repelling the enemies. Everyone in Profound Literature grotto-heaven is grateful for your kindness."

Qi Sea Ancestor smiled brightly as he held Old Immortal Hua Yu's hands and pulled him up: "We are both humans, it is natural for us to band together and help each other against the variant humans."

Old Immortal Hua Yu said with hatred: "Wu Shuai is trying to overturn humanity's rule, he is a lunatic and a despicable fellow. He is an enemy of everyone in Profound Literature grotto-heaven, we won't rest until he dies!"

Qi Sea Ancestor nodded: "In the current era, chaotic times are coming, who can stay out of it? It is good that you realize this!"

Old Immortal Hua Yu cupped his fists and bowed again: "Looking at the immortals in this world, only Ancestor's might and prestige has spread everywhere, your moral conduct is worthy of being respected. From today onwards, Profound Literature grotto-heaven will be at your command, we will listen to your arrangements."

Qi Sea Ancestor smiled: "Brother Hua Yu, let's join hands in fighting the variant humans, we will protect our homelands and fight for a beautiful future."

Chapter 2010: Influencing The Five Regions

Profound Literature grotto-heaven.

A tea ceremony was in session.

Old Immortal Hua Yu sat on the lower seat while he let Fang Yuan have the main seat.

Fang Yuan used Qi Sea Ancestor's identity to talk with the Gu Immortals, obtaining first hand information regarding the part of white heaven above Eastern Sea.

There were not just Profound Literature grotto-heaven's Gu Immortals who participated in the tea ceremony. After Qi Sea Ancestor repelled the enemies, Gu Immortals continued to arrive to reinforce them.

These Gu Immortals were from the surrounding forces and were late in reinforcing Profound Literature grotto-heaven, but Old Immortal Hua Yu asked them to stay and join this tea ceremony regardless.

Qi Sea Ancestor said frankly: He had already allied with Heavenly Court and wanted to recruit the human forces in the two heavens, to fight against Wu Shuai's variant human alliance and defend the righteous path of humanity.

Old Immortal Hua Yu was naturally the first to support it, the other forces also responded quite passionately. Many of the Gu Immortals even express their willingness to join Qi Sea Ancestor's faction to fight Wu Shuai's violent and lawless alliance.

Some Gu Immortals hesitated while many others had to report to their superiors to come to a decision.

The tea ceremony ended. Fang Yuan was quite satisfied with the result.

The first step was important if he wanted to interfere in the two heavens' grotto-heavens. With Wu Shuai's active cooperation, almost all the two heaven's Gu Immortals recognized Wu Shuai's might and felt insecure. Everyone realized they could not evade this calamity because even a powerful force like Profound Literature grotto-heaven was almost exterminated. If not for Qi Sea Ancestor lending a hand, Profound Literature grotto-heaven would have ceased to exist.

Chaotic times were coming and no one could stay out of it. Only by stepping on the waves of chaos could they survive and grow stronger.

Qi Sea Ancestor needed only slight effort to persuade five grotto-heaven forces. Of course, it would take some more effort to integrate them. And important details like profit distribution and other rules had yet to be finalized.

Even so, Qi Sea Ancestor's action had already caused a huge change in the two heavens' forces, even affecting the overall situation of the conflict between humanity and the variant human races.

Fang Yuan naturally would not conceal this news, the moment the tea ceremony ended, he spread this news in treasure yellow heaven.

In an instant, the Gu Immortal world of the five regions was shaken.

Some sighed at the changing state of the world and the impending chaos, some praised Qi Sea Ancestor's righteous move and felt he could shoulder the responsibility to lead humanity, some were guessing Wu Shuai's next move, and some were thinking of Eastern Sea's political situation. Qi Sea Ancestor was publicly recognized as the most powerful expert in Eastern Sea, now that he was so close with Heavenly Court, how would Eastern Sea's righteous path forces face this relationship?

The five regional walls were gone, the independent five regions merged into one, changes in any one side could change the whole situation of the five regions. Every move of an expert with an identity and status like Qi Sea Ancestor could deeply influence the whole world.

Eastern Sea, Shen clan.

"Are there still no clues on Ancestor Shen Shang's whereabouts?" Shen Cong Sheng sighed: "I don't blame you, qi tides are appearing everywhere, Divine Emperor City is a very tightly protected area."

A Shen clan Gu Immortal asked: "First supreme elder, Qi Sea Ancestor has already allied with Heavenly Court now, they even handed over the latter half of Primordial Origin's true inheritance. What should we do?"

Shen Cong Sheng replied: "I have already discussed this with Song Qi Yuan, Hua Cai Yun, and other first supreme elders. Qi Sea Ancestor is our Eastern Sea's expert, he cannot be recruited by Heavenly Court. Every clan will take out a portion of cultivation resources from their treasuries and gather them into a big gift to build a good relationship with Ancestor."

Shen clan's Gu Immortal nodded, not objecting to it.

Qi Sea Ancestor was the most valuable existence to rope in, besides his battle strength, it was also because he cultivated qi path.

Currently, Eastern Sea's super forces were thinking of developing qi path and they would have double the results if they could get Qi Sea Ancestor's help in this aspect.

Fang Yuan put on a great show before, everyone in Gu Immortal world thought Qi Sea Ancestor liked to give guidance and support the younger generation. This made Eastern Sea's super forces feel there was a high possibility in this matter.

Western Desert, Fang clan's headquarters.

Fang Gong's expression was dark: "We are willing to pay such a huge price but Heavenly Court still doesn't want to release Fang Di Chang?"

One of the gathered Fang clan Gu Immortals said: "First supreme elder, in my opinion, Heavenly Court is not sincere at all, they are just stalling for time and fooling us."

"Hmph!" Fang Gong slammed his right fist on the table.

He was furious but helpless.

In the fate war, Fang clan's losses were the largest. Not only did they lose Divine Bean Palace, even their strategist Fang Di Chang was captured by the enemy and there was no news of him until now.

Fang clan naturally thought Fang Di Chang was captured by Heavenly Court. Thereupon, they secretly contacted Heavenly Court and wanted to pay a huge price to redeem Fang Di Chang.

But Heavenly Court had all along been stalling their request.

Fang Di Chang was extremely important to Fang clan, without him, Fang clan would be without a strategist.

After Fang clan refined Divine Bean Palace, they had the possibility of raising their status and becoming the leader of Western Desert's righteous path. But Divine Bean Palace and Fang Di Chang were gone, destroying Fang clan's dream of becoming the leader.

Fang Gong was in a very bad mood, especially after hearing of Qi Sea Ancestor's actions.

"Qi Sea Ancestor has already begun to lead Eastern Sea, but me? Fang clan? We are just stagnating at the same spot! Sigh..." Fang Gong felt helpless.

The only thing that gave him some joy was that Fang Di Chang had already prepared for the future and had passed on Fang clan's wisdom path inheritance to Fang Yun.

"Since Heavenly Court is not willing to release Fang Di Chang, we can only prioritize on cultivating Fang Yun." Fang Gong made the decision.

They could not wait any longer.

Time waits for no one!

Cultivating a Gu Immortal, especially a competent wisdom path Gu Immortal, required a long time.

Central Continent, Heavenly Court.

Qin Ding Ling looked at the intel and smiled, muttering to herself: "Fang clan is actually willing to pay such a huge price to buy back Fang Di Chang. If they knew Fang Di Chang was already replaced and is now Fang Yuan's clone, what would they feel?"

Heavenly Court already knew of Fang Di Chang's identity.

The current Divine Emperor City was guarded by Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's will. He had already informed Qin Ding Ling of this.

Although Fang Di Chang was sealed in Divine Bean Palace's painting, he had a portion of the authority and was resisting stubbornly, even Genesis Lotus' will could do nothing about it.

"But it will be over soon." Qin Ding Ling smiled: "That earlier batch of Gu Immortal seeds we sent in are developing extremely well, they already possess strength to defeat Fang Di Chang. As long as we capture him, we can use the close connection between him and Fang Yuan to search for the location of Fang Yuan's main body."

Spectral Soul was secretly searching for Fang Yuan's main body, Heavenly Court was doing the same as well.

Qin Ding Ling knew Fang Yuan was in a poor state currently and it was the best time to kill Fang Yuan. If they could kill Fang Yuan, not only would it restore Heavenly Court's reputation, there would even be enormous spoils of war. Be it the various inheritances on Fang Yuan, his Gu worms, his sovereign immortal aperture, secluded domains of heaven and earth, and so on, they were all things Heavenly Court wanted.

Qin Ding Ling was taking control of Heavenly Court in place of Fairy Zi Wei, although she was only a luck path Gu Immortal, she tried her best and was busy everyday, her hard work was showing results.

Internally, Heavenly Court was leading the ten great ancient sects, actively cultivating talents and recovering their strength.

Externally, Heavenly Court was allying with Eastern Sea, they roped in Qi Sea Ancestor first but the price was half of Primordial Origin's true inheritance. They would soon capture Fang Di Chang, and their hopes of capturing Fang Yuan's main body were even higher than Spectral Soul!

"Everything will get better."

"My Heavenly Court is and will continue to be the supreme leader of humanity!"

Chapter 2011: Divine Bean Soldier Calamity

Divine Emperor City.

Inside the painting, Fang Di Chang waved his hand, immediately, a large amount of white sand flew out and scattered around.

The white sand fell on the ground and immediately melted into puddles of milk that seeped into the ground.

Blop blop....

Air bubbles rose from the ground, the beans buried under the ground devoured the milk and grew rapidly.

In three minutes, Fang Di Chang expended the small amount of rank eight immortal material milk sand he had. The barren land became extremely fertile and green bean sprouts broke out of the ground surface.

"Again." Fang Di Chang took out a snow path immortal material.

The immortal material was thrown to the air and was digested by Divine Emperor City, turning into broken lightning rays that covered the whole bean field.

The broken lightning slightly touched the tender bean sprouts and agitated their growth potential, the bean sprouts began growing with a visible speed.

"Continue." After the lightning rays dissipated, Fang Di Chang took out the third immortal material.

Time continued to pass, about three days and three nights later, Fang Di Chang slowly stopped his actions.

He looked at the field, the beans had already grown into divine bean soldiers. They were standing in rows, silent and still like statues as they waited for Fang Di Chang's orders.

Fang Di Chang sighed, thinking: "This is the last batch of divine bean soldiers. My immortal materials are basically all spent."

As a clone of Fang Yuan, after Fang Di Chang was schemed by Genesis Lotus' will, he had been trapped in the painting.

Over this period of time after the fate war, he had been waiting for his main body to rescue him while using all his strength to accumulate troops.

But even by now, the main body had not come to save him, Fang Di Chang could only prepare to save himself.

He was now trapped in the painting, unable to contact the main body and even unable to access treasure yellow heaven. But he had refined Divine Bean Palace, so he still held a portion of the authority. This was the reason Genesis Lotus' will was unable to do anything to him in a short period of time.

Fang Di Chang used this authority to borrow Divine Bean Palace's strength in cultivating divine bean soldiers.

He was constantly accumulating divine bean soldiers, and now, their size had already reached an enormous scale.

"It is time, move out, invade and seize control of all the paintings!" Fang Di Chang gave a command without any hesitation. The divine bean soldier army began to set out.

They split into countless divisions as they moved towards the edge of the painting and invaded other painting worlds.

Outside Emperor City was a large farmland, wheat billowed in the autumn wind and many farmers were harvesting them.

"This year is an abundant year!"

"Yes, every family has made good harvests."

"What is this noise?"

The farmers were talking happily when they suddenly heard strange sounds and were bewildered.

A group of over three hundred divine bean soldiers charged into this painting world.

They discovered these farmers and behaved like sharks that smelled blood, they moved extremely quickly and killed anyone they saw.

"Run!"

"There are monsters, run!"

"Spare me. Spare...."

Guh.

Blood splattered everywhere, the last farmer's head and body were separated, falling into a pool of blood.

Divine bean soldiers killed all the humans and occupied this painting world.

At another painting outside of Emperor City.

It was spring and the scenery was beautiful.

A large group of scholars, students and young ladies went for an outing.

In the midst of their joyful talks, several divine bean soldiers appeared suddenly, causing the girls to scream.

"They dare to offend our young ladies!"

"What are these things?"

The scholars and students looked curiously as the guards surrounded the divine bean soldiers.

The divine bean soldiers began to attack, the guards were already on guard so the battle went to a standstill.

"These strange things have bad intentions!"

"Where did these things come out from?"

"Forget that, let's talk after killing them first."

The scholars and the students cooperated with the Gu Master guards and attacked, killing these divine bean soldiers without wasting much energy.

But soon, an army of a thousand divine bean soldiers arrived in this painting world.

This time, the guards, scholars and students were unable to resist, after a bitter struggle, most of them were killed and stepped on mercilessly by the divine bean soldiers, while a small portion retreated from this painting world and managed to survive.

Each divine bean soldier had extraordinary strength and was at least of desolate beast level, but in the painting world, they had to follow its rules, where the gap between immortal and mortal was minuscule.

Moreover, divine bean soldiers were transported to other painting worlds randomly, so their scales were not equal.

Fang Di Chang made a heavy attack but the divine bean soldier army was scattered everywhere and engaged in their respective invasions. Thus, some divine bean soldiers made good progress, some met strong resistance, while some were directly annihilated by the Gu Masters in the painting world.

Even so, Fang Di Chang soon revealed a satisfied smile.

"My guess was right."

"Divine Bean Palace's paintings are connected with Emperor City's paintings. Although I am sealed here, my divine bean soldiers originated from Divine Bean Palace and are of the same origin as the whole of Divine Emperor City, so they can move out."

"The more painting worlds these divine bean soldiers occupy, the more control I will have over Divine Emperor City. After gaining a certain amount of control, I can even go a step further and suppress Genesis Lotus' will, becoming the owner of Divine Emperor City!"

Fang Di Chang's huge move this time made the Gu Immortal seeds, sent by Heavenly Court into Divine Emperor City's painting world, gather and discuss a plan.

"What is going on with these divine bean soldiers?" Chen Da Jiang frowned.

Sun Yao's eyes were red: "I also don't know, these monsters appeared and began killing wantonly, they are extremely vicious. Those pitiful beggars and homeless people were all killed by these monsters."

"Maybe this is our fortuitous encounter or maybe it is a test?" Tang Ru Qi guessed.

Ying Sheng Ji frowned: "I killed many divine bean soldiers, but I have not made any gains until now."

Wei Wu Shang analyzed calmly: "Divine bean soldiers are a product of Divine Bean Palace, according to rumors, Gu Immortals can raise these wood path soldiers in a large scale in Divine Bean Palace. When it is time to battle, the Gu Immortal can release them to fight the enemies. Previously, when Divine Bean Palace was with Western Desert, they scattered a large number of divine bean soldiers to fight our Central Continent's ten great ancient sects."

"So what is the reason behind these divine bean soldiers' sudden appearance?" Zhao Shu Ye asked.

Wei Wu Shang shook his head: "I don't know, it has been some time since we arrived here but the painting world here is too vast and profound, we don't know a lot of its secrets."

"What is the point of trying to figure out the reason?" Right at this time, Xiao Qi Xing walked over.

"Ah, it is Brother Xiao."

"What information do you have? Or do you know the truth of the matter?"

These Gu Immortal seeds asked one after the other, they thought highly of Xiao Qi Xing because he had the best progress among them.

He mixed into the military faction and continued to advance in ranks and was already a junior officer now.

Xiao Qi Xing said: "I don't care about the reason behind these divine bean soldiers' appearance, I only know the higher-ups have sent the order to mobilize the army to exterminate these divine bean soldiers. This time, I am leading my troops alone and need assistance. We will cooperate and kill these divine bean soldiers. There will definitely be rewards after the battle."

"It is fine with me. These monsters should be killed!" Chen Da Jiang said.

Sun Yao nodded: "These divine bean soldiers are too vicious, they are simply disregarding human lives. I will take revenge for those pitiful beggars and homeless people."

"Count me in too." Zhao Shu Ye also expressed her stance.

Soon, all of these Gu Immortals agreed and temporarily joined Xiao Qi Xing as his subordinates.

Xiao Qi Xing laughed heartily, he was pleased and proud with this huge increase in strength and manpower: "Move out! Let us kill these divine bean soldiers."

Chapter 2012: Fang Di Chang's Death

Divine Emperor City, painting world.

In the vast plaza, Xiao Qi Xing led a large group of troops and was facing a group of divine bean soldiers.

The scale of this group of divine bean soldiers was bigger than Xiao Qi Xing's side.

"How do we fight them?" Sun Yuan Hua had just asked when the divine bean soldiers charged.

Xiao Qi Xing stopped his side from attacking and smiled: "Everyone, please stay put for now and look at how I fight them."

Saying this, Xiao Qi Xing flicked his fingers repeatedly, a large amount of Gu worms flew out of his aperture.

These Gu worms fell to the ground and turned into human shapes. Most of them were ordinary soldiers, a few clearly looked like elites, and an extremely small number of them looked much more brave and valiant.

"These are soldier Gu, sergeant Gu, lieutenant Gu?" Gu Ting narrowed his eyes.

"They should be." Wei Wu Shang counted roughly: "There are over five hundred of them, looks like Xiao Qi Xing progressed really well in the military camp to be able to accumulate so many human path Gu worms."

"Formation!" Xiao Qi Xing shouted while activating arrow formation Gu.

These soldiers immediately gathered, captains led lieutenants, lieutenants led sergeants, and sergeants led soldiers.

And the entire army formed a giant arrow that rushed head on towards the incoming divine bean soldiers.

"Charge—!"

Xiao Qi Xing's army roared loudly, on the contrary, the divine bean soldiers were silent like there was no life.

The two sides were like colliding waves which began to mix into each other.

Xiao Qi Xing's gaze was like lightning as he put all his attention on controlling his troops.

In the chaotic battle, his troops were further divided but they always maintained the most basic military formation.

On the contrary, the divine bean soldiers were a messy and disordered group.

After the initial stalemate, the situation began to slowly fall into Xiao Qi Xing's grasp. Once he occupied the upper hand, this advantage snowballed and soon, it turned into absolute dominance.

Finally, Xiao Qi Xing's side won a complete victory with all divine bean soldiers killed off.

"How is it?" Xiao Qi Xing returned with victory and showed off to the other Gu Immortal seeds.

Zhao Shu Ye rolled his eyes, not bothering to reply.

"Brother Xiao is truly amazing!" Chen Da Jiang raised his thumb.

"Hahaha." Xiao Qi Xing laughed heartily and said to Chen Da Jiang: "If you had walked the same path as me back then, you would also have such accomplishments today."

"We should continue. We have only cleared up one painting." Wei Wu Shang said.

"Don't be careless. These soldiers are only yellow bean divine soldiers, they are the most basic type of divine bean soldier." Gu Ting said.

They continued to march forward and fight divine bean soldiers.

After a while, they arrived at the most flourishing street of Divine Emperor City.

Divine bean soldiers were wantonly killing the people in the city and it was a scene of chaos.

Sun Yao's eyes turned red with fury. The first time she entered here, she had arrived at this street and enjoyed its flourishing scenes. She had never expected such a beautiful scene to be completely destroyed by the divine bean soldiers, everywhere was littered with corpses and blood flowed into a river.

"This will need everyone's assistance." Xiao Qi Xing was modest for once: "The paths are narrow and vision is not clear, my troops won't be able to move properly."

The other Gu Immortal seeds had no objections as they charged to the front lines and attacked.

Xiao Qi Xing stayed at the rear, observing the situation while controlling the soldiers to move forward.

He was deeply aware that he came to compete for Genesis Lotus' true inheritance, these Gu Masters beside him were his greatest competitors. Know yourself and your enemy, and you will never be defeated, this was the best opportunity to gain information about these people.

These Gu Master elites of Central Continent's ten great ancient sects were indeed extraordinary.

Xiao Qi Xing had made a lot of progress, these Gu Masters were also not any inferior.

Ying Sheng Ji continuously took out doctor Gu, which took human forms and saved people everywhere.

Chen Da Jiang went through the outer gate, a group of officers moved around him as he joined the front lines with a long sword and a steel chain.

Sun Yao gave a bigger surprise to Xiao Qi Xing, three female dancers moved around her, their long sleeves fluttered in the wind and weakened the divine bean soldiers. Moreover, Sun Yao also held a human path killer move — Joy in Helping People; this move strengthened her allies.

As for Wei Wu Shang, he appeared and disappeared as he moved in the chaotic battle like a fish in water.

"This guy has already mastered thief Gu." Xiao Qi Xing realized.

These elites immediately shone brightly the moment they made their moves. Xiao Qi Xing also felt heavy pressure as he warned himself: "I really cannot underestimate these people!"

This chaotic battle lasted for five minutes before the whole street was cleared.

Without staying any longer, Xiao Qi Xing's group marched towards other paintings once again.

The divine bean soldiers in their path were all annihilated.

Naturally, they were not the only group who were counterattacking. The warriors in the painting worlds also organized many groups and participated in the battle, killing the divine bean soldiers.

Ye Fan and Hong Yi were also mixed among other groups, they were secretly conversing.

"These divine bean soldiers are really odd, there are so many types of them."

"The ten great ancient sects' members have also grown, we need to conceal ourselves and not be discovered by them."

They were the earliest people to enter the painting world.

At this moment, their accumulation far surpassed the Central Continent elites, but Ye Fan and Hong Yi could only move secretly. After all, the five regions world was the main world, once they were discovered by Heavenly Court, the situation would become a mess.

The counterattacking groups became faster the more they killed, their efficiency was increasing continuously and casualties were reducing.

After they had sufficient experience, they completely saw through the types of divine bean soldiers. Yellow bean divine soldiers were only cannon fodder, green bean soldiers could shoot flying arrows, red bean soldiers could self-detonate, black bean soldiers had the greatest defense.

After understanding the characteristics of the different divine bean soldiers, they began to launch targeted attacks. These divine bean soldiers were far weaker than their external appearance.

The counterattacking groups continued to gain victories and seized back more territories.

Finally, they gathered on the city walls of Divine Emperor City.

There was an ocean of divine bean soldiers outside the city walls, Xiao Qi Xing could not help taking in a sharp breath when he saw this.

The enemy force was overwhelming, it was not something their group could handle. They could only have a chance of defending the city by allying with other groups.

Divine bean soldiers rushed forward without any formation.

Xiao Qi Xing's group attacked with long range skills from top of the city walls.

Divine bean soldiers were like ants as they began climbing the city walls.

The ones guarding the city staked their lives to counterattack, not retreating a step.

The whole battlefield was like a huge meat grinder, large amounts of lives were lost every second.

This battle lasted three days and three nights.

Xiao Qi Xing collapsed and sat weakly on the ground. His snowy-white military robe was already dyed red with blood.

Cheers spread continuously in the surroundings, they had won. This largest group of divine bean soldiers was completely exterminated by them.

Victory was assured!

Next would be to clear up the remaining small groups of divine bean soldiers in every painting.

"Wait a second, we seem to be able to walk out of Divine Emperor City."

"We can follow the path the divine bean soldiers took and attack their base!"

When they were clearing up the battlefield, many made a big discovery.

The troops began to gather once again and battled their way to Fang Di Chang.

In this painting world, Fang Di Chang's strength was greatly reduced but he still had a group of divine bean soldiers around him.

"So you are the main culprit behind all these!"

"You are going to pay for your sins!"

"Why, why do you need to kill these innocent people, what grudge do you have against them?"

Emotions surged, but Xiao Qi Xing's group glanced at each other and moved towards the rear silently.

"So the cause of the divine bean soldier calamity was him."

"He is a Gu Immortal of Fang clan, Fang Di Chang, who had once refined Divine Bean Palace."

"I did not expect him to still be alive, and he is creating chaos in the painting world!"

"Don't tell me, did our sects send us here to get rid of him?"

"Strange, why didn't Heavenly Court attack and kill Fang Di Chang directly? Maybe this is a test for us, or maybe we can only deal with him while following the rules of the painting world?"

Xiao Qi Xing's group conversed quickly, their expressions were extremely serious. They were the ones chosen and nurtured by their respective sects, thus they had a lot of information about the Gu Immortal world, they had detailed information about the participants of the fate war.

"Kill!"

"Take revenge for our friends and family!"

"I will cut him into a thousand pieces!!"

The Gu Masters of the painting world attacked Fang Di Chang.

"A bunch of trash." Fang Di Chang stood at the center and commanded his troops calmly. The divine bean soldiers beside him changed their formation and moved smoothly like water. The cooperation between the various types of soldiers was extremely smooth and fluid.

Instantly, the warriors of the painting world suffered heavy casualties.

Xiao Qi Xing's group was also shocked.

"The scale of these divine bean soldiers is quite small, how could they have such results?"

"With a Gu Immortal commanding them, they are completely different from before."

"What should we do? Battle or retreat?"

"Fight! We have numbers on our side, Fang Di Chang might be strong, but the gap between us is not the gap between immortal and mortal. We have a high chance of success!"

"Slaughter the immortal!!"

Someone shouted the slogan which made Xiao Qi Xing's group extremely excited.

The moment they joined in the battle, the Gu Masters in the front lines felt like they had received strong reinforcements.

In fact, not only them, even Ye Fan and Hong Yi were also mixed in the battle, helping out secretly.

Fang Di Chang snorted coldly. Under his command, the divine bean soldiers' formation kept on changing while being extremely stable.

Xiao Qi Xing's group battled hard for a long time, but to their horror, they discovered that the casualty difference between the enemy and their side had reached a terrifying level. There were only negligible losses to the divine bean soldiers.

"What should we do?"

"An immortal is still an immortal in the end!"

"Let alone when Fang Di Chang is a wisdom path Gu Immortal."

Xiao Qi Xing's group's morale fell sharply and they had the thought of retreating, not daring to fight with Fang Di Chang.

But at this time, Fang Di Chang's body shook suddenly as he coughed a mouthful of blood. He snorted coldly and looked up at the sky, laughing coldly: "Genesis Lotus' will, you couldn't endure it and took action after all."

Fang Di Chang was suppressed by Genesis Lotus' will, his control over the divine bean soldiers was no longer as smooth as before.

Xiao Qi Xing's group immediately felt the pressure on them reducing sharply, they were surprised and happy as they attacked once again.

Fang Di Chang's divine bean soldiers continued to fall till they were all annihilated.

Fang Di Chang had no choice but to attack personally, he rampaged through the army, killing everyone in his path with no one being able to rival him.

This did not last long, his condition continued to deteriorate as he began to receive injuries.

After some more time, Fang Di Chang was soaked in blood and started to stagger.

"To think that I, Fang Di Chang, would actually die in such a place!" Fang Di Chang shouted in sadness as he self-detonated resolutely.

Boom!

The Gu Masters surrounding him were wiped out with no intact corpses.

After a short period of shock, the surviving Gu Masters shouted in joy.

"We won!"

"We finally killed the demon."

"Sob... father, mother, I have avenged you."

Xiao Qi Xing's group was also excited and their faces were flushed red: "We killed an immortal! We succeeded in slaughtering the immortal!"

Chapter 2013: Survival Through Death

Xiao Qi Xing's group strolled along the streets.

The huge battle had just ended, the flourishing and bustling street had turned into a scene of desolation, with no pedestrians moving around. Even if there were, they were mostly injured ones.

"Fang Di Chang is not worthy of being in Western Desert's righteous path! He slaughtered innocents and caused many deaths. Letting him die like this is really letting him go easy." Chen Da Jiang said hatefully.

Ying Sheng Ji sighed as he added: "Yes, this was once a place filled with rich vitality."

"Hehehe. You guys are truly funny." Wei Wu Shang laughed: "This is only a painting world, it is Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable's killer move. The people here are not real existences. No matter how many are dead or injured, after a few years, it will be restored back to normal."

"Yes. Compared to these things, I am more curious about the rewards the sects will give us!" Gu Ting said.

Xiao Qi Xing's eyes brightened: "We killed an immortal as mortals, and even got rid of the hidden disaster in Divine Emperor City. With such a huge contribution, not only our sects, even Heavenly Court should personally reward us, right? Hahaha!"

Xiao Qi Xing laughed heartily and was inwardly pleased.

He had the best performance and had contributed the most in putting down the divine bean soldiers and eliminating Fang Di Chang.

In terms of rewards based on contribution, he would be at the top!

In an alley which the group passed by, two beggars were sitting at a corner, looking at everything with indifference.

The behaviors of these ten great ancient sects' Gu Immortal seeds naturally fell into these two beggars' view.

"I owe my thanks to you, Brother Shen." One beggar transmitted his voice.

The other beggar laughed: "Should I address you as Fang Yuan, or Fang Di Chang?"

The other beggar replied: "I am only a clone, and strictly speaking, I can't even be considered a clone now, I am only a remnant will. So, you don't need to address me as Fang Yuan. As for Fang Di Chang, he is already dead, having died by self-detonation. I am a nameless person now, just a lowly beggar remains."

Shen Shang's eyes shone: "You are too modest. Even without me, you were already prepared to use death to escape."

The other beggar nodded, not denying it: "In my previous plan, if I could occupy and seize the painting worlds with the divine bean soldiers, it would have been the best result. But the chance for this was not high. By preempting the actions to take after defeat, I was naturally prepared for everything. Self-detonation destroyed my body and soul, but this will was secretly left behind."

Pausing for a moment, Fang Yuan's will continued: "I have to thank you for your help regardless. If I relied on just my methods, there is a high probability of Genesis Lotus' will discovering me. But with you shielding me, it is a completely different case. Shen Shang, your human path attainment continues to grow by the day."

Shen Shang chuckled: "That is true. Since the fate war, after I deciphered the venerable human path killer moves, my human path attainment rose quite a bit. And after I arrived in this painting world, I acted as a beggar, observing and experiencing life which gave me a lot of insight. A beggar has a beggar's advantage; beggars stand at the lowest level of society, they can observe the attitudes of people, experience kindness and harshness, feel hunger and fullness, warmth and cold."

Shen Shang then changed the topic, asking: "What do you plan to do now? Leave here or continue to stay?"

Fang Yuan's will did not hesitate: "I am unable to leave here. Even if only a will remains of me now, it has only temporarily escaped the observation of Genesis Lotus' will and has not grasped a way to leave. What about you?"

Shen Shang also shook his head: "I also haven't found the method to leave. I have already secretly checked those Gu Immortal seeds of the ten great ancient sects. They are able to enter and exit here because they have obtained the approval of Genesis Lotus' will. But I believe that as long as I continue to stay in hiding and research, my human path attainment will continue to accumulate and attain a qualitative change. By that time, I can find a method to leave this place."

Fang Yuan's will looked deeply at Shen Shang, he could see Shen Shang was happy to stay in here.

However, when Fang Yuan thought of it, it was also not strange.

Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable had made this huge move, he created a special small world to develop human path.

Over here, human path was supreme and other paths were secondary. Human path had the greatest development while other paths had little progress.

At the same time, this world followed the rules of the mortal world, there was an insignificant gap between immortals and mortals, which was more beneficial for the development of human path.

Moreover, the inside and outside were separated, when outsiders came here, they would be isolated from the five regions and could not even connect to treasure yellow heaven. This stopped information from spreading outside or entering and corrupting the people here. Thus, it created an isolated sacred land of human path.

Shen Shang primarily cultivated human path. In here, he was like a gluttonous monster that saw absolutely rare delicacies, he was like a fish in water and even felt deeply attached to this place.

Fang Yuan's will was currently possessing a body, it was created from Shen Shang's beggar Gu.

He had two choices in front of him now. One was to wait for the main body to rescue him, the other was to cultivate alongside Shen Shang and use Shen Shang's strength to get free.

All the information concerning the divine bean soldier calamity was gathered in Qin Ding Ling's hands.

"Fang Di Chang died by self-detonation?" Qin Ding Ling frowned.

This result somewhat disappointed Qin Ding Ling, she had been hoping to capture this clone of Fang Yuan alive. And through him, deduce the location of Fang Yuan's main body.

"I did not expect Fang Yuan's clone to resolutely kill himself, but this also conforms to Fang Yuan's vicious personality." Qin Ding Ling did not hold much doubts.

"If we could capture him alive, that would have been better. In the painting world, the gap between immortals and mortals is not big. Unfortunately, these Gu Immortal seeds have not grown enough and were unable to grasp the opportunity." Qin Ding Ling sighed inwardly.

Xiao Qi Xing's group thought they made important contributions by slaughtering an immortal, but in her mind, Qin Ding Ling reviewed it poorly.

However, even so, Qin Ding Ling decided to reward these Gu Immortal seeds heavily. They were important cultivation targets after all.

After dealing with the matter of rewards, Qin Ding Ling put her attention on Eastern Sea's conflict once again.

Eastern Sea's conflict was the clash between humans and variant humans.

One side was led by Qi Sea Ancestor while the other was led by Wu Shuai. They had fought several times in the immemorial two heavens as well as sea areas of Eastern Sea, and the battles were becoming increasingly fierce.

After Qi Sea Ancestor saved Profound Literature grotto-heaven, he united several grotto-heaven forces in the two heavens.

Although Wu Shuai was defeated, he was not willing to show any weakness. On one hand, he gathered the forces of the two heavens that joined him, on the other hand, he ambushed and invaded those grotto-heaven forces that wanted to wait and see.

Wu Shuai's direction was extremely clear and blunt.

Before attacking the five regions, he must clean up the two heavens to stabilize their base.

On one hand, this was because the distance between the two heavens' grotto-heavens was short and they could dispatch troops easily. If Wu Shuai ignored this, when the main army was outside in the future, the grotto-heavens only needed to pose an attack and it could cause Wu Shuai's army to end up losing their home ground.

On the other hand, qi harvest fruits of various sizes had appeared in grotto-heavens of Wu Shuai's subordinates. Every time Wu Shuai attacked another grotto-heaven, he would test the variant human Gu Immortals' suggestions to get rid of the qi harvest fruits. Wu Shuai's side was in dire need of such trial and error.

Because of Wu Shuai's violent strategy, more and more human forces in the two heavens sought Qi Sea Ancestor's protection.

Qi Sea Ancestor defended the grotto-heavens while integrating various forces. But on the whole, they were still at a disadvantage.

Wu Shuai's two heavens alliance was strengthening at a much faster speed than Qi Sea Ancestor's.

He was actively protecting the variant humans' benefits, which caused increasingly more variant human grotto-heavens to join him. In the two heavens, variant human grotto-heavens were much larger in numbers than human grotto-heavens.

The final batch of variant human forces who adopted the thought of waiting and seeing took the initiative to side with Wu Shuai. On one hand, they were forced to because of the situation, on the other hand, if they did not surrender, there was no hope in resolving the hidden danger of the qi harvest fruits in their grotto-heavens.

Wu Shuai's prestige soared but the qi harvest fruit's issue was still troubling him. The two heavens alliance tested many methods but they had all failed in eliminating qi harvest fruits.

Over at Qi Sea Ancestor's side, the progress in researching the mysteries of qi harvest fruit was also quite slow.

Wu Shuai's and Qi Sea Ancestor's sides fought frequently, but there were not many casualties. It was because both sides were not focused on eliminating the other side, but on clearing up the danger of the qi harvest fruits.

"The one who knows the most about the mysteries of the qi harvest fruit is probably Demon Immortal Qi Jue. Unfortunately my strength is restrained at present and unable to deal with him." Fang Yuan sighed in pity.

He had already resolved the huge problem of heaven's will, but he still had no clue as to how to refine heaven path dao marks.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue, who Fang Yuan was thinking about, had currently arrived at Western Desert.

"It should be nearby." Demon Immortal Qi Jue flew low and searched everywhere.

He did not succeed in borrowing Gu from Qi Sea Ancestor, so he used qi path investigative methods to search for other qi path Immortal Gu.

And on this search, he found several qi path Immortal Gu.

These qi path Immortal Gu were mostly wild Immortal Gu, they were naturally born after enormous qi tides, as for the rest, they were looted from other Gu Immortals.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue did not go overboard, he only looted qi path Immortal Gu and spared the Gu Immortals.

Moving and stopping along the way, Demon Immortal Qi Jue gradually left Eastern Sea and arrived at Western Desert.

"I deduced that a qi path Immortal Gu is near here." Just as Demon Immortal Qi Jue was mumbling, a Gu Immortal suddenly appeared within his investigative range.

Rank eight Gu Immortal, Red Heart Traveler!

Chapter 2014: Qi Jue Takes Blood Qi

Seeing this Gu Immortal, who was wearing a headband and a green robe, having a tall and powerful stance and handsome appearance, Demon Immortal Qi Jue's mind shook: "That qi path Immortal Gu I deduced, could it be on this person?"

The moment this thought emerged, Demon Immortal Qi Jue attacked!

With a loud sound, a giant white qi hand moved to catch Red Heart Traveler.

Almost at the same time that Demon Immortal Qi Jue discovered Red Heart Traveler, Red Heart Traveler also discovered Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue did not recognize Red Heart Traveler, but Red Heart Traveler already had Heavenly Court's first hand information on Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

Seeing the white qi hand fly towards him, Red Heart Traveler's heart jumped and he quickly evaded.

Red Heart Traveler was a Heavenly Court Gu Immortal and the previous Demon Judgment Board leader, he was very strong. During the fate war, he came to Western Desert and disguised as a blood path demonic immortal, attracting the attention of many super forces of Western Desert's righteous path, thus restraining a large number of hostile forces for Central Continent.

Looking at the whole of Western Desert's Gu Immortal world, Red Heart Traveler had the confidence to fight against almost any Western Desert Gu Immortal. But right now, his opponent was Demon Immortal Qi Jue, one of the strongest Gu Immortals in the present age.

Red Heart Traveler was well aware that he was not Demon Immortal Qi Jue's match. The gap was too large, and the loser of this battle was certain to be him.

So Red Heart Traveler retreated without any hesitation.

At the next moment, Demon Immortal Qi Jue saw a lump of blood red light emerge behind Red Heart Traveler's head, after which the latter's speed increased sharply and was able to dodge his qi hand.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue exclaimed slightly, mumbling inwardly: "Blood path again? It seems like blood path is very prolific in this age."

Demon Immortal Qi Jue was naturally not willing to let go of Red Heart Traveler so easily, so he gave chase.

One chased and one fled, they had soon traveled over ten thousand li.

To his surprise, Demon Immortal Qi Jue discovered his main movement method was actually unable to catch up to Red Heart Traveler. Naturally, he was not left behind in the dust either.

"I have already modified my movement method but I am still unable to catch up to this person. Who is this person? A rank eight blood path Gu Immortal…."

Demon Immortal Qi Jue searched his memories and gradually found some clues.

He had previously soul searched Qing Hui Zi and obtained a lot of information. Red Heart Traveler's true identity was not exposed but he created havoc in Western Desert, and with the sensitive identity of a rank eight blood path expert, information regarding him was already spread in treasure yellow heaven and every Gu Immortal in the world had learned of it.

After chasing for some more time, Demon Immortal Qi Jue suddenly shouted: "Where exactly are you running to?"

His preparation was finished, he activated a killer move.

Red Heart Traveler immediately felt the surrounding qi currents engulf him, severely affecting his speed.

He sighed inwardly, he could only turn around and fight Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue's moves were majestic and powerful, milky white qi currents surged like a tsunami with unstoppable might.

When they truly fought, there was no surprise, Red Heart Traveler fell into a disadvantage. But his methods also were not weak, blood red light spread and blood red flowers bloomed, there was no evil feeling, on the contrary, they were warm and righteous as they defended him.

Red Heart Traveler struggled with all his might, but in just several rounds, his whole body was soaked with sweat. He sighed internally: "As expected of a monster that was recorded in history, he is too strong!"

Red Heart Traveler felt he was like a small boat that was using all its strength to dodge and delay for time under the tidal wave-like attacks of Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

After several more rounds, Red Heart Traveler was already in a perilous situation.

At this time, there was suddenly a beast roar. An immemorial desolate beast drilled out from the desert and went for a surprise attack on Demon Immortal Qi Jue from behind.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue was caught off-guard but he did not panic, he waved his hand and a mountain-like giant qi hand slammed into the immemorial desolate beast.

But just as this immemorial desolate beast was about to be struck by the giant hand, it suddenly let out bright light and transformed into an immemorial swallow that shot towards Demon Immortal Qi Jue like a black arrow.

"So it is a transformation path Gu Immortal! Haha, interesting." Demon Immortal Qi Jue was slightly surprised, he praised while he fought against this immortal.

The aid was from Nine Spiritual Fairy.

She and Red Heart Traveler had come to Western Desert together to help each other out.

With her reinforcement, Red Heart Traveler's situation immediately turned better, he managed to escape from the horrible outcome of death.

"We can't fight for long! This old demon is truly terrifying, we are not his match. We are only able to resist him now because he is not familiar with our methods yet." Red Heart Traveler hurriedly transmitted his voice.

He had fought Demon Immortal Qi Jue and felt the terror of an expert at the peak of the present age. Demon Immortal Qi Jue was unable to get rid of him because he had resurrected not long ago and had yet to completely adapt to the changes. If they truly fought, it was only a matter of time before Heavenly Court's two immortals were killed by Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

"I have an idea, follow me!" Nine Spiritual Fairy transmitted her voice, retreating while fighting.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue chased after the two immortals all the way to a desert.

Nine Spiritual Fairy suddenly transformed into an immemorial desolate beast and held Red Heart Traveler in her mouth before plunging into the desert.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue snorted coldly: "Foolish action!"

With a clap of his hands, heaven and earth shook. Milky white qi current slammed the desert surface like a tsunami, the surrounding hundred li of desert was forcibly pressed down to over ten feet deep!

Nine Spiritual Fairy let out a muffled groan as she suffered heavy injuries.

Red Heart Traveler quickly used healing methods on her.

Nine Spiritual Fairy did not dare to return to fighting and concentrated only on moving deeper into the ground.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue was just about to plunge into the desert and continue chasing when he suddenly heard a beast roar. At the next moment, a huge immemorial soul beast flew out of the nearby desert ground.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue's pupils shrunk slightly when he saw this immemorial soul beast.

This immemorial soul beast had a strange shape and looked quite furious. It had a tortoise shell, four tiger paws, dragon tail, snake neck, and a human head. Its head was full of disheveled hair and its eyes were letting out ominous light and fury.

This was a legendary immemorial desolate beast with many Immortal Gu!

"Oh, you found Qing Chou." Seeing Demon Immortal Qi Jue tangled with the immemorial soul beast, Red Heart Traveler exclaimed in shock.

This immemorial soul beast was Qing Chou.

After Divine Bean Palace was seized by Fang clan, Qing Chou left Divine Bean Palace and hid itself in some areas.

But in the fate war, Divine Bean Palace and Emperor City had merged into one and Genesis Lotus' was in control of it. After the fate war, Genesis Lotus' will naturally handed all kinds of information to Heavenly Court.

Not only did Qin Ding Ling know of Fang Di Chang's true identity, she also obtained information on Qing Chou. Divine Bean Palace had imprisoned Qing Chou for so many years, Genesis Lotus' will had an extremely high understanding of it and knew of a secret method to find it.

Qin Ding Ling obtained this secret method and secretly commanded Nine Spiritual Fairy to search for Qing Chou and subdue it.

Qing Chou was a legendary immemorial beast, not only did it have outstanding battle strength, it also had a natural ability to recognize everything related to Spectral Soul. If Heavenly Court obtained it, not only could they deal with Fang Yuan, they could even deal with Spectral Soul, it could be considered as killing two birds with one stone.

Nine Spiritual Fairy had found Qing Chou's location not long ago, but her strength was insufficient and she had no confidence in succeeding. When Red Heart Traveler ran into Demon Immortal Qi Jue, she thought of a plan to lure Demon Immortal Qi Jue into fighting with Qing Chou.

"Amazing, like this, we can watch from the sidelines and even possibly benefit from their conflict." Red Heart Traveler smiled.

"Qing Chou is not Demon Immortal Qi Jue's match, we need to observe the situation before making a decision." Nine Spiritual Fairy talked while moving deeper into the ground, the further away they were from the battlefield, the better.

However, beyond the expectations of Heavenly Court's two immortals, Demon Immortal Qi Jue felt something amiss and breathed out boundless qi currents that filled the sky.

He entered them and quickly disappeared.

Without an opponent, Qing Chou also chose to leave the battlefield, escaping to the horizons.

Deep underground, Heavenly Court's two immortals looked at each other. Red Heart Traveler suddenly said: "Damn it! That Blood Sea true inheritance is going to be taken!"

Nine Spiritual Fairy was stunned for a moment before reacting: "You really found that blood path true inheritance?"

Red Heart Traveler nodded, sighing: "Heavenly Court's clues were not wrong, the crucial key was the qi tide that exposed the Blood Sea true inheritance. I searched for over half a month before finally arriving at the location. But I ran into Demon Immortal Qi Jue over there."

Nine Spiritual Fairy was silent.

Meanwhile, Demon Immortal Qi Jue returned back to the original spot.

"It is really here!" He inspected for a while, discovering the target was still here and had not moved.

After trying for a while more, he successfully obtained this Blood Sea true inheritance.

Back then, Blood Sea Ancestor had set up hundreds of thousands of inheritance sites that spread over Central Continent, Southern Border, Northern Plains, Western Desert and Eastern Sea. Among them, there were nine true inheritances.

One of the true inheritances had now fallen into Demon Immortal Qi Jue's hands.

"Blood path true inheritance… amazing, with this true inheritance, it will be several times easier for me to deal with blood path Gu Immortals."

"And this blood qi Immortal Gu is really suitable for me. Hahaha."

Demon Immortal Qi Jue laughed heartily.

Almost all the killer moves he activated before consumed qi path immortal materials. Now that he obtained a qi path Immortal Gu, his strength was raised further.

Although there was still some difference from his peak condition in history, he was already much stronger than when he fought Fang Yuan.

Chapter 2015: Sand Wolf City's Huge Change

Western Desert.

Wind blew hard and sand flew everywhere. A merchant caravan pulled by camels was moving with difficulty through the barren desert.

"Oh heavens, we finally returned to Sand Wolf City." Inside the caravan, Peng Da spoke with deep emotions as he showed an exhausted expression.

Gu Master Mo Li was sitting on a camel to the side, he looked at Peng Da and laughed: "Kid, your words are quite different from when we moved out the first time."

Peng Da's face flushed a little. When Mo Li had just organized the merchant caravan, Peng Da had been extremely excited and thought the adventure would be amazing and fun.

But after a few caravan trips, Peng Da had already fully realized his former naivety. In this world, peddling was not only difficult and extremely dangerous, it was also extremely tiring. With even some slight carelessness, his fragile life would be lost in the vast and merciless desert.

However, Peng Da's emotions resonated with other Gu Masters in the merchant caravan.

"Yes, we are back home again."

"We did not encounter any danger in this journey, but it was truly exhausting. I am going to take a good bath after returning."

"I am already unable to control myself, I'll go drink my fill at the tavern, hahaha."

Mo Li smiled, he thought of his wife as well as his son, who had changed a lot recently. His son was selected and was heavily cultivated, his prodigal son had truly turned over a new leaf.

These beautiful wonders of life gave Mo Li brand new hope and motivation. Being a caravan merchant was difficult, but he found joy in his own way.

"Wait, something is going on!" The investigative Gu Master who was at the forefront of the caravan suddenly shouted.

Peng Da immediately tensed up while also feeling somewhat strange. According to common sense, this was near Sand Wolf City and there should be no danger here. So why was there the sudden warning?

Mo Li immediately activated his investigative Gu worm, his body slightly stiffened as he shouted: "The situation is strange, rush forward with full speed!"

Peng Da and the rest did not know the reason but seeing Mo Li take the lead, they naturally believed in the merchant caravan leader and followed quickly.

When they got close to Sand Wolf City, they did not even need to use Gu worms to discover the abnormalities.

Puffs of gray smoke curled upwards, there was also fire and a burnt smell in the air that all came from Sand Wolf City.

Everyone in the merchant caravan had a bad feeling as they moved even faster.

Finally, they arrived in front of Sand Wolf City's gate.

"Impossible!"

"What exactly is going on?!"

"Oh heavens, this is a dream, right? It must be a dream."

Some of the merchant caravan members simply knelt on the ground, some broke down and started crying, even the most stable, leader Mo Li, was standing in a daze.

Peng Da's eyes were wide open as he looked at the scene in front of him in disbelief.

The flouring Sand Wolf City had now become ruins. There were corpses everywhere, rubble and wreckage littered the roads, fire burned and smoke was everywhere, the scene was too horrible to look at.

Mo Li mumbled when he suddenly jolted, running towards the inner city.

His movement jolted many people, Gu Masters began rushing to their homes.

Peng Da did not have a home so he rode a camel and followed Mo Li.

Mo Li was fast, and with anxiety burning his heart, he directly left Peng Da far behind. Fortunately, Peng Da had returned to Sand Wolf City several times and knew the path to Mo Li's home.

When Peng Da reached Mo Li's home, he saw ruins. Mo Li was kneeling on the ground, silently looking at his wife's corpse that he had dug out.

Peng Da, however, sensed deep sadness from Mo Li's silence.

"How could this be? What exactly happened here?" While Peng Da was sad, even more so, he was bewildered.

As far as he was concerned, Sand Wolf City was a large city with many Gu Masters stationed here, but it was actually destroyed and turned into a city devoid of life!

What kind of strength could have the power to destroy the whole of Sand Wolf City?

Was it a qi tide disaster?

But it did not look like that at all from the traces.

"This world is truly too dangerous. People are living in danger, even Gu Masters are the same. There is simply no safe place." Peng Da felt his insignificance growing increasingly.

He looked at Mo Li who was kneeling like a statue and opened his mouth several times before finally saying: "Uncle, we need to pull ourselves together. Don't forget you still have a son."

These words shook Mo Li, his eyes lit up with some hope once again.

"Peng Da, thank you for your reminder! My son is still in the inner city area, he is a Gu Immortal seed and is heavily nurtured. He must be okay, he has to be guarded properly! Let's go find him!"

Mo Li carried his wife's corpse and rushed towards the inner city area with Peng Da.

The whole inner city area had turned into a huge crater.

The inner city area — was gone!

Several caravan members were standing at the edge of the crater, watching it blankly.

Mo Li walked towards them and looked at the huge crater in front of him, his face turned extremely pale and his lips trembled, unable to say anything.

Peng Da took in a sharp breath of air, he could see this huge crater was a beast's footprint. Such a large footprint meant this beast was unimaginably huge!

"This is not man-made."

"A beast calamity!"

"A mountain sized beast attacked Sand Wolf City and killed everyone!"

The caravan members analyzed and started weeping again.

Mo Li fell into deathly silence and Peng Da did not know how to console him. Mo Li once had a beautiful home and now it was all gone, only he himself was remaining.

As far as Mo Li was concerned, as far as the surviving caravan members were concerned, fate was simply too cruel!

Boom—!

Just at this time, there was a sonic boom in the sky above everyone.

This sound immediately attracted everyone's attention.

"Could it be that the giant beast did not leave?" Peng Da quickly raised his head and saw two figures floating in the sky.

"Gu Immortals!" The other Gu Masters shouted.

"Disaster befell this place as well." The Gu Immortals in the sky talked, their voices echoing and spreading below, they did not conceal it.

"This damned beast, it has caused my Mo clan to suffer such disastrous losses. Wait until I capture it, I will pull out its tendons and flay its skin to ease my anger." Another Gu Immortal said in fury.

"Let's go, we will catch up to it soon." The two Gu Immortals quickly flew away.

The Gu Masters on the ground were silent for a while when someone suddenly started to cry out loud.

"Father, mother, you died so miserably. I, your son, cannot avenge you, but the immortals will uphold justice for you!"

Peng Da was silent, his mood was extremely heavy. At this moment, he suddenly had a realization: Even if one becomes a Gu Master, even if they are a rank five Gu Master, what use is it? Only by becoming a Gu Immortal could they have some sort of control over their own fate in this world.

"I want to follow them to take a look." Mo Li suddenly said with a resolute expression.

"Leader, are you crazy?" The surrounding Gu Masters quickly persuaded.

Mo Li's attitude was firm: "I am incompetent! I cannot avenge my wife and child, but I will stake all my strength to see the death of the culprit with my own two eyes! If I can't even grasp this chance, even if I live on, I will feel regret for the rest of my life!"

These words resonated with the remaining Gu Masters, they agreed and expressed that they wanted to move alongside Mo Li to see justice being upheld.

"Uncle, I also want to follow you." Peng Da said.

"You should stay behind, kid." Mo Li's expression softened somewhat as he looked at Peng Da.

Peng Da smiled bitterly: "Uncle, you have saved me time and time again, you are my closest person in this world. Since I followed you, I will definitely not separate with you at this crucial moment. Let me continue to follow you, uncle!"

Mo Li looked deeply at Peng Da for a good while before nodding and saying with a hoarse voice: "Then follow me, rascal."

The group of Gu Masters followed the direction the Gu Immortals flew towards and left the ruins of Sand Wolf City.

On the way, the footprints of the giant beast was exceptionally obvious, which kept them on the correct path.

They rushed like this for a day and a night when they suddenly heard thunder in the horizon.

"This is not thunder, it is the fight between the Gu Immortals and the giant beast!"

"Listen closely, you can vaguely hear a beast's howl."

The Gu Masters were excited as they sped up, wanting to get closer.

But at this time, a dark qi current sprayed out like a rainbow crossing the sky.

A thread of the qi current fell near the Gu Masters. A trace of the dark qi brushed past a Gu Master's shoulder.

That Gu Master suddenly cried out in terror, his skin and muscles started rotting and he soon melted into a white skeleton!

Everyone was horrified at this shocking change and quickly escaped in all directions.

Fortunately, the dark qi dispersed with the wind and did not linger.

"It is too dangerous to go closer!"

"This is only the aftereffect of the fight between the Gu Immortals and the giant beast, we have no strength to resist it."

"If we move in any closer, we will lose our lives."

Most of the Gu Masters stopped and turned back.

"I still want to try it. You can leave." Mo Li was the only remaining Gu Master.

Peng Da still wanted to follow him, but this time, Mo Li's attitude was firm, he drove him away.

Alone, Mo Li moved some distance with difficulty, when he climbed up a sand dune and looked, he could not help taking in a sharp breath at what he saw.

Far away in the horizon, dark fog covered everywhere.

The fog was clearly the dark qi current from earlier. In the dark fog, Mo Li could vaguely see a figure of a mountain-sized beast as well as the occasional lightning flashes.

Mo Li breathed in deeply and was about to continue moving forward when he was suddenly hugged from behind.

"Uncle, do you want to die? Don't go any forward, you will lose your life!" Peng Da shouted.

"Brat, why haven't you left yet?" Mo Li was furious.

Peng Da said with sincerity: "Uncle, you are my benefactor, how can I forget your kindness and watch you send yourself to death's door? I know you want to die, your condition is not right, I have been following you all the way but you were unable to discover me! Uncle, live on, don't kill yourself!"

But Mo Li was not persuaded: "Brat, get lost!"

"I won't!"

"Screw off——! This has nothing to do with you. You are still young and have a long life ahead of you, don't come here to die."

"Uncle, I will save you!"

"I don't need you to save me, even if I die, I will stake my life to take revenge. Even if it is an insignificant attack, as long as it lands on that damned beast, I will be satisfied!!"

Boom——!

Just as the two were bickering, a hurricane flew over from the battle on the horizon.

The hurricane was like a pillar that connected heaven and earth, it moved quickly towards the two.

"Damn it!" Peng Da and Mo Li simply did not have the time to dodge and were swept away by the hurricane.

The two insignificant figures disappeared into the violent hurricane in an instant.

Chapter 2016: Dazzling Smile

Western Desert.

Dark clouds covered the sky and thunder rumbled as the fierce fight of the Mo clan Gu Immortals with the mysterious giant beast continued.

"Die, beast!"

"I will tear out your bones and tendons as resources to compensate for the losses my Mo clan suffered."

The two Mo clan Gu Immortals were furious, the giant beast brought disaster to Mo clan, causing heavy losses. The areas these two were responsible for suffered even more severe damage.

"You want to kill me?" During the battle, the mysterious giant beast suddenly spoke human words.

Mo clan's two immortals were shocked and their hearts jumped wildly.

At the same moment, the giant beast opened its mouth and shot out its long purple-red tongue.

The long tongue moved with astonishing speed and pierced through a Mo clan Gu Immortal's body. Almost instantaneously, this Mo clan Gu Immortal was corroded by the strong poison and turned into nothingness.

Only the immortal aperture turned into an indistinct light speck and fell to the ground.

"You are a legendary immemorial beast!?" The remaining Mo clan Gu Immortal was horrified and retreated in panic.

But it was already late.

The mysterious giant beast was Qing Chou. It laughed coldly as ghost qi started surging around it. The dense layers of ghost qi turned into ghostly figures which blocked the Mo clan Gu Immortal.

Qing Chou closed in slowly: "Didn't you want to kill me and pull out my bones and tendons?"

Mo clan's Gu Immortal shouted in fear: "Spare me, I belong to Mo clan. Spare me and Mo clan won't pursue you any further."

"Pursue me?" Hearing this, a trace of anger flashed past Qing Chou's face: "You two idiots do not even know you are being used by others. Go and die!"

"Ahhh—!" The Mo clan Gu Immortal let out a painful shriek as ghostly figures pounced on and killed them.

After killing these two Gu Immortals, Qing Chou looked towards the desert.

Sand flew wildly on the ground, turning into a giant monster, it was an immemorial sand monster. This was the assistance brought by the Mo clan Gu Immortals, they were able to restrain Qing Chou by using it.

But the Mo clan Gu Immortals had not expected Qing Chou to be a legendary immemorial desolate beast with wisdom that surpassed ordinary humans. Qing Chou took advantage of this point, pretending to be an ordinary immemorial desolate beast, which made the Mo clan immortals complacent and relax their guard. Then with Qing Chou's fierce counterattack, the immortals died.

With the death of the Mo clan immortals, this immemorial sand monster was no longer controlled; its movement began to slow down and it stood on the ground while looking at Qing Chou.

Qing Chou stared at the immemorial sand monster: "Get lost!"

The immemorial sand monster shook with fear and immediately turned around, plunging into the desert and escaping.

Qing Chou scared away the monster but the surrounding ghost qi intensified further, it looked at a certain area in the sky and sneered: "Two despicable worms, are you still not coming out?"

The moment its words came out, Heavenly Court's two immortals, Nine Spiritual Fairy and Red Heart Traveler, slowly showed themselves. They were floating in the sky side by side and were looking down at Qing Chou.

Previously, when Red Heart Traveler was searching for the Blood Sea true inheritance, he was obstructed by Demon Immortal Qi Jue. After realizing Demon Immortal Qi Jue's goal, Red Heart Traveler resolutely gave up on the Blood Sea true inheritance and continued to chase Qing Chou with Nine Spiritual Fairy.

After all, Qing Chou's matter concerned Heavenly Court's plan. And, even if he got the Blood Sea true inheritance, it would only raise Red Heart Traveler's strength. The more important thing was clear with one glance.

Nine Spiritual Fairy and Red Heart Traveler possessed Heavenly Court's secret method, so they continued to trace and soon discovered Qing Chou.

But the two did not dare to make a move rashly.

This was Western Desert, enemies were all around them, and it was not the territory of these two immortals. If they rashly started a fight, with the other being a legendary immemorial desolate beast, once the fight entered a stalemate, Western Desert's native Gu Immortals would interfere and the situation would become too unstable.

After some discussion, Nine Spiritual Fairy transformed into an immemorial desolate beast and destroyed the surrounding resource points, attracting some Mo clan Gu Immortals.

The two Mo clan immortals brought an immemorial sand monster but they were not even able to make Qing Chou expend its energy, instead, Qing Chou discovered traces of the two Heavenly Court immortals.

With their plan failing and Qing Chou exposing their position, the two Heavenly Court immortals showed themselves and attacked.

Boom boom boom!

The two immortals were both rank eight and were extraordinary indeed. Their moves were violent and their attacks were like unceasing waves.

Qing Chou immediately fell into a disadvantage.

But Qing Chou was an immemorial desolate beast, its body was extremely tough and thick, there was no injury even after getting hit by several rank eight killer moves.

After dozens of exchanges, it became familiar with the techniques of the Heavenly Court immortals and began to slowly turn around the situation.

However, this did not last long, a qi tide began to appear.

It was because the immortal apertures of the dead Mo clan immortals had opened the entrance and started to absorb heaven and earth qi to stabilize themselves.

There was a difference in the heaven and earth qi in these two immortal apertures and the outside world, and along with the accumulated impact from the fights between the Gu Immortals and Qing Chou, a giant qi tide was formed.

Qing Chou suffered heavy restriction in the qi tide, its strength fell sharply. On the contrary, the two Heavenly Court immortals had offered their immortal apertures and only had phantom apertures, thus they were not affected too much in the qi tide.

Qing Chou roared and struggled but it was all in vain.

It then realized that the two Heavenly Court immortals still had another layer of planning. They did not just use the two Western Desert immortals, they even calculated their immortal apertures in their plan!

Just as Qing Chou was fighting bitterly, Peng Da shook his head and opened his eyes.

"Where am I?" After a moment of daze, he discovered he was being carried by Mo Li and they were moving on a huge sand dune.

"Uncle, you saved me again." Peng Da sighed.

"You are awake." Mo Li smiled.

"Uncle, you can put me down."

But Mo Li shook his head: "Your injuries are severe, although I healed you, you should not move within a short period of time."

Peng Da smiled bitterly: "I have troubled uncle again. Where is this?"

Mo Li replied: "Sigh, we were swept away for over ten thousand li by the hurricane, we are now going back."

Mo Li had lived many years in the desert, he naturally had a method to distinguish the directions.

Peng Da was immediately worried after hearing Mo Li's words: "Uncle, you still want to return? You want to go back and die?!"

Mo Li was silent for a while, his voice was low and deep, containing resolution: "I also know returning is risky, but if I don't even see the appearance of the killer of my wife and son, I will never be able to rest easy!"

"Uncle..." Peng Da did not know what to say. He understood the sadness and hatred Mo Li was feeling right now, and it was because of this, he was unable to persuade him further.

Mo Li continued: "Brat, I am thankful for your concern. After we travel a bit further, I will drop you off with enough water and food. It won't be an issue for you to cross the desert and get to the nearest city."

"Uncle, I won't leave, I can't leave you alone."

"Don't make a scene!"

"I am not making a scene, you are the one who is irrational!"

Just as the two were quarreling, the sand below Mo Li began to move and formed a huge whirlpool that sucked both of them inside.

Mo Li quickly used his Gu worms but it was of no use.

He was pale with shock: "What is going on? My Gu worms actually have no effect!"

Peng Da also tried with no result, his face was extremely pale: "Is this quicksand? We are going to be sucked in!"

This quicksand was too strange, their methods were useless on it.

The two were getting closer and closer to the center of the quicksand, their bodies were slowly buried under the sand and their faces were ashen.

"Am I going to die?" Peng Da mumbled.

Mo Li heaved a deep sigh: "I implicated you, Peng Da."

"I, I don't blame you uncle. It was all my choice." Peng Da felt his heart beating wildly and his throat parched, he did not know what to express.

The feeling before impending death was really the worst!

But soon, Peng Da's attention was caught by another thing.

He found that uncle Mo Li who usually had great mental fortitude was actually crying.

Mo Li sobbed: "I am going to die but my revenge has yet to be done! I did not even see the killer's true appearance. I am too weak, too weak! I don't even have the qualifications to approach the enemy. The gap between immortals and mortals is too big, I am only a mortal, I am like an ant!"

Peng Da opened his mouth to console Mo Li, but he did not know what to say.

At the next moment, the hot sand poured into his mouth as Peng Da quickly closed it. His whole body was buried and his sight was filled with darkness.

"Am I going to die?"

"I am dying like this?!"

"Hehehehe, I am truly pitiful, to think that my journey in this new world is going to end like this."

"I really don't want to die, I really don't want to die!"

Suddenly, in his dark vision, there were specks of starlight.

"Huh? I didn't die?" Peng Da sat up and looked at the scene in front of him in disbelief.

He was now at the bottom of a dry well, the quicksand whirlpool continued to rotate in the entrance of the well, but the strange thing was that the sand did not fall down.

There was a mysterious force here that stopped the quicksand whirlpool and only allowed Peng Da and Mo Li to enter it.

"Uncle, uncle?" Peng Da immediately saw Mo Li and shouted twice before he got a reaction.

"Kid, you are awake? This is an immortal opportunity, we have struck gold!" Mo Li turned around, saying with excitement and shock: "This is very likely an inheritance left by a Gu Immortal."

"Uncle, you are certain?" Peng Da's eyes opened in incredulity, this was too dreamlike, the ups and downs of life came too suddenly.

He was not a greenhorn who had just transmigrated, the current Peng Da had traveled with Mo Li's caravan many times and knew about the Gu world. Gu Immortals and Gu Immortal inheritances were always a topic of discussion among Gu Masters in their idle time, he did not expect the unreachable thing to appear in front of him now.

"Damn it, damn it!"

"Why is there no reaction?"

Mo Li attempted many things and was getting restless but the starlight showed no reaction.

"Uncle, this might not be a Gu Immortal inheritance, right? I feel like you are thinking too much." At this time, Peng Da finally stood up and walked towards Mo Li.

Mo Li did not retort, he also began to doubt his previous judgment.

But right at this time, the starlight suddenly made a movement. Like tidal waves, they passed by Mo Li and entered Peng Da's body.

The two were shocked.

This happened so fast that when they reacted the starlight had already entered Peng Da's body.

Without the starlight, the well fell into darkness.

Mo Li activated his Gu worm, creating a lump of fire in his hand that brightened the well once again.

Peng Da was standing on the spot in daze like a statue with his eye eyes wide open.

Mo Li quickly neared him: "Peng Da, Peng Da! Are you alright?"

Only then did Peng Da react: "Un... uncle, you were correct, this is truly a Gu Immortal inheritance and it is Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's inheritance!"

"What, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable?!" Mo Li was shaken, they had a lot of understanding regarding venerable existences as well. Due to the current time and situation, the Gu Immortal world's knowledge was no longer secret among mortals.

Mo Li's gaze turned slightly complicated: "This means to say, Peng Da, you are an otherworldly demon? No wonder the inheritance did not respond to me."

Peng Da felt ashamed: "Uncle, I didn't intentionally conceal it from you. It was just that..."

"Alright." Mo Li waved his hand: "So what if you are an otherworldly demon? You are still Peng Da, the person I know, isn't that so?"

Peng Da was extremely moved and nodded his head quickly: "Yes! Thank you for understanding, uncle."

Mo Li shook his hand: "Alright, alright, you really struck it big this time. Since you inherited the Demon Venerable's inheritance, then use the method to leave here quickly. Ordinary methods are useless here."

Peng Da felt ashamed: "The situation is like this, uncle, although I have many Gu worms, I cannot use them. This is the first time I am seeing these Gu worms and need a lot of practice. Moreover, according to the inheritance, I must use one of the killer moves to leave here."

"Then practise it quickly, ask anything you don't understand, uncle will guide you!"

"Yes, thank you uncle."

"Is there still a need for thanks between us?" Mo Li smiled: "Practise quickly, we don't have much water and food."

As the inheritor, it did not matter if Peng Da ate or drank in the well, but Mo Li could not share the same benefit.

Over the next few days, Peng Da practised without resting. He was only a mortal so the Gu worms he practised with were all mortal Gu.

This was the first time he was coming in contact with these Gu worms, although there were detailed explanations in the inheritance, he still needed to practise and master these Gu worms.

Mo Li helped Peng Da to study and learn, once they had some progress, Peng Da would hand the Gu worms to Mo Li for demonstration and guidance.

Mo Li was an experienced Gu Master, although he did not have the qualifications to inherit the Thieving Heaven true inheritance, he had much more efficient ways to probe these Gu worms.

Finally, Peng Da was barely able to master the usage of several Gu worms and found a way to use a killer move.

"Go on Peng Da, try to succeed in one attempt!" Mo Li encouraged Peng Da.

"Watch this, uncle." Peng Da used the killer move for the first time but it did not succeed.

The killer move activation failed and he suffered backlash, he coughed blood and fell on the ground.

"Peng Da, are you okay?" Mo Li quickly inspected Peng Da's body.

Peng Da squeezed words out through his mouth: "I have disappointed you, uncle. But rest assured, I will definitely... ah!"

Suddenly, his eyes opened wide.

He then looked at his chest with an incredulous expression.

His chest was pierced through by Mo Li's hand, his heart was destroyed because of this sneak attack!

"Un... uncle..." Even more blood started flowing out of Peng Da's mouth.

Mo Li raised his head slowly, his eyes were filled with tears and his expression was extremely twisted, unfamiliarity and fear filled Peng Da's mind.

Mo Li's voice was extremely hoarse: "I want revenge, I want revenge! But the true inheritance chose you, uncle had no other options, Peng Da! You are too young, you practised for so long but you could not even master a killer move. Uncle cannot wait any longer, uncle cannot depend on you."

Mo Li then took out his hand.

Peng Da powerlessly fell onto the ground, his eyes helplessly looking at the entrance of the well.

He was dead.

But Mo Li did not stop, he activated his Gu worms and captured Peng Da's soul.

"Alright, the Thieving Heaven true inheritance is mine now." Mo Li laughed. Peng Da's blood was splattered on his face, his bloodstained face had a dazzling smile.

Chapter 2017: Bai Ning Bing Versus Hei Lou Lan

Central Continent, on a certain nameless and ordinary peak.

Four Gu Immortals arrived at the base of the mountain while concealing themselves.

"Hei Lou Lan is on this mountain." Ying Wu Xie looked at the peak and spoke.

At his sides were Fairy Zi Wei, Old Man Zheng Yuan, and Bai Ning Bing.

After Fairy Zi Wei and Old Man Zheng Yuan forced Bai Ning Bing to surrender, they obtained Ying Wu Xie's whereabouts. Ying Wu Xie was a split soul of Spectral Soul and his mission had always been to rescue his main body.

But due to his strength and Fang Yuan's arrangements, Ying Wu Xie could not enter Heavenly Court. After the fate war, fate Gu was destroyed and Fang Yuan escaped, while Ying Wu Xie wandered around Central Continent, resenting Fang Yuan for not saving Spectral Soul's main body.

After Fairy Zi Wei provided enough evidence, Ying Wu Xie learned his main body was no longer in Heavenly Court and had gotten free by himself.

Ying Wu Xie was exulted, he directly abandoned Fang Yuan and joined Fairy Zi Wei's group.

Through Ying Wu Xie, Fairy Zi Wei's group learned that he had just recently separated from Hei Lou Lan. Thus, the four immortals quietly arrived at this place.

Ying Wu Xie said softly: "Hei Lou Lan is a formidable person, although her cultivation is low and her battle strength is not high because future self has lost its effect, she has great endurance and knows how to wait patiently, she is ambitious and cannot be looked down upon."

Ying Wu Xie did not doubt his side's strength, but what he was most worried was if Hei Lou Lan would side with them and betray Fang Yuan or not.

In this aspect, Fairy Zi Wei was confident, she said with a smile: "I have full confidence in making Hei Lou Lan surrender. She has a complex relationship with Fang Yuan, but it is not firm. Hei Lou Lan wants to kill her own father for revenge, this is her greatest wish. Fang Yuan has captured Hei Cheng and because his strength is higher than Hei Lou Lan's, she has always been controlled by him. We can use this to make her surrender."

Know yourself and your enemy, and you will never be defeated.

Back then, Fairy Zi Wei tried all sorts of methods to deduce Fang Yuan's position, but could not do anything because Fang Yuan was slippery like an eel and his most skilled wisdom path aspect was in blocking deductions.

Fairy Zi Wei could not do anything against Fang Yuan, but she investigated everything about Fang Yuan's subordinates. But at that time, even if she wanted to use these indirect ways to find Fang Yuan's location, they all ended up in failure.

But now, Fairy Zi Wei was going against Hei Lou Lan. Those past failures had now become her source of confidence.

Immediately, Fairy Zi Wei made arrangements: "This time, Ying Wu Xie, you stay behind. Bai Ning Bing, you will approach Hei Lou Lan. You can say you obtained news from Ying Wu Xie and came to visit. When you near her, sneak attack and seal her in ice. After you get her under control, I will persuade her."

"How about I go with her?" Ying Wu Xie did not feel assured.

Bai Ning Bing glanced at him and flew away.

Ying Wu Xie quickly looked at Fairy Zi Wei, Fairy Zi Wei, however, shook her head: "We will watch it from here."

Bai Ning Bing flew across the sky like a flash of white light, she looked down at the peak and shouted: "Hei Lou Lan, are you here?"

After a while, Hei Lou Lan came out from a mountain cave and frowned slightly as she looked towards Bai Ning Bing: "Why are you here?"

Bai Ning Bing laughed and pointed at Hei Lou Lan: "I have joined Spectral Soul now and have come to capture you. Hei Lou Lan, if you are smart, then just let yourself be captured."

Hei Lou Lan's eyes opened wide: "Are you for real?"

At the base of the mountain, Ying Wu Xie almost stomped his foot in anger: "I knew that Bai Ning Bing would spoil the matter. Her nature is eccentric and she prioritizes fun. She did this on purpose, she definitely felt this way would be more interesting!"

Sure enough, Bai Ning Bing's laughter was heard: "Of course I am for real!"

Saying so, she turned into white light and charged at Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan had already been preparing and with a shout, she raised her hands and sent out a large amount of flames to counter the white light.

Bai Ning Bing was caught off-guard and was forced back to the sky.

But she looked even more excited: "Fire path method? You actually changed to this path? Haha, interesting, I already wanted to fight you! But how long can you block me for?"

Immortal killer move — Bai Xiang!

Bai Ning Bing directly activated her trump card method, her body was no longer a flesh and blood body, and was covered in overflowing frost qi that even shrouded the mountain peak.

Hei Lou Lan entered the mountain cave and Bai Ning Bing gave chase without being afraid of any traps.

The two fought inside the cave, causing explosions that cracked and shattered the mountain rocks.

After several exchanges, Hei Lou Lan fell into a disadvantage and her situation did not look good.

Hei Lou Lan's aptitude, temperament, and natural talents were at top level, but her fortune was not good and she ran into Fang Yuan too early. Fang Yuan dominated her and used Hei Cheng to control her, which greatly influenced her cultivation.

Hei Lou Lan's strength qi Immortal Gu, flying bear strength Immortal Gu, and self strength Immortal Gu became Fang Yuan's possessions. Slavery Immortal Gu was also borrowed by Fang Yuan and consumed. Divert disaster Immortal Gu was destroyed when she underwent tribulation.

During the period of the fate war, Hei Lou Lan almost always relied on the killer move future self. Once the future self was broken, Hei Lou Lan returned to her previous self.

Fang Yuan did not summon her back, Hei Lou Lan also held ambitions and did not want to be controlled by Fang Yuan, so she actively searched for a way to be free.

She possessed her aunts' true inheritances, and after enough pondering, she resolutely changed to cultivating Blazing Heaven Demoness' fire path.

But unfortunately, before she had good progress, she was discovered by Fairy Zi Wei and was now chased by Bai Ning Bing.

Hei Lou Lan felt bitter inside, she wanted to retreat but was chased closely by Bai Ning Bing.

When she slowly lost the strength to attack and was about to be captured by Bai Ning Bing, a white light flew over from the horizon.

This white light appeared slow but was extremely fast, Bai Ning Bing's Bai Xiang form actually could not dodge it and was struck.

In an instant, Bai Xiang froze in the air, no longer moving.

"Hei Lou Lan has reinforcements?!" Ying Wu Xie was shocked.

"Not reinforcements, this should be Longevity Heaven's members." Fairy Zi Wei said with a smile.

Ying Wu Xie realized, Fairy Zi Wei had already taken Bai Ning Bing's nature into her calculations, her main goal had been to use Bai Ning Bing to trigger Longevity Heaven's ambush. The reason she did not send Ying Wu Xie was in fact because she wanted to protect him, Ying Wu Xie was Spectral Soul's clone after all, he was truly one of them. And Bai Ning Bing, who possessed Bai Xiang, was the perfect candidate to probe the ambush!

"This is a time path killer move, is it Fang Yuan?" Hei Lou Lan had a complex expression as she looked towards the horizon through the gaps in the cave.

Rank eight Immortal Gu House Calamity Luck Altar appeared in the horizons, and in almost an instant, arrived at the center of the battlefield.

Calamity Luck Altar sent out a strong light that shone on the unmoving Bai Ning Bing.

Although the killer move Bai Xiang was amazing, Calamity Luck Altar was a rank eight Immortal Gu House that was personally created by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. If Bai Ning Bing was struck head-on, her death was certain.

Fairy Zi Wei quickly made a move, sending out a purple aurora to cover Bai Ning Bing while blocking Calamity Luck Altar's powerful light.

"I was wondering who it was, so it turns out to be the leader of the defeated Heavenly Court!" Bing Sai Chuan's voice came from Calamity Luck Altar.

Fairy Zi Wei shook her head slightly and flew to the sky with Old Man Zheng Yuan: "We have already joined Lord Spectral Soul, we are no longer in Heavenly Court's faction."

Bing Sai Chuan sneered: "Like I care about which side you are on! Hei Lou Lan is my Longevity Heaven's descendant, she is a member of Northern Plains. Don't even dream of harming her!"

Fairy Zi Wei retorted: "The five regions have merged, all the regional walls have disappeared, what do you mean by Northern Plains? We will need to fight to decide where Hei Lou Lan goes."

Bing Sai Chuan did not speak any nonsense, he directly controlled Calamity Luck Altar to collide into Fairy Zi Wei.

A huge battle erupted!

Hei Lou Lan and Bai Ning Bing were put under control, unable to budge.

Hei Lou Lan's face was ashen, she was fully aware that be it Heavenly Court or Longevity Heaven, they were trying to use her to search for clues about Fang Yuan!

This was the result of having low cultivation level, she had become an object for the two sides to fight over. No one asked her if she was willing or not.

This battle did not last long, both sides were holding back.

It was Fairy Zi Wei who took the initiative to stop: "No need to fight anymore, there is no harm in giving Hei Lou Lan to you."

Bing Sai Chuan had Immortal Gu House Calamity Luck Altar while Fairy Zi Wei was without Star Constellation Chessboard and was in a weakened state. The reason she attacked was because she wanted to trigger a qi tide and use it to claim victory.

But Bing Sai Chuan clearly knew of Fairy Zi Wei's plan and made Calamity Luck Altar use all its might. Fairy Zi Wei saw the battle turning increasingly fierce and knew her side would have to use their full strength if they wanted to hold on until the qi tide arrived, so she directly chose to stop.

"We have a common objective, it doesn't matter where Hei Lou Lan ends up in. Fang Yuan is at his weakest state currently, if we miss this rare chance and let him recover, it will be too late. We can even work together, what do you think, Bing Sai Chuan?" Fairy Zi Wei made a proposal.

Then, she showed evidence to prove her current faction.

"Who could have thought that there would be a day when we cooperate!" Bing Sai Chuan was silent for a while before sighing.

Both sides had their own venerable as their backer and they both wanted to kill Fang Yuan, they had the qualifications to cooperate as well as a common goal, so working together was indeed a wise choice.

Chapter 2018: Impending Fatal Calamity

Central Continent, deep beneath a certain Earth Trench.

Calamity Luck Altar was floating in the air, there were tall cliffs on both sides, while below it was unfathomable darkness.

It was emitting soft light and did not conceal its aura, scaring away any beast that tried to approach it.

At the middle of the cliff was a giant cave that was dug by Fairy Zi Wei and the rest.

Purple light flickered in the cave and a wisdom path formation was already set up, Fairy Zi Wei sat at the center and Old Man Zheng Yuan sat at the assistant's position, on one hand, he was using human path methods to cooperate with Fairy Zi Wei, on the other hand, he was using a portion of the immortal formation to guard against Bing Sai Chuan.

After all, it was the first time these two sides were collaborating, they had to err on the side of caution.

There were several formation cores at the edges of the formation as well. Bai Ning Bing, Hei Lou Lan, and Ying Wu Xie were sitting in these formation cores as the crucial clues.

Purple light swayed, rising and falling at times like tides.

After a long while, Fairy Zi Wei opened her eyes slowly and stopped this wisdom path immortal formation, the overflowing purple light dissipated slowly.

"How is it?" Bing Sai Chuan's question came from Calamity Luck Altar.

Fairy Zi Wei sighed and shook her head: "It is still not enough. But this method is absolutely effective. These three have set alliance agreements with Fang Yuan, their connections are extremely tight. As long as we capture even more Gu Immortals, we can deduce Fang Yuan's exact location."

The large formation was dismantled and the Gu worms flew back to Fairy Zi Wei's immortal aperture.

Ying Wu Xie and the others stood up.

Bai Ning Bing smiled: "This is not difficult. During the fate war, Fang Yuan had dispatched not only us but also a large number of transformation path Gu Immortals."

Hei Lou Lan added: "From what I know, these transformation path Gu Immortals were incorporated after Fang Yuan annexed an immemorial grotto-heaven. After the fate war, Fang Yuan disappeared without leaving behind any traces, these people should still be scattered around Central Continent."

Ying Wu Xie shook his head: "But these transformation path Gu Immortals don't have a close connection with Fang Yuan, it is better if we look for Lady White Rabbit and Fairy Miao Yin, these two are crucial characters that are only second to us."

Fairy Zi Wei had stored all the Gu worms by now, she did not have formation flag Gu or similar methods, it was rather time-consuming every time she dismantled the formation.

She looked towards Calamity Luck Altar which had been guarding from the side: "It is better if we split our forces to search for White Rabbit and Miao Yin. If we encounter Fang Yuan's transformation path Gu Immortal subordinates along the way, we can make the decision to make a move at our own discretion."

Shortly after, Bing Sai Chuan's response came from Calamity Luck Altar: "Of course. For our following plans, we will need more communication between us."

Fairy Zi Wei nodded: "Indeed."

Although the scale of this cooperation was small and duration was short, it had huge significance and both sides had begun to trust each other.

Calamity Luck Altar picked up Hei Lou Lan while Bai Ning Bing and Ying Wu Xie stayed with Fairy Zi Wei, both sides separated and departed on their own.

Immemorial two heavens.

Crescent Moon grotto-heaven.

"Fairy Crescent Moon, you won't surrender even if the alternative is death?" Xiao He Jian, Lady Cold Ash and the rest were looking down from high above, looking at the dying Gu Immortal in the ruins.

Fairy Crescent Moon had rank eight cultivation and was the owner of Crescent Moon grotto-heaven. She had the terrain advantage but she was completely outnumbered, she was only hanging on her last breath now.

She spat and said with hatred: "You bandits, my Crescent Moon grotto-heaven has no conflicts with the outside world and has never provoked you nor had any ambitious plans. I will never surrender to you!"

"Then die!" Lady Cold Ash was already impatient, she pointed her finger, a grey light shot out and struck Fairy Crescent Moon.

Lady Cold Ash put her hand inside her sleeve, Fairy Crescent Moon's soul was carried by the grey light and brought to her.

"This is a rank eight Gu Immortal's soul, devouring her soul will be much more effective and also much easier to absorb." Lady Cold Ash was Spectral Soul, but he was able to conceal it from the whole of Wu Shuai's alliance.

Xiao He Jian looked at her: "Lady Cold Ash, you battled in the front lines and slaughtered countless enemies, collecting a vast number of mortal souls and many Gu Immortal souls. Those are your battle spoils, but Lord Alliance Leader specially asked for this rank eight soul. You cannot take it."

Spectral Soul was slightly stunned before smiling and handing this rank eight soul to Xiao He Jian: "Since our alliance leader wants it, why would I dare to take it."

Inside her heart, however, she was snorting coldly: "I shall hand this to you for the time being, in the future, I will settle both our old and new grudges together!"

Xiao He Jian nodded with approval and took Fairy Crescent Moon's soul while consoling Lady Cold Ash: "Let's go, let the others clean up here. Follow me to see the alliance leader and report the battle."

"I can finally get close to Wu Shuai. This is a good chance!" Spectral Soul's mood lifted upon hearing that.

However, when the two arrived in Dragon Palace's hall, they only saw Wu Shuai's will sitting on the main seat.

Wu Shuai's will heard the report and praised: "Lady Cold Ash, you made the most contributions in this invasion of Crescent Moon grotto-heaven, well done."

"It is our duty to work for alliance leader." Lady Cold Ash was extremely disappointed but showed a smile on her face.

"Alright, you can leave. When we hand out the rewards based on contribution later, you will not be disappointed." Wu Shuai's will waved his hand.

The two left Dragon Palace, Spectral Soul, however, felt discontent inwardly: "It is really a pity that we were not able to see alliance leader."

Xiao He Jian glanced at her, feeling some disdain towards Lady Cold Ash's conduct in trying to flatter the alliance leader when they were not even in front of him: "How can Lord Alliance Leader be available whenever you want? He has been in closed cultivation to resolve the danger of the qi harvest fruits. We only need to follow his orders."

"Yes."

Xiao He Jian's expression softened as he patted Lady Cold Ash's shoulder: "Work well and follow me, you will be able to play a key role in the alliance one day!"

"Then I will depend on lord's guidance." Spectral Soul put up a performance while internally scheming on when to capture Xiao He Jian!

"It is good that you understand." Xiao He Jian smiled and walked forward.

He had joined the alliance because of Qi Jue's true inheritance, as a lone force, he was suppressed by Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and others. But Xiao He Jian's strength surpassed ordinary rank eights, he was slowly stabilizing his footing in the alliance and had won over some Gu Immortals under him.

Lady Cold Ash's performance had been extremely outstanding in the latest battle and she had displayed extraordinary battle strength, so despite her being a pure human, Xiao He Jian wanted to rope her in to his side.

On the other side.

"Granny Skeleton has arrived—!" The doorman shouted.

Granny Skeleton entered the hall and saw Qi Sea Ancestor on the main seat, she quickly cupped her hands and bowed, getting straight to the point: "Skeleton grotto-heaven is willing to come under Qi Sea Ancestor."

Qi Sea Ancestor nodded: "Hahaha, Granny Skeleton, you are wise. You will not regret joining my side."

Granny Skeleton sighed and asked: "I wonder when Lord Ancestor can get rid of the qi harvest fruit's problem?"

"I have already made good progress in this, you can rest assured." Fang Yuan changed the topic, "Skeleton grotto-heaven is the nearest to Crescent Moon grotto-heaven. Crescent Moon grotto-heaven has now already fallen to Wu Shuai's side, I am willing to send troops and station some Gu Immortals in Skeleton grotto-heaven, I hope you can cooperate."

Granny Skeleton sighed, although Fang Yuan did not show the ability to resolve the danger of qi harvest fruits, due to the outside world's condition, Granny Skeleton could only lower her head and join him.

"With the current situation, there is really nothing else I can do. Currently, there are almost no unaffiliated grotto-heavens left in the immemorial two heavens. They have either joined Wu Shuai or have been recruited by Qi Sea Ancestor. Sigh, I wonder what the future will be like." Granny Skeleton did not obtain the answer she wanted and left worriedly.

The pressure on Fang Yuan was also increasing.

"A wisdom path great expert was deducing about me just now, the strength is also quite high! It seems like Fairy Zi Wei."

Fairy Zi Wei was deducing the whereabouts of Fang Yuan, Fang Yuan naturally sensed it. This was the same as a contest of the two's wisdom path methods across space.

"According to my luck, this situation is not looking good. The fatal calamity is impending, danger is lurking everywhere, and there is only a trace of hope."

Fang Yuan's Cooking Luck Pot might only be at rank seven, but he could glance at a portion of his luck and deduce the entirety from it.

Fang Yuan had already made positive progress regarding the qi harvest fruits. But he was still at his wits' end on how to refine heaven path dao marks.

He was aware that this trace of hope fell on the heaven path dao marks. Only be refining the heaven path dao marks and recovering his strength could he get free from the incoming calamity. If he could not refine them or did not refine them in time, it would be dangerous.

"But where is this breakthrough point that I seek?"

Chapter 2019: Rank Eight Hatred Gu

Western Desert.

The intense rank eight level battle was still continuing.

Qing Chou roared, its tongue shot out with lightning speed.

Bam bam bam...

The blood red figures that surrounded Qing Chou were easily pierced and destroyed by its tongue.

Every time the blood red figures exploded, Red Heart Traveler's face would turn a shade paler. His brows were furrowed and his teeth were clenched shut, but his fighting spirit did not diminish as he used all his strength to maintain the battlefield killer move.

"Red Heart Traveler won't be able to hold on for long like this." Nine Spiritual Fairy, who was fighting Qing Chou, had been paying attention to Red Heart Traveler's condition.

They had tied down Qing Chou with a lot of difficulty, Red Heart Traveler had used a battlefield killer move and was able to temporarily entrap this legendary immemorial desolate beast.

However, Qing Chou had intelligence comparable to a human's, after it discovered it was unable to break free from this battlefield killer move, it concentrated its attacks on Red Heart Traveler in order to break through.

Once Red Heart Traveler was unable to hold on, the battlefield would dissipate and Qing Chou could walk out free. With this experience, it would definitely be extremely vigilant and it would be almost impossible to capture it again in a short period of time.

"Fine! I can only use that move." Nine Spiritual Fairy gritted her teeth and made a huge decision.

Immortal killer move — Nine Spiritual Transformations!

Her body suddenly shook as she transformed back to her human form. She was a transformation path great expert and should be much stronger after transformation to another form. But right now, even though she returned to her human form, her aura was surging and she was even stronger than her previous self. Nine spiritual lights shot out one after another from her immortal aperture and formed an enormous nine-colored barrier of light, the barrier had nine layers with distinct colors.

Qing Chou had been concentrating on Red Heart Traveler, so it felt a great shock from Nine Spiritual Fairy's sudden outburst and quickly split some of its attacks towards her.

But at this stage, the killer move nine spiritual transformations was already completed and had no flaws.

Nine Spiritual Fairy gave a clear roar, the nine-colored barrier shook and the nine layers of light mixed together, becoming extremely dazzling.

The mixed light sphere then transformed into a rhinoceros with a large head and small body, and was shining with various colors. It charged towards Qing Chou.

Qing Chou roared and gave up on Red Heart Traveler for the moment, and without dodging, it charged towards this rhinoceros.

With a loud explosion, the surroundings shook intensely.

After the two enormous monsters collided, it was actually Qing Chou who had to take a small step back while the huge rhino only stopped in its spot.

Qing Chou was shocked and furious, it had not expected this rhino to be so strong. As far as it was concerned, this multi-colored rhino was translucent and it could even see Nine Spiritual Fairy who was in the center, there was no feeling of it being a solid transformation. But the collision made Qing Chou realize: this multi-colored rhino was stronger than the previous solid transformations!

"Qing Chou fell into a disadvantage in the collision, this is the first time since the battle started! Nine spiritual transformations is indeed worthy of being a legendary transformation path killer move." Red Heart Traveler was happy and worried at this sight. The price of using nine spiritual transformations was very high, after a Gu Immortal cultivates the killer move nine spiritual transformations, they can only use it nine times in their life.

Nine Spiritual Fairy had chosen to expend one usage of such a valuable killer move on Qing Chou, it showed her determined will!

Qing Chou roared, its bestial nature was agitated, it charged at Nine Spiritual Fairy again.

But the multi-colored light sphere that Nine Spiritual Fairy was in changed suddenly, from a large rhino to a southern fire sparrow.

The fire sparrow spread its wings and flew to the sky.

Qing Chou charged at empty space, without even looking up, it activated its defensive methods.

Sure enough, at the next moment, Qing Chou heard the sharp cry of the fire sparrow, then the sparrow collided onto its back. Whoosh, blazing flames engulfed it.

Qing Chou's hurriedly activated defensive methods only lasted for a few breaths of time before they broke.

Qing Chou counterattacked fiercely, beast roars and bird cries mixed together, the two sides were at a deadlock.

Red Heart Traveler finally had a brief respite and quickly used the time to adjust his condition. While regulating his breath and observing the battle, he started to feel worried.

"Qing Chou is too sturdy, although it is being suppressed and the battle tempo is firmly held by Nine Spiritual Fairy, it has sufficient stamina."

"On the contrary, Nine Spiritual Fairy might hold the upper hand and have control over the battle, but she cannot last for long. If there is no external help and this goes on, she will definitely run out of stamina and die."

Red Heart Traveler decided to take a risk.

He accumulated his strength while waiting patiently. After waiting for two hours, he finally saw a chance.

The chance was momentary, Red Heart Traveler immediately made his move!

He spat out a mouthful of blood. The fragrant blood flew to the air and started rotating. Like a miniature blood sun, it emitted endless blood red light, rushing to Qing Chou.

Although Qing Chou was in a fierce battle with Nine Spiritual Fairy, it had never let go of its vigilance against Red Heart Traveler.

However, when it used its killer move to block this tiny blood sphere, it was of no use. The blood sphere seemed to be illusory, it passed through the obstruction and struck Qing Chou's chest, turning into a red sun insignia.

Qing Chou's expression changed immediately, it could feel that its every movement was being tied down by the red sun insignia.

This was an extremely powerful seal, it quickly showed its might, it slowed down movement, interfered with killer moves, and lowered fighting spirit.

"Damn it, damn it!!!" Qing Chou roared and started attacking wildly.

Nine Spiritual Fairy used all her strength to hold Qing Chou back, but was being beaten back little by little.

With a loud explosion, Qing Chou finally broke through Red Heart Traveler's battlefield killer move.

However, Red Heart Traveler had a smile of victory on his face.

Qing Chou's whole body was bound by blood threads, the source of the countless blood threads was the blood sun insignia at the center of its chest.

"Success. Cough cough cough!" Red Heart Traveler coughed out large mouthfuls of blood, his face pale like paper.

Nine Spiritual Fairy quickly suppressed the increasingly slower Qing Chou while transmitting her voice: "Red Heart, do you need my help?"

Red Heart Traveler shook his head slowly and used a killer move with difficulty, healing his wounds while enduring the intense pain.

Nine Spiritual Fairy spent much effort before finally suppressing Qing Chou.

Looking at Qing Chou, who was bound by the blood threads like a mummy, Nine Spiritual Fairy praised: "What method is this, it could actually capture Qing Chou!"

Red Heart Traveler was barely able to reply: "This is a temporary move I created, I have not named it yet."

Nine Spiritual Fairy looked towards Red Heart, slightly widening her eyes: "I am truly amazed!"

Red Heart Traveler shook his head, smiling bitterly: "Don't overestimate me. I detected that Qing Chou's vital Gu was rank eight hatred Gu, so I made this move. If it were other legendary immemorial beasts, this move would be a joke. I could have the chance to use this move because you did not hesitate to activate nine spiritual transformations."

Nine Spiritual Fairy also shook her head: "Capturing Qing Chou concerns the plan of capturing Fang Yuan, this is an important matter for Heavenly Court and for the people of the world, how could I refuse to pay such a small price. But is this hatred Gu the one recorded in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>?"

"Yes." Red Heart Traveler nodded.

Nine Spiritual Fairy sighed: "This explains why Qing Chou can distinguish its enemies. Unfortunately, it did not have a killer move to make full use of it. Now that we have captured it, we can take out the hatred Gu and use Heavenly Court's killer move to find the location of Fang Yuan, Spectral Soul, and other demons!"

Red Heart Traveler restrained his aura: "Let's go, we cannot stay here for long."

They had engaged in a fierce battle for a long while, although the battlefield killer move saved a lot of time and also concealed most of the traces of battle, there were bound to be Gu Immortals who would come to check this place.

Not to mention other forces, Mo clan's assembled troops might already be rushing on their way.

Nine Spiritual Fairy and Red Heart Traveler had battled for a long while, their conditions were not perfect. They detained Qing Chou and moved towards Central Continent.

Sure enough, just a short while after they left, several Gu Immortals of Mo clan arrived with surging momentum in an Immortal Gu House.

"There was a fierce battle here!"

"Although there are few traces, it can be seen that it was a rank eight level fight."

"No wonder my clan's Gu Immortals perished so quickly."

"Give chase, we have an Immortal Gu House with us, they won't be able to run far!"

Mo clan's group followed the traces and chased the two Heavenly Court immortals.

Several days went by again.

A sandstorm blew and a Gu Master was struggling to move in the desert.

He reached the center of the battlefield and saw the deep craters that were mostly buried by the sandstorm. He raised his head and roared.

This person was Mo Li, who killed Peng Da and seized Thieving Heaven's true inheritance!

He went through all kinds of troubles to get here as soon as possible, thinking of seeing the true appearance of the culprit that killed his wife and son, but he was too late.

"I am going to find you and cut you to pieces!"

"No matter who you are or what monster you are, I will kill you!!"

Mo Li knelt on the desert and roared towards the sky.

Peng Da's soul was floating beside him. Peng Da gave a cold laugh: "Hehehe, you, a mere mortal, wants to take revenge against an immortal beast?"

"So what if it is an immortal beast?" Mo Li's eyes were red as he stared at Peng Da's soul, his expression was malevolent: "I have Thieving Heaven's true inheritance, I have Thieving Heaven's true inheritance! I can definitely become a Gu Immortal and succeed in taking revenge!"

Peng Da laughed again: "There is another possibility as well, this immortal beast was already killed by the Gu Immortals. You have no target to take revenge against already."

Mo Li was stunned and was silent like a statue.

After a long while, he suddenly moved his hand and grabbed the throat of Peng Da's soul, he seemed to be in a state of insanity: "No! It won't die, I won't allow it to die! It must die by my hands!!"

Mo Li continued to shout: "I will become a Gu Immortal, I have Thieving Heaven's true inheritance, I can definitely take revenge! I can definitely take revenge! Tell me, tell me how to use the next Gu worm!"

While grabbing Peng Da's soul, Mo Li activated his Gu worms, wisps of white smoke and sizzling sounds came from the area where Mo Li's hand touched Peng Da.

Peng Da's soul immediately let out a sharp screech from the unbearable pain: "I will speak, I will speak, this is called electric circuit Gu."

"Electric circuit Gu? What is this thing?"

Peng Da's soul hesitated for a bit: "How can I explain this? You are not an otherworldly demon, you won't be able to understand what an electric circuit is. Simply speaking, it is the path that electric currents move along."

Mo Li sneered: "What is so hard to understand about it? It is not like I have not read \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>! \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> has recorded that lightning Gu chose to cooperate with Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance to find a way out, they eventually managed to leave immemorial blue heaven. This should be the true meaning behind electric circuit[1]!"

Peng Da's soul was stunned.

Mo Li kept on praising: "Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable is truly worthy of being a venerable. He actually has such creative thoughts, he must have obtained the inspiration from \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, thus creating electric circuit Gu!"

Peng Da's soul: "..."

[1] It can be read as 'Lightning Path/Road' which is how these Gu world people interpret the Gu. Back

Chapter 2020: Rank Nine Lightning Gu

Forest Lightning grotto-heaven.

"Forest Lightning Grotto Lord, you betrayed the two heavens alliance and actually colluded with Qi Sea Ancestor, this is an unforgivable sin and you will be executed for it." Xiao He Jian looked down from above.

Behind him were a large number of Gu Immortals from the two heavens alliance. They were all standing silently and expressionlessly, showing the numerical superiority.

On the contrary, Forest Lightning Grotto Lord was facing the enemies alone, his strength paled in comparison.

Forest Lightning Grotto Lord gave a bitter smile: "Since you found out, I don't have anything to say. But do you think I am willing to collude with the enemy? The alliance wants to experiment on the qi harvest fruit in my Forest Lightning grotto-heaven. None of the alliance's previous attempts have succeeded and all the grotto-heavens they have tested on have detonated. I sided with the two heavens alliance for self-protection. But now, you want to sacrifice my home? Since that is the case, it is better to surrender to the enemy, I might even have some new hope."

Xiao He Jian frowned, snorting coldly: "You have no confidence in our two heavens alliance and Lord Alliance Leader Wu Shuai. Perhaps this time will succeed."

Forest Lightning Grotto Lord chuckled: "If alliance leader Wu Shuai had a fair disposition, I would have nothing to say. But he is clearly protecting variant humans while sacrificing humans. The grotto-heavens the alliance has experimented on are all human grotto-heavens. Wu Shuai is a dragonman after all, I have seen through this alliance's farce! Human Gu Immortals present here, watch carefully, this will be your outcome in the future. After me, it will be your turn."

Hearing this, the human Gu Immortals clearly had a slight change in expressions. Forest Lightning Grotto Lord had no doubt spoken of what they were worried about.

Wu Shuai and Qi Sea Ancestor were the same person, they naturally had a tacit agreement. They looked to be confronting each other on the surface, but were secretly dividing the two heavens' forces. By now, there were no neutral grotto-heavens in the two heavens. The grotto-heavens in the two heavens were either destroyed or had joined Wu Shuai or Qi Sea Ancestor.

After the two sides divided the two heavens, they ceased fighting and began to find a way to solve the qi harvest fruit problem.

Compared to Qi Sea Ancestor who was researching in closed cultivation, Wu Shuai's qi path attainment was clearly much weaker. So, Wu Shuai's two heavens alliance had no choice but to experiment and be very rough with their actions to pursue efficiency. The experiments to eliminate the qi harvest fruits had failed many times and destroyed many grotto-heavens as a result.

When it was Forest Lightning grotto-heaven's turn, Forest Lightning Grotto Lord was not willing to bet his home, so for self-protection and survival, he secretly contacted Qi Sea Ancestor.

He was truly an unfortunate guy, Qi Sea Ancestor and Wu Shuai were in essence the same person.

Qi Sea Ancestor was Fang Yuan's main body and he informed Wu Shuai directly.

Wu Shuai thus sent the command to Xiao He Jian to gather some Gu Immortals to punish the traitor.

Looking at Forest Lightning Grotto Lord, Xiao He Jian sneered silently and said with impatience: "Who is going to get this criminal?"

Lady Cold Ash stepped forward like she wanted to be the vanguard: "Let me."

Xiao He Jian nodded: "Good."

Lady Cold Ash directly charged towards Forest Lightning Grotto Lord, Xiao He Jian was inwardly happy and thought: "Cold Ash is perceptive and has a lot of capability. My efforts to win her over were not a waste."

Lady Cold Ash fought with Forest Lightning Grotto Lord, both were at rank eight and went at each other, neither yielding a step.

The other Gu Immortals of the two heavens alliance were watching the battle from atop the clouds. In a fight between Gu Immortals, for a group attack to work, they would have paid attention to cooperation. Different paths would cause conflicts between dao marks, if there was no skillful cooperation, it might instead waste their efforts.

Naturally, this did not hinder the observing Gu Immortals from accumulating their energy and attacking when there was a chance.

But the two heavens alliance's Gu Immortals did not find any opportunity to sneak attack.

Lady Cold Ash gradually gained the upper hand and control of the battle. Forest Lightning Grotto Lord saw the situation was bad and immediately escaped below ground.

Lady Cold Ash was Spectral Soul's disguise after all, how could Forest Lightning Grotto Lord be her match? The deadlock earlier was only a deception, it was nothing more than Spectral Soul's act.

Xiao He Jian saw Forest Lightning Grotto Lord fleeing and laughed heartily: "Chase!"

The immortals gave chase.

They did not care about the large Forest Lightning grotto-heaven and only targeted Forest Lightning Grotto Lord. As long as they got rid of this sole rank eight, other resistances would not be an issue.

They even took the initiative to maintain the safety of Forest Lightning grotto-heaven, after all, this grotto-heaven needed to be tested on and they would have a share in the distribution of the resources inside it.

Forest Lightning Grotto Lord kept on moving deep underground.

Lady Cold Ash did not give chase and stayed beside Xiao He Jian.

Soon, the first group of Gu Immortals who had entered deep underground returned with soot covering them.

When he obtained their report, Xiao He Jian was slightly stunned: "There is such a thing? There is a lightning forest deep underground?"

The returning Gu Immortals naturally brought evidence.

Through methods similar to shadow image Gu, the two heavens alliance's immortals saw a vast lightning forest.

In the pitch-black underground, lightning flashed and thunder rumbled every moment.

The flashes of lightning formed a tall silver tree. The tall tree only lasted for a moment, but it had large thunder leaves, many silver lightning branches and so on, they were materialized and tempted all the immortals.

"Heaven, these are all priceless lightning path rank eight immortal materials!"

"This is only the superficial wealth of the lightning forest. According to the records in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, the source of lightning forest is lightning Gu. The size of this lightning forest is enough to prove there is a rank eight lightning Gu here!"

"Forest Lightning Grotto Lord wants to resist by relying on lightning Gu?"

"Hmph, wishful thinking. How could a mere rank eight Immortal Gu oppose our two heavens alliance?"

The immortals discussed but no one was willing to enter the forest.

After all, the lightning forest was a dangerous area and Forest Lightning Grotto Lord possessed an enormous terrain advantage here. If they rashly invaded, it was very likely to be an unrewarding venture.

Xiao He Jian frowned: "Who will go capture Forest Lightning Grotto Lord?"

Lady Cold Ash stood up once again without hesitation.

Xiao He Jian showed a pleased smile: "Cold Ash, if you win, your contribution will be at the top for this battle."

"Thank you." Lady Cold Ash was about to move.

"Wait." Night Heavenly Wolf Lord also walked out: "The Lightning forest is a dangerous region, let me accompany Cold Ash. If there is any unexpected mishap, I can be of some assistance."

"Let's do it that way then." Xiao He Jian agreed to Night Heavenly Wolf Lord's request.

Thereupon, the two immortals charged towards the depths of the underground. Other Gu Immortals along with Xiao He Jian were floating in the air, watching the battle as well as waiting patiently.

Lady Cold Ash charged to the bottom and arrived in front of the lightning forest. She directly opened her immortal aperture and let out countless soul beasts.

The soul beasts charged towards the lightning forest like a violent tide.

Rumble...

Lightning struck continuously and explosions resounded unendingly. There were severe losses to the soul beasts, they used their lives to forcibly pave open a path.

Lady Cold Ash and Night Heavenly Wolf Lord smoothly entered the depths of the lightning forest.

"I didn't think Lady Cold Ash would actually deal with the lightning forest like this."

"She is really resolved to suck up to Xiao He Jian regardless of the cost."

"There have been many rumors recently about the alliance leader wanting to make Xiao He Jian a vice alliance leader?"

"The alliance only has one vice alliance leader, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch, currently. It is not strange for Lord Wu Shuai to make this arrangement to keep the balance between his subordinates."

"Lady Cold Ash might be a human Gu Immortal but she doesn't want to have the same outcome as Forest Lightning Grotto Lord's. So she wholeheartedly wants to climb ranks in the alliance, she is doing her best to protect her grotto-heaven."

Gu Immortals observed the battle while conversing secretly.

After a while of effort, Lady Cold Ash and Night Heavenly Wolf Lord fought their way to the center of the lightning forest and saw Forest Lightning Grotto Lord once again.

Forest Lightning Grotto Lord was refining rank eight lightning Gu and quickly stopped the refinement when he saw the two immortals. He shouted in anger: "Stop! If you take one more stop, I will destroy this lightning Gu!"

The immortals were surprised.

"So this lightning Gu is still a wild Immortal Gu and Forest Lightning Grotto Lord has not actually refined it?"

"What is going on?"

"Haha, I understand! Forest Lightning Grotto Lord's ambition is not small."

"Oh, please explain."

"If I am not wrong, this lightning forest should have been just an ordinary lightning path resource point at the start. But at a certain point, it gave birth to a wild lightning Gu. Because of this lightning Gu, the lightning path resource point gradually transformed into a small lightning forest. Forest Lightning Grotto Lord did not refine this wild lightning Gu, instead he added resources to grow this lightning forest. The larger the scale of the lightning forest, the lightning Gu, which is the source, will also keep on advancing further. Forest Lightning Grotto Lord kept on investing resources and finally advanced this wild lightning Gu to rank eight!"

The two heavens alliance's Gu Immortals saw through the ambitions of Forest Lightning Grotto Lord.

Forest Lightning Grotto Lord was a lightning path Gu Immortal and was not proficient in refinement path. But this lightning forest was created naturally, it was simply nature refining Gu itself!

Forest Lightning Grotto Lord cleverly borrowed the power of nature and added momentum to the original foundation, his goal was to advance lightning Gu to rank nine level!

And during this process, if he refined this wild Immortal Gu, the process of nature refining Gu would be interrupted and could not be recovered.

Thus, Forest Lightning Grotto Lord had left this wild lightning Gu in its state and did not refine it.

It was extremely difficult to seize other's Gu worms. But wild Immortal Gu were different.

A rank eight wild Immortal Gu, the crucial thing was that it even had the possibility of advancing to rank nine! This discovery was extremely huge, Xiao He Jian and the rest opened their eyes wide, revealing greed and wariness.

"This is of vital importance, we cannot be rash." Xiao He Jian quickly transmitted his voice to Lady Cold Ash and Night Heavenly Wolf Lord.

Lady Cold Ash and Night Heavenly Wolf Lord paused their attacks.

Forest Lightning Grotto Lord spoke conditions: "As long as you spare me and my Forest Lightning grotto-heaven, I will offer this lightning Gu to you."

Xiao He Jian quickly contacted Wu Shuai and reported this matter.

The matter concerned a future rank nine lightning Gu, Xiao He Jian did not dare to decide by himself.

Chapter 2021: Blue Heaven Shatters

Soon, Xiao He Jian received the reply. He personally flew underground and faced Forest Lightning Grotto Lord: "Alliance Leader has said that he can let you go, but Forest Lightning grotto-heaven must belong to the alliance. Of course, the alliance will not carry out any risky attempts on the qi harvest fruit in the grotto-heaven."

"No!" Forest Lightning Grotto Lord's attitude was extremely firm: "This grotto-heaven is my home, I will not give it up! It won't change owners, this is my territory, what qualifications does the alliance have to seize it? I will look after the lightning Gu for the moment, retreat and don't try to invade again from now on. I can set an agreement with the alliance to never seek lightning Gu. If the alliance wants rank nine lightning Gu, you can provide the resources to raise it in the lightning forest here."

Xiao He Jian did not respond and only reported Forest Lightning Grotto Lord's request to Wu Shuai.

Wu Shuai mumbled for a while, unable to come to a decision.

He then sent this information to the main body through secret methods and let the main body decide.

Fang Yuan fell into deep thought.

"Rank nine Immortal Gu have supreme might, it is indeed worth yielding a step. But this lightning Gu is only rank eight currently. To raise it to rank nine, who knows how many resources and how big of a price we have to pay. And there could be many unexpected mishaps during this process!"

"Another crucial point is that lightning Gu's information cannot be concealed, this news will definitely lead to chaos. Be they Heavenly Court, Longevity Heaven, or other forces, they will all interfere. Wu Shuai's and Qi Sea Ancestor's forces must have an all-out battle in the end."

Fang Yuan's wisdom path attainment was deep and immediately deduced the future changes.

Forest Lightning Grotto Lord concealed the secret of lightning Gu because he wanted to keep it for himself. But now that he could not keep it, he could only use this chip to negotiate.

Since he could secretly contact the enemy, he would not just negotiate with Wu Shuai's alliance, he was sure to contact Qi Sea Ancestor.

Fang Yuan's Qi Sea Ancestor disguise protected humanity and had allied with Heavenly Court, he could never let a variant human force like Wu Shuai's alliance obtain rank nine lightning Gu!

Thus, Qi Sea Ancestor would have to send troops.

At that time, Forest Lightning Grotto Lord would surely curry favor with both sides and strive to win some respite. This Forest Lightning Grotto Lord truly had high astuteness and was deeply aware of the way of survival of the weak.

But like this, it was bound to increase the friction between Qi Sea Ancestor and Wu Shuai. This was exactly what Fang Yuan had been trying to avoid.

And at that time, Heavenly Court would definitely add fuel to the fire, even Longevity Heaven, Demon Immortal Qi Jue, and the five regions' forces would stir up the situation from the dark.

Although Fang Yuan was the leader of both sides, he was unable to restrict every subordinate. In the fight between these subordinates, if anyone died, Wu Shuai and Qi Sea Ancestor would need to take some action to preserve their side's benefit and prestige. The situation would escalate and continue being irremediable until it finally leads to an all-out battle.

But if Fang Yuan suppressed the situation, this would not fit the attitudes of Wu Shuai and Qi Sea Ancestor. It would definitely be filled with giant loopholes in the eyes of wisdom path Gu Immortals. Heavenly Court would start to have doubts and the whole situation would turn even more dangerous.

Thus, this situation was not as simple as just a lightning Gu.

This would implicate many things, it would involve variant humans, humans, and even the overall situation of the two heavens and five regions!

Fang Yuan was unable to come to a decision immediately for such a huge matter.

After all, he had to think of many factors, the important thing was that his current strength had fallen. He was at his weakest state and now was the time when he needed to rest and recuperate.

"I remember lightning Gu is recorded in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, the power it showed was quite strong..."

Fang Yuan browsed through \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, chapter four, section thirty —

Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance and Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence were sent flying away by fate Gu and were forced to leave Ren Zu, arriving at immemorial blue heaven.

Rumble!

Thunder rumbled unceasingly here. Lightning flashed, imprinting the sky and forming a forest of lightning.

"I am angry! I am angry!" The source of this lightning forest was a lightning Gu, it was roaring continuously.

Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance and Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence were extremely afraid. The lightning was too strong, so long as a lightning bolt struck them, they would be heavily injured or even die.

They did not move at all, afraid of lightning Gu discovering them and bombarding them to death.

They waited patiently for lightning Gu's anger to dissipate. They would move once it calmed down.

But lightning Gu was extremely angry and its anger did not show any signs of decreasing. The lightning forest kept on growing in size.

"What should we do?" Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence was worried: "How can we return to father? Brother, do you have any good suggestions?"

Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance shook his head, his brows furrowed: "It is all fate Gu's fault! It forcefully separated us from father, I am definitely going to take revenge in the future. Argh, my heart hurts every time I think of fate Gu."

Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance held his chest, he found his heart aching more and more.

How could this be?

He quickly opened up his chest and looked at the depths of his heart.

"Oh, why is there a Gu in my heart?" Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance was astonished: "It is no wonder my heart is in constant pain, this Gu was biting on my heart."

Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence also saw this Gu worm: "Isn't this love Gu? I heard father mentioning it before."

"No, I am hatred Gu." The Gu worm spoke: "Although I look similar to love Gu on the surface."

Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence urged: "Hatred Gu, why are you gnawing on my brother's heart, please stop quickly."

But hatred Gu said: "I won't! I am building my home here, I am changing your brother's heart into a heart of hatred."

Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance was furious: "Who allowed you to build your home in my heart? Get out quickly, I don't welcome you. If you don't get out, I will crush you to death!"

Hatred Gu laughed loudly: "I was attracted by lightning Gu's anger, but unexpectedly discovered that your heart is more suitable for my home. I won't leave."

Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance was furious, he actually put his hand inside his heart and grabbed hatred Gu.

Hatred Gu was like a curved blade without a handle, Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance's hand was pierced and bled as he grabbed it.

He clenched his teeth and exerted strength, crushing hatred Gu to death.

But at the next moment, hatred Gu resurrected from the blood and became even bigger.

Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance crushed it to death again, hatred Gu revived once again, its size becoming slightly bigger again.

"It is useless." Hatred Gu said: "Hatred cannot be killed, vengeance only breeds more hatred and grudges, the more you treat me like this, the more your hatred will increase."

Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence was somewhat stunned and helpless against hatred Gu.

"It hurts, it hurts, it hurts!" Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance covered his chest, his face pale from the pain.

Hatred Gu was drilling in and out of his heart, creating holes after holes, transforming his heart into a heart of hatred.

The current Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance hated fate Gu even more.

"If I was not sent flying here by fate Gu, how could I have encountered hatred Gu? How could my heart be pierced by hatred Gu?"

"I will definitely destroy fate Gu, I will definitely take revenge."

The more Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance thought, the more he hated. He was no longer afraid of angering lightning Gu, he stood up suddenly.

"Sister, let's go, I don't want to stay here." Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance held Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence's hand.

But Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence hesitated: "Brother, there is lightning all around us, we don't know when it will strike, it is too dangerous."

Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance said: "Sister, don't be afraid. The hatred in my heart has shown me a path, that is the path of revenge. There is no lightning on this path, as long as I follow it, I can find fate Gu and take revenge against it. Quick, follow me!"

Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance dragged Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence.

The strange thing was that despite lightning bolts crackling around them, not a single one struck Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance and Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence.

The two ran and ran when they suddenly collided into something.

"What is ahead?" Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence touched the air in front of her and found it was like a transparent wall.

"This is the heavenly wind qi wall, the border of the immemorial nine heavens." Hatred Gu explained.

"Brother, there is a wall ahead, we cannot leave." Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence said helplessly.

But Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance had a different perspective: "Where is the wall? I only see the path ahead, as long as we follow along this trail, we can definitely leave and find fate Gu!"

Time and again, Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance got up and rushed forward before colliding into the heavenly wind qi wall, his head bled as he fell to the ground. Then, he climbed up and charged forward again.

Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence wanted to stop him, but Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance did not listen.

Hatred Gu laughed: "It is useless. I have already built my home in his heart, although his eyes are open, he can only see the path that I point towards, he cannot see any other thing. Hahaha."

Right at this time, lightning Gu sensed Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance and Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence, the terrifying lightning forest began to quickly spread towards them.

There was no road to advance or retreat, Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence was extremely anxious but did not have any ideas: "It would have been great if we still had wealth Gu!"

Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance did not listen to her, he continued to collide into the heavenly wind qi wall. Blood filled the ground.

Lightning Gu finally reached closer, Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence cried: "Am I going to die here?"

But Lightning Gu restrained its power and approached slowly, it let out a rumbling sound: "Don't worry, oh humans, I won't harm you or injure you. On the contrary, I want your help."

Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence stopped crying and asked curiously: "Lightning Gu, you are so strong, how can we possibly help you?"

Lightning Gu: "I have been trapped here all along, immemorial blue heaven is large but I am already sick of it. I want to go out but I am unable to find a path that leads to the outside, thus I am angry. Anger often leads to hatred, so hatred Gu was attracted here."

"But from your brother, I can see the path to exit. Therefore, humans, let us cooperate. I will help you break the heavenly wind qi wall and you will bring me out of here, alright?" Lightning Gu proposed.

Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence and Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance were very happy at this suggestion.

"I agree to it. Your help will be great." Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance replied.

Thereupon, lightning Gu landed on Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance's hand and started to emit a terrifying radiance.

Hatred Gu laughed loudly: "Let me lend you a hand."

Lightning Gu obtained hatred Gu's strength and became extremely powerful.

Rumble rumble...

Lightning Gu erupted with fierce strength, not only destroying the heavenly wind qi wall but even shattering the whole of immemorial blue heaven!

"Quickly leave!" Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance was greatly shocked and knew that they had created a huge disaster, he quickly grabbed his sister and left with lightning Gu and hatred Gu.

Chapter 2022: Heavenly Court Seeks To Fight

"According to \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, hatred Gu and lightning Gu can cooperate and amplify each other's power to form a terrifying killer move that directly destroyed immemorial blue heaven?"

Fang Yuan read it carefully again as he wondered, did this mean that these two Gu worms could counter heaven path?

Where were heaven path dao marks most gathered in?

Undoubtedly, the immemorial nine heavens.

Besides them, there was Fang Yuan's body.

"This seems to be an avenue to resolve my current predicament." Fang Yuan pondered: "But only lightning Gu is here, it won't work without hatred Gu. Where is this Gu worm? Is there currently such an Immortal Gu in existence? If not, how do I refine it? If it exists, the situation is even more troublesome as I will need to scheme and plan to seize it."

"In fact, even if I have these two core Immortal Gu, it is still a mystery on how to form them into that killer move. \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> is too vague about it."

Just at this time, Qin Ding Ling personally sent a letter through treasure yellow heaven.

Fang Yuan opened and read it, the letter Gu directly talked about Forest Lightning grotto-heaven's matter. Qin Ding Ling was very eager about lightning Gu, and even wanted Qi Sea Ancestor to stop researching the qi harvest fruits for the time being and lead his subordinates to cooperate with Heavenly Court in fighting for lightning Gu.

"Why is Heavenly Court so anxious?" Fang Yuan's eyes shined with bright light: "Also, they obtained the information too quickly. Looks like they have arranged some spies on Wu Shuai's side."

Qin Ding Ling was not Fairy Zi Wei after all, she was slightly hurried in doing things, which allowed Fang Yuan, who had deep wisdom path attainment to deduce some possibilities.

"Since that is the case..." Fang Yuan smiled bitterly, Heavenly Court's urgent letter made him come to a decision.

Forest Lightning grotto-heaven.

Xiao He Jian's expression changed slightly, he had received Wu Shuai's command.

His gaze turned cold as he shouted: "Alliance Leader sent the command to kill Forest Lightning Grotto Lord without worrying about lightning Gu. It is nothing to lose a mere rank eight Immortal Gu. We must execute all the Gu Immortals of Forest Lightning grotto-heaven and then attempt to get rid of the qi harvest fruit. Don't worry about the grotto-heaven's resources, use all your strength to complete the task in the shortest time possible!"

"What?!" Hearing these words, not only Forest Lightning Grotto Lord, even Lady Cold Ash and Night Heavenly Wolf Lord were astonished.

This was a future rank nine Immortal Gu, Wu Shuai gave up on it so resolutely?

For an instant, none of the three immortals made a move due to the shock.

Night Heavenly Wolf Lord was Heavenly Court's mole, he naturally thought of helping to preserve Forest Lightning Grotto Lord to harm Wu Shuai's alliance.

And Lady Cold Ash was basically Spectral Soul, he also thought of preserving this point of conflict that would incite a fierce battle between Wu Shuai and Qi Sea Ancestor. As long as there was chaos, he could gain many chances to act.

Forest Lightning Grotto Lord suddenly shouted: "Xiao He Jian, such audacity, you actually gave a false command. Wu Shuai is expanding his strength, how can he give up on the future rank nine Immortal Gu? As someone who joined recently, you truly have ill intentions!"

Xiao He Jian's expression turned cold from Forest Lightning Grotto Lord's incrimination.

He did not retort, instead glaring at Lady Cold Ash and Night Heavenly Wolf Lord: "This is our alliance leader's command! Are you going to believe a traitor or me? Attack!"

Saying so, Xiao He Jian did not wait for the two and charged in by himself.

Bam bam bam...

Killer moves were let out, destroying a large portion of the lightning forest.

"Charge!" The alliance immortals who were above ground also received Xiao He Jian's order and came over, besieging this lightning forest.

Since the situation became like this, Lady Cold Ash and Night Heavenly Wolf Lord could not care about their own schemes, they sighed and joined the group in attacking.

"Wu Shuai, you are really cruel! You are so narrow-minded, you will definitely die miserably!" Forest Lightning Grotto Lord knew he was going to die and let out a vicious curse while exerting strength to destroy lightning Gu.

"In your dreams." At the next moment, Lady Cold Ash suddenly appeared behind him.

Forest Lightning Grotto Lord stiffened, Lady Cold Ash took the chance and actually seized lightning Gu from his hands!

"What method is this?" The immortals were astonished.

Although Spectral Soul's attainment levels had fallen to a miserable level, he still had plenty of methods. The accumulation of a venerable could not be estimated by ordinary rank eight Gu Immortals.

"Great job!" Xiao He Jian was exulted. He had held no hope in taking lightning Gu, but who could have thought it would truly be seized. This was Lady Cold Ash's merit and his as well. By now, his vice alliance leader position was already half confirmed. The remaining half would be by completing the task given by Wu Shuai!

Forest Lightning Grotto Lord counterattacked madly.

To preserve lightning Gu, Lady Cold Ash had forcibly endured his attacks and got injured.

"Retreat and guard lightning Gu!" Xiao He Jian quickly came to help, he blocked Forest Lightning Grotto Lord for Lady Cold Ash.

To prevent interference, other immortals began to plunder resources while watching Xiao He Jian fight Forest Lightning Grotto Lord alone.

Forest Lightning Grotto Lord had already fought with Lady Cold Ash before, his condition was not optimal and almost all of his methods were exposed.

Based on the superficial strength shown, Xiao He Jian was stronger than Lady Cold Ash as well.

This battle held no suspense, and soon, Xiao He Jian defeated Forest Lightning Grotto Lord.

Forest Lightning Grotto Lord was not resigned to being defeated and was still thinking of escaping.

But the surrounding Gu Immortals had been observing the battle and encircled Forest Lightning Grotto Lord with no way for him to flee.

Forest Lightning Grotto Lord was beheaded and Forest Lightning grotto-heaven was destroyed. The alliance's experiment on the qi harvest fruit failed this time as well.

Moreover, because Wu Shuai asked for the battle to be finished as quickly as possible, most of the resources in Forest Lightning grotto-heaven were destroyed. The participating Gu Immortals could only collect very few resources.

The greatest gain was that wild rank eight lightning Gu. But it was clear this was going to be handed to Alliance Leader Wu Shuai.

Fang Yuan thought for a good while before finally deciding to deal with the problem directly, getting rid of Forest Lightning grotto-heaven so that the conflict could not grow.

Wu Shuai's fast decision not only astonished the alliance members, it even destroyed Heavenly Court's plan.

Qin Ding Ling had obtained first hand information from Night Heavenly Wolf Lord and immediately contacted Qi Sea Ancestor.

Fang Yuan received the letter; in the letter, Qin Ding Ling was still insisting on seizing lightning Gu even though it had already fallen into Wu Shuai's hands. Even if they could not seize lightning Gu, they had to destroy it!

"Looks like Heavenly Court is determined to get lightning Gu. Heavenly Court should have lightning Gu's Immortal Gu recipe, they can refine it themselves if this Gu is destroyed."

Fang Yuan was even more curious, why was Heavenly Court so anxious to get lightning Gu? Why did such the powerful Heavenly Court have such pressing needs for this Immortal Gu? Lightning Gu was not fate Gu after all!

Fang Yuan did not understand Heavenly Court's scheme, but Qin Ding Ling's attitude made Fang Yuan's previous plan fall through.

Fang Yuan made Wu Shuai destroy Forest Lightning grotto-heaven without any regards for the safety of lightning Gu to strangle the possible conflict to death and prevent a war between the two sides.

But Heavenly Court held an attitude akin to asking for battle, Fang Yuan also could not refuse it easily.

After all, Qi Sea Ancestor was allied with Heavenly Court.

How should he deal with this?

Chapter 2023: Inviting Qi Sea

Profound Literature grotto-heaven.

Capital city, Su clan.

There was a book house erected inside a certain guest room's courtyard.

This book house was a mortal Gu House, it had the form of a tree house, covered with green leaves and branches.

Right now, Li Xiao Bai was sitting cross-legged inside the book house.

A beautiful girl was standing in front of him, she was Su Qi Han. Su Qi Han's expression was somewhat serious: "Xiao Bai, have you really thought it through? A vital Gu cannot be changed easily."

Li Xiao Bai nodded with a smile: "Qi Han, don't be too worried. I have thought it through properly, I am most interested in composing poems. So to me, poetry Gu is the most suitable vital Gu. It was just that I was not qualified to change my vital Gu before. But since this book house has extraordinary might and has the function of assisting me in changing vital Gu, how can I let go of such a chance?"

Su Qi Han sighed: "Since you have decided, I won't urge you anymore. I will guard you from outside."

"Mm." Li Xiao Bai did not stand on ceremony, directly closing his eyes.

After he obtained this Book House inheritance, he returned to the capital city and reunited with Su Qi Han. Although he lost in the poetry competition, he had already proven himself. Su Qi Han invited him to stay temporarily in Su clan, no one opposed to it, instead, this became a beautiful story.

Li Xiao Bai was not stingy, after staying in Su clan, he shared this Book House inheritance with Su Qi Han. The two spent almost every day in the book house, continuously cultivating, researching, and communicating intimately with each other.

Although the two had undergone intimate activities because of a coincidence, they did not have close feelings for each other. Su Qi Han's previous actions came from her own high moral character.

But over these days of contact, Su Qi Han increasingly appreciated Li Xiao Bai's talents and started to feel an attraction to him.

Li Xiao Bai obtained this fortuitous encounter but did not conceal it from Su Qi Han and shared it with her. From this, Su Qi Han saw that Li Xiao Bai's character was pure and kind, willing to give her anything, he was definitely not a heartless scholar.

Although the two had not been officially engaged, Su Qi Han had already treated Li Xiao Bai as her sole lifelong partner.

Su Qi Han walked out of the book house with worry: "This book house has high value and contains many branches of information path like verses, ditties, odes and songs. However, these branches are limited to Gu Master cultivation and there are no ways to advance to Gu Immortal. I have already hinted Xiao Bai many times that as long as he marries into and lives in my Su clan, he can obtain Su clan's Calligraphy Immortal cultivation technique. Unfortunately, he has no interest in calligraphy and is wholeheartedly focused on poems. Oh, since he likes it, I have no way to persuade him otherwise. If he accomplishes nothing in the future and stays as a Gu Master, I will work hard to become a Gu Immortal and an official of the Imperial Court. I will protect and take care of him for the rest of my life. I will watch him compose and recite poems, as long as he is happy, I am also happy."

Profound Literature grotto-heaven had an Imperial Court.

The high ranking officials of the Imperial Court were all Gu Immortals. Su Qi Han was Su clan's most beloved daughter and the apple of their eye, her aptitude and talents were astonishing as well, so it was natural for her to come in contact with Su clan's immortal cultivation technique.

"Young miss, you should take a rest, you will be tired if you keep on standing. With us here, Great Scholar Li's safety is guaranteed." The guards and the maids urged Su Qi Han.

Su Qi Han shook her head: "Stand guard outside the courtyard. I will personally guard him here."

The book house started shaking, gentle light spread from the inside to the outside through the windows.

A few minutes later, the book house turned silent, the leaves and the branches were no longer shaking.

Inside the book house, Li Xiao Bai opened his eyes slowly.

The process of changing vital Gu went smoothly, Li Xiao Bai looked inside his aperture and saw a Gu worm that looked like a heart; it had a red jade-like texture and was covered by a layer of light gold radiance.

It was his new vital Gu, rank five Gu worm — Poetry.

Poetry Gu was classified in information path and belonged to a side-branch of information path cultivation. The most common form of information path cultivation were oaths and vows, like sea oath Gu, mountain pledge Gu, promise Gu, black and white paper Gu. Second was transmitting information like goose Gu, paper crane Gu, butterfly letter Gu, flying sword letter Gu, messenger dove Gu, and so on. Thirdly was watching, listening, reading, and writing, for example, water text Gu belonged to the writing category. Beast language Gu was related to reading and speaking.

Verses, ditties, odes, songs, and so on were simply not mainstream.

Li Xiao Bai had made such a decision, it was no wonder Su Qi Han was worried about his future prospects.

But she did not know Li Xiao Bai's true intention.

"This grotto-heaven's environment is special as it is under the effect of the killer move, assisting literary talents. As long as I create great poems, I can obtain rewards and advance quickly. The five regions chaotic war is drawing close, such a way that can quickly increase one's strength with no side-effect is priceless. Although Su Qi Han can get in contact with Gu Immortal cultivation methods, she does not know the outside world's situation."

"I have changed my vital gu to poetry Gu, next, I will practice poetic Gu and emotion poetry Gu, use gather poem Gu to gather poems externally and advance poem wall Gu. Additionally, I should also practice poem boundary Gu, this is an extremely outstanding Gu worm which effect is similar to a battlefield killer move."

Just as Li Xiao Bai was thinking, the door was opened slowly and Su Qi Han entered with a concerned look.

"Xiao Bai." Su Qi Han spoke softly.

Li Xiao Bai gave a light smile and nodded towards her: "Everything went smoothly."

Su Qi Han smiled, her beautiful watery eyes revealed delicate concern: "That's good."

Boom—!

Suddenly, the sky shook and an explosion resounded throughout the grotto heaven.

"What's going on?" Li Xiao Bai and Su Qi Han were alarmed and rushed out of the room, they looked at the sky but it was clear and blue. A gust of wind blew past them.

The wind only lasted for a very short period of time, and after it passed by, there was no other abnormality.

The mortals, Gu Masters, and even Gu Immortals living in the capital city sensed this suddenly appearing and disappearing abnormality. Most of the people were baffled, but a few Gu Immortal officials who knew the inside details were joyous.

"Success!" In a certain area of Profound Literature grotto-heaven, Old Immortal Hua Yu bowed deeply towards Qi Sea Ancestor in excitement: "Congratulations to Ancestor for successfully handling the qi harvest fruit calamity. Ancestor has saved the whole of Profound Literature grotto-heaven, this favor is the same as giving us new life! From now on, if you have any orders for me, I will undoubtedly use all my strength without question!"

Qi Sea Ancestor laughed heartily, lifting Old Immortal Hua Yu up: "No need to be so courteous."

The immortals standing at the side were extremely happy.

"Ancestor has divine might!"

"Wu Shuai's side tested repeatedly and destroyed so many grotto-heavens. Ancestor tried for the first time and succeeded, Wu Shuai can never match you."

"I wonder when Ancestor can resolve our qi harvest fruit problem?"

"Yes, our grotto-heavens' qi harvest fruits have already become extremely large and are getting closer to self-detonation."

Gu Immortals praised loudly while also urging Fang Yuan to continue his work.

Fang Yuan waved his hand: "This test was a success but I sensed some flaws in it. I need to be in closed cultivation for three days to solve this issue. At that time, I will clear up the danger for everyone, wouldn't that be even better?"

The immortals were exulted: "We shall listen to Ancestor's arrangements!"

Fang Yuan smiled, a sharp light flashing across his eyes.

Heavenly Court.

Soon, Qin Ding Ling received this news and immediately showed joy: "Good, good! My choice to cooperate with Qi Sea Ancestor was indeed correct."

Qi Sea Ancestor did not let down their expectations, not only creating a method to resolve the qi harvest fruit problem, but even succeeding after using it once. According to the information, Profound Literature grotto-heaven's qi harvest fruit was not only safely removed, the fruit also burst and formed a harmless qi tide that swept past the whole grotto-heaven and raised the grotto-heaven's foundation by a good amount.

Qin Ding Ling was in a great mood.

Over this period of time, Heavenly Court had already walked out of the shadow of defeat in the fate war. With Qin Ding Ling and the other Heavenly Court immortals' schemes and efforts, good news came one after another.

Firstly, the variant human forces were restrained, secondly, Qing Chou was captured, and now, the qi harvest fruit's danger was eliminated.

"But now, should we get rid of the qi harvest fruit in Heavenly Court first or try to fight for lightning Gu?"

Qin Ding Ling could not come to a decision by herself and gathered the Heavenly Court immortals for a meeting.

"Qi Sea Ancestor is worthy of being a qi path great expert, with this method, his force will be stable and in an impregnable position."

"Wu Shuai's alliance is still experimenting with various methods, their qi path attainment is too shallow."

"As long as Qi Sea Ancestor defers for some time, there might not even be a need to start a fight and Wu Shuai's alliance will break apart by itself."

Qin Ding Ling shook her head at this optimistic plan: "Wu Shuai is a formidable person. Even a rabbit will bite if it is forced to a corner, let alone this dragonman. Once he obtains this news, he might immediately lead his troops to fight Qi Sea Ancestor."

"That's right. Qi Sea Ancestor can safely remove the qi harvest fruits, but Wu Shuai cannot. The longer their fight is delayed, the more unfavorable it is to Wu Shuai. It is very likely for Wu Shuai to send his troops."

"In that case, we have to move ahead of time and ask Qi Sea Ancestor to resolve the qi harvest fruit in Heavenly Court."

"You are right. Once the battle starts, Qi Sea Ancestor will not be able to deal with too many matters, he will definitely have to bear the full force attack from Wu Shuai. The situation is already like a conflict between fire and water, the fight won't be stopped easily once it starts, and it might really be a life and death battle."

Qin Ding Ling looked at Nine Spiritual Fairy: "How is the refinement of hatred Gu going?"

Nine Spiritual Fairy shook her head: "There has been a breakthrough just recently. Hatred Gu's condition is extremely strange, it has already merged into Qing Chou. We found a method to refine hatred Gu just recently. It will take quite long to refine hatred Gu. But the good news is that if we succeed, we can manipulate Qing Chou as well."

Qin Ding Ling nodded: "Since hatred Gu has yet to be obtained completely, there is no need to hurry in seizing lightning Gu. We will conceal this news as much as possible and invite Qi Sea Ancestor to come to Heavenly Court secretly and deal with the qi harvest fruit. After finishing this matter, we will then fight with Wu Shuai."

The immortals did not have any objections.

"But how should we reward Qi Sea Ancestor?" A Gu Immortal asked.

"This is not difficult. Qi Sea Ancestor is very interested in the qi path Immortal Gu in my Heavenly Court's treasury. In the previous letters, he had repeatedly asked to borrow these qi path Immortal Gu, but I did not agree and kept on making excuses." Qin Ding Ling smiled.

Another Gu Immortal added: "We also need to be on guard against another person, Demon Immortal Qi Jue!"

Qin Ding Ling nodded: "I have also considered it. This demon is also a qi path great expert, if he collaborates with Wu Shuai, it will balance the situation of both sides again, he is a huge threat."

"It is difficult to track Demon Immortal Qi Jue, who knows where he has gone now. He has just revived and is not familiar with the various paths of the present age. He is currently purchasing qi path immortal materials in treasure yellow heaven and exchanging for inheritances of every path, he is taking even Gu Master inheritances. Wu Shuai has chips to transact with him!"

Qin Ding Ling stressed once again: "So the current plan is to immediately invite Qi Sea Ancestor to Heavenly Court while hiding the information and striving for every second we can get!"

Chapter 2024: Strategies of the Three Parties

Within Dragon Palace, the atmosphere was heavy.

"The situation has become like this, what do you all think about it?" Wu Shuai was the only person seated, he had already gathered the alliance's immortals and explained to them the actions that Qi Sea Ancestor took inside Profound Literature grotto-heaven.

Heavenly Court tried all ways to conceal the information but at the same time, Wu Shuai informed all of the Gu Immortals within the two heavens alliance.

After hearing this nightmarish news, the response was huge as all of the immortals' expressions changed.

"Is this for real?" Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch asked immediately before reacting to what he had said, his face turned pale: "I am not questioning Lord Alliance Leader, but this is truly too sudden and surprising."

Wu Shuai snorted coldly: "Do I need to lie to you?"

"This is not good!" Xiao He Jian's expression was solemn: "Qi Sea Ancestor is a qi path great expert, since Demon Immortal Qi Jue was able to use a qi harvest fruit to revive, then there is also a high chance that Qi Sea Ancestor can get rid of the threatening qi harvest fruits. If the enemy has a method to get rid of the qi harvest fruits, they will have a complete upper hand in this situation."

"Indeed, indeed."

"What do we do now?"

"My tribe's grotto-heaven's qi harvest fruit has already grown to a huge size, if we do not get rid of it, it will explode soon."

"But our experiments have not succeeded once, we already ruined many grotto-heavens."

"It is impossible for us to come to a peaceful truce with Qi Sea Ancestor, we should be wary of them using this chance to attack us!"

The immortals discussed as their tone contained fear and panic.

Spectral Soul who was acting as Lady Cold Ash stood among them, cheering secretly. He wanted the war to start as soon as possible, if there was chaos, he would gain a great opportunity to take action.

Night Heavenly Wolf Lord showed the same attitude as the rest but he was happy on the inside. He had already joined Heavenly Court, this situation was very advantageous to him.

"Panicking to this degree, what a disgrace!" Gu tribe's leader suddenly shouted.

Everyone looked towards him.

Even though Gu tribe's leader joined the two heavens alliance, he had always been silent. But everyone knew that he was the closest person to Wu Shuai. In terms of Wu Shuai's trust, he surpassed Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian, who were both vice alliance leaders!

Gu tribe's leader suddenly spoke, Xiao He Jian shook internally as he realized something. Before he spoke, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch had already taken the initiative: "With Lord Alliance Leader here, we have nothing to fear. At this crucial juncture of life and death, I am willing to follow Lord Alliance Leader and listen to your commands."

Xiao He Jian cursed internally but he quickly followed: "I will listen to Lord Alliance Leader's decision!"

Wu Shuai nodded slightly, snorting: "The current situation is critical, if we sit and wait here, we will definitely perish, there is no exception. We have to fight with all our strength now for a hope of survival. They are able to eliminate the qi harvest fruit because of Qi Sea Ancestor's method. As long as we do our best and kill Qi Sea Ancestor, we will gain complete victory. Even if we cannot kill him, as long as we gravely injure him, the situation will also be alleviated."

After Wu Shuai said that, Gu tribe's leader immediately shouted: "Alliance Leader is wise!"

Wu Shuai looked at Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian, these two vice alliance leaders immediately shouted: "Alliance Leader is wise, this plan is superb!"

"What ideas do you all have? If anyone has a better suggestion, you can tell us now." Wu Shuai purposely asked the other Gu Immortals.

But what ideas could these people have?

In fact, Wu Shuai said he was going to attack the enemies because he had no other choice now, this was their only hope. Other than this, could they surrender to Qi Sea Ancestor?

It was not that they did not know this, but nobody had the guts to say it. Forest Lightning grotto-heaven was the best example, everyone saw that pitiful end, who would still dare to follow in its footsteps?

"Since everyone agrees, we will discuss about the way we will send our troops, we will use our time efficiently and catch the enemy off guard." Wu Shuai said as he decided with lightning speed.

Gu tribe's leader added: "Lord Alliance Leader is right, every second we waste now will mean the enemy gets an additional second of advantage."

Immediately, the immortals started to discuss their offensive strategy.

This discussion lasted nearly an hour before they came up with a refined plan.

Wu Shuai opened the door of Dragon Palace, ordering the immortals to make preparations, they would move out in seven days.

Night Heavenly Wolf Lord returned to Night Wolf grotto-heaven, he mobilized his forces and gathered more troops while quickly informing Heavenly Court of this new development.

After Qin Ding Ling received the information, she summoned the Heavenly Court immortals for a meeting.

"The situation has changed, it seems that Wu Shuai has some spies around Qi Sea Ancestor."

"Like I said before, we cannot underestimate Wu Shuai."

"Since Wu Shuai is going to take the initiative to attack, let's use this chance to take him down!"

"That will be hard, they have Dragon Palace and Di Zang Sheng to defend them. Unless we can awaken some immortals from the graveyard, we will not have sufficient strength to deal with the enemies."

"Time is too pressing, we have seven days and the situation will occur far away in Eastern Sea."

"We can only inform Qi Sea Ancestor now and ask him to make preparations while pretending to be ignorant. When Wu Shuai attacks, he will definitely suffer a setback."

"Did you forget that Wu Shuai has spies around Qi Sea Ancestor? If Qi Sea Ancestor learns this information from us, it will also likely alert Wu Shuai."

Prince Feng Xian suddenly spoke at this time: "Why must we inform Qi Sea Ancestor?"

The discussions suddenly stopped.

"Qi Sea Ancestor is our ally, if we do not tell him about this, it will not benefit our alliance."

Prince Feng Xian shook his head slowly as he smiled: "As long as we keep quiet, why would Qi Sea Ancestor find out that we know this? Our spy in the two heavens alliance has always been kept as a secret, if we tell him now, the spy might get exposed."

"We ally with Qi Sea Ancestor because we need his strength to resolve Heavenly Court's problem of the qi harvest fruit, we also want to use him as our pawn to gather an external force that can resist the variant human forces from getting stronger."

Prince Feng Xian continued to speak: "And thirdly, if possible, we want to recruit Qi Sea Ancestor into becoming a Heavenly Court member."

Qin Ding Ling looked at Prince Feng Xian: "Then in your opinion, what should we do?"

Prince Feng Xian breathed in deeply: "In my humble opinion, we should pretend that we do not know this and act according to our original plan. Now that Qi Sea Ancestor has already secretly moved out, he will arrive in Heavenly Court in three days. By then, we can get him to solve our problem of the qi harvest fruit."

"Heavenly Court is huge and has immense foundation, the qi harvest fruit here is the largest in the world. Qi Sea Ancestor suggested us to create a qi path immortal formation, it will take at least six days to get rid of the qi harvest fruit. We can purposely delay the formation creation time, if Wu Shuai's invasion succeeds, Qi Sea Ancestor's force will suffer a huge loss."

"Qi Sea Ancestor will become anxious and want to return to help them but as the person controlling the formation, how can he leave? Qi Sea Ancestor's force will be without a leader, they will not be able to defeat Wu Shuai. In fact, even if they get wiped out, so what?"

"Our strength will not fall while Qi Sea Ancestor will become a loner. By coming to Heavenly Court secretly and failing to protect his force, causing its destruction, his reputation will fall to rock bottom. Eastern Sea's Gu Immortal world will also look down on him. Who would respect someone who goes missing in battle while helping forces of other regions?"

"At that point, Qi Sea Ancestor will understand that his status in Eastern Sea will never recover. By then, we will have no worries anymore, we can send people to take revenge for him. During the process, we can move him with logic and emotion, by tempting him with future gains, I am sure there is a high chance we can get him to join Heavenly Court."

The immortals were silent, they looked at each other before looking towards Prince Feng Xian.

At this moment, all of the immortals' gazes became different from before.

After hearing Prince Feng Xian's strategy, their impression towards him changed completely!

Prince Feng Xian's arms were behind his back, he stopped speaking as he smiled.

This scheme was vicious, none of the Gu Immortals here thought of it except him, the reason was because of his own life experiences.

Prince Feng Xian came from Spirit Affinity House, he was used as a spy initially to develop in Northern Plains. After many years, he became rank eight and also married into Gong tribe, he was the strongest spy in Northern Plains that came from Central Continent.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals have been too used to being overlords, their mindsets were also too fixed in place. But all of the immortals here were rank eight elites, they soon understood that Prince Feng Xian's plan was the most advantageous to Heavenly Court.

Even if Wu Shuai claims victory, so what?

Only the grotto-heavens in the two heavens would suffer. Even if Eastern Sea gets involved in the fight, its foundation would not be affected.

Even if Eastern Sea's righteous path was toppled, that would only be one region. Humanity would still be the ruler of the world!

"Alright." Qin Ding Ling looked at everyone's expressions as she said, making a decision: "We will act according to Prince Feng Xian's proposal."

Chapter 2025: Three Qi Immortal Gu

Heavenly Court was constantly filled with bright light.

Fang Yuan, who was disguised as Qi Sea Ancestor, had already arrived in Heavenly Court.

He floated in the air as he observed the qi harvest fruit in front of him.

The qi harvest fruit in Heavenly Court was large beyond common sense, it was like a towering mountain range, vast and colossal.

"Such a huge qi harvest fruit cannot even fit in an ordinary rank eight grotto-heaven, it will destroy the aperture walls from its sheer size. Only Heavenly Court has such a deep foundation and because of the use of Cang Xuan Zi's space path fruits, the space inside is large enough to accommodate this qi harvest fruit."

Fang Yuan sighed internally.

The last time he came to Heavenly Court, he had participated in the fate war with his original appearance and caused Heavenly Court to lose badly. This time, he was acting as Heavenly Court's friend, he was here to resolve their problem of the qi harvest fruit.

Changes in situations and circumstances were often hard to predict.

"How is it?" Qin Ding Ling stood beside Fang Yuan, asking.

Fang Yuan nodded: "This is the first time I've seen such a huge qi harvest fruit, it shows that your foundation is truly unfathomable, this is truly the number one force in the world."

After pausing for a while, Fang Yuan continued: "After my inspection earlier, even though my method is effective, this qi harvest fruit is too big. We need to set up the immortal formation first, the larger the qi path immortal formation, the more time we can save."

Qin Ding Ling was slightly surprised: "Ancestor, to think that you have already come up with the immortal formation's design."

Fang Yuan shook his head: "No, the qi path immortal formation that we will set up is only going to amplify my qi path killer moves. The actual way to get rid of the qi harvest fruit is still through the qi path killer moves that I will use."

Qin Ding Ling nodded upon hearing this, the explanation was logical.

She smiled as she took out a qi path rank eight Immortal Gu: "Heavenly Court does not lack qi path Immortal Gu, to resolve the problem of the qi harvest fruit, Heavenly Court is willing to use up our qi path resources. Ancestor, look at this Immortal Gu."

Fang Yuan's attention was drawn to this Immortal Gu.

"Don't tell me this is... human qi Immortal Gu?" Fang Yuan's pupils expanded as his expression changed.

Human qi Immortal Gu resembled a bee, it was thumb-sized and constantly moved its wings, floating above Qin Ding Ling's palm, it emitted a cloud-like qi.

Qin Ding Ling handed human qi Immortal Gu to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan extended his hand and held the Gu, he looked at it fixedly and praised: "Good Gu, good Gu. This Gu is related to human path, it has immense potential for development!"

Qin Ding Ling smiled as she took out a second Immortal Gu, handing it to Fang Yuan.

This was earth qi Immortal Gu, it resembled a butterfly, brown in color, it also gave off a cloud-like qi.

Fang Yuan's left hand held human qi Immortal Gu while his right hand held earth qi Immortal Gu, he looked at them with great interest: "Wonderful, wonderful."

"And this is heaven qi Immortal Gu." Qin Ding Ling said as she passed Fang Yuan a third rank eight Immortal Gu.

Heaven qi Immortal Gu resembled a dragonfly, it was green in color and had eight pairs of thin bluish wings, when it moved its wings, its entire body would emit a translucent qi current.

Fang Yuan had a solemn expression: "This heaven qi Immortal Gu is tightly connected with heaven path. Truthfully speaking, the method that I created to get rid of the qi harvest fruit only succeeded after I comprehended a trace of heaven path's profundity. If I had this Gu, I would have succeeded much earlier."

"Gu Immortals cultivate all sorts of paths, human path and heaven path are the most unique. Ancestor, you have already reached the peak of qi path, thus you are able to mimic other paths easily and comprehend the true meaning of various paths." Qin Ding Ling praised before changing her words: "These three qi Immortal Gu are the core of triple qi retraction killer move, they are priceless treasures of Heavenly Court. Only Heavenly Court members can have them."

Qin Ding Ling saw Fang Yuan's expression and felt internally happy, she hinted to him that these Gu worms would be available if he joined Heavenly Court.

After hearing this, Fang Yuan showed a hesitant expression, but he was smiling to himself internally.

All of the expressions he showed were just an act.

If he really cultivated qi path solely, these three qi Immortal Gu would be incredibly alluring. Fang Yuan had tried many times already, these three qi path Immortal Gu were the cores of triple qi retraction, they could not be replaced. If he used other qi path Immortal Gu in place of them, even if he manages to create a triple qi retraction killer move, its value in battle would fall drastically.

Thus, even though Fang Yuan had the complete Primordial Origin qi path true inheritance now, he did not benefit much from it.

Furthermore, Qi Sea Ancestor was just one of Fang Yuan's identities. He also had no lack of rank eight Immortal Gu. Attitude, Mutation, Wisdom Sword, Years Flow Like Water, Soul Beast Token, Regret, Spring, Summer, Big Qi, Region, Addition, Steal Life, Water Refinement, Advance Refinement, Dream Token, he simply had too many of them.

In Fang Yuan's eyes, only rank nine Immortal Gu could truly excite him.

But rank nine Immortal Gu were too rare.

He originally had one, which was wisdom Gu. But this Immortal Gu was tampered by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable long ago, he had no choice but to sacrifice it in the fate war.

Qin Ding Ling lent all three qi Immortal Gu and let Qi Sea Ancestor familiarize himself with them, she also arranged several Gu Immortals to modify the qi path immortal Gu formation with Qi Sea Ancestor.

Having everyone's help, the qi path immortal formation was finalized in a few days.

Fang Yuan and the Heavenly Court immortals started to set up the formation.

This qi path formation's main owner was naturally Fang Yuan.

But in the other formation cores, there would be Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals stationed, they could help him out while also supervising his actions.

Qi Sea Ancestor was an outsider after all, even though he underwent an alliance agreement, he was still not a Heavenly Court member. How could Heavenly Court not guard against him?

The truth was, the assisting Gu Immortals were not the only ones guarding against him.

The core Immortal Gu of this qi path formation, Heaven Qi, Earth Qi, and Human Qi, were temporarily lent to Fang Yuan by Qin Ding Ling. If any situation occurs, Heavenly Court could immediately take them back and make Fang Yuan lose control of the entire qi path formation.

This qi path formation was modified along with several Heavenly Court Gu Immortals. Even if they had low qi path attainment, they still had general knowledge, it was hard to deceive them. Also, Fang Yuan did not conceal anything inside this qi path formation.

The formation was definitely not an issue.

"Earth qi Gu, go!" Fang Yuan first tossed earth qi Immortal Gu as he instilled immortal essence.

Earth qi Immortal Gu quickly flew out, it went into the ground below the qi harvest fruit.

Boom!

Suddenly, with a loud explosion, the ground below the qi harvest fruit started to shake, earth qi started to rise up continuously.

Fang Yuan started to collect the earth qi, the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals around him also took action, some helped with the gathering while others set up small formations around the small holes that the earth qi emerged from.

While Fang Yuan was setting up his formation, deep underground at another area of Heavenly Court, there was a huge underground square.

Qing Chou's mountain-like body was deep within this underground square, unmoving like a statue.

Bam...

Suddenly, a loud sound could be heard from afar.

The underground square shook slightly, several cracks appeared on the ground.

But Red Heart Traveler, who was defending this place, was not flustered, he immediately acted to stabilize the situation. The cracks on the ground could be seen disappearing at an observable rate.

"What's the commotion?" Qing Chou suddenly spoke, but strangely, its voice was actually Nine Spiritual Fairy's.

Nine Spiritual Fairy was actually inside Qing Chou's body, trying to forcefully refine hatred Gu.

"From this commotion, Qi Sea Ancestor must have started to create his formation. He used earth qi Immortal Gu as the first foundation of the formation, it involved the earth vein. Meanwhile, we are at one of the main earth veins, thus we could feel the influence." Red Heart Traveler spoke: "Earlier, you were at a crucial moment, so I did not inform you of this. But don't worry, this cannot interrupt our plan."

"Mm." Nine Spiritual Fairy stopped worrying as she said: "Then let's hurry up, if we can refine hatred Gu at the same time as the elimination of the qi harvest fruit, Heavenly Court will have a double celebration."

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals had already recovered from the trauma of the fate war, they became braver after the humiliation, they worked harder and had greater morale now.

Days later, the qi path formation was created, Fang Yuan was the main user and activated his method to eliminate the qi harvest fruit.

The qi harvest fruit was continuously shaved off from Fang Yuan's killer move, but this qi harvest fruit in Heavenly Court was just too big, some time was needed to completely destroy it.

Days passed, the qi harvest fruit was removed by over ten percent.

Qin Ding Ling hurried to Fang Yuan as she showed a solemn expression: "Ancestor, the situation in Eastern Sea has changed, this is not good."

Fang Yuan looked shocked: "What happened?"

"Wu Shuai suddenly led his alliance to launch an invasion, they have split into three groups, they are attacking the grotto-heaven forces that have submitted to our side. Because we were caught off guard, our losses are quite severe." Qin Ding Ling said.

"News that I came here should have been kept a secret. How did this happen? How did Wu Shuai find out so quickly?" Fang Yuan's expression changed, there was anxiety in his tone.

"Ancestor, you want to return to help Eastern Sea?" Qin Ding Ling purposely asked.

"That is so." Fang Yuan frowned: "But this method needs my full attention, if I stop halfway, there might be problematic consequences."

Qin Ding Ling cupped her fists at Fang Yuan: "Ancestor, please consider the big picture! It is unexpected that Wu Shuai attacked so soon, but if you return now, that will be what Wu Shuai wants to see. Only after eliminating the qi harvest fruit can we have a safe territory to count on. By then, you can lead our Heavenly Court's immortals to return to Eastern Sea and retaliate, you can say that you went to seek reinforcement from Heavenly Court, but Wu Shuai attacked and trapped you temporarily. By gathering our strength, we will kill Wu Shuai and get rid of the two heavens alliance. That is the true way to seek victory."

Fang Yuan did not speak, he only looked at Qin Ding Ling deeply.

Long after, he spoke in a grim tone: "Wu Shuai attacked with his full force, he must have been prepared for this. Does Heavenly Court know of their plans in advance?"

"Definitely not." Qin Ding Ling shook her head, showing a firm expression.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly, he showed a struggling expression as he sighed helplessly: "Forget it, I will stay here and control the formation until we get rid of the qi harvest fruit. But during this time, I need Heavenly Court to send people to assist Eastern Sea!"

Qin Ding Ling sighed as well: "We will do our best."

Fang Yuan gritted his teeth as he said: "Once I get rid of the qi harvest fruit, I will need to return and help them. But these days of unceasingly controlling the formation will cause my battle strength to fall. I need Heavenly Court to give me the three qi Immortal Gu to kill the enemies and claim victory."

Qin Ding Ling's expression changed, even though Fang Yuan spoke politely, his request for reward was really absurd, it far exceeded Qin Ding Ling's bottom line.

She rejected as she shook her head: "The three qi Immortal Gu are the treasures of Heavenly Court, only our members can..."

Before she finished, Fang Yuan interrupted: "Eastern Sea's immortals are all my subordinates."

Qin Ding Ling still shook her head: "We will remember ancestor's sacrifice, but even as Heavenly Court's leader, I cannot give you three rank eight Immortal Gu. At most, we can give you one as compensation."

"How can one Gu compensate for the people in the grotto-heavens?" Fang Yuan showed slight anger.

Boom!

While the two were negotiating, a loud sound could be heard in the sky.

A rank eight Immortal Gu House directly charged in with a fierce aura!

Heavenly Court's immortals were all shocked.

The Immortal Gu House that invaded Heavenly Court was Dragon Palace!

"How can this be?!" Qin Ding Ling could not waste time with Fang Yuan anymore, she immediately flew out of the formation to face the enemies.

Dragon Palace's door opened as Wu Shuai sat on his throne, speaking from deep within Dragon Palace: "Qin Ding Ling, we meet again."

"Wu Shuai, why are you here?" Qin Ding Ling shouted as several Gu Immortals gathered behind her.

Wu Shuai smiled coldly as he kicked a head that was near his feet.

This head fell from the stairs of the dragon throne, rolling into Central Great Hall. The person had died with his eyes wide open, it was Night Heavenly Wolf Lord.

"Old scoundrel Qi Sea can get rid of qi harvest fruits, your Heavenly Court wants to conceal this information and secretly eliminate your internal threat? Hehe, wishful thinking! I am here to destroy your Heavenly Court and also kill that old scoundrel Qi Sea, let's see who in this world can stop my rise to supremacy!"

Wu Shuai said that as he stood upright, he waved his hand and shouted: "Kill!"

At the next moment, immortals rushed out of Dragon Palace, attacking with ferocious expressions.

Chapter 2026: Fang Yuan Appears

Central Continent, deep beneath a certain Earth Trench.

Fairy Zi Wei controlled the wisdom path formation, purple light flickered within it without spreading out.

Within the formation, other than Bai Ning Bing, Hei Lou Lan, and Ying Wu Xie, there was Fairy Miao Yin and Lady White Rabbit, as well as several other Gu Immortals.

After the fate war, these Gu Immortals were all left outside by Fang Yuan.

Fairy Zi Wei and the rest worked together with Bing Sai Chuan's group, capturing all of these people.

As the purple light faded, the formation stopped working, Fairy Miao Yin's expression was uncertain while Lady White Rabbit had anger in her eyes, they were both unable to move.

"Aren't you surrendering?" Ying Wu Xie laughed coldly.

"Hmph, you traitor!" Lady White Rabbit shouted angrily.

Bai Ning Bing also came over with a cold and indifferent expression: "I would advise you to reconsider, after all, you have just lost your greatest value."

Fairy Miao Yin heard this, she became more uncertain.

At this moment, Fairy Zi Wei stored away the formation as she stood up. She was very weak now after using her full strength to make the deduction, the cost was high. But joy was apparent on her face.

"It looks like she succeeded." Bing Sai Chuan was waiting outside the formation, he smiled upon seeing this.

Hei Lou Lan walked towards Bing Sai Chuan from Fairy Zi Wei's position, stopping behind him.

Fairy Zi Wei smiled lightly: "We have enough clues, we achieved success! I have already deduced Fang Yuan's location, guess where this crafty demon is hiding?"

Bing Sai Chuan frowned: "Your question is an obvious hint in itself. Don't tell me that this scoundrel Fang Yuan has been hiding in Heavenly Court?"

Fairy Zi Wei nodded: "According to my deductions, he is indeed in Heavenly Court now!"

The immortals heard this and showed varying expressions.

Ying Wu Xie gritted his teeth: "He is crafty indeed, his departure from Heavenly Court earlier was just a smokescreen, he must have been hiding in Heavenly Court all along."

Old Man Zheng Yuan sighed: "No wonder we could not find his main body!"

Bai Ning Bing laughed loudly, praising: "Exciting! This is truly Fang Yuan's attitude."

Bing Sai Chuan frowned: "But how could he possibly hide until now without getting detected by Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals?"

Fairy Zi Wei's eyes flickered with bright light: "I can only deduce that he is in Heavenly Court now, he might not have been there the entire time. But in terms of ability, this demon is unfathomable. His growth is too fast, every time he fights, his enemies will see an explosive growth in his strength."

Bing Sai Chuan sighed: "Now that Fang Yuan is hiding in Heavenly Court, what can we do? Do we go and attack Heavenly Court? Should we inform Heavenly Court about this and let them kill him, but wouldn't that allow them to get all of his inheritances?"

Bing Sai Chuan represented Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, they cared about the benefits of Northern Plains' Longevity Heaven. Furthermore, they had spent a lot of effort to deduce Fang Yuan's location, telling Heavenly Court about it was quite a loss for them.

Old Man Zheng Yuan reminded: "No matter what, we need to tell our master about this important information!"

Fairy Zi Wei replied: "I have already reported it to master when I stored the formation away."

Heavenly Court.

Intense battle erupted.

Boom!

Lady Cold Ash dodged with rapid speed, avoiding the explosion of a killer move.

She was the disguise of Spectral Soul, he had just received Fairy Zi Wei's information, he was not in a good mood.

"Fang Yuan is in Heavenly Court now? Of course he is, I knew about that long ago!"

Memories surfaced in Spectral Soul's mind regarding the event that happened days ago.

The Gu Immortals were called to assemble in Dragon Palace, Wu Shuai used the excuse that they were going to discuss the matter about attacking Qi Sea Ancestor.

But halfway through the meeting, Wu Shuai suddenly took action.

Dragon Palace roared, Night Heavenly Wolf Lord was caught off guard, he was hit by the killer move dreamy light smoke and was taken down without putting up a fight.

"Everyone, don't panic, this person is a spy in our alliance, he is the informant of Heavenly Court." Wu Shuai pacified the immortals while taking out evidence.

Looking at the concrete evidence, the immortals were shocked and furious, they wanted Night Wolf grotto-heaven to pay the price for this betrayal.

Wu Shuai shook his head: "We definitely need to punish Night Heavenly Wolf Lord, but the urgent matter is not this. We need to look at the big picture!"

Gu tribe's leader frowned: "Lord Alliance Leader, because of this traitor Night Heavenly Wolf Lord, our plan to attack has been exposed. If we go ahead with it, we will no longer hit our enemies by surprise."

Wu Shuai smiled grimly: "There is important information I have yet to tell you. Qi Sea Ancestor is not in Eastern Sea now, he has already gone to Central Continent's Heavenly Court many days ago."

"This is good news!" Many Gu Immortals heard this and rejoiced.

But Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch's expression was grim: "What's good about this? The reason why we are attacking Qi Sea Ancestor is because of his ability to get rid of the qi harvest fruits for others. Now that he is not around, what is the point of our assault?"

The Gu Immortals who cheered became stunned, after realizing the situation, the atmosphere in Dragon Palace became much grimmer.

"Don't worry, everyone." Wu Shuai spoke as everyone's gazes landed on him.

He continued: "It is quite simple to resolve this problem. Since Qi Sea Ancestor has gone to Central Continent's Heavenly Court, we will also head to Heavenly Court and kill Qi Sea Ancestor who is over there!"

"...What?"

"This..."

The Gu Immortals in the palace hesitated.

"It is not easy to attack Heavenly Court."

"Heavenly Court is the number one human force in the world, even though it lost in the fate war, we cannot possibly defeat it."

Many Gu Immortals wanted to give up.

But Wu Shuai snorted coldly: "You fools."

He scolded them in public, the loud noises in the palace became silent, all of the Gu Immortals did not dare to speak anymore.

"Why aren't you thinking about the reason why Heavenly Court invited Qi Sea Ancestor to visit them in secret?" Wu Shuai purposely asked with a stiff expression.

Xiao He Jian, who reacted quickly, said instantly: "Does this mean that Heavenly Court also has the problem of the qi harvest fruit?"

Wu Shuai chuckled: "Your grotto-heavens have the problem of the qi harvest fruit, Heavenly Court is also a grotto-heaven situated in white heaven, why wouldn't they have the same problem?"

After hearing this, the immortals realized at once.

This was actually just their own mentality. In their mind, Heavenly Court was the supreme organization, even though it lost the fate war, they still displayed terrifying might and foundation. They had only lost because of enemies like Fang Yuan and Red Lotus Demon Venerable. From the variant human Gu Immortals' perspective, this was not an illogical loss, it did not undermine Heavenly Court's terrifying strength.

And because of this, the variant human Gu Immortals subconsciously thought that even if Heavenly Court had the problem of the qi harvest fruit, they could resolve it themselves, after all, Heavenly Court was created by Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, who became venerable through qi path.

"Lord Alliance Leader is wise!" Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch patted his forehead: "Heavenly Court invited Qi Sea Ancestor to resolve their threat of the qi harvest fruit, because even though they have their qi path inheritance, they lack a qi path Gu Immortal."

"Also, why did Heavenly Court choose to ally with Qi Sea Ancestor? Other than wanting to resist us, they also want to alleviate their own problems."

"Precisely." Wu Shuai looked at Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch with an expression of praise: "You guys are not too stupid after all. Heavenly Court is at its weakest state now, while Qi Sea Ancestor has gone to resolve the qi harvest fruit problem. As long as we attack them during this period, the result will be shocking when we catch them unguarded!"

"If we attack Heavenly Court before Qi Sea Ancestor starts working on the qi harvest fruit, we will attack the qi harvest fruit and force them to go on the defensive. This way, we will hold the initiative and be able to retreat or advance at will."

"If Qi Sea Ancestor is using his killer move to eliminate the qi harvest fruit while we attack Heavenly Court, that will be even better! We can disrupt him with our full strength and cause Qi Sea Ancestor's killer move to fail and suffer a backlash. If we work harder, we might be able to kill him on the spot."

Wu Shuai said calmly.

"But what if Qi Sea Ancestor has already gotten rid of the qi harvest fruit by the time we attack Heavenly Court?" A Gu Immortal asked with caution.

Wu Shuai snorted coldly: "Heavenly Court's foundation is too deep, their qi harvest fruit is also very extraordinary, if Qi Sea Ancestor spends effort to get rid of it, his own condition will definitely slip. Of course, this is just the worst case scenario, but we are in an urgent situation in the first place, we will need to take risks for any hope. Other than this, do you have other ideas?"

Facing Wu Shuai's question, everyone was silent.

In this situation, they had no choice but to follow Wu Shuai and attack Heavenly Court.

But...

Many of the Gu Immortals were still hesitant, including their vice alliance leaders, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian.

"Or perhaps, we can try to experiment and find a way to get rid of the qi harvest fruit?" A Gu Immortal asked softly.

Wu Shuai's expression sank a little, he scolded in his head: "These variant human Gu Immortals have been cowards for too long, they have absolutely no courage to take risks."

But Wu Shuai predicted this earlier, he started to laugh.

"Why is Lord Alliance Leader laughing?" Gu tribe's leader asked.

Wu Shuai stopped his laughter as he said: "The truth is, I am also worried about bringing you fools to attack Heavenly Court. But I have invited a strong reinforcement to help us, because of him, I learned about Night Heavenly Wolf Lord's betrayal."

"Oh? Who?" The immortals were curious.

Lady Cold Ash's gaze flickered, having a guess.

At this moment, from behind Wu Shuai, a Gu Immortal walked out. He wore a white robe, his black hair extended to his waist, he had a peerless face with divine brilliance, cold light oozed out of his abyss-like eyes.

"Ahhh!"

"Fang Yuan..."

"It's him, it really is him."

The immortals' pupils shrunk as their expressions changed, all of them were shocked.

Under everyone's gaze, Fang Yuan spoke slowly in a cold tone: "Heavenly Court has gone too far, now that I have regained my strength, I am about to attack them. Without Duke Long, who can stop me?"

His voice resounded in the palace, nobody dared to retort to him. Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and the rest had palpitating hearts, with a monster like Fang Yuan leading them, they gained a huge boost in morale and confidence!

Fang Yuan was someone who had defeated Heavenly Court, his battle strength was apparent to the whole world!

Undeniably, he was the number one demon in the current world.

Chapter 2027: Heavenly Court's Crisis

Roar—!

The Evil Dragon's roar shook heaven and earth, whipping up storms and clouds. Its mountain range-like body moved at the front, followed by the immortals of the two heavens alliance, and finally, Dragon Palace at the end.

Primordial qi wall!

This was the method left by Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, it appeared once again when Heavenly Court was attacked, but it could not stop Di Zang Sheng's advancement!

"The five regions became one, this Evil Dragon has gotten much stronger! Furthermore... ever since the fate war, after Fang Yuan broke the primordial qi wall, even though it recovered a little, it is much weaker than before." Qin Ding Ling frowned, she quickly analyzed the situation, with just the primordial qi wall, they could stall for some time but they could not stop this Evil Dragon!

"Lady Qin, do you need me to battle?" At this moment, Nine Spiritual Fairy transmitted and asked.

Heavenly Court once had transformation path great experts, Zhang Fei Xiong and Flesh Whip Immortal, but now they were dead, Nine Spiritual Fairy was the only transformation path great expert left.

"No, we are only one step away from subduing Qing Chou, continue to refine hatred Gu." Qin Ding Ling transmitted before shouting: "Shabi Ninety-five, Ruan Dan, aren't you going to fight yet?!"

Hearing a tiger roar and crane cry at once, two legendary immemorial desolate beasts appeared in front of Di Zang Sheng.

The three legendary immemorial desolate beasts fought intensely, causing the entire place to rumble.

After just a few rounds, Ruan Dan and Shabi Ninety-five started to retreat. They were in pitiful states, with just physical brawling, they were not Di Zang Sheng's match.

Thus, they started to use killer moves, instantly, grey light shot out like blades, pill light exploded.

Di Zang Sheng roared, purple-gold light appeared on its body, blocking all of the offensive killer moves.

Next, the golden light faded away. Di Zang Sheng's whiskers grew out rapidly, each of them shot out like countless snakes, the commotion was huge.

Facing this attack, Shabi Ninety-five and Ruan Dan had to retreat.

"This Evil Dragon actually has Immortal Gu now, it can use killer moves!" Qin Ding Ling's heart sank, she took a look at Dragon Palace.

Di Zang Sheng was a legendary immemorial beast to begin with, it had superior intelligence and could use Gu worms to activate killer moves. But before the fate war, it was enslaved by Dragon Palace and had no time to obtain Gu worms. Thus, during the fate war, it could only fight using its physical body. That was why it could not resist Feng Jiu Ge's destiny song, it was handled very quickly, even against other killer moves, it could only resist using its body.

But after the fate war, Wu Shuai made considerations to prepare Gu worms for Di Zang Sheng.

At that time, Wu Shuai was quite poor, he did not have excessive Immortal Gu.

Even though the main body had many Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan was moving around in Western Desert, he did not meet with Wu Shuai initially, also, even though he had Immortal Gu, they were not suitable for Di Zang Sheng.

But Wu Shuai had great luck, he grasped onto his opportunity and became the leader of the two heavens alliance.

With sufficient resources, Wu Shuai started to equip Di Zang Sheng. By now, Wu Shuai and his main body had taken over the two heavens alliance, by using the excuse of eliminating the qi harvest fruit, he destroyed several grotto-heavens and made forceful transactions with the Gu Immortals of the two heavens alliance, Di Zang Sheng finally gathered enough Gu worms to form some basic killer moves.

Di Zang Sheng suppressed Ruan Dan and Shabi Ninety-five, forcing them to retreat as it charged forward ferociously.

Qin Ding Ling yelled as she flew up into an Immortal Gu House. Several Immortal Gu Houses flew towards Di Zang Sheng, they formed a defensive line.

Di Zang Sheng's advancement was halted, Shabi Ninety-five and Ruan Dan also joined the encirclement.

"We finally stopped it!" Qin Ding Ling calmed down slightly, but at this moment, she saw Dragon Palace flying around, towards the qi harvest fruit.

Heavenly Court's qi harvest fruit was too huge and too eye-catching!

Wu Shuai was too vicious, he attacked the enemy's weakness, Qin Ding Ling's expression changed as she quickly moved a portion of the Immortal Gu Houses to block Dragon Palace.

"The situation is critical, if the qi harvest fruit is destroyed, the whole of Heavenly Court will face destruction! Quickly awaken the people sleeping in the immortal graveyard!" Zhou Xiong Xin urged.

"Or we can let Nine Spiritual Fairy and Red Heart Traveler join the fight!" Bai Cang Shui suggested.

Qin Ding Ling gritted her teeth, deciding: "Awaken those in our immortal graveyard!"

More than half of Heavenly Court's immortal graveyard was destroyed, there were only a small number of Gu Immortals left sleeping in it. But with the awakening of these people, they formed sufficient force to handle the pressure, their defensive line that was precarious became stable now.

"Go and attack the qi harvest fruit!" Wu Shuai gave an order to the alliance army.

These Gu Immortals had dispersed earlier, they were like scattered sand, trying to make their way through the qi wall and towards the qi harvest fruit.

Seeing this, Qin Ding Ling felt enraged, she gritted her teeth, she was furious: "I will grind the bones of these variant humans into ash, I will kill them all!"

The two heavens alliance's Gu Immortals were not very strong but they had the numbers, and right now, Heavenly Court's weakness was their lack of manpower.

"Don't worry, there are many variant human Gu Immortals but they are all cowards. As long as we send one person to kill several of these invaders, they will lose their morale and not dare to progress further!" Prince Feng Xian suggested.

"Who can take on the task?" Qin Ding Ling quickly asked.

Che Wei replied with his actions, he turned into a flash of light and flew out of the Immortal Gu House, towards the qi harvest fruit.

"Die!" He flew like a great eagle, unleashing killer moves that were extremely powerful, his might could not be resisted.

"Ahh—!"

"What killer move is this?"

Out of two variant human Gu Immortals, one was heavily injured, the other was killed on the spot.

At the crucial moment, Che Wei displayed outstanding battle strength, both sides were similarly shocked.

After all, he had just defeated two variant human Gu Immortals with rank eight cultivation level.

"That killer move seems to be from a whole new path?"

"Too terrifying. Before we can understand its background, if I charge towards him, I will definitely be split into two by his blade."

"Let's wait for Fang Yuan to attack instead!"

The Gu Immortals of the two heavens alliance were hesitant, they stopped moving forward.

"These useless trash!" In the depth of Dragon Palace, Wu Shuai frowned with anger showing on his face.

At the crucial moment, these variant human Gu Immortals were completely useless, they were not even qualified to be cannon fodder.

But Wu Shuai was prepared for this, he waved his hand: "Your turn to fight!"

Four figures flew out of Dragon Palace, they were the Four Dragon Generals, Zhang Yin, Granny Rong, Yang Zi He, and Old Man Bei Feng, who took the place of Shi Miao.

These four rank eight Gu Immortals were enslaved by Dragon Palace, they had absolute loyalty and did not fear death, they split up into four different directions and advanced.

Even though Che Wei was strong, he could only block one person.

"Protect me!" Qi Sea Ancestor transmitted to Qin Ding Ling: "Now is a crucial moment, if we stop here, the consequences will be unthinkable."

Qin Ding Ling almost wanted to grit her teeth till they shattered, the three dragon generals were very close to the qi harvest fruit, she had to take a risk and mobilize Immortal Gu Houses to block them.

At the same time, two Gu Immortals flew out of the Immortal Gu Houses to resist the dragon generals.

Roar—!

Right when Heavenly Court managed to block the Four Dragon Generals, over on Dragon Palace's end, it exerted force to stop Ruan Dan. Using this chance, Di Zang Sheng rammed Shabi Ninety-five away as it charged forward, managing to reach the qi harvest fruit.

Di Zang Sheng opened its mouth and spat out a torrent of green qi.

The green qi shattered the immortal formation and hit the qi harvest fruit.

The qi harvest fruit shook intensely, Qi Sea Ancestor's expression changed, he spat out a mouthful of blood, the killer move was halted, he seemed to have suffered great backlash.

"Oh no!" The expressions of Heavenly Court's immortals changed.

"We succeeded!" The subordinates of Wu Shuai started to cheer, their morale rose.

The qi harvest fruit was damaged, it implicated Heavenly Court. The land of Heavenly Court cracked, Earth Trenches appeared, earth qi rumbled, heaven qi shook, the sky became chaotic as countless clouds and gusts of wind stirred.

Crack, crack.

The aperture wall of Heavenly Court started to crack, large pieces of the wall fragments fell off and created huge holes that connected to the outside world.

Even the fate war did not deal such great damage to Heavenly Court!

The appearance of the qi harvest fruit created a fatal weakness in Heavenly Court.

"Die!" Che Wei was enraged, his left hand was like a blade, his right hand was like a spear, both hands pushed forward as two golden-silver lights pierced Yang Zi He.

Yang Zi He died!

Wu Shuai laughed loudly, shouting: "Today is the day Heavenly Court faces destruction."

Qin Ding Ling's eyelids twitched, even though Wu Shuai's side suffered more losses, he was not wrong about it. With their greatest weakness, the qi harvest fruit, Wu Shuai had the initiative in this battle!

"Heavenly Court is facing a crisis, what should we do?" Even someone like Qin Ding Ling felt lost at this moment.

Amidst her feeling of loss, she also felt fear: "Don't tell me Heavenly Court is going to be destroyed in my hands?"

Right at this moment, Qi Sea Ancestor transmitted to her: "The situation is quite critical, we need to take a risk."

Qin Ding Ling responded subconsciously: "What risk?"

"Earlier, my qi path Immortal Gu were destroyed, I can no longer use the previous method to eliminate the qi harvest fruit. But I had created a killer move that is incomplete, it can cause the qi harvest fruit to shrink temporarily." Qi Sea Ancestor said.

Qin Ding Ling's eyes shined, she saw hope in this desperate situation, she quickly said: "Ancestor, please use it! As long as we get through this crisis, Heavenly Court will not disappoint you."

Heavenly Court's greatest problem was the qi harvest fruit now. It was too big, like a mountain range, it was the biggest target for killer moves. But if it shrunk, it would be much easier to protect.

"We need to be fast, this killer move is not complete, I can only hold on for some time." Qi Sea Ancestor said as he flew towards the qi harvest fruit.

When he was about to crash into it, he turned into a human-shaped qi current that fused into the qi harvest fruit.

The qi harvest fruit shook, as expected, it started to shrink.

After a few breaths of time, it went from a mountain range-like size into the size of a horse carriage.

This change made the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals surprised but also happy.

An Immortal Gu House flew down and floated above the qi harvest fruit, it shot out a grand pillar of light that enveloped the entire qi harvest fruit.

Wu Shuai's side rained down a torrent of killer moves but they could not affect the pillar of light at all.

Di Zang Sheng and Dragon Palace arrived again.

"Stop them!" Qin Ding Ling shouted, but their situation was too passive, they had no choice but to retreat.

The qi harvest fruit shrank again, it went from a horse carriage to the size of a normal gourd.

Seeing that they were about to lose again, Qin Ding Ling quickly asked: "Ancestor, can you move the qi harvest fruit away?"

Qi Sea Ancestor replied weakly: "This is already my limit! I researched on Demon Immortal Qi Jue's revival method, I can only shrink the fruit but I cannot move it. This method has only been created haphazardly, it is not complete, you need to quickly think of a solution!"

Qin Ding Ling was out of ideas already, she originally wanted to send the members of the ten great ancient sects here to fight. But Central Heaven Gate of Heavenly Court, which could deploy members, was destroyed by Fairy Zi Wei during the fate war.

But at the next moment, the primordial qi wall shattered, countless qi currents landed on Di Zang Sheng's body.

Di Zang Sheng's battle strength fell rapidly, its threat level was lowered.

This was the backup method of Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, it was used on Fang Yuan during the fate war. At that time, Fang Yuan could not break away from it, Limitless Demon Venerable had to take action to help him block these qi currents.

But now, the chess game had ended, the two venerables' silhouettes were gone, there was nothing that could help Di Zang Sheng.

In an instant, Di Zang Sheng was suppressed by Shabi Ninety-five.

Heavenly Court's crisis was temporarily alleviated.

On Wu Shuai's side, they lost their most important battle strength, Dragon Palace had to step up and use the killer move dreamy light smoke, as Heavenly Court had no way of countering it, Dragon Palace's demonic might surged.

"This cannot go on, our Heavenly Court lacks people with peak battle strength after all!" Qin Ding Ling gritted her teeth.

If Duke Long was here, how could these enemies act so ferociously?

"Qi Sea Ancestor has peak battle strength too but he faced backlash from the failure of the killer move. He is also not a member of Heavenly Court, why would he fight to the death for us?"

While Qin Ding Ling was thinking of this, Qi Sea Ancestor transmitted again.

"The biggest key now is to get rid of the qi harvest fruit. As long as it is removed, we can go on the offensive without worries. There is still hope now, my killer move only lacks the final part for completion! There is a high chance of success."

Qin Ding Ling's heart shook: "What do you need?"

Qi Sea Ancestor replied: "I need Heavenly Court's heaven path true meaning, I need to raise my heaven path attainment level and conceptualize the complete killer move rapidly to get rid of the qi harvest fruit!"

Chapter 2028: Heaven Path Research Results

After hearing that Qi Sea Ancestor wanted heaven path true meaning, Qin Ding Ling smiled bitterly: "Even though Heavenly Court has deep foundations, we have never seen nor heard of heaven path true meaning."

"Oh? Why is that so?" Qi Sea Ancestor asked.

"Because nobody can cultivate heaven path. If it can be cultivated, why would our Heavenly Court create Heaven Overseeing Tower to make use of fate Gu?" Qin Ding Ling's words were filled with deep emotions.

No Gu Immortal could cultivate heaven path, therefore, heaven path true meaning had never existed!

It was not easy for a Gu Immortal to leave behind true meaning.

To leave behind true meaning, wisdom path and rule path had the greatest ease. As for other paths, they had to reach a certain level of mimicking these paths to leave their true meaning behind. For example, Long Hair Ancestor's refinement path true meaning or Reckless Savage's transformation path true meaning.

After hearing Qin Ding Ling's reply, Fang Yuan did not feel dejected.

He came prepared, his request was actually his probing towards Heavenly Court's foundation, what if they had it after all?

Heavenly Court not having heaven path true meaning was not unexpected.

Qi Sea Ancestor (Fang Yuan) sighed deeply as he transmitted to Qin Ding Ling: "Then there is no hope. I can only come out and fight alongside Heavenly Court to kill these variant humans."

Qin Ding Ling instantly became anxious.

The qi harvest fruit was Heavenly Court's fatal weakness, the reason why they could still maintain a deadlock was because Qi Sea Ancestor made the fruit smaller. Once he lets go and it returns to being mountain size, Heavenly Court would be in a difficult spot, the situation would be hard to turn around.

Qin Ding Ling was facing immense pressure now.

Some of her pressure came from the enemies, but a portion came from within her.

After the fate war, the immortal graveyard was heavily damaged, Heavenly Court's foundation was reduced, Qin Ding Ling had to take on this responsibility and manage all the affairs of Heavenly Court, which was on the brink of destruction.

She worked hard over these days, she had given it her all, she exerted her body and mind for Heavenly Court, trying to restore its former glory.

Similar to the other Heavenly Court members, Qin Ding Ling had an intense feeling of belonging to Heavenly Court.

But now, the enemies were attacking suddenly, they even had the fatal weakness of the qi harvest fruit, Qin Ding Ling sensed a huge danger: "Was Heavenly Court going to be destroyed in this fight? Was it because of her failure to defend it, would she be the biggest sinner of Heavenly Court's history?"

Rumble!

The intense battle continued, Dragon Palace rampaged unhindered.

Qin Ding Ling took charge of the situation, observing the battlefield, while mobilizing the people and communicating with Qi Sea Ancestor.

With both internal and external threats, the pressure was pushing her to make a gamble.

"Qi Sea, do not give up. Even though Heavenly Court does not have heaven path true meaning, we have abundant heaven path research results. I will hand them to you!"

Qin Ding Ling passed an information path Immortal Gu to Qi Sea Ancestor without hesitation.

"My plan succeeded!" Fang Yuan received this information path Immortal Gu, he sighed deeply in his heart as he looked into it immediately.

"Brilliant! Wonderful! Astounding!" Fang Yuan only saw a small portion but his eyes shined with bright light, he praised it continuously in his heart.

For the last three million years, Heavenly Court rose to become the number one human force in the world. These years, they initially followed the will of heaven, before trying to resist it later, followed by altering heaven's will and interfering with the Heavenly Dao.

Their heaven path research results were abundant, they undeniably had the most progress in the world!

Fate Gu was a heaven path Immortal Gu, it could not be used by anyone. But Heavenly Court forcibly created Heaven Overseeing Tower and unleashed a portion of fate Gu's might.

In the five hundred years of his previous life, why did Spectral Soul infiltrate Heavenly Court? A large portion of the reasons were to try obtaining the heaven path research results!

As for why Limitless Demon Venerable decided to make a bet with Star Constellation's will and set up a game of chess, wasn't it because he wanted to use Heavenly Court's heaven path research results to help in his plan within Crazed Demon Cave?

And now, they ended up in Fang Yuan's hands.

Fang Yuan looked into them, his heart shook.

He saw two killer moves.

One was named heaven-human sensation, the other was called human executing heaven's work, they were both created by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable.

Heaven-human sensation allowed a Gu Immortal's will to interact and fuse with heaven's will. Human executing heaven's work was built on the foundation of heaven-human sensation, it allowed a Gu Immortal to replace heaven's will to a certain degree.

Precisely because of these two killer moves, Star Constellation's will could interfere and affect heaven's will, she could even replace heaven's will to control fate Gu and allow Heavenly Court to have a decisive rule for three million years!

"The solution lies in this!" Fang Yuan acutely sensed that these two killer moves were the key to breaking out of his current predicament.

He took a risk to come to Heavenly Court now and deceive Qin Ding Ling, it was to achieve his goals, which were finally reached.

"Qi Sea, I wonder if these research results can help you complete the killer move?" Qin Ding Ling asked while in intense battle.

Fang Yuan coughed: "Your heaven path research results are quite helpful to me. But modifying a killer move right now carries risk, I need you to fight and stall for time, get me as much time as possible."

Qin Ding Ling gritted her teeth: "Ancestor, you need to be fast, we can only do our best. In the worst case, we have to give up Heavenly Court and save the Gu Immortals instead."

She had already made plans for the worst case scenario.

Fang Yuan continued to read.

Following the two killer moves were the concepts that Star Constellation Immortal Venerable came up with, Fang Yuan looked at them and gained deep enlightenment.

"My will represents heaven's will, heaven's will represents my will... so that's it, so that's it."

Fang Yuan remained stationary as he focused on comprehending this information, he allowed his clone, Wu Shuai, to continue leading the two heavens alliance to fight against Heavenly Court.

Because of Primordial Origin's method, Di Zang Sheng was no longer as strong, Ruan Dan suppressed it. As for Shabi Ninety-five, it had already rejoined the defensive line, to become part of the force that resisted Dragon Palace.

Under Wu Shuai's control, Dragon Palace charged around the battlefield unhindered, Heavenly Court was greatly troubled by its power.

But on the other hand, the Gu Immortals of the two heavens alliance were suppressed, they were not as powerful as each Heavenly Court Gu Immortal.

Compared to the Heavenly Court members, they were lacking in strength. Only two people had equivalent battle strength, they were the two vice alliance leaders, Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian.

As for Spectral Soul, who was pretending to be Lady Cold Ash, he continued to conceal himself, on the surface, he was desperately fighting and unable to put up strong resistance.

"This is a prime opportunity! Fairy Zi Wei, bring everyone and participate in the battle in Heavenly Court!" Spectral Soul gave instructions: "Fang Yuan is in Heavenly Court, I will kill him, the members of Heavenly Court, and Qi Sea Ancestor."

Fairy Zi Wei received the instructions and asked: "Do we include Longevity Heaven's group? Do we tell them about the situation in Heavenly Court?"

Fairy Zi Wei had only deduced Fang Yuan's location, Bing Sai Chuan knew about it too. But he did not know about Heavenly Court's current situation, he just thought that they were being cautious.

In that case, Bing Sai Chuan would need to conceal the information of Fang Yuan's location. Even though he wanted to let them fight each other as well, if Heavenly Court captures or kills Fang Yuan, they would gain all of his inheritances and Immortal Gu, wouldn't that be benefiting them?

Thus, Bing Sai Chuan's plan was to continue working with Spectral Soul's side and try to attack Heavenly Court together next time.

Spectral Soul recalled the attack from Giant Sun during the fate war and snorted coldly, he did not hesitate: "No need to tell them, hide this from them, your group will come alone!"

Thus, Fairy Zi Wei did not say anything, after leaving Bing Sai Chuan's group, her group headed towards Heavenly Court.

Heavenly Court was damaged and the aperture wall was cracked, it became connected to the outside world. Fairy Zi Wei and the rest could get in very quickly.

"Fairy Zi Wei's group cannot turn the situation around, we need to wait until both sides suffer mutual loss before we can exert the maximum impact." Spectral Soul considered.

For him, the best case was for Wu Shuai and Heavenly Court to cripple each other's battle strength. By then, if he took action, he would reap huge gains.

"But why hasn't that scoundrel Fang Yuan done anything?" Spectral Soul observed Dragon Palace while at the same time, an Immortal Gu House from Heavenly Court attacked him.

Spectral Soul withheld his killing intent, he abandoned a group of soul beasts, retreating continuously.

In order to lay low, he decided to wait and endure.

But this Immortal Gu House came for him and used a killer move, a ray of profound light shot out towards Spectral Soul.

Spectral Soul's heart shook as he hesitated. He had the ability to dodge this but Lady Cold Ash did not. There was no choice, he abandoned another group of soul beasts to block the Immortal Gu House and stall for time.

"Die!" Che Wei suddenly appeared behind Lady Cold Ash, his body shined in golden light, his aura was sharp as a blade.

"Do you really think I'm easy to bully?" Spectral Soul was deeply enraged but he decided to keep up the act.

Boom!

Che Wei's attack landed on Lady Cold Ash, she fell towards the ground as she coughed out mouthfuls of blood.

Lady Cold Ash's aura weakened continuously until it was completely still.

"Dead!"

"I killed another one."

Che Wei did not sense Spectral Soul, he flew away in the Immortal Gu House, towards the other areas of the battlefield.

Spectral Soul remained on the ground like a corpse, not moving and pretending to be dead.

Boom boom boom!

A while after he landed on the ground, a series of immortal killer moves turned into lightning as they shot down, erupting around Spectral Soul's body.

Lady Cold Ash was turned into char, half of her flesh was cooked and emitted the fragrance of meat.

"I'll endure!" Spectral Soul gritted his teeth.

Bam.

With a loud sound, Di Zang Sheng also fell, it landed on top of Spectral Soul.

Next, Ruan Dan flew towards Di Zang Sheng and shouted excitedly: "Attack, attack, attack, attack, attack!"

Bam bam bam...

The ground shook intensely, Spectral Soul's bones were almost all crushed: "I'll endure!"

Di Zang Sheng and Ruan Dan flew away, soon, an Immortal Gu House came.

It was Dragon Palace.

Immortal killer move — Dreamy Light Smoke!

Wu Shuai used a dream path killer move and chased after Qin Ding Ling relentlessly.

Qin Ding Ling dodged the attack rapidly, the dreamy smoke killer move could not turn around in time, it was about to land on Spectral Soul.

Spectral Soul: "..."

"Enough is enough!" At the next moment, he rose up abruptly, waving his hand, black qi permeated throughout the entire battlefield.

Whoosh, the ground shook, mountains rumbled, all of the Gu Immortals present were blown away by the impact.

Chapter 2029: What's The Situation?

"What... what's the situation?" As black qi surged, Xiao He Jian was forced to retreat with shock on his face.

He saw the moment when Lady Cold Ash was killed by Che Wei, he felt a little pity for her. To think that soon after, she would actually revive!

"Was she pretending to be dead earlier, but because of bad luck, the dream path killer move almost hit her, so she had to retaliate? But... why does Lady Cold Ash have such battle strength?"

Not only was Xiao He Jian shocked, the other Gu Immortals had the same doubts.

But compared to Heavenly Court, the two heavens alliance was also filled with joy. After all, even though Lady Cold Ash was deeply concealing her strength, she was still one of them.

"That hit earlier has power similar to Duke Long. Is Lady Cold Ash someone on Duke Long's level? Hmph, I refuse to believe it!" A Gu Immortal on Heavenly Court's side flew out again, it was none other than Che Wei, who was displaying great might in this battle.

Che Wei flew towards Lady Cold Ash, all sorts of signs showed that the move earlier was Lady Cold Ash's trump card, it could not be used often.

"Die!" Che Wei's body radiated with golden light as he flew towards Lady Cold Ash like a crashing meteor.

At the same time, somewhere underground far from the battlefield.

Two Heavenly Court members were still trying to forcefully refine hatred Gu.

Red Heart Traveler controlled the formation while Qing Chou remained unmoving like a statue.

Nine Spiritual Fairy's voice came from within the statue: "We are almost done, in just a few more minutes, we will thoroughly refine hatred Gu!"

Once she said that, Qing Chou's dim eyes burst open, endless blood red light shot out of its eyes!

"What is going on?" Nine Spiritual Fairy shouted in shock.

"What happened?" Red Heart Traveler asked while instilling immortal essence, raising the power of the immortal formation.

But Qing Chou's body started to shake with greater intensity.

"It's hatred Gu... oh no!" Nine Spiritual Fairy suddenly shouted, she flew out of Qing Chou's body like a flash of light.

Roar—!

Qing Chou regained freedom, it roared towards the sky, its voice resounded throughout the area, exploding with thunderous impact.

Boom!

At the next moment, Qing Chou charged out of the formation, flying towards the surface, leaving behind a damaged formation and two immensely shocked Heavenly Court rank eight Gu Immortals.

Red Heart Traveler, who was controlling the formation, suffered a considerable backlash, he quickly assisted the falling Nine Spiritual Fairy as he asked: "Qing Chou has flown to the battlefield, what in the world happened?"

Nine Spiritual Fairy was still in a daze, she said in uncertainty: "Maybe I saw wrongly, but at that moment, rank eight hatred Immortal Gu burst out with terrifying power, it... it had a trace of a rank nine Immortal Gu's aura!"

At this time, the battlefield had already shifted its attention from Dragon Palace and the qi harvest fruit to Lady Cold Ash.

Lady Cold Ash's attack was too powerful, it shocked all of the Gu Immortals.

Che Wei arrived before her, Lady Cold Ash only snorted coldly as her body flew up, turning into black light as she charged towards Dragon Palace!

At the same time, Lady Cold Ash shouted in a loud voice: "Fang Yuan, it is time for us to settle the score!"

Spectral Soul had a straightforward idea, since Fang Yuan was not showing up, he would force him out.

Times were different now.

During the fate war, Spectral Soul was very weak, he could only escape and recuperate using Fairy Zi Wei and Old Man Zheng Yuan's strength. But now, he had already gained much of his strength, he was no longer weak.

"What is going on?" The immortals were truly stunned.

Lady Cold Ash actually ignored Che Wei, she went straight for Dragon Palace!

"Internal strife?" Che Wei's movement halted for a moment.

"Wait and see first, this might be their scheme!" Qin Ding Ling wanted to play safe, she got the immortals to gather.

Wu Shuai frowned, he moved Dragon Palace to retreat.

But Lady Cold Ash was faster!

She placed her palm at the top of Dragon Palace.

It seemed like a weak action but it made the entire Dragon Palace fly out like a cannonball.

At the same time, the silhouettes of immemorial soul beasts appeared on the surface of Dragon Palace.

Roar roar roar...

Each immemorial soul beast silhouette that flickered would deal a huge attack to Dragon Palace. After more than ten immemorial soul beasts appeared, there was already a huge hole at the top of Dragon Palace, the pillars broke and tiles cracked, it was a terrifying sight.

Che Wei watched with sweat on his forehead, he knew the power of Dragon Palace, but Lady Cold Ash had dealt such damage to it with just one palm strike.

"So Lady Cold Ash is actually so strong! I was simply courting death earlier by attacking her." Che Wei immediately changed directions as he retreated.

"Lady Cold Ash, what are you doing?!" Xiao He Jian shouted.

"What soul path killer move is this, it has such power..." Even though Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch showed an angry expression, he was enveloped in cold sweat.

Dragon Palace was still retreating.

"Can you escape?" Lady Cold Ash smiled coldly, she was about to attack again when a huge shadow enshrouded her body.

Lady Cold Ash turned back to take a look, she saw Qing Chou, having the size of a mountain, it had gotten close to her at some point, opening its bloodthirsty mouth as it tried to devour her.

"Hmm?" Seeing this, even Lady Cold Ash's gaze froze for a second.

Spectral Soul was aware of Qing Chou's existence. But he did not expect to meet Qing Chou at this place and time.

Seeing that Lady Cold Ash was about to die, suddenly, her body turned into black smoke as she drifted away, dodging Qing Chou's attack.

"Beast, scram!" Lady Cold Ash shouted, she stretched out her hand and placed it on Qing Chou's head.

The scene from earlier was seen again, immemorial soul beast silhouettes appeared around Qing Chou as they flickered.

Bam bam bam...

Each time a silhouette appeared, an explosive sound would follow.

Qing Chou was soon covered in injuries but it did not retreat even in the danger of death!

Spectral Soul was just about to chase after Dragon Palace when Qing Chou blocked his path again.

"Spectral Soul, I will kill you, I will kill you!" Qing Chou shouted as it pounced at Lady Cold Ash.

Spectral Soul was enraged: "I have no time to waste with you."

He controlled Lady Cold Ash's body as he prepared a terrifying killer move. Black smoke started to come out of Lady Cold Ash's seven orifices, her aura was growing at a terrifying manner.

Black smoke gathered and moved towards Qing Chou.

Qing Chou's offensive killer move went into the black smoke.

After a breath's time, the black smoke scattered, Qing Chou's killer move landed on Lady Cold Ash without becoming weaker at all.

Lady Cold Ash's expression turned to shock, she was sent flying after being caught off guard.

"Rank nine Immortal Gu? No, just an incomplete product." Lady Cold Ash swallowed a mouthful of blood, she squinted her eyes and looked at Qing Chou, her expression was stern.

Nine Spiritual Fairy had just arrived in the battlefield, her pupils shrunk: "I did not sense wrongly, rank eight hatred Gu is going to become rank nine!"

"Qing Chou originated from the souls that Spectral Soul slaughtered. The core Immortal Gu that created Qing Chou was hatred Gu, but hatred Gu and Qing Chou had an extraordinary connection. Not only did hatred Gu create Qing Chou, Qing Chou is also nourishing and nurturing hatred Gu."

"Maybe hatred Gu was just rank six, or even four or five at the start. But as Qing Chou grew, its endless hatred allowed hatred Gu to continuously grow until now. It is already moving from rank eight to rank nine!"

Rank nine hatred Gu!

Chapter 2030: Spectral Soul's Demonic Might

What was this situation?

Seeing that Lady Cold Ash got sent flying by Qing Chou, the immortals present were stunned.

The rank nine Immortal Gu aura was not fake, but it was too weak, the main part of the aura was still at the level of rank eight Immortal Gu. This was something that was unheard of.

An incomplete rank nine Immortal Gu?

All the immortals were bewildered.

Gu refinement had always been a strict process, be they human or hairy man refinement methods, they had their specifications.

This was true for both Fang Yuan and Long Hair Ancestor. There had never been a case where a Gu worm could still be used in battle during refinement.

But the truth was in front of them, the immortals had to admit the fact.

"What refinement method is this?" Many Gu Immortals became quite excited: "This will start a new trend of refinement path!"

"Spectral Soul? Qing Chou possesses hatred Gu, it should not be wrong. To think that Lady Cold Ash's body was actually taken over by Spectral Soul."

"Seeing what Spectral Soul said, it seems that Fang Yuan is here too, hiding in Dragon Palace?"

The Gu Immortals were startled and puzzled.

Too many unexpected incidents had happened in this battle. Heavenly Court, the two heavens, Spectral Soul, and Fang Yuan all had their own plans, nobody knew the entire situation clearly. Even though Fang Yuan was reborn, he was the same.

Spectral Soul's identity was exposed, Fang Yuan felt quite relieved about it.

Dragon Palace retreated even more quickly. Wu Shuai recalled the three dragon generals, at the same time, the Gu Immortals of the two heavens alliance guarded Dragon Palace against Spectral Soul.

Wu Shuai did not dare to risk letting the immortals of the two heavens alliance into his Dragon Palace, the appearance of Spectral Soul made everyone else suspicious as well.

"I can't wait anymore..." Qi Sea Ancestor (Fang Yuan) gritted his teeth before activating his hidden method. He was originally intending to wait some more, but with Spectral Soul's appearance and Qing Chou's assault, he understood that the situation was out of his control, he needed to act quickly!

Fang Yuan immediately contacted Qin Ding Ling: "The modification has some results, protect me well, we will go into the critical period now!"

"Understood!" Joy flashed on Qin Ding Ling's face, this was the best news she had heard since the battle started.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals shrunk back to form a tight defensive circle, they defended against Spectral Soul and Wu Shuai's Dragon Palace.

Roar—!

Qing Chou charged towards Lady Cold Ash.

Hatred Gu's rank nine aura was getting stronger, it seemed like Spectral Soul's appearance had summoned the deepest hatred in Qing Chou's heart, this intense feeling of hatred was rapidly helping to refine hatred Gu.

Hatred Gu activated, amplifying Qing Chou's strength comprehensively. Especially offensive killer moves, their might was increased to a terrifying level.

Spectral Soul and Qing Chou fought, he actually got suppressed for some time.

The killing intent on his face became denser, after a few rounds, he spat out a mouthful of black qi.

The black qi was small and insignificant, but once it flew towards Qing Chou, it made Qing Chou's movements slow, its attacks were no longer rapid.

Spectral Soul's body shook, turning into countless phantoms and surrounded Qing Chou tightly.

Qing Chou possessed hatred Gu, it should be able to find out the real Spectral Soul. But against the countless Spectral Souls, it showed a confused expression, having lost its target.

Spectral Soul's main body suddenly appeared on the back of Qing Chou, he stretched out his palm and his entire forearm was stabbed into Qing Chou's body.

Qing Chou's body started to shiver, it felt extreme pain as it raised its head and roared!

Qing Chou unleashed immortal killer moves consecutively, ignoring its own state as it assaulted Spectral Soul who was on its back.

Spectral Soul endured the endless assault but continued to sustain his current method.

Qing Chou fell on the ground, with a loud sound, the earth rumbled, a huge pit was created.

Qing Chou rolled on the ground, it was unable to shrug off Spectral Soul.

"Oh no, he is trying to refine Qing Chou!" Qin Ding Ling saw what was happening, her heart jumped, she wanted to order the Gu Immortals to disrupt Spectral Soul.

But Wu Shuai moved one step earlier.

Dragon Palace unleashed dreamy light smoke as a cloud of pink smoke flew towards Spectral Soul.

Spectral Soul was not afraid of other methods but dream path methods were still threatening.

He had no choice but to stop and retreat for now.

Qing Chou regained freedom as a result but it was very weak, it almost fell to the ground.

In contrast, Spectral Soul flew to the sky with an increased aura. Evidently, the method used against Qing Chou earlier was not just enslavement, it also had a special ability to extract its strength.

Seeing this, almost all the Gu Immortals' hearts sank.

Qing Chou has a quasi-rank nine hatred Gu, its battle strength rose drastically, reaching the levels of Fang Yuan, Duke Long, and Feng Jiu Ge during the fate war, but it was ineffective against Spectral Soul.

Other than catching Spectral Soul off guard initially, once he was prepared, Qing Chou got easily countered afterwards.

In the end, Qing Chou was still an immemorial soul beast, it was against Spectral Soul, who was primarily a soul path cultivator and had the deepest knowledge of this. Spectral Soul had a bunch of methods to counter immemorial soul beasts, in fact, the reason for the creation of soul beasts was Spectral Soul himself.

"What a pity, I was so close to enslaving this legendary desolate beast. Hmph! Fang Yuan, you are courting death." Spectral Soul's plan was foiled, he emanated killing intent with a cold expression, attacking Dragon Palace again.

The two sides fought again, Wu Shuai put in all his effort but he could not resist Spectral Soul's methods, he was forced to retreat.

Spectral Soul's demonic might was overwhelming, he dominated the entire battlefield without difficulty. Dragon Palace, which was showing great performance earlier, could not defend against his unparalleled power.

His killer moves were endless, they either had great strength or peculiar effects, they were all hard to defend against.

Spectral Soul had already recovered, even though he was not at the level when he refined sovereign immortal fetus Gu on Yi Tian Mountain, he had mostly regained his strength.

Wu Shuai controlled Dragon Palace to fight against Spectral Soul, during this time, Qing Chou and the rest also interfered, but they were all suppressed, the situation was getting increasingly dangerous.

After more than ten rounds of fighting, Dragon Palace was heavily damaged, the three dragon generals all died at Spectral Soul's hands. Thankfully, there was the killer move dreamy light smoke that Spectral Soul was worried about.

The Gu Immortals of the two heavens alliance could not be depended on, they all hid at one side. Spectral Soul's might was too terrifying, whoever got close would die.

"The time is about ripe." Wu Shuai finally received the instructions from his main body.

He let out a breath of air, driving Dragon Palace towards the qi harvest fruit.

Qin Ding Ling and the rest had formed into a defensive line, they became alarmed, they shot out endless profound lights.

Wu Shuai shouted: "Heavenly Court, if you still refuse to take action, after Spectral Soul kills me, you will all die as well."

Qin Ding Ling retorted: "Stop right now, whoever comes here will face our full-on assault!"

During the fight between Spectral Soul and Dragon Palace, Heavenly Court had been watching at the side, not doing anything. Qin Ding Ling and the rest were waiting for Fang Yuan, as long as he stayed motionless, they would not attack. Nobody knew what vile schemes this demon Fang Yuan was preparing after all!

Wu Shuai did not care, he steered Dragon Palace to get close to Heavenly Court's defensive line.

Behind him, Spectral Soul chased relentlessly.

Qin Ding Ling's expression was grim, she ordered: "Attack Dragon Palace, force it back!"

Rumble...

All sorts of killer moves landed on Dragon Palace, creating beautiful ripples of various colors in the sky. Dragon Palace was like a crumbling boat, riding against the dangerous waves.

Large numbers of Gu worms died, including Immortal Gu.

This battle caused severe losses to Dragon Palace, the price to repair it would be extremely high.

"Oh no, it is getting close!"

They watched as Dragon Palace almost went past Heavenly Court's defensive line, at the crucial moment, Shabi Ninety-five and Ruan Dan came out to block Dragon Palace despite the danger.

But soon, Spectral Soul also arrived, chaos ensued.

"Die!" Spectral Soul's killing intent surged, he soon gained the upper hand.

Heavenly Court's defensive line was collapsing.

Right at this moment, Qi Sea Ancestor's laughter could be heard.

Swish swish swish!

The originally condensed qi harvest fruit exploded into a tsunami, engulfing heaven and earth, clouds and winds raged, at once, the entire battlefield was filled with qi currents over a massive range.

At once, all the Gu Immortals lost their sense of direction, they could only see white qi in front of them, they could not even see their own fingers.

At the center of the qi currents, there was a baby shape gathering, it devoured the white qi.

In a few breaths of time, the baby grew rapidly, turning old as it became Qi Sea Ancestor's appearance, having rank eight cultivation level!

Fang Yuan's main body flickered, he waved his sleeves, a split soul that was prepared in advance flew out, carrying Gu worms and immortal essence into Qi Sea Ancestor's body.

After the split soul arrived, the Qi Sea clone opened his eyes.

While Fang Yuan's main body used the opportunity to enter Dragon Palace.

Chapter 2031: Chasing, Escaping

Fang Yuan had always taken action after planning, even though this venture to Heavenly Court was dangerous, he had made ample preparations.

He refined Heavenly Court's qi harvest fruit into his qi path clone, while the main body went into Dragon Palace at this very moment. Even though there were many Gu Immortals in the battlefield, nobody found out the truth.

Fang Yuan's qi path clone breathed in deeply, all of the white qi got absorbed into his body.

Next, he pushed with both arms as a thunderous sound occurred, a dense qi wall formed and pushed towards Dragon Palace and Spectral Soul with overwhelming might.

Spectral Soul's eyes shined with bright light, black qi burst out of his body and crashed into the qi wall, emitting a loud sound.

The qi wall was corroded but the surrounding qi wall came to fill it up again. Spectral Soul made use of this timing to turn into black light and penetrate through it like a flash of lightning.

A portion of Spectral Soul's focus was kept on Qi Sea Ancestor, while most of his attention remained on Dragon Palace.

Dragon Palace was huge, it would not be easy to pass the qi wall. Once Dragon Palace exposed a weakness while resisting the qi wall, Spectral Soul would take action and make use of Qi Sea Ancestor's killer move to deal a huge blow to Dragon Palace.

Right when the qi wall was about to crash into Dragon Palace, its door opened, Fang Yuan stood upright, appearing in front of everyone.

Immortal killer move — Unlimited Qi Sea!

Fang Yuan was already well prepared, he raised his right arm now as he grabbed towards the qi wall with his five fingers.

The colossal qi wall shook as it collapsed, countless qi currents were drawn by a formless force, going into Fang Yuan's immortal aperture.

"Fang Yuan!"

"He was here after all."

"This move again! During the fate war, he used this move to unravel primordial qi wall!"

The immortals saw Fang Yuan's appearance as all of them shook.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were all ashen, after they lost the fate war, Fang Yuan had turned into a nightmare that shrouded over their minds.

The two heavens alliance's Gu Immortals were joyful instead. Seeing Fang Yuan's action, it was clear that he was on their side.

Spectral Soul's pupils shrunk, Fang Yuan's performance was quite shocking. He was troubled by the heaven path dao marks after all, how could he still display such immense battle strength?

The entire battlefield fell into peculiar silence.

Fang Yuan and Qi Sea Ancestor appeared at the same time, the entire battlefield's situation was turned around in an instant.

Heavenly Court protected Qi Sea Ancestor, Spectral Soul was alone, while Fang Yuan was standing in front of Dragon Palace, the three strongest Gu Immortals prepared to face off against each other.

In the Gu world, strength reigned supreme, the following battle would depend on these three people.

"To think that this day would come when Heavenly Court fails to be the leader of this confrontation." Qin Ding Ling sighed in her heart as she transmitted to Qi Sea Ancestor, asking about his condition.

Qi Sea Ancestor immediately replied: "Even though I got rid of the qi harvest fruit, I suffered considerable injuries. I will need everyone from Heavenly Court to work together to survive this crisis."

Qin Ding Ling said again: "Heavenly Court's greatest threat was resolved thanks to you, ancestor. After we survive this, Heavenly Court will definitely reward you satisfactorily!"

Qin Ding Ling was trying very hard to gain Qi Sea Ancestor's help, at this moment, Dragon Palace flew out like an orange meteor towards the sky!

After this catastrophic battle, Heavenly Court was completely covered in holes. Dragon Palace escaped along one of these loopholes, easily leaving Heavenly Court and entering immemorial white heaven.

The remaining immortals looked at Dragon Palace's figure with stunned expressions.

Even though Fang Yuan appeared and cooperated with Wu Shuai, the two of them had actually escaped.

Was this the showing of the number one demon?

"It seems that Fang Yuan has not recovered."

"Even though that move was ferocious and broke Qi Sea Ancestor's qi wall killer move earlier, he was likely at his limit!"

"Do we chase them? This demon Fang Yuan is too crafty, I am afraid that this is just his plan to lure us out. He might have an immortal formation outside lying in ambush, waiting for us to head into his trap."

The Heavenly Court Gu Immortals hesitated while the two heavens alliance Gu Immortals cursed in their hearts.

The expert and leader that they placed their hopes and morale on had actually escaped, they fled so quickly!

All of these two heavens alliance Gu Immortals were left in Heavenly Court, they were abandoned.

"Fang Yuan, where are you running to? Die here and now." Spectral Soul snickered as he used Lady Cold Ash's body to rush out of Heavenly Court, chasing after Dragon Palace.

Roar—!

Qing Chou roared, it was gradually recovering the strength that it lost, even though the rank nine aura of its hatred Gu was not complete, it was already much denser than before.

"Spectral Soul, I want you to die!" Qing Chou, who had unresolvable hatred, did not hesitate, it chased after Spectral Soul.

Thus, in the battlefield, only Heavenly Court's immortals, Qi Sea Ancestor, and the two heavens alliance's Gu Immortals were left.

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian looked at each other.

They were in an awkward situation now!

"We will chase them!"

"Protect Dragon Palace!!"

Ice Crystal Immortal Monarch and Xiao He Jian worked together for the first time, they shouted something that they did not believe in as they charged out of Heavenly Court.

The remaining two heavens alliance Gu Immortals followed after them, shouting and jeering as they also went out of Heavenly Court along with the two vice alliance leaders.

"Are we going to kill these variant human Gu Immortals?" Prince Feng Xian asked Qin Ding Ling.

Qin Ding Ling looked towards Qi Sea Ancestor, she thought about it before saying resolutely: "No! These variant human Gu Immortals are just minor problems, the most important thing is Fang Yuan. Two people will stay behind to take care of the place, the rest will follow me to pursue and kill Fang Yuan!!"

Fang Yuan was not in good condition now, it was the best time to kill him.

If they manage to kill Fang Yuan, the loot they could gain would be extremely favorable to Heavenly Court. Fang Yuan had too many good things, he had countless Immortal Gu and exceptional inheritances. Even without them, as long as they could capture his soul and extract the memories of his previous life, it would be incredibly precious to Heavenly Court!

In fact, even if Heavenly Court gets nothing from killing Fang Yuan, just the fact that he died at their hands would allow Heavenly Court to regain their morale, they would break free of the trauma of the fate war, they would be at the top of the world again.

"Even if we cannot kill Fang Yuan, we cannot let Spectral Soul kill Fang Yuan!" Furthermore, Qin Ding Ling was also wary of that old monster Spectral Soul.

"Ancestor..." Qin Ding Ling was about to speak when Qi Sea Ancestor interrupted her.

"No need to say anything, be it Spectral Soul or Fang Yuan, they are both demons, us righteous path members should execute them all. Time is pressing, our opportunity is slipping, we need to chase them now!" At the crucial moment, Qi Sea Ancestor displayed the demeanor of a heroic leader of the righteous path!

The Heavenly Court immortals felt much closer to him after hearing that.

Qin Ding Ling nodded gravely, without Qi Sea Ancestor's help, they would not be able to chase Fang Yuan safely.

"The main body's situation is strange, I need to look after him. These Heavenly Court Gu Immortals are much better cannon fodder than those two heavens alliance immortals!" Qi Sea Ancestor made his plan internally, leading the Heavenly Court immortals as they chased.

This way, Dragon Palace was at the front, followed by Spectral Soul, who was getting closer.

Followed by Qing Chou.

Followed by Qi Sea Ancestor and the Heavenly Court immortals.

As for the two vice alliance leaders of the two heavens alliance, they had already escaped from Heavenly Court with the other immortals, they scattered all over the place thinking only of escaping, nobody dared to join this battle anymore.

At this moment, Dragon Palace was still tightly shut.

Fang Yuan sat on the ground, modifying the two killer moves, heaven-human sensation and human executing heaven's work.

Fang Yuan lacked more than half of the Gu worms needed for these killer moves. He had to modify the moves and swap out the Gu worms so that he could use these moves.

Immortal Gu were unique, these two killer moves were newly obtained, Fang Yuan had quite a bit of difficulty in the modification.

After attempting it for some time, Fang Yuan changed his tactic, he gave up on the Immortal Gu level and targeted the aspect of a mortal killer move.

Fang Yuan connected to treasure yellow heaven and soon gathered the relevant mortal Gu worms. With the necessary Gu worms and after modifying the move from an immortal killer move to a mortal killer move, the difficult became nearly nonexistent.

With these two mortal killer moves, Fang Yuan stopped the formation in the sovereign immortal aperture, no longer using qi tides to cleanse the immortal aperture's nine heavens and five regions.

Soon, heaven's will was produced.

Fang Yuan sent a portion of his will towards the heaven's will.

Next, he activated the killer move heaven-human sensation, Fang Yuan fused into the heaven's will.

After that, he activated human executing heaven's work.

After a while.

Fang Yuan's eyes shined with bright light: "I sensed... a certain group of heaven path dao marks!"

If he had to replace the word 'sensed', Fang Yuan would choose another word, caught.

Originally, Fang Yuan knew about the heaven path dao marks in his body, but he could only let them be. But now, when he could sense them, it meant that these heaven path dao marks were under his control temporarily.

With this crucial breakthrough and Fang Yuan's expertise in Gu refinement, it was only a matter of time until he refined all of these heaven path dao marks into his own.

Chapter 2032: Target, Crazed Demon Cave

Rumble!

With a loud sound, Dragon Palace shook intensely from the impact, a large portion of its roof cracked and fell. While falling, these fragments turned into Gu worm corpses, scattered by the intense winds in the sky.

Spectral Soul had caught up!

He was extremely fast, even though Wu Shuai was moving Dragon Palace at top speed, he could not reach Spectral Soul's speed.

Spectral Soul's body was covered in pitch black smoke, each time he attacked, Dragon Palace suffered great damage.

Wu Shuai had to put in his effort to repair it, thankfully, he had many Gu worms in his storage, he was amply prepared.

Fang Yuan frowned tightly, his expression was slightly grim.

He came to Heavenly Court using Qi Sea Ancestor's identity to find a way to resolve his heaven path dao mark problem. Once his goal was achieved, he chose to retreat, Fang Yuan had never cared about the title of the number one demon.

However, even though Fang Yuan got what he wanted, he needed time now, what he lacked was sufficient time to execute his plan.

"Now, Spectral Soul is chasing after me, Heavenly Court will do the same, these people will not let me retreat easily. It is very difficult to escape from this situation!"

Fang Yuan's movement ability had always been improving. Long ago, his strongest movement method was the killer move sword escape after transforming into an ancient sword dragon. After that was Omni-directional Travel, followed by Fixed Immortal Travel and the killer move comprising Fixed Immortal Travel as the core.

But among these methods, even Omni-directional Travel could not match Spectral Soul's speed. Fixed Immortal Travel's killer move might be usable but Fang Yuan was very weak now from the disturbance of the heaven path dao marks.

There was still some time until Fang Yuan could resolve this disturbance and fully refine the heaven path dao marks.

Fang Yuan tried to think about it from another perspective, be they Spectral Soul or Heavenly Court, they wanted him dead. The former used all of his accumulations to refine sovereign immortal fetus Gu but Fang Yuan snatched it away. The latter's headquarters were ravaged by Fang Yuan, their biggest pillar of support, fate Gu, was also destroyed by him. Heavenly Court was the leader of the righteous path, they cared about reputation, but in the fate war, Fang Yuan destroyed their reputation.

Before now, Heavenly Court could not find Fang Yuan so they did not do anything to him. In the future, when he recovered his strength, they would also be unable to deal with him.

Now that Heavenly Court found Fang Yuan, they would definitely try their best to kill him!

Such opportunities seldom knock twice, they could not let this chance slip by.

Fang Yuan knew about his circumstances clearly, thoughts collided in his mind continuously as he tried to find a solution for this problem.

But soon, his expression changed.

The heaven path dao marks on his body started to transform again, causing problems, their disturbance became stronger by several times.

When dealing with the qi wall earlier, even though Fang Yuan caused a huge scene, he was actually cooperating with Qi Sea Ancestor secretly, his true battle strength was not as it appeared.

But just this much, with Fang Yuan secretly using human path methods to counter the interruption of the heaven path dao marks, was already the greatest limit.

Externally, Spectral Soul was attacking Dragon Palace furiously, the walls were cracking, tiles were sent flying all over the place. Internally, the heaven path dao marks were wreaking havoc in his body, preventing Fang Yuan from doing anything.

The situation was dangerous, even surpassing the fate war. After all, Fang Yuan could still use Spring Autumn Cicada then, but now, this greatest trump card was unusable.

Fang Yuan could not rebirth, if he made a mistake now, he would die a pitiful death.

Spectral Soul emanated deep killing intent, it pierced through Dragon Palace, Fang Yuan's hair stood on ends.

Fang Yuan's lips curled up, he had already made a decision —

Head to Crazed Demon Cave!

The heaven path dao marks were interfering with Fang Yuan, preventing him from using many killer moves. Even if he could use them, the effect would be very low.

Fang Yuan had to borrow external help to alleviate this crisis.

Any other location would not be very helpful to Fang Yuan. After all, Dragon Palace was the one escaping and moving at the front, if he entered a dangerous place, Dragon Palace would face the brunt of the danger. The pursuer would benefit instead, Spectral Soul would have an easier time.

But Crazed Demon Cave was different. At the lower levels of Crazed Demon Cave, Fang Yuan could use the sovereign immortal body to travel to the next layer quickly, the rest would all be stopped in their tracks.

As for whether Spectral Soul could pass through, Fang Yuan did not know, but it was worth a gamble. Spectral Soul was not in perfect condition after all, he also did not have the sovereign immortal body!

"Even if Spectral Soul can forcefully make his way through, his battle strength would suffer. The lower layers are also extremely huge and mysterious, I can definitely stall for time against Spectral Soul in there."

Fang Yuan made up his mind, he immediately moved Dragon Palace in another direction, towards the north.

As for Wu Shuai, he focused on repairing Dragon Palace.

Spectral Soul saw that Dragon Palace was escaping, he breathed in deeply before rapidly approaching it.

He extended his hand and landed on Dragon Palace. Next, countless immemorial soul beast silhouettes flickered, each time they attacked, a piece of Dragon Palace's walls shattered.

After an entire round of attacks, several pillars holding up Dragon Palace had cracks emerging.

Wu Shuai had a solemn expression: "Oh no, this killer move is extremely powerful, it can attack the Immortal Gu House both internally and externally. The core Immortal Gu of Dragon Palace are quite damaged!"

Fang Yuan's main body squinted his eyes, Dragon Palace's door was shut but his vision was unobstructed, he could see the situation outside.

Fang Yuan said calmly: "Spectral Soul used this soul path killer move earlier, but it is much stronger now. Evidently, he has modified it during this bit of time!"

This was truly terrifying.

Spectral Soul had great strength, even though he was no longer rank nine, he was definitely at Duke Long's level of battle strength.

Even though he lost most of his attainment levels, it seemed that soul path did not fall by too much.

Even though Spectral Soul had only fought Dragon Palace for a short while, he had already comprehended the weaknesses of Dragon Palace, he could modify his killer moves to show much greater effect.

Furthermore, Spectral Soul had abundant battle experience, far deeper than Fang Yuan, during his era, he was renowned for killing everything in his way in the entire world!

After several more rounds, Dragon Palace could not resist Spectral Soul anymore, Fang Yuan sighed as he sent out another Immortal Gu House.

It was a silver-white ship with a long and thin body, it flew like a flying sword with silver light shining around it, stabbing towards Spectral Soul.

It was Myriad Year Flying Warship.

Spectral Soul moved in a flicker and dodged it easily.

Myriad Year Flying Warship turned around and used a killer move, targeting Spectral Soul.

At once, Dragon Palace tried to escape while Myriad Year Flying Warship helped to defend it. Spectral Soul chased after them with immense demonic might, the winds and clouds were raging around him.

Fang Yuan's main body was disrupted by the heaven path dao marks, but because Immortal Gu Houses were individual structures, they were not restricted by this problem.

As long as the Immortal Gu House had Fang Yuan's will and immortal essence, Myriad Year Flying Warship could still continue to fight.

However, Spectral Soul had formidable strength and all sorts of killer moves, not only were they strong and hard to defend against, they mostly had peculiar effects and easily overwhelmed Fang Yuan's efforts, allowing Spectral Soul to firmly control this situation.

Even with the power of two rank eight Immortal Gu Houses, he was not Spectral Soul's match.

"Most importantly, the Twelve Zodiac battle formation was completely destroyed during the fate war. Otherwise, with the combination of Twelve Zodiac battle formation and Myriad Year Flying Warship, even Spectral Soul would have some problems against them."

Fang Yuan considered the situation and did not change his plan, he still focused on escaping.

After getting the heaven path research results, Fang Yuan just needed time to gather his advantage. As long as he survives this problem, after he resolved the problem of the heaven path dao marks, it would be Fang Yuan's turn to shine.

Spectral Soul was going all-out on offense. In his opinion, this was the best opportunity to kill Fang Yuan and reclaim the sovereign immortal body. Not just the sovereign immortal body, he could also get the dream realms that Fang Yuan obtained. Spectral Soul would be able to regain all of his attainment levels as a result.

In this world, what could allow Spectral Soul to rapidly regain his strength? Undoubtedly, it was Fang Yuan! Fang Yuan was simply a moving treasure chest in Spectral Soul's eyes.

"Spectral Soul, die! I want you to die!!" Qing Chou approached him with wind and lightning surrounding it.

Myriad Year Flying Warship and Dragon Palace fought against Spectral Soul while moving, they could not travel quickly. Thus, Qing Chou caught up to them.

Qing Chou's eyes were blood red, its face was distorted in a terrifying manner, it only cared about Spectral Soul!

In just this period of time, the rank nine aura of the hatred Gu within it got denser again, it was quite shocking to see.

Qing Chou got stronger again!

It growled, a human-faced lightning ball flew out of its throat.

The lightning ball was extremely fast, green-black in color, it was eerie and icy, moving without a sound.

Spectral Soul waved his hand, a giant whip made of black fog appeared, seeking to send the lightning ball flying.

But the face on the lightning ball snickered as it raised its speed, avoiding the whip as it approached Spectral Soul.

Spectral Soul was about to use another killer move when the lightning ball self-detonated.

Rumble!

The might of the explosion was terrifying, Spectral Soul was sent flying far away.

The range of the explosion was wide, even Dragon Palace and Myriad Year Flying Warship were not spared, they both suffered some damage.

Qing Chou endured the aftermath of the explosion as it approached Spectral Soul relentlessly.

"This senseless beast!" After being disrupted for multiple times, Spectral Soul felt deeply enraged.

Fang Yuan used the chance to flee.

Spectral Soul saw Dragon Palace's movement and became even more angry: "Little scoundrel, don't think of escaping!"

Dragon Palace's speed fell instantly.

At the areas where Dragon Palace was damaged, black smoke appeared and lowered its speed severely.

"What killer move is this? When did Spectral Soul use it?" Fang Yuan was shocked, at once, he had an idea of moving into Myriad Year Flying Warship instead.

But regrettably, black smoke also appeared on Myriad Year Flying Warship, it moved slowly too.

The black smoke faded away very quickly but Spectral Soul also regained his momentum, after forcing Qing Chou away, he approached Dragon Palace again.

At once, the three parties engaged in a chaotic battle.

Fang Yuan wanted to shrug off Spectral Soul but Qing Chou was overwhelmed with rage, it did not have any intention to cooperate with him.

Qing Chou only wanted to take revenge on Spectral Soul, it did not care about Fang Yuan, almost all of its moves also implicated Dragon Palace. At times, to protect himself, Fang Yuan had to fight Qing Chou as well.

After some time, Spectral Soul regained the upper hand again.

Even though he was just the soul of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, his battle strength was extremely high, he also fought differently from Duke Long's dominance, he was more skilled at using ruthless attacks with piercing killing intent, he was vicious and maniacal.

But he had a terrifyingly clear understanding of the situation, he often made use of his opponent's methods to make them cancel out each other's moves.

Spectral Soul slowly attacked less and less, but in this chaotic fight, his advantage was rising bit by bit.

After noticing this, even Fang Yuan's heart was turning cold.

Chapter 2033: Chaotic Battle

"In terms of battle experience, I cannot compare to Spectral Soul!" During the three way chaotic battle, Fang Yuan sensed the difference between him and his enemy. Even though he had been reborn many times, in terms of total battle experience, Fang Yuan could not compare to a venerable.

"The main problem is that Qing Chou is not being logical, even though it attacks ferociously, it ignores its own condition, Spectral Soul made use of it many times. If this were a conscious Qing Chou, the battle would not be like this."

Fang Yuan felt the situation was unfortunate in his heart. Even though hatred Gu was progressing towards rank nine and Qing Chou was getting stronger, without any wisdom, no matter how strong it was, it was still toyed around by Spectral Soul.

Even after using Dragon Palace and Myriad Year Flying Warship, Fang Yuan still felt helpless. This was something that had never happened before.

Fang Yuan was still focusing on retreating, he fought while escaping.

Even though he was the weaker side now, as long as Spectral Soul could not activate a battlefield killer move to trap him, Fang Yuan was still free to escape.

Dragon Palace was the first to break through the heavenly wind qi wall, heading towards Central Continent. Myriad Year Flying Warship did its best to protect it.

Spectral Soul moved behind like a trail of black smoke, following after them closely.

Behind them were Qing Chou's colossal body, crashing through the qi wall and leaving immemorial white heaven, reaching Central Continent.

Qi Sea Ancestor, Qin Ding Ling, and the rest had all left Heavenly Court, they were chasing behind.

When they found that Fang Yuan and the rest had entered Central Continent, Heavenly Court's immortals became anxious.

"This scoundrel Fang Yuan could've traveled through the vast immemorial white heaven but he chose to go to Central Continent. Since he is in trouble, he wants to implicate the innocent people as well, he truly deserves a pitiful death!"

Qi Sea Ancestor snorted coldly: "Fang Yuan has been a problem for too long, if we can kill him this time, it would be the fortune of the people in the world."

As he said that, he used a secret method to tell the main body about their movement.

Fang Yuan immediately understood that Heavenly Court's pursuers were arriving soon. But he had no solution, his speed was greatly dragged down by Spectral Soul.

When Heavenly Court's group arrived, they found that Spectral Soul was suppressing Fang Yuan and Qing Chou.

Qin Ding Ling frowned as she hesitated, telling Qi Sea Ancestor: "Ancestor, please deal with Fang Yuan, kill him with your full strength."

But how could Qi Sea Ancestor attack the main body, he pondered and said: "In this situation, Fang Yuan is weak while Spectral Soul is strong. They are both demonic path overlords, if we deal with Fang Yuan and get hit by his final trump cards, Spectral Soul will be the eventual winner."

Qin Ding Ling shook her head: "Ancestor, you are not familiar with Fang Yuan, he is too crafty, he definitely has methods left unused. Maybe this situation is only a layer of his concealment, we need to kill him now, we cannot give him any opportunities."

Qi Sea Ancestor: "..."

Heavenly Court had suffered too much at Fang Yuan's hands, Qin Ding Ling's wariness and fear towards Fang Yuan surpassed even Spectral Soul!

But thinking about it, when Spectral Soul Demon Venerable was invincible in the world, he did not deal so much damage to Heavenly Court compared to the current Fang Yuan. It was quite easy to understand how Qin Ding Ling and the others felt like this.

Qi Sea Ancestor could only ask the main body secretly, what were they going to do?

If there was no choice, Qi Sea Ancestor would have to expose himself and fight Spectral Soul so that the main body could escape.

Fang Yuan replied: "Don't worry, let me try something first."

Dragon Palace's door opened, a Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body flew out.

Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique flew towards Spectral Soul, the latter's pupils shrank as he retreated immediately.

Bam.

The Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body self-detonated, turning into a large lump of dream realm that floated in the sky, turning into a barrier.

Dragon Palace and Myriad Year Flying Warship used this chance to pull some distance away from them.

Spectral Soul got around the dream realm as he chased again.

But Qing Chou could not think properly, it got trapped in the dream realm.

Roar—!

The aura of hatred Gu burst out of Qing Chou's body as it broke free from the dream realm, it chased after them again.

"This is?!"

"Qing Chou actually broke away from the dream realm, it was not trapped?"

"It's hatred Gu! \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> has a vague description about it — hatred has no dreams!"

Fang Yuan was also quite shocked about this.

Qing Chou did not have any dream path methods but it used hatred Gu to break free. Dream path was ahead of the current era, it was unstoppable, but it could not stop Qing Chou's hatred Gu?

"Hatred has no dreams... or rather, against rank nine hatred Gu, the dream realm was not big enough?" Fang Yuan had a thought.

It was like the killer move dreamy light smoke, if it landed on Spectral Soul, it would only trap him for some time before he got free, Dragon Palace would shatter from the internal impact.

Dreamy light smoke was too weak against Spectral Soul, but if it rose to rank nine level, the situation would be different.

Even so, when Spectral Soul was attacked with dreamy light smoke, he would still dodge it without hesitation.

He was very fast, moving like a specter, in close distance, it was almost the same as teleportation, it was too hard for dreamy light smoke to hit him.

However, the good thing for Fang Yuan was that Spectral Soul could not deal with dream realms currently.

"I obtained the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique method from Shadow Sect, Spectral Soul definitely knows about it. However, he lacks the crucial Immortal Gu, he cannot use relevant killer moves."

After sensing this, Fang Yuan immediately created many Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies and self-detonated them.

Bang bang bang bang.

In the blink of an eye, Dragon Palace and Myriad Year Flying Warship were surrounded by dream realms, there was no gap between them.

Spectral Soul snorted coldly, stopping his attacks.

"This Fang Yuan..." Qin Ding Ling gritted her teeth, Fang Yuan's method was too shameless, Heavenly Court had no way to deal with it.

"Be careful of Spectral Soul!" Qi Sea Ancestor reminded them.

Fang Yuan suddenly enclosed himself, Heavenly Court's members were in an awkward spot.

Spectral Soul looked at them coldly, Qi Sea Ancestor stood in front of them steadfastly.

Qing Chou growled angrily, it attacked Spectral Soul again without fear.

Spectral Soul said in displeasure: "Lowly beast! Since you want to die, I will grant you your wish."

His body vanished on the spot, at the next moment, he appeared on Qing Chou's back. But right when Spectral Soul was about to attack Qing Chou, a qi path killer move shot towards him.

Spectral Soul had no choice but to resist it, Qing Chou used the chance to move away, it spat out a human-faced lightning ball again, escaping danger.

Spectral Soul looked at Qi Sea Ancestor with a cold gaze. Earlier, Qi Sea Ancestor was the one who attacked him.

Qi Sea Ancestor looked at Spectral Soul warily, at the same time, he explained to Qin Ding Ling: "We cannot let Spectral Soul succeed. He seems to be able to absorb the power of the immemorial soul beast, is it possible for Heavenly Court to capture Qing Chou again?"

Qin Ding Ling sighed: "We have already lost the best opportunity. Qing Chou's strength rose greatly, we need to find another opportunity in order to forcefully refine hatred Gu."

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals did not blame Qi Sea Ancestor for making a move on his own, after all, what he did was very logical. From the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals' perspective, Fang Yuan was trapped in the dream realm now, Qi Sea Ancestor was helping Qing Chou to attack Spectral Soul for the sake of Heavenly Court.

At the next moment, Spectral Soul attacked the Heavenly Court immortals.

Qing Chou followed closely behind him.

The three sided chaotic battle started again, but this time, Heavenly Court took the role of Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was temporarily safe, he only had to take note of the moving dream realms. To form a tight defense, he needed to self-detonate Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies to fix any gaps in his defensive line.

Immortal killer move — Yin-yang Great Killer Hands!

Rumble!

With a loud explosion, two huge hands, one black and one white, appeared out of nowhere.

The two hands were so large they could loom over heaven and earth, they had an intrinsic pattern, at this moment, they grabbed at Spectral Soul.

Spectral Soul suddenly shouted shrilly, when he appeared again, he was already right in front of Qi Sea Ancestor. At the center of the yin-yang hands where Spectral Soul was originally at, there was an immemorial soul beast.

Spectral Soul shot out a wave of black smoke that landed on Qi Sea Ancestor.

Immortal killer move — Heavenly Combat Cloak!

Qi Sea Ancestor retreated, heavenly combat cloak melted from the effect of the black smoke, but this strange move was blocked after all.

Even though Qi Sea Ancestor was a newly created clone of Fang Yuan's, he had incredible strength from originally being Heavenly Court's qi harvest fruit. With sufficient qi path Immortal Gu, his battle strength was not any lower than before.

Even so, Qi Sea Ancestor was suppressed by Spectral Soul, the situation was getting increasingly passive.

Qin Ding Ling led the Heavenly Court immortals to help Qi Sea Ancestor, she also ordered Spirit Affinity House to send Feng Jin Huang over to the fight.

Feng Jin Huang had dream path Immortal Gu, she could use pure dream reality seeker transformation to break Fang Yuan's defensive line.

Qin Ding Ling's target had always been Fang Yuan!

Fang Yuan's main body hid inside Dragon Palace as he watched the battle, using all of his time to refine as many heaven path dao marks as possible.

"Master, we have arrived!" During the chaotic battle, Fairy Zi Wei and Old Man Zheng Yuan led their group as they entered the battlefield.

Before Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals could react to it, far away, someone flew over as well.

"Let this old man join in the fun as well."

It was Demon Immortal Qi Jue!

Chapter 2034: Everyone Wants to Kill Fang Yuan

In this three sided chaotic battle, the appearance of Fairy Zi Wei's group and Demon Immortal Qi Jue made the situation increasingly complex.

"Go and block Heavenly Court." Spectral Soul ordered.

Fairy Zi Wei and Old Man Zheng Yuan quickly attacked with killer moves, the shining wave of attacks assaulted Qin Ding Ling and the rest with ferocity.

Other than Qi Sea Ancestor, Qin Ding Ling and the rest were all inside their Immortal Gu Houses, they were not afraid of Spectral Soul's reinforcements.

Heavenly Court's immortals were only furious, they were not angry about Fairy Zi Wei and Old Man Zheng Yuan's betrayal but the fact that he used a vicious method to enslave them.

Heavenly Court believed in Fairy Zi Wei's and Old Man Zheng Yuan's loyalty. They knew that it was because of Spectral Soul that they betrayed Heavenly Court.

Spectral Soul snickered: "How does it feel to fight against your former allies? It will be up to you to save them, if you miss this opportunity, you will likely never have another chance in the future."

Heavenly Court's immortals heard this, their attacks halted for a moment.

Qin Ding Ling had sharp brows, she frowned as she ordered: "Spectral Soul wants to make us unwilling to attack, he is stalling for time. Forget about Zi Wei's and Zheng Yuan's lives, killing them is the same as releasing them from this predicament!"

At the crucial moment, Qin Ding Ling displayed the foresight of a leader, she showed her resolute nature.

Spectral Soul heard this, he frowned lightly.

He started to act more quickly, attacking Qing Chou again.

Fighting against him, Qing Chou soon got suppressed.

"Stop him!" Seeing that Spectral Soul was trying the same thing again to extract Qing Chou's strength, Qin Ding Ling shouted: "Ancestor, please stop him!"

Even without her reminder, Qi Sea Ancestor had already flown towards Spectral Soul.

But at the next moment, a gush of qi currents flew out like a heavenly river, obstructing Qi Sea Ancestor.

Qi Sea Ancestor stopped his movement, he looked at the attacker: "Qi Jue!"

Demon Immortal Qi Jue smiled lightly, blocking his path: "Qi Sea, our previous battle was interrupted by Heavenly Court, that was not satisfying. Let us fight fairly this time."

The hearts of Heavenly Court's immortals sank.

At the crucial moment, Demon Immortal Qi Jue actually came to help Spectral Soul!

What sort of agreement did they make?

Fairy Zi Wei was surprised too, Demon Immortal Qi Jue was definitely an unexpectedly strong reinforcement!

Purple light flickered in her eyes as she realized: "Long ago, Demon Immortal Qi Jue had already started buying all sorts of inheritances in treasure yellow heaven of various paths. He is from the Olden Antiquity Era, he revived after the destruction of fate Gu. Using these inheritances, he can catch up to the current great era!"

"The reason why Qi Jue is helping us is likely because master made a deal with him, he sold a large number of inheritances."

Fairy Zi Wei made an accurate guess.

Even though Demon Immortal Qi Jue did not expose his identity in treasure yellow heaven, he did not conceal himself either, his intentions were clearly known to everyone.

Since Heavenly Court could notice Demon Immortal Qi Jue's actions, why wouldn't Spectral Soul?

Because of historical reasons, Demon Immortal Qi Jue would not cooperate with Heavenly Court. But Spectral Soul was also in the demonic path, he had a vast number of inheritances, he was the most ideal person to transact with Qi Jue.

"Fang Yuan, you cannot escape today." Spectral Soul smiled coldly, he arrived at Qing Chou's back again.

At the next moment, he attacked!

Qing Chou growled angrily but its strength was being absorbed by Spectral Soul. As an immemorial soul beast, even with the quasi-rank nine hatred Gu, Qing Chou was completely countered by Spectral Soul.

Qing Chou's aura fell greatly while Spectral Soul became more energized and lively.

After he finished his absorption, he kicked, Qing Chou fell towards the ground.

Next, he charged towards Fang Yuan at lightning speed.

Immortal killer move — Pure Dream Reality Seeker Transformation!

The dream realms surrounding Dragon Palace had a huge chunk missing, they turned into Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies as they flew into Spectral Soul's immortal aperture.

Spectral Soul actually had enough Immortal Gu to unleash the killer move, pure dream reality seeker transformation!

He had purposely let Fang Yuan go earlier without using this move, now that he got rid of Qing Chou, he let his reinforcements block Heavenly Court and Qi Sea Ancestor while he finally went after Fang Yuan!

All the immortals were shaken.

The battle had been in Spectral Soul's grasp since the start.

In history, Spectral Soul was renowned for his killing intent, but that did not mean that he could only kill to solve his problems. He was aloof, crafty, and vicious, but when he was alive, he had no need to use any of these methods, his own strength was sufficient to kill all problems.

But now that Spectral Soul's strength was not much higher than his enemies, he started to use various methods to complement his battle strength.

At once, a large number of dream realms were reclaimed by Spectral Soul.

Fairy Zi Wei and the rest fought against Heavenly Court while Qi Sea Ancestor battled Demon Immortal Qi Jue, facing a disadvantage.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue had the secluded domain of heaven and earth, 'Xi', he resisted Qi Sea Ancestor, who cultivated qi path.

The situation was critical, Fang Yuan could not use the dream realms to stop his enemies anymore.

The door of Dragon Palace suddenly opened, several Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies flew out of his dream realm defensive line, directly heading for Spectral Soul.

Boom boom boom.

The Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies self-detonated, creating dream realms in the air.

Spectral Soul quickly dodged them, he managed to avoid being trapped by the dream realms.

But using this chance, Wu Shuai moved Dragon Palace out of the dream realm circle through one of the gaps, with Myriad Year Flying Warship following behind closely.

The intent of the two Immortal Gu Houses was obvious.

"Where are you trying to go?!" Spectral Soul shouted as he got past the dream realms, approaching them again.

Fang Yuan was his main target, he needed to be killed.

This was a prime opportunity, Spectral Soul was going to follow Fang Yuan no matter where he went.

Spectral Soul stared at Dragon Palace and Myriad Year Flying Warship, his eyes flickering with killing intent and determination!

At the next moment, Dragon Palace and Myriad Year Flying Warship split up, they escaped in two directions.

Spectral Soul was dazed.

What should he do?

When Myriad Year Flying Warship and Dragon Palace were inside the ring of dream realms, they were isolated from the outside, Spectral Soul had no idea which one Fang Yuan was hiding in.

There was only one Spectral Soul, he could not chase after both Immortal Gu Houses.

But Spectral Soul made his decision almost instantly, he shouted: "Demon Immortal Qi Jue, chase after Myriad Year Flying Warship! After we succeed, I will not stint on your reward."

Demon Immortal Qi Jue chuckled as he used Xi Land to absorb one of Qi Sea Ancestor's killer moves, he easily moved away and chased after Myriad Year Flying Warship.

Spectral Soul went after Dragon Palace instead.

After receiving his orders, Fairy Zi Wei started to retreat.

"What do we do?" Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals asked Qin Ding Ling.

Qin Ding Ling looked at Fairy Zi Wei and the rest, saying without hesitation: "Kill Fang Yuan first!"

But the problem that Spectral Soul faced earlier was also happening to Heavenly Court, which Immortal Gu House was Fang Yuan in?

"Do we just pick one and gamble on our luck?" Qin Ding Ling frowned, even though she was not willing to do that, Heavenly Court lacked wisdom path Gu Immortals, they could only do this.

"I can help you people." Fairy Zi Wei suddenly stopped her movement as she said: "I have a way to deduce Fang Yuan's location."

Heavenly Court's immortals were dazed.

"What method? How long will it take?" Qi Sea Ancestor asked.

"With our help, it will only take a moment." Bing Sai Chuan's voice resounded, everyone turned around, seeing that Calamity Luck Altar had arrived.

"They finally arrived." Fairy Zi Wei let out a breath of air.

She was obviously the one who asked the Longevity Heaven members to come. Earlier, Fairy Zi Wei and the rest received orders from Spectral Soul to deceive Longevity Heaven and assault Heavenly Court on their own. But the situation changed too quickly, on the way here, Fairy Zi Wei analyzed the situation and made the plan to use Longevity Heaven's strength.

After getting Spectral Soul's permission, Fairy Zi Wei contacted Longevity Heaven immediately.

As Calamity Luck Altar approached, Bing Sai Chuan said: "Our lord said that this world does not need too many chess players."

The immortals' hearts shook.

Bing Sai Chuan's lord was obviously Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

All the signs showed that this venerable had deep aspirations, he still had abundant will and strength left in the world.

In the current situation, Fang Yuan was the most likely person to become venerable. Immortal zombie Giant Sun did not want this to happen, thus, he changed his plan and decided to kill Fang Yuan before he could grow fully!

Qin Ding Ling gritted her teeth, she was stuck at a difficult contemplation.

Cooperate with Spectral Soul and Longevity Heaven?

The former was a demonic path venerable, the latter was a strong foe during the fate war, they were all responsible for the destruction of fate!

Ally with them?

Qin Ding Ling only thought about it for a few breaths of time before she squeezed out a word: "Alright."

Like what Bing Sai Chuan said earlier, there was no need for too many chess players in the world. Fang Yuan was destined to be their enemy, he was a walking treasure chest, everyone wanted to kill him first, after that, Heavenly Court would deal with Spectral Soul and Giant Sun!

Chapter 2035: Qing Clan's Revenge

Rough winds howled in the desert, while the oasis carried a warm breeze.

Sandstones piled into a mountain as hot steam rose. There was a calm lake beneath the sandstones, green trees were growing as their leaves rustled under the evening wind, creating the scene of a paradise in Western Desert.

Western Desert's Qing clan's base was situated at this oasis that was called the 'Qing oasis'.

Qing clan's Gu Immortals were all gathered in a hall. On the icy cold floor of the hall, there were several fragments of Gu worms, all of the Qing clan Gu Immortals were fixing their gazes on these fragments.

"Qing Heng's life tablet Gu shattered?!"

"What is happening?"

"Qing Heng died, he had left to hunt the Southern Border Gu Immortal Ming You. Did he really die at Ming You's hands?"

Qing Heng was a rank seven expert of Qing clan, even though he was sent by the clan to kill Ming You, the clan was very confident in him. Recently for some reason, news that Qing clan obtained Divine Bean Palace had spread, all the other super forces were probing them. With Qing Heng's death, Qing clan became suspicious about the truth, was this a test by the Western Desert forces?

"Report—! We have accurate information, Ming You was the one who killed Qing Heng, he has great strength and acts ruthlessly."

Qing clan flew into a rage.

"This Gu Immortal from another region has gone too far!"

"We need to kill this Ming You, we will grind his bones to dust, we will show the other Western Desert super forces the consequences of offending our Qing clan!"

"Before killing him, we should capture this Ming You and invite the other Western Desert Gu Immortals to watch. Only by pulling out his tendons and ripping his skin in public, to humiliate and torture him to death, can I feel satisfied from this revenge."

"Kill!"

"Kill him!"

"He is merely a Gu Immortal from another region, he came to Western Desert alone, he actually dared to kill our Gu Immortal, he truly has no fear of heaven and earth."

"Even though Ming You was able to kill Qing Heng, he only has rank seven cultivation level, if first supreme elder takes action, it would be too excessive, rumors would also spread that our Qing clan is bullying the weak. In my opinion, we should send out Qing Jing and Qing Hua Lan."

"No, to play safe, we should send Qing Chen as well. With three immortals, they will definitely be able to capture that Ming You alive!"

"Let him experience regret and pain."

"Hurry! Don't let that scoundrel escape."

"Kill Ming You, display the might of Qing clan!"

"Ming You must die, when our clan refines Divine Bean Palace in the future, our Qing clan will stand at the top of Western Desert's Gu Immortal world!!"

...

These sentences echoed in Qing Chou's ears, the scenes of the past flashed in Qing Chou's mind.

Different from its usual fragmented memories, this time, its memory was very clear and complete. At the same time, the hatred in its heart surged in a tsunami, rampaging in Qing Chou's entire body and mind.

Hatred!

Deep hatred!

Feeling increasingly intense hatred, Qing Chou opened its eyes.

Time flew by quickly, countless years had passed since then.

Qing Chou's eyes were bloodshot.

It found that it was still lying on the ground, recalling that when fighting Spectral Soul earlier, it was sent flying to the ground, crashing and falling unconscious.

"Roar!"

Qing Chou roared as it stood up within the deep pit.

The rank nine aura of hatred Gu became even denser, the power of hatred surged throughout Qing Chou's body.

"Ming You, Ming You!"

"Spectral Soul, Spectral Soul!"

Qing Chou roared towards the sky, its eyes were covered in rage, its hair was disheveled, even though Spectral Soul had already gone after Dragon Palace, the power of hatred Gu allowed Qing Chou to locate Spectral Soul easily without a problem.

Rumble!

Qing Chou had a mountain-like tortoise shell, tiger claws and dragon tail, as well as a snake neck and human head, it flew up rapidly as winds surrounded it, charging towards the direction of Spectral Soul. As for Fairy Zi Wei and the rest who were creating a formation in the sky, it ignored them.

Among these Gu Immortals in the sky, there was one elderly Gu Immortal, he had wide sleeves and fluttering white hair, he was Fang Yuan's clone, Qi Sea Ancestor.

Seeing that Qing Chou was flying away, Qi Sea Ancestor let out a breath of air, no longer worried.

Earlier in Western Desert, even though Fang Yuan used familiar face to transform, he was still chased by Qing Chou.

Qing Chou possessed hatred Gu, because of the influence of karma divine tree, it had an intense connection to Spectral Soul and everyone related to him.

Fang Yuan's main body could not deceive Qing Chou while Qi Sea Ancestor was Fang Yuan's clone, he would definitely be sensed by Qing Chou as well.

But now, Spectral Soul and Fang Yuan were enemies, they wanted each other to die, thus, because of their changed relationship, Qing Chou no longer went after him.

"Even though Qing Chou's threat is gone, Fairy Zi Wei is still a big problem." Qi Sea Ancestor cast his gaze at Fairy Zi Wei.

Fairy Zi Wei wore a purple-gold dress, she had a graceful figure with hair that extended to her waist. She moved mysteriously as she flew in the sky, her fingers fluttering like butterflies in the sky, countless Gu worms were sent out and used together, in the sky, an amazing wisdom path immortal formation was already taking shape, one could see its form already.

Old Man Zheng Yuan assisted at the side.

Qin Ding Ling, Che Wei, and the other Heavenly Court Gu Immortals looked at Fairy Zi Wei, they had complex emotions, there was hatred, anger, pity, and sadness.

There was a round altar that was almost in contact with the wisdom path formation, floating in the sky. It had white jade railings and shining aurora, this was rank eight Immortal Gu House Calamity Luck Altar.

Calamity Luck Altar was controlled by Bing Sai Chuan, he had a sharp gaze as he looked at Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals and Qi Sea Ancestor, not daring to relax his mind.

Calamity Luck Altar protected Fairy Zi Wei and the rest, as well as the wisdom path formation.

Longevity Heaven, who represented Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, had already cooperated with Spectral Soul's Shadow Sect long ago.

"Fang Yuan has the potential to become a venerable, we cannot let him do as he pleases. If such a person becomes a venerable, it will not benefit any of us." Bing Sai Chuan transmitted, he tried to convince Qi Sea Ancestor, Qin Ding Ling, and the rest, not knowing that Fang Yuan's clone was right here.

Qin Ding Ling only listened to him, she did not reply.

The winds howled around her, causing her cape to flutter, she wore a tight golden armor and was tall and grand, she had a valiant demeanor.

She stared at the wisdom path formation at times, looking at the dream realms occasionally.

This dream realm was left behind by Fang Yuan. He had originally tried to use the dream realms to stop his enemies, but Spectral Soul plotted against him instead. Fang Yuan had to escape from this battlefield, this dream realm was left behind, shining and moving on its own continuously.

"Where is Fang Yuan now? I only saw that Dragon Palace and Myriad Year Flying Warship flew out of the dream realm and escaped the battlefield. There is a third possibility, he is still hiding in this dream realm!" Qin Ding Ling thought to herself.

Precisely because of this reason, she stayed behind to guard this dream realm.

Fang Yuan was too crafty, even though staying in the dream realm seemed stupid, there was a chance that Fang Yuan might do this purposely.

Seeing that the wisdom path formation was completing, Qi Sea Ancestor felt increasing pressure.

"I can't wait anymore!" Thoughts collided in Qi Sea Ancestor's mind, he thought: "Looking at Fairy Zi Wei's attitude, with Bai Ning Bing and Ying Wu Xie at the lead, this formation might likely deduce the main body's location. The main body does not have much foundation in information path, otherwise, if we could break our connection with Bai Ning Bing and Hei Lou Lan, even three of Fairy Zi Wei combined would not be able to do anything."

"Fairy Zi Wei and the rest have great strength, with Calamity Luck Altar's defense and Bing Sai Chuan's wariness towards Heavenly Court, if I attack now, I will not be able to destroy the formation, Heavenly Court would instead get suspicious of me."

The Qi Sea clone was powerful, but he could not turn this situation around alone and suppress everyone, the key person now was still Qin Ding Ling!

Qi Sea Ancestor listened to Bing Sai Chuan's words while asking Qin Ding Ling in secret: "Looking at this situation, Shadow Sect and Longevity Heaven think highly of this formation. But can we trust them? Regardless of whether Fairy Zi Wei can deduce a result successfully, the formation is still under her control. If she tells us a location, how do we ensure that it is right? Will Fairy Zi Wei hide anything from us?"

The Qi Sea clone started to sow discord, he could not let Bing Sai Chuan ally with the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals too. Otherwise, the main body would face the pressure of Shadow Sect, Longevity Heaven, and Heavenly Court, it would be too much!

If this was the Heavenly Court from Fang Yuan's previous life, they would definitely have no inclination to work with other forces.

But fate Gu was destroyed by Fang Yuan, Heavenly Court lost their greatest spiritual banner, they also suffered many setbacks and lost a lot of reputation. One could say that their title of the number one human force was already undeserved, they faced a lot of criticism.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were all elites, they learned from this lesson and started to change. Qin Ding Ling was the leader of Heavenly Court, she started to gather help and put down her pride, earlier, when Qin Ding Ling took the initiative to help Qi Sea Ancestor chase away Demon Immortal Qi Jue, it was the best proof of this.

Thus, the probability that Heavenly Court, Shadow Sect, and Longevity Heaven would work together was not low.

The Qi Sea clone's words were very effective, Heavenly Court and Fairy Zi Wei could not trust each other. This way, even if Fairy Zi Wei's deduction succeeded, it would not have any meaning.

Qin Ding Ling was silent for a while before transmitting to Qi Sea Ancestor: "I would like ancestor to go and chase after Dragon Palace and Spectral Soul."

Qi Sea Ancestor was slightly dazed: "Do you know the location of Fang Yuan already?"

"I don't." Qin Ding Ling smiled at Qi Sea Ancestor.

The Qi Sea clone looked at Qin Ding Ling deeply in the eye, he realized that Qin Ding Ling knew what she was doing, she had never trusted Shadow Sect's Fairy Zi Wei or Longevity Heaven, trusting them was stupid. The reason she stayed behind was to guard the dream realm and also rest and recover.

Heavenly Court lacked a peak rank eight battle strength, after leaving Heavenly Court, they also lost their territorial advantage. They seemed powerful and had great morale but if they were careless, they would suffer huge losses.

Heavenly Court could not afford to lose anymore!

Qin Ding Ling had to be vigilant and careful.

Right now, Spectral Soul was chasing Dragon Palace, Qing Chou was chasing Spectral Soul, while Demon Immortal Qi Jue was chasing Myriad Year Flying Warship.

Qin Ding Ling knew that Demon Immortal Qi Jue, who had Xi Land, was Qi Sea Ancestor's greatest counter, even if Fang Yuan was inside Myriad Year Flying Warship, Qi Sea Ancestor would not be able to do anything to Demon Immortal Qi Jue even if he went there.

Instead, if Qi Sea Ancestor chased after Spectral Soul, he would be able to influence the situation.

From Heavenly Court's perspective, Fang Yuan was someone who needed to die, Shadow Sect or Longevity Heaven were enemies as well. But Heavenly Court's strength was not like before, they were very weak, even though Qi Sea Ancestor was on their side, he was still not their member after all.

Qin Ding Ling sighed deeply: "Fang Yuan is too crafty, even though him splitting up seemed simple, it allowed the pressure on him to decrease greatly, we have no choice but to stay behind and temporarily stop chasing him."

"Spectral Soul is stronger than Demon Immortal Qi Jue, if he kills Fang Yuan and gets everything, this former Demon Venerable will rise up again!"

"Qi Sea Ancestor, we hope you can think for the sake of everyone in the world, let these two demons fight it out while our righteous path remains victorious in the end."

Qin Ding Ling was a talented leader after all! Even though she was leading a weaker Heavenly Court, she had never given up, she made plans to try and raise their chances of victory as much as possible.

Chapter 2036: Strong, Weak

"Go." Fairy Zi Wei called out as her fingers moved rapidly, producing countless shadows. The killer move activated, a thousand Gu worms flew out and turned into a vague purple shadow that filled up the final blank area of the wisdom path formation.

The Gu Immortals watched were all first rate Gu Immortals in the entire five regions, seeing this, they could not help but admit that Fairy Zi Wei was very skilled at setting up formations.

Fairy Zi Wei let out a breath of air, perspiration gathering on her forehead.

Her eyes stared at the formation before her, at this point, it was time to add in the core Immortal Gu.

This situation was quite peculiar, Fairy Zi Wei was setting up the formation in front of many strong foes. There was a chance that these Gu Immortals might attack her during the process, thus, Fairy Zi Wei used a rare method for this arrangement, she first placed the mortal Gu and set up a bare framework first, before filling it up with Immortal Gu at the end.

Fairy Zi Wei temporarily stopped her actions to catch a breather, she looked at Qin Ding Ling and Calamity Luck Altar.

Calamity Luck Altar was shining in brilliant light, the Gu Immortal controlling the Immortal Gu House, Bing Sai Chuan, knew about her worries, he transmitted: "With my protection, you can rest assured, quickly set up the formation."

Fairy Zi Wei did not have Fang Yuan's formation flag Gu, otherwise, she would not need to set up this formation each time.

She knew that time was running out, after hearing Bing Sai Chuan's words, she started to put Immortal Gu into the formation.

Each time an Immortal Gu was placed, the formation would shake once and shine in a beautiful purple light, the scene was incredibly beautiful, it was a pity that none of the Gu Immortals had the mood to appreciate it.

Inside Calamity Luck Altar, Bing Sai Chuan stared at the formation, guarding against any potential threats that would attack, he broke the silence as he said: "Hei Lou Lan, you have been with Fang Yuan for a long time, what do you think he would do in this situation?"

Hei Lou Lan was standing right beside Bing Sai Chuan, even though she was a woman, her face had strong contours, she possessed sharp and long brows, bright eyes and a heroic aura.

Hei Lou Lan heard the question, she thought about it and said: "Fang Yuan only has three options, Dragon Palace, Myriad Year Flying Warship, or to stay in the dream realm.

"Hiding in the dream realm is too risky for Fang Yuan. Not only can Spectral Soul take the dream realm away, Heavenly Court also has ways to deal with the dream realm. If I were Fang Yuan, I would not stay here and wait for death."

"Of course..." Hei Lou Lan smiled helplessly: "This is not guaranteed to be the case, thus, Heavenly Court chose to stay by the dream realm. Fairy Zi Wei has also stayed behind to make deductions using the formation, she is also observing the dream realm. She is a wisdom path great expert, she knows that she cannot interfere with the two Immortal Gu Houses, she is most needed here."

"Myriad Year Flying Warship is faster than Dragon Palace, this can deceive the enemy, but I do not think that Fang Yuan would hide inside it. This is because Myriad Year Flying Warship is still slower than Spectral Soul, but its defense is lower than Dragon Palace. If Spectral Soul chooses to chase Myriad Year Flying Warship and attack it, Myriad Year Flying Warship would not last as long as Dragon Palace."

Hei Lou Lan smiled coldly: "During the fate war, Fang Yuan lost his Twelve Zodiac battle formation, if it were still around, he would likely escape in Myriad Year Flying Warship. Thus, I think that Fang Yuan is most likely hiding inside Dragon Palace!"

Hei Lou Lan had an eerie gaze: "Spectral Soul likely thinks the same too, that is why he chased Dragon Palace while asking Demon Immortal Qi Jue to go after Myriad Year Flying Warship, he made precautions for both situations. Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal body originated from Spectral Soul, he also has all of Spectral Soul's dream realms. If Spectral Soul can kill him and reclaim the sovereign immortal body and the dream realms, he will rise up once again!"

"Even though we want to kill Fang Yuan, we cannot let Spectral Soul succeed. Even though Shadow Sect is working with us now, they have ill intentions. After all, Fairy Zi Wei managed to deduce the fact Fang Yuan was in Heavenly Court but they kept it from us, allowing Spectral Soul to attack Heavenly Court alone. Only when they needed our reinforcement did they call for us."

"Thus, in my opinion, we should just watch from the side and exert influence on the situation. If possible, it will be best if we can take down Spectral Soul, Fang Yuan, and Heavenly Court in one move!"

"Hahaha." Bing Sai Chuan laughed loudly, praising: "Good analysis! Quite impressive. Northern Plains' Hei tribe was too disappointing, but you live up to Giant Sun's bloodline. I'll tell you the truth, after I woke up, I received information about you. After observing you for some time, I can say that you are a genius! It was just that your life was quite tough, you were schemed against by your father and suppressed by Fang Yuan, you merely lacked an opportunity to develop, otherwise, you would not be in this state."

Hei Lou Lan heard the praise, her gaze focused on Bing Sai Chuan's face.

Bing Sai Chuan had a tall body, his face was gentle but there was an ugly scar extending from his right ear to his left cheek. He originally had a cold expression but now, he looked at Hei Lou Lan with admiration and satisfaction.

Hei Lou Lan's heart jumped, an intense feeling appeared in her heart. Bing Sai Chuan's appreciation towards her ability was probably the most valuable fortuitous encounter in her life!

After realizing that, Hei Lou Lan did not hesitate anymore, she stood straight and cupped her fists: "I will listen to lord's orders!"

Bing Sai Chuan laughed loudly, before stopping as he looked at Hei Lou Lan with a solemn and serious gaze: "Good, Hei Lou Lan, are you willing to rebuild Northern Plains' Hei tribe?"

Northern Plains' Hei tribe had been taken down long ago, it was now occupied by Heavenly Lord Bai Zu to develop his tribe. Hei tribe's Gu Immortals even became members of Bai Zu tribe, they were simply the disgrace of the Huang Jin bloodline.

Hei Lou Lan expressed her willingness to do so no matter what.

"But I am currently too weak..." Hei Lou Lan purposely showed a hesitant expression filled with difficulty.

Bing Sai Chuan waved his hand as he tossed her a Gu worm.

Hei Lou Lan quickly received it, she saw that this rank seven Immortal Gu looked like a black and gold beetle, it was very heavy, Hei Lou Lan did not recognize it at once.

Bing Sai Chuan explained: "Hei Lou Lan, you have the Great Strength True Martial Physique, you should cultivate solely strength path, your future will be very bright. You have our Huang Jin bloodline, you are a Northern Plainsman from birth, I am sure you will not disappoint me, we will not stint on your strength path resources from now on. Take this strong Gu first, even though it is rule path, it suits you very well."

"Strong Gu?!" Hei Lou Lan's body shook.

"Alright, Fairy Zi Wei's formation is ready, go inside first." Bing Sai Chuan instructed.

Hei Lou Lan left Calamity Luck Altar and went into the formation.

She had a plain expression but her heart was filled with deep emotions and turbulence. Strong Gu was recorded in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, it had a close connection to the Great Strength True Martial Physique. Bing Sai Chuan gave this legendary Immortal Gu to Hei Lou Lan, it showed how much he wanted to nurture her.

Hei Lou Lan realized in her heart: "It seems that my life is going to undergo a huge change now!"

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, chapter five, section thirty-one states —

Ren Zu lost freedom Gu, he was anguished and only recovered after a long time.

Ren Zu was troubled, he asked cognition Gu: "Oh cognition Gu, how can I obtain freedom Gu again? After what happened last time, freedom Gu will not approach me anymore."

Cognition Gu answered: "Oh human, why do you desire freedom Gu so much?"

Ren Zu replied irritably: "Don't you know the reason already? I am searching for freedom in order to break free of the restraints of fate."

Cognition Gu answered once again: "Then I have nothing much to tell you. Haven't you told fate Gu the answer to this question already?"

Ren Zu was dazed before he recalled.

Before he went insane, he met fate Gu. When he was harmed by fate Gu, he shouted at it that he would use his own strength and wisdom to obtain freedom, he would eventually break free from fate's control!

Ren Zu's eyes brightened: "Oh Gu, I remember now, thank you for the reminder. I need to rely on myself to break free of fate. I already have my own strength, what I lack is my own wisdom. I need to let self Gu eat a mouthful of wisdom Gu, just like how it ate a part of strength Gu in the past."

"But where is wisdom Gu?" Ren Zu asked cognition Gu.

Cognition Gu: "I do not know. Wisdom Gu has been to many places, its location is not fixed. You can find wisdom in countless places, so human, you need to find it yourself."

Ren Zu nodded as he set off on his journey again.

He walked and walked and walked, one day, he saw two Gu worms chasing each other along the road.

One Gu worm was white and tiny, it escaped ahead as it begged for mercy: "Stop chasing me, stop chasing me, I do not want to be eaten by you."

The other Gu was clearly larger in size, it had thick armor and said in a deep tone: "I want to eat you, I want to eat you! No matter where you escape to, I will eat you!"

The tiny white Gu was about to be caught by the larger Gu behind, it suddenly saw Ren Zu and hid behind him: "Oh human, I beg of you, quickly save me."

Ren Zu saw that this Gu worm was so pitiful, it was chased by another Gu worm, unable to fend for itself, he felt like he was seeing himself.

At this instance, a new heart grew in his chest — the heart of sympathy.

Ren Zu stretched out both arms as he stopped the larger Gu: "Stop, stop chasing it."

The armored Gu shouted: "Hey human, are you obstructing me? No, you cannot stop me, you are unable to stop me."

"Why is that so?" Ren Zu was curious.

The armored Gu explained: "I am strong Gu, that is weak Gu. Since time immemorial, the rule of nature is that the strong prey on the weak. Thus, strong must eat weak, weaklings are the food of the strong."

Ren Zu sighed as he tried to convince the Gu: "Then why don't you let it off just this once, look at how pitiful it is."

Strong Gu sneered: "Not even once! In the eyes of the strong, weaklings have no stature, there is no sympathy for the weak. This is because heaven and earth will never pity the weak, it will only marvel at the incredible feats of the strong. Weaklings are born to be subdued, controlled, and devoured by the strong."

Ren Zu saw that his words fell on deaf ears, he could only deny strong Gu forcefully: "I have already saved this Gu, go and eat others."

Strong Gu knew that it could not beat Ren Zu alone, it could only fly away in dissatisfaction: "I will be back."

Chapter 2037: Myriad Destruction Lightning Forest

Bai Ning Bing, Ying Wu Xie, and the rest went into the formation one by one, finally, Fairy Zi Wei also went to the center of the formation, activating it.

The deduction was beginning.

Qi Sea Ancestor did not move, he stayed at the original spot.

"If I take action now to destroy the formation, will it help my main body?" Qi Sea Ancestor analyzed, he estimated his chances.

Once the formation was damaged or even destroyed, the Gu Immortals inside would suffer backlash, but Qi Sea Ancestor could not be certain of the exact effect.

Furthermore, if Qi Sea Ancestor struck now, the secret that he was Fang Yuan's clone would be exposed for sure.

"If only I could convince Qin Ding Ling and the rest to strike together." Qi Sea Ancestor sighed internally.

Even though Qin Ding Ling was not a wisdom path great expert, she was not so easy to deceive. Qi Sea Ancestor did not even dare to say anything odd now, otherwise, Heavenly Court might find out the truth instead.

"Ancestor, time is pressing, you need to consider the big picture!" Qin Ding Ling was secretly sending transmissions to him, trying to convince Qi Sea Ancestor. She wanted him to chase after Dragon Palace and Spectral Soul, but Qi Sea Ancestor started to talk about payment instead.

Qi Sea Ancestor sighed: "Fairy Qin, precisely because of the big picture, I am being shameless in asking you for the three qi Immortal Gu. My methods are all known by the enemies, only with these Immortal Gu can I gain a boost in strength and catch the enemies by surprise. For the sake of the people, for the righteousness of humanity, I hope you will consider the big picture and give those three Immortal Gu to me."

Qin Ding Ling mentally rolled her eyes, this Qi Sea Ancestor was not just shameless, he was incomparably so, using this opportunity to ask for huge compensation. He wanted three rank eight Immortal Gu at once, the cores of Primordial Origin's true inheritance! He was simply too greedy.

But Qin Ding Ling had many worries now, if she fell out with Qi Sea Ancestor, Heavenly Court would not have any peak rank eight battle strength, they would likely be targeted by Shadow Sect and Longevity Heaven.

Qi Sea clone purposely chose this current situation to exert pressure on Qin Ding Ling.

Qin Ding Ling sighed: "Qi Sea Ancestor, why must you force us now? Back then, in Eastern Sea, who helped you to resist Demon Immortal Qi Jue?"

Qi Sea Ancestor replied: "If we want to talk about favors, I am sure you all owe me more. I have already gotten rid of Heavenly Court's biggest threat, the qi harvest fruit is gone now. Also, in this battle, I have never slacked off, I took risks alongside all of you."

Qin Ding Ling was silent for a while before she replied solemnly: "I can give heaven qi and earth qi Immortal Gu to you, but human qi Immortal Gu is out of the question. This is the bottom line of Heavenly Court, please understand our circumstances, ancestor."

Qi Sea Ancestor accepted the result.

The truth was, the Qi Sea clone did not think he would get all three qi Immortal Gu to begin with. They were all rank eight Immortal Gu connected to Primordial Origin true inheritance, they were too valuable, far beyond the value of the supposed payment. Heavenly Court could have used other resources to pay him, but because the situation was really urgent now, the Qi Sea clone fought for the greatest benefit.

Of course, the fact that Qin Ding Ling gave the two qi path rank eight Immortal Gu to Qi Sea Ancestor on the spot caused all of the Gu Immortals to gasp in amazement.

Qi Sea Ancestor obtained two Immortal Gu, he said his goodbyes to the Heavenly Court immortals as he chased after Dragon Palace immediately.

"I finally got him to work." Qin Ding Ling felt very tired, but this outcome was not too bad. She would not give all three qi Immortal Gu to Qi Sea Ancestor, she had to keep at least one to use as bait against him.

Furthermore, Qi Sea Ancestor obtained two qi Immortal Gu, he only needed human qi Immortal Gu to be able to use the killer move triple qi retraction, this temptation was probably even greater now that he had two of them.

Dragon Palace flew rapidly in the wild winds.

In the dream realm earlier, Wu Shuai got sufficient time to put all his effort into repairing Dragon Palace, at least from the outside, it looked restored.

"The damage to the core Immortal Gu cannot be resolved quickly, this is already my limit!" Wu Shuai was very worried.

Behind Dragon Palace, a female rank eight soul path immortal was chasing it relentlessly.

It was Spectral Soul who was inside Lady Cold Ash's body. He emanated black qi as he surged with killing intent, he locked onto Dragon Palace without any signs of hesitation or giving up.

"You cannot escape, Fang Yuan! Even if you escape to the ends of the world, I will definitely kill you." Spectral Soul had just said that when his pupils expanded.

Wherever Spectral Soul's gaze landed, smoke that was pitch black appeared, quickly reaching Dragon Palace.

The smoke expanded rapidly, with a soft sound, it turned into a round spiral that had an immense suction force.

Wu Shuai was controlling Dragon Palace, he was caught by surprise as Dragon Palace's speed fell, it fell towards the black smoke spiral.

"What move is this?!" Wu Shuai gritted his teeth, veins bulged on his forehead as he tried to move Dragon Palace to the sky.

Ever since they fought, Spectral Soul's soul path methods had been endless, it was hard to guard against them. Especially when Spectral Soul was such an expert with abundant experiences, he could use these soul path killer moves beyond their usual limits.

Dragon Palace turned around with difficulty, attempting to fly away from the black smoke spiral from above.

Spectral Soul sneered, he pointed his finger. Black light quickly gathered on his finger, it shot out, instantly hitting the area around Dragon Palace.

The tiny black light expanded rapidly, turning into an immemorial soul beast.

Seeing that the immemorial soul beast was about to pounce on Dragon Palace, Wu Shuai was shocked, his pupils expanded rapidly.

If Dragon Palace got hit, its movement would be obstructed, it would fall into the black spiral along with the immemorial soul beast. In that case, the precious time that Fang Yuan obtained through this tactic would be completely wasted.

At the crucial moment, Wu Shuai shouted, his eyes shined with mysterious dazzling light.

Dragon Palace reacted to it, golden light erupted, a wave of pink smoke rapidly gathered, easily dragging the immemorial soul beast away, into the depths of Dragon Palace. The powerful immemorial soul beast could not resist it at all!

Spectral Soul was not surprised.

This was the dream path killer move — Dreamy Light Smoke.

Wu Shuai got rid of the immemorial soul beast, Dragon Palace managed to fly far above the spiral.

At this time, Spectral Soul's body suddenly appeared near Dragon Palace, his eyes shined with cold light: "I have been waiting for this!"

At the same time, 'Spectral Soul', who was far away, faded into nothingness.

Spectral Soul slammed with his palm, the silhouette of a soul mountain appeared and pressed down on Dragon Palace.

This soul mountain was huge, the top was beyond the clouds, looking from below, Wu Shuai's entire vision was obstructed.

It covered the entire sky!

But the soul mountain's appearance was very familiar to Wu Shuai.

"Isn't this Dang Hun Mountain?" Wu Shuai was shocked and uncertain.

Bam!

With a loud sound, Dang Hun Mountain crashed down on Dragon Palace.

Dragon Palace's beautiful roof met with a devastating blow. Countless tiles shattered, many Gu worms died at once.

And even worse was that due to the impact, even though Dragon Palace struggled, it was slammed into the black smoke spiral by the giant soul mountain.

The spiral surrounded the entirety of Dragon Palace, an immeasurable suction force started acting on it.

Dragon Palace spun around along with the spiral, losing its sense of direction. Wu Shuai had to leave his throne as he tried to think of a way to break out of this situation, but it was hopeless in the short term.

"Don't tell me this is Spectral Soul's truth strength?" Wu Shuai gritted his teeth.

Spectral Soul unleashed several killer moves in succession, Wu Shuai was very tired in trying to deal with them. The great rank eight Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace could not put up a resistance, with Spectral Soul's array of killer moves, he managed to suppress Dragon Palace forcefully.

Wu Shuai stared with furious eyes, he had to try and delay for time, he instilled immortal essence to try and fix the Immortal Gu House, wanting to maintain his defensive position.

"In this situation, the main body's safety is in my hands! But how long can I last?" Wu Shuai was completely unsure at this point.

Fang Yuan's main body was deep inside Dragon Palace.

The heaven path dao marks prevented him from doing anything now. The unlimited qi sea killer move he used earlier against the primordial qi wall was also prepared for a long time, he used human path methods to find a gap in the restriction of the heaven path dao marks, allowing him to make one move.

But with just that action, after breaking the qi wall, the heaven path dao marks reacted and started to obstruct Fang Yuan in another way.

Thankfully, Fang Yuan did not get greedy and quickly stopped using his killer move. Otherwise, the strong interference would cause his killer move to fail, he would suffer intense backlash.

Fang Yuan only found that human path could resist heaven path. Dream path might be effective but his attainment in dream path was not high enough.

Ever since he obtained Heavenly Court's heaven path research results, Fang Yuan had been researching on them.

He was fighting against time!

It was possible that a minute's or even a second's difference would lead to either surviving or dying.

Immortal killer move — Heaven-human Sensation!

Immortal killer move — Human Executing Heaven's Work!

Within the sovereign immortal aperture, Fang Yuan's will mixed with heaven's will, he sensed various heaven path dao marks.

Refine them!

Immortal killer move — Unrestrained Heavenly Mark!

This killer move was meant to deal with heaven path dao marks, Fang Yuan did not care about the cost, he expended rank eight immortal essence rapidly, he quickly refined three heaven path dao marks successfully.

"Wu Shuai, persevere, I have already made a huge breakthrough!" The moment Fang Yuan transmitted to Wu Shuai, a change occurred in the immortal aperture.

Fang Yuan's success infuriated heaven's will.

The heaven path dao marks were like angry beasts, they were originally scattered all over the place, but now they gathered together.

Rumble!

Thunder rumbled as lightning roared, dark clouds formed as wild winds blew.

The heaven path dao marks triggered a huge change, in just a few breaths of time, a tribulation was formed!

At that instant, earth shook as mountains rumbled, lightning flashed and shattered rocks, the earth was crying out in sorrow.

Fang Yuan's heart jumped: "Don't tell me that forcefully refining heaven path dao marks will anger the Heavenly Dao and cause a tribulation to occur? Or maybe the killer move I used has a problem?"

Lightning clouds continued to form and spread out. Soon, they spread over a hundred li, several thousand li, tens of thousands of li, and over a hundred thousand li!

Millions of lightning bolts flickered continuously, this was like a huge forest made of lightning bolts!

Myriad tribulation — Myriad Destruction Lightning Forest!

It was not an earthly calamity, a heavenly tribulation, or a grand tribulation, it was actually a myriad tribulation.

Only a rank eight Gu Immortal could face such a tribulation.

It was a myriad tribulation, they put fear into most rank eight Gu Immortals!

Chapter 2038: Internal and External Problems

Fang Yuan immediately frowned, as if a huge rock was weighing on his mind, his expression turned grim.

He did not think that a myriad tribulation would occur.

Rank eight Gu Immortals stood at the peak of the Gu Immortal world, but for each one of them, every myriad tribulation was a troublesome hurdle.

In the current Gu Immortal world, most rank eight Gu Immortals have not gone through one myriad tribulation. For example, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu and Yao Huang were like this, even Prince Feng Xian was the same.

Back then, why did Old Ancestor Xue Hu try all means possible to refine fortune rivalling heaven Gu? It was to deal with his first ever myriad tribulation in this life! It was a pity that he created a huge commotion and ended up with a huge loss, not only did Old Ancestor Xue Hu fail to refine fortune rivalling heaven Gu, he even lost the whole of Snowy Mountain blessed land.

Western Desert's Thousand Transformations Ancestor had gone through one myriad tribulation. He survived it by a hairsbreadth, he was forced to recuperate for a long time. During the period, his beloved Fairy Cui Bo was killed by Fang Yuan, yet he could only send Dancer Hong Yun to investigate it.

Beast Calamity Immortal died after suffering heavy injuries from his first myriad tribulation, leaving behind Beast Calamity grotto-heaven.

Bo Qing was a rank eight Gu Immortal who had passed two myriad tribulations, Duke Long was too. Throughout history, both of them were top tier experts merely below venerable level.

Even though Fang Yuan possessed over a million dao marks after becoming a rank eight Gu Immortal, the truth was that he used the sovereign immortal aperture's specialty to annex grotto-heavens, he skipped all his myriad tribulations.

Thus, Fang Yuan had not gone through a single myriad tribulation.

In his case, myriad tribulations were still huge problems. And the biggest issue now was that this current situation was really inappropriate to undergo tribulation. Fang Yuan could not estimate how long Wu Shuai could last, after all, Spectral Soul was a terrifying foe that they could not assess!

"I need to refine these heaven path dao marks as soon as possible, only after that can I face Spectral Soul!"

"But to refine heaven path dao marks, I need to undergo myriad tribulation?"

Fang Yuan felt like there was a tsunami now, he went up the mountain to avoid the flood but found out that this was actually a volcano! And now, this volcano was about to erupt.

Externally was Spectral Soul, internally was the myriad tribulation, at this moment, Fang Yuan fell into the greatest predicament of his life so far.

"No, I still have a chance!" Even in this situation, Fang Yuan remained calm, he was not flustered.

At the same time, at another area.

Myriad Year Flying Warship and Demon Immortal Qi Jue were escaping and chasing respectively.

Suddenly, 'Fang Yuan' flew out of Myriad Year Flying Warship, using his killer move with ferocity as he forced back Demon Immortal Qi Jue temporarily.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue immediately used his investigative method, after confirming this, he transmitted to Spectral Soul: "Fang Yuan is here with me, I can't deal with him alone. Come quickly! Otherwise, he might escape."

Spectral Soul heard the news and got stunned for a moment.

"Is Fang Yuan really not in Dragon Palace?" Spectral Soul thought rapidly, his attacks also slowed down as a result.

Right now, even though Dragon Palace was trapped, it was still a rank eight Immortal Gu House, it could last for a while.

Fang Yuan was rushing against time, Spectral Soul was the same. If he wasted time with Dragon Palace, even if he destroyed it, Fang Yuan would escape, then this entire pursuit would fail because he could not meet his goal.

Victory in battle was never important, only the benefits behind it mattered. Combat was just one of the ways to gain benefits, the glory of victory was completely irrelevant to Spectral Soul.

"Fang Yuan has familiar face, he can create a will and give it immortal essence and Immortal Gu to create a false impression of being the main body." Spectral Soul knew about this information, thus he was quite troubled now.

Even though he was strong, far beyond other Gu Immortals, he could be called the number one in the world, but Fang Yuan was crafty and hard to catch, this situation was quite vexing.

Spectral Soul knew he had to be vigilant, otherwise, he would follow in Heavenly Court's footsteps. This Fang Yuan was just too good at escaping!

The sovereign immortal aperture was facing countless lightning bolts, ever since the myriad tribulation formed, it had been attacking non-stop.

Mini Southern Border suffered severe damage!

The Heavenly Dao sought to balance deficit and surplus, which area in the sovereign immortal aperture was the most developed? It was undoubtedly Mini Southern Border. Thus, the Heavenly Dao created this myriad tribulation that targeted Mini Southern Border.

"Myriad tribulation — Myriad Destruction Lightning Forest!" Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, doing his best to make arrangements. He ignored Spectral Soul who was outside now, he let Wu Shuai try to stall for time.

Rumble…

Cloud Bamboo Mountain was completely broken apart into countless pieces by the lightning bolts.

There were eight desolate beast cloud foxes living on the mountain, and eleven desolate plant spear tip bamboos, they were completely wiped from existence by the lightning bolts. Cloud qi roots, white hair ginseng and a vast number of ordinary spear tip bamboos were all destroyed too.

The seven colored cloud soil inside the mountain were also affected, they were scattered all over the place, after the damage from the lightning, their value fell drastically.

Cloud Bamboo Mountain was originally taken from Southern Border's Chi clan by Fang Yuan, it had the weakest defensive formation, thus at this moment, it was completely decimated beyond recognition.

Soon, the other resource points started to face problems too.

"I need to solve this internal threat as soon as possible!" Fang Yuan thought to himself, but the power of the myriad destruction lightning forest was terrifying, he could not do anything about it, each of his actions were still restricted by the heaven path dao marks.

Thankfully, there was a bunch of Gu Immortals in the sovereign immortal aperture.

Among them, Xue Er, Shi Shi Cheng, and Mo Tan Sang were nurtured by Fang Yuan to become the new leaders of their variant human tribes. Their cultivation level was too weak, asking them to help out was simply sending them to death's doors.

"I will help!" At the moment of crisis, an elderly Gu Immortal stepped up, emanating rank eight aura.

Since when did Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture gain such a powerful expert?

This elderly man was none other than the sole rank eight in Beast Calamity grotto-heaven, the current generation Combat Beast King.

Ever since Fang Yuan's plan succeeded and he annexed Beast Calamity grotto-heaven, all of the Gu Immortals inside were turned into his subordinates. After that, Fang Yuan gave them the true method of Gu cultivation.

During the fate war, most of the rank seven Gu Immortals were sent out to fight, until now, Fang Yuan did not have any time to recall them, they were still wandering around in the five regions.

Combat Beast King was a different case, because he had been cultivating inside Star Collection City, his strength rose greatly.

This was Fang Yuan's backup plan during the fate war to guard against people trying to invade his immortal aperture.

During the fate war, this situation did not occur, and now that the sovereign immortal aperture had a myriad tribulation, with Fang Yuan unable to make a move, he could only send out the Combat Beast King.

Winds blew, starlight shot out.

The rank eight star sea snail corpse was taken out by Fang Yuan, handed to Combat Beast King. The Combat Beast King did not hesitate, he immediately used his killer move and turned into a giant covered in starlight armor.

The giant roared as his body flew up towards the sky of lightning clouds.

Crack!

When the giant reached half the distance, several lightning bolts combined into one, the pillar-like bolt shot down on the star armored giant.

If this were in the past, Combat Beast King would definitely die from getting hit by this. But after this period of cultivation, he had already learned how to use immortal killer moves.

Thus, the defensive killer move was used by Combat Beast King before he moved, it managed to resist the lightning bolts.

But the giant's advancement was also halted at this moment.

The giant landed back on the ground, its majestic body shivering as sparks remained on its body, Combat Beast King's limbs were going numb, his movements were greatly affected.

"Myriad tribulations are truly terrifying!" Combat Beast King was tongue-tied, he spoke with deep shock.

Fang Yuan frowned tightly.

Earlier, the lightning bolts combined to target Combat Beast King, that was the work of heaven's will. The heaven path dao marks were too densely gathered now, heaven's will was naturally being produced.

With the manipulation of heaven's will, the terrifying myriad tribulation became even more adaptive, it led to despair.

"I have the killer move heaven's will dissipation, I can even get rid of heaven's will in dream realms. Unfortunately, I cannot use it now!" Fang Yuan sighed to himself, he needed to refine the heaven path dao marks, he had to mingle with heaven's will and use both heaven-human sensation and human executing heaven's work to capture the location of the heaven path dao marks. After that, he would use unrestrained heavenly mark to refine the relevant heaven path dao marks.

Thus, heaven's will was necessary.

Once Fang Yuan gets rid of the heaven's will, he would also not be able to refine these heaven path dao marks.

"But the heaven path dao marks gathered and created a myriad tribulation, this greatly affected my refinement of the heaven path dao marks, my efficiency is less than one percent of before!"

Originally, the heaven path dao marks were scattered all over the sovereign immortal aperture, they were like divided troops, Fang Yuan could refine them group by group, the refinement was very effective. But now that the heaven path dao marks gathered into one tight group, Fang Yuan would have huge problems in trying to target them, his refinement also started to have no progress.

With this speed of refining the heaven path dao marks, how long would it take?

Fang Yuan's circumstances were really precarious!

"Oh no, I can't hold on anymore!" When it rains, it pours, at this moment, Wu Shuai shouted loudly as he requested for Fang Yuan's help.

This dragonman clone was also in a bind now.

Veins were bulging on his forehead, he was sweating profusely, Dragon Palace was trapped in the black smoke spiral, it was taking huge damage at all times. With cracking tiles and pillars, the whole of Dragon Palace was visibly shrinking.

Wu Shuai could only do his best to repair it, but his speed could not match Spectral Soul's destruction.

Seeing that a crucial area was about to be destroyed, Wu Shuai had no choice but to ask for help.

Fang Yuan knew that his clone would not ask unless he was desperate. He sighed to himself as he switched his attention to the outside world.

After inspecting the situation, Fang Yuan immediately took action to help Wu Shuai with the repair of the Gu House.

They managed to alleviate the situation, but it was not enough!

Suddenly, Wu Shuai gasped: "Why are Spectral Soul's attacks getting slower?"

Fang Yuan realized at once, he said: "I created a fake main body over in Myriad Year Flying Warship, it seems to have worked. Spectral Soul is hesitating now, he has always been worried that I would escape. He has no idea that Dragon Palace is about to collapse, he thinks the rank eight Immortal Gu House can still last for some time. If my 'main body' in Myriad Year Flying Warship escapes during this period, even if he manages to take down Dragon Palace and kill you, his plan will fail regardless."

Wu Shuai's eyes shined: "It will be great if we can deceive him now!"

Chapter 2039: Sorrowful Wind Mountain Range, Wang Xiao Er

"It'll be difficult." Fang Yuan sighed deeply.

Almost the same time as he said that, Spectral Soul, who was outside, attacked even quicker than before!

Spectral Soul shouted coldly: "Fang Yuan, you are truly a disappointment. How long are you going to hide? I'll tell you the truth, Fairy Zi Wei has already deduced your location earlier."

"Entrusting your hope to deceit, this is the way of the weak. I gave you sovereign immortal fetus Gu, it was truly a waste!"

"Come out and fight me, in this case, even if you die, people of the world will not say that you were cowardly, being afraid of the strong while bullying the weak."

"Damn it!" Wu Shuai's hope was dashed, he could not help but grit his teeth.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly, frowning and not answering. From his perspective, what was the point of reputation? What he cared about was whether Fairy Zi Wei really succeeded in her deduction, was Spectral Soul trying to deceive him now, was it all an act just to bait out Fang Yuan?

The Qi Sea clone had already left, so Fang Yuan did not know about the situation over there.

"Even now, the wisdom path formation is still working, we cannot forget another possibility, that is Fairy Zi Wei trying to delay Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven's action by telling Spectral Soul about the result secretly in advance. Sigh, I can't care about it now." Fang Yuan sighed as he quickly tossed away this question.

It was not that he found out the truth, but Dragon Palace's current condition was too dangerous, he had no choice but to take action.

Fang Yuan opened the door of his immortal aperture slightly, letting out the immemorial year beasts that he had prepared!

Several immemorial year beasts roared as they charged out of Dragon Palace, attempting to destroy the black smoke spiral, while a few of them charged towards Spectral Soul.

"Your efforts are futile." Spectral Soul made his move, black smoke spread out from his body and whipped up a dark storm, shrouding the surrounding over an immense range.

He pointed repeatedly with his finger, each attack only carried a trace of smoke but it was incredibly fast, the power was overwhelming. When the black smoke hit the immemorial year beasts, it immediately expanded into countless dense smoke chains that binded the immemorial year beasts.

The immemorial year beasts struggled but the black smoke chains were boosted by the black smoke spiral, they became thicker and tighter. The immemorial year beasts could struggle at first but soon they became unable to move, they were swept away by the spiral without resistance.

"These are just petty tricks, you are truly a disappointment, Fang Yuan." Spectral Soul flew up into the sky as he looked down at the black smoke spiral.

The great rank eight Immortal Gu House Dragon Palace was like a toy, once its details were exposed, it was completely toyed around with like a harmless object.

Wu Shuai gritted his teeth, activating the killer move dreamy light smoke.

Spectral Soul chuckled, spitting out several soul balls. The tadpole-like soul balls had tails, they moved rapidly in the air, quickly entering the immemorial year beasts.

Thin black qi appeared around the immemorial year beasts' bodies, the black smoke chains fused into the black qi and caused it to become much thicker.

The three immemorial year beasts regained freedom, they growled angrily as they attacked Dragon Palace!

One of the immemorial year beasts directly jumped into the range of dreamy light smoke.

Their control was actually taken over by Spectral Soul.

Dreamy light smoke swept away one immemorial year beast, Wu Shuai felt powerless. With Spectral Soul controlling the situation now, he had ample time and initiative, dreamy light smoke could no longer pose a threat, it was just a small problem.

The soul path killer moves that Spectral Soul was using now were all unheard of by Fang Yuan and Wu Shuai, they had never seen any moves like these.

The foundation of a rank nine venerable was truly unfathomable!

High in the sky, the wisdom path formation continued to operate.

Fairy Zi Wei stayed at the central control area, she showed an appearance of working her hardest to make deductions.

Longevity Heaven's and Heavenly Court's immortals surrounded the wisdom path formation.

Qin Ding Ling silently looked at the wisdom path formation, just earlier, Heavenly Court transmitted news that the few Gu Immortals staying back successfully suppressed Di Zang Sheng.

Di Zang Sheng was hit by Primordial Origin's qi path killer move, its condition was slipping rapidly. When Fang Yuan escaped, he abandoned it to its own demise. Now, it was not strange that Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals suppressed it.

This point alone showed how anxious Fang Yuan was, he even gave up something like Di Zang Sheng, it showed that he was at his weakest point.

And this fact amplified Qin Ding Ling's killing intent towards Fang Yuan.

This was a rare opportunity that could not be lost!

After suppressing the Evil Dragon, the remaining Gu Immortals started to repair Heavenly Court grotto-heaven. They quickly fixed the holes, Heavenly Court's crisis was finally alleviated.

This also allowed Qin Ding Ling to let out a sigh of relief, but she still had other worries.

"Qi Sea Ancestor has just left recently, with Dragon Palace's speed and direction, it should have already reached Intestinal Gorge, right?" Qin Ding Ling thought to herself.

Fang Yuan escaped in Dragon Palace, moving out of immemorial white heaven and into Central Continent. This enraged Heavenly Court and also caused them to be worried that the aftermath of the battle might cause severe losses.

Intestinal Gorge was the northern entrance of Sorrowful Wind Mountain Range, it was created during the Olden Antiquity Era when a beastman expert died and fused with the surrounding mountains. It was under the control of one of Central Continent's ten great ancient sects, Black Heaven Temple.

Qin Ding Ling had already transmitted the details to Black Heaven Temple, asking them to send out their Immortal Gu House and move along Intestinal Gorge. If there was a chance they would strike, if the enemies were too strong, they would abandon Intestinal Gorge and preserve their strength as the main goal.

After receiving Heavenly Court's orders, Black Heaven Temple went into an alert state, they mobilized all of their strength and started to move out.

But after waiting for a long time, they did not see Dragon Palace nor Spectral Soul.

Qin Ding Ling did not know that Spectral Soul had already intercepted Dragon Palace along the way, they were still above the sky of Sorrowful Wind Mountain Range.

Sorrowful Wind Mountain Range was huge, extending over hundreds of thousands of li, compared to other mountain ranges, it was relatively gentle, the resources here were not abundant, most of the mountains were barren. Thus, even though it was in Black Heaven Temple's territory, they did not care much about it.

This place mostly produced wind path resources, in the past, a rank seven Gu Immortal of Wind Cloud Manor came here to cultivate in seclusion, he managed to breakthrough to rank eight, it was Old Man Bei Feng. It was a pity that his life was filled with hardship, he first got captured by Fang Yuan during the fate war and became enslaved by Dragon Palace. In the intense battle earlier, Old Man Bei Feng died already.

He was not the only one, all of the Four Dragon Generals died in this battle. Even the strongest of the enslaved, Di Zang Sheng, was now suppressed by Heavenly Court.

On a certain mountain of Sorrowful Wind Mountain Range.

Several youngsters were herding sheep, they got into an argument.

A youngster was being bullied, he was the weakest and thinnest person here, he took several steps back amidst the argument.

"Wang Xiao Er, this mountain is occupied by us, there is no place for you here."

"Scram now, get lost from our sight."

Several youngsters wore thick leather jackets, they had muscular bodies and vicious expressions.

Wang Xiao Er's clothes were patched up with many tattered areas, he looked like a beggar.

He resisted weakly: "But my sheep need to eat, if I do not feed them sufficiently, uncle and aunt will beat me up when I return."

The youngsters laughed loudly, the strongest one struck and pushed Wang Xiao Er to the ground.

"Go to the other mountain to herd your sheep, there is still some grass there. Scram now! Otherwise, I will break your leg!" The muscular young man threatened viciously.

Wang Xiao Er struggled to get up, he did not resist, he only moved his small group of sheep and left the mountain.

He walked with his thin legs, crossing rivers and steep paths. There was no road on the mountain, Wang Xiao Er often fell down and suffered bruises from the hard rocks on the ground, only the sheep behind him were traveling without any problems.

Wang Xiao Er finally found a small patch of grass, the sheep got tired and thirsty after running around, even without his command, they went forward and competed to eat the food.

Wang Xiao Er was so tired he laid down on the rock and watched the sheep fighting to eat, he sighed to himself: "Recently, the sorrowful winds in the mountains are getting more violent, there is less and less grass available. That is why they chased my sheep away from that grassland."

The patch of grass was tiny, it was completely gobbled up by the sheep after some time. The stronger sheep ate the most food while the remaining sheep growled in hunger.

Wang Xiao Er shook his head, this mountain had little grass, it was scattered all over the place. If he wanted to feed all the sheep, he would need to head to another mountain. It would not only waste time but energy as well.

"Oh sheep, oh sheep, at least you guys have food. In order to feed you all, I will definitely have to return late. I will definitely be beaten up by uncle and aunt, I will have to eat leftover rotten food."

Even though Central Continent was the most developed among the five regions, most of the mortals still lived difficult lives, it was common to starve.

Right at this time, there were suddenly rumbling noises heard.

Wang Xiao Er raised his head, this was a strange situation, why was there thunder rumbling in this bright sky?

After that, he slowly opened his mouth and saw a shooting star falling from the sky.

The shooting star became larger and larger in his vision, winds became stronger, the rumbling sounds were deafening, even the temperature of the air rose.

Wang Xiao Er was completely stunned, he froze on the spot, the surrounding sheep sensed the danger, they started crying out and running around.

Not just the sheep, the wild beasts on the mountains were also scrambling, the originally quiet mountain suddenly became very lively.

As the shooting star got closer, Wang Xiao Er finally got a good glimpse of it.

This shooting star was actually a mountain-sized beast!

The wild beast crashed down with a loud sound, coincidentally, it was the mountain that Wang Xiao Er lived on!

The mountains collapsed as rocks flew, earth shook as the mountain trembled, dust clouds rose up rapidly.

The village on the mountain was instantly destroyed, there were anguished cries of people mixed with the growls of beasts, Wang Xiao Er could hear these sounds spreading through the air currents produced.

Rumble rumble rumble…

As Wang Xiao Er stared with a frightened gaze, terrifying cracks were spreading on the ground, soon, the surroundings of the mountain peak also cracked, they fell apart piece by piece.

The youngsters who chased Wang Xiao Er away earlier all met with a disaster!

"Am I going to die?" Wang Xiao Er sat on the ground helplessly.

He seemed to have lost all of his strength, he could only watch as the dust clouds devoured him like a hungry beast that ate everything in its path.

Inside the dust clouds were countless rock shards carried by the wind.

One of them hit Wang Xiao Er's forehead.

Before he fainted, his final thought was that of confusion, why did a giant beast fall from the sky?

Chapter 2040: Qing Mouth

Above the clouds, in the sky.

Dragon Palace barely managed to create a golden light to shield itself, but it was trapped inside the black smoke spiral, resisting against the ferocious attacks from the outside.

Only three immemorial year beasts that Spectral Soul took control of were left.

The rest were all defeated by Wu Shuai using Dragon Palace. As for their falling corpses and what mountains they destroyed, how many people they killed, nobody in this battle cared, they could not afford to bother with the devastating disaster that a mortal boy like Wang Xiao Er experienced.

The remaining three immemorial year beasts regained their senses after the black smoke dissipated, they fought against Spectral Soul once again.

But Wu Shuai had a heavy mood.

These immemorial year beasts were collected by Fang Yuan in an attempt to restore his Twelve Zodiac battle formation, at this crucial moment, he had to use them for battle.

The result was that due to Spectral Soul's methods, they became used by him instead.

After the fight earlier, the remaining three immemorial year beasts were all injured, they could not be used to break out of this situation. Spectral Soul easily managed to resolve Fang Yuan's method, he dealt with the situation without breaking a sweat.

Not only could Spectral Soul control soul beasts, ordinary enslavement path methods were also useless against him, he could use it against the enemy instead!

Wu Shuai was deeply worried: "At this rate, how long can we last?"

Fang Yuan frowned tightly, his opponent was Spectral Soul now, he was trying hard to maintain his defense, but inside sovereign immortal aperture, the myriad tribulation was rampaging and causing destruction. After this short while, Mini Southern Border lost many resource points, his losses were rapidly increasing.

The bigger problem was that even if Fang Yuan gave up a portion of his immortal aperture, he could not break free from the myriad tribulation. This was because the heaven path dao marks that created the tribulation were very special, they could move around. He had to endure the myriad tribulation forcefully to get past this biggest hurdle.

Spectral Soul's eyes shined with cold light, he did not chase after his enemies and attack Dragon Palace again, instead, he looked away.

In his vision, a black dot appeared.

Soon, this dot expanded as a legendary immemorial beast showed its appearance, it had a tortoise shell, four tiger paws, dragon tail, snake neck, and a human head. Its hair was disheveled and it had a twisted expression filled with insanity.

It was Qing Chou who had caught up!

Spectral Soul did not avoid Qing Chou's pursuit, instead, he started to smile coldly: "Since you are here to court death, that will be the best outcome."

However, when Qing Chou reached Spectral Soul, the corner of its tortoise shell split open as a pair of bat wings formed instantly! This was very similar to the wings of the green claw ghost winged lion.

Immortal killer move — Qing Mouth!

Qing Chou opened its mouth, as it had a human face, its mouth was not big, but right now, its mouth opened to form a huge green-black hole.

The hole expanded rapidly, it shot out and devoured Spectral Soul in one mouthful.

The hole rapidly shrunk as it entered Qing Chou's mouth. Qing Chou swallowed as it gulped, a ball could be seen flowing down its snake neck, into its stomach.

"Good chance!" At this moment, brilliance flashed in Wu Shuai's eyes.

"This move was left behind to deal with you, scumbag!" Qing Chou roared loudly in joy after devouring Spectral Soul, memories surfaced in its mind again...

"What, all three Gu Immortals we sent were killed by Ming You?"

"Impossible!"

"But that is the truth. Ming You first pretended to be weak and got injured on purpose, causing our three immortals to split up to look for him. He ambushed them at a corner and found the opportunity to launch a shameless sneak attack on them. Out of carelessness, all three immortals met with their demise."

Qing clan's hall turned silent.

They wanted to restore their reputation but they ended up suffering even greater losses. A rank seven Gu Immortal was not easy to nurture, especially when they were elite rank seven Gu Immortals of Qing clan.

The losses were really huge for Qing clan, their foundation was definitely shook.

"Ming You deserves death! We were too careless... this lesson is very important, we need to remember it and pass it down to the future generations. I am going to deal with him personally." Qing clan first supreme elder said.

The immortals were silent, nobody expressed their objection.

Sending a rank eight Gu Immortal against the rank seven Ming You was really not something to be proud of. But Qing clan could not afford to lose anymore, all of the super forces in Western Desert were watching them like a joke!

However, when Qing clan's first supreme elder was about to set off, he received a challenge letter.

This letter came from another Western Desert super force which had deep enmity with Qing clan, they requested a battle with Qing clan first supreme elder, wanting to use the result of this battle to decide their territorial boundary.

"Damn it, at this juncture!" Qing clan's Gu Immortals shouted immediately.

"They are doing this on purpose. But the territorial boundary determines the ownership of a resource point, the benefits involved are too much. What do you think?" Qing clan first supreme elder hesitated at this moment.

"I will go and end Ming You's life." Qing clan's second supreme elder stood up.

"You?" The first supreme elder hesitated.

Second supreme elder smiled: "I only have rank seven cultivation level but Ming You is heavily injured, he needs to recuperate. We have already learned of his details, even though his methods are innovative and peculiar, they are mostly soul related. My immemorial desolate beast green claw ghost winged lion is his nemesis. Not just that, I created an immortal move called Qing mouth, I gained inspiration from the green claw ghost winged lion and created it. Once used, it can devour souls. Don't worry everyone, I can definitely take this Southern Border Gu Immortal's life."

"Alright, go ahead. Be careful on this trip." Eventually, first supreme elder nodded and agreed.

"With second supreme elder taking action, we will definitely succeed!"

"Ming You is as good as dead, he is not a threat, our problem now is still this challenge letter."

"Second supreme elder, you must avenge Qing Hua Lan and the rest!"

...

"I finally took revenge for all of you!" As his memories faded away, Qing Chou could not help become choked with tears, hot tears started to flow out of its red eyes.

Revenge was finally taken, it felt relieved and free.

"Such a familiar sight..." Spectral Soul spoke in a casual tone from within Qing Chou's stomach.

Qing Chou's body instantly froze.

Next, it felt bitterness.

Deep bitterness.

Intense bitterness!

An indescribable and unendurable bitterness!

Bitter, it was too bitter.

"Ugh..." Qing Chou's expression turned pale, it gagged as it almost wanted to vomit.

It quickly gritted its teeth, enduring desperately.

The taste of bitterness surged like a huge tsunami, it crashed towards the limits of its endurance.

Qing Chou growled in pain, its entire body was shivering from the bitterness, it could no longer fly as it fell towards the ground.

While descending, it started to feel hungry!

It was as if there was an empty space in its stomach.

No, it was not just hunger, it was a sort of loss. It was as if its entire body was experiencing a loss.

"Now, you should know how Qing clan's second supreme elder died in my hands? Indeed, I purposely got hit by Qing mouth killer move. Do you know why I am so confident? Hehe." Spectral Soul chuckled from inside Qing Chou's stomach.

Long ago, when Spectral Soul was still young, before he went up against Western Desert's Qing clan...

Ming You who was extremely successful in life met with a wild green claw ghost winged lion and suffered a terrible defeat.

"Impossible! The soul path I created actually failed to beat a beast. Even though it is an immemorial desolate beast, my soul path... how can my soul path be so pathetic and weak?!"

Ming You who was tired after a long fight fell to the ground, he stared at the green claw ghost winged lion with a crazed expression of disbelief and indignance.

The green claw ghost winged lion stood on four legs, it looked at Ming You who was on the sandy ground, its entire body was casting the shadow of death down on him.

Next, the green claw ghost winged lion lowered its head as it opened its bloodthirsty mouth.

Plop.

With a soft sound, the green claw ghost winged lion bit off Ming You's leg.

Ah——!

Ming You cried out in pain, after losing his entire right leg, blood poured out of the wound.

The intense pain caused him to curl his body, twisting around on the ground. Soon, the surroundings were dyed red from blood.

After biting off his right leg, the green claw ghost winged lion swallowed it and felt annoyed by the moving Ming You, it stretched out its right claw and pressed him firmly on the ground.

No matter how Ming You struggled, he could not resist the strength of this beast.

The green claw ghost winged lion lowered its head and bit off Ming You's left arm this time, swallowing it.

Ming You cried out in pain again, his eyes turned white as he almost fainted from pain.

The pain was even more severe this time, earlier when his right leg was bitten off by the green claw ghost winged lion, it was a quick action, but this time, his left arm was torn off forcefully. There was still a small chunk of flesh left on his shoulder, the white arm bone could be seen with the naked eye.

Ming You resisted, he used a soul path killer move with his full strength, but all his attack only impacted the green claw ghost winged lion slightly, it did not move back at all.

Because of the attack, the green claw ghost winged lion lost its patience, it opened its mouth for the third time and ate Ming You entirely.

It started to move its teeth and chew.

Ming You's body was pierced and minced, his bones were all shattered. His brain was not spared either, blood matter and brain matter mixed together, along with his minced flesh, they were all swallowed by the green claw ghost winged lion.

Only Ming You's soul was left.

However, the green claw ghost winged lion could not digest human bodies, it only ate souls as food.

Ming You's soul could not escape from the green claw ghost winged lion's stomach, he was rapidly broken down by the gastric acid.

The shadow of death loomed over him.

Ming You's soul shook intensely, he realized that death was approaching him.

"Am I going to die..."

"Dying in the mouth of a mere beast?"

Damn it!

Indignance!

"I am still too weak. I can do much more!"

"I can definitely do more things, I have just created soul path..."

But his soul path methods were countered by the green claw ghost winged lion. This immemorial desolate beast was simply the natural nemesis of Ming You!

"I cannot die here. I will not accept this outcome."

"There must be a way, there has to be a way!"

"My immortal aperture is still inside my flesh body, it is still with me. My Gu worms are around too... but soul path is useless here. I, I still have food path!"

But the food path killer moves he had could not resist the green claw ghost winged lion, otherwise, he would have used them already, he would not end up like this.

"If existing food path killer moves are useless, I will create new food path killer moves!"

This was wishful thinking, but for Ming You, it was his only hope, even though the hope was extremely slim.

Ming You did not think about the unlikeliness of this action, he only focused on thinking, doing his best to create his concept.

Never before was he so concentrated on something!

His soul was still eroding, it became smaller and smaller.

His thoughts were producing at an increasing slower speed.

Soon, even his thoughts could not move anymore.

"I... cannot... give up..."

"I have to think... I got it... \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>..."

"That's right, didn't Ren Zu get eaten as well?"

Chapter 2041: Bitter Taste, Swallow Loss

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, chapter five, section thirty-two.

Ren Zu continued on his journey, after a while, a huge Predicament entered Ren Zu's vision.

Strong Gu was inside this Predicament's body, it laughed: "Oh human, I am back again. This time, I have help, let's see what you can do!"

Ren Zu had to stop walking, even though the Predicament before him was huge, he did not fluster.

Long long ago, Ren Zu had been chased by a group of Predicaments as he escaped, but after he gave his heart to hope Gu, those Predicaments which feared hope escaped in panic.

"Oh hope Gu, I need your help."

Ren Zu summoned hope Gu but the light of hope did not scare away this Predicament.

What was going on?

"Haha!" Strong Gu laughed: "Oh human, this Predicament has gained my help, it will definitely be the greatest Predicament you have ever met in your life. With just hope, how can you possibly defeat it?"

Ren Zu could not think of a way.

At this moment, weak Gu that was shielded by Ren Zu spoke in a soft voice: "Oh human, thank you for protecting me. Don't worry, I have an idea, let's scare this Predicament away!"

"You can scare it away?"

Weak Gu shook its head: "Oh human, even something as weak as me has a method to survive in life. Against those that want to eat or bully me, I will often put up a deceiving disguise, to make others think that I am very strong."

"This world favors the strong. Even if we are weak, we need to disguise ourselves as strong beings or we will be bullied everywhere."

"Oh human, you can do it. Don't you have fear Gu? Isn't attitude Gu on your face?"

Ren Zu heard weak Gu's suggestion and decided to try it.

He first twisted his appearance using attitude Gu, revealing his teeth and showing a fierce expression. Next, he used fear Gu to scare the Predicament as it bore its teeth, sprawling on the ground and staring at Ren Zu vigilantly.

Ren Zu was dazed: "Why didn't we scare it away?"

Weak Gu urged: "Didn't it jump earlier? This means that my method works, but we need to put in more effort. Oh human, why don't you put attitude Gu on top of self Gu? What is the best form of deceit or disguise? It is to deceive even yourself. By doing that, we should be able to deceive the Predicament."

Weak Gu continued: "As long as the Predicament thinks that you are strong, it will definitely let you pass. That is because Predicaments often take the initiative to give way to the strong."

Ren Zu took off the mask on his face as he placed attitude Gu on self Gu.

However, it was pointless.

The Predicament did not run off in fear.

Ren Zu realized at once: "I understand now, when a person faces a huge predicament, putting up a facade will never solve the real problem."

Strong Gu laughed: "Oh human, stop wasting your effort. With me here to remind the Predicament, how can you guys possibly deceive it? You should not have saved weak Gu, weak people often like to jeer and taunt others, showing a ruthless demeanor to conceal their own weakness inside."

Ren Zu was helpless, he could only stall for time temporarily.

Suddenly, he had a flash of inspiration as he said to strong Gu: "You said that the law of survival is for the strong to eat the weak, I agree with that. But how do you prove that you are strong while we are weak? If you cannot prove this, on what basis are you allowed to eat us?"

Strong Gu was dazed: "It is because I am strong Gu and that is weak Gu."

Ren Zu shook his head: "Just your names alone cannot prove anything. Moreover, other than both of you Gu worms, myself and this Predicament are also here."

Strong Gu smiled coldly: "Then I have a good method to prove it! We will eat a portion of each other, whoever fails to persevere to the end will lose, whoever is weak deserves to be eaten."

Ren Zu saw that he could not stall for any more time, he had to take a risk: "Then we will do that. Don't regret it! However, which of us will eat first?"

Strong Gu was confident in its strength, it chuckled: "So what if I let you go first?"

Ren Zu assessed the Predicament with his gaze, the truth was he had never eaten any Predicaments before.

Ren Zu thought about it before he had an idea: "Then I will eat the head of the Predicament first."

Thus, Predicament took off its head and gave it to Ren Zu.

Ren Zu only took a bite when his face became distorted, he almost vomited on the spot: "So bitter!"

It turned out that this was a huge bitter head[1].

Not just that, even though the Predicament lost its head, it was still standing, the neck that was missing a head did not bleed at all, there were no issues at all.

"Haha!" Strong Gu laughed: "Oh human, you chose wrongly, by just eating bitter heads, you cannot resolve any predicaments. Moreover, whether you are capable of eating this huge bitter head is another question altogether! If you cannot eat it, it means that you are a weakling, you deserve to be eaten by us."

Compared to the Predicament's head, Ren Zu's body was very small.

Ren Zu knew that strong Gu was right, he could not afford to lose. If he lost, not only would he fail to protect weak Gu, he would even lose his life and become the food of the Predicament.

Ren Zu could only frown as he opened his mouth, continuing to eat the bitter head.

After taking dozens of mouthfuls, Ren Zu suddenly stopped, he opened his mouth and almost vomited.

Hope Gu encouraged him: "Oh human, don't vomit. If you grit your teeth, you can devour any hardship that comes your way. Humans do not just need to eat food, they also need to taste bitterness."

Ren Zu nodded as he continued to eat.

Halfway through, the fear Gu on his body started to shout: "Oh heaven, when will we ever finish eating it?"

Ren Zu also felt a trace of despair.

Courage Gu quickly said: "Oh human, you cannot be afraid of tasting bitterness. Don't fear bitterness, suffering is only temporary, if you start to fear suffering, you will suffer for life."

With the help of courage Gu, Ren Zu finally managed to eat all of the bitter heads after great hardship.

Ren Zu wiped his mouth as he looked at strong Gu with difficulty: "You can choose now."

Strong Gu smiled: "Then we will eat your skin first."

Ren Zu had to pull off the skin on his body as he threw it to the Predicament.

The Predicament had no head, it stuffed Ren Zu's skin down its neck. Ren Zu's skin was completely eaten but its huge belly did not expand at all.

Strong Gu asked again: "Oh human, what are you going to eat next?"

Ren Zu was troubled now, he had just eaten the Predicament's head, it was too bitter, even though he endured the process, his stomach was almost full now.

As for the Predicament, even though it had no head, it was still alive and standing.

"What should I eat now? I ate too much earlier, my stomach is reaching its limit, if I have to eat a lot, my stomach might burst and I'll die." Ren Zu thought to himself, he had to eat the most important and fatal part of the Predicament's body!

But which part of the Predicament's body was the most important?

After thinking for a long time, Ren Zu finally had an idea, he said to strong Gu: "Then I will eat the part that you absolutely do not want me to eat."

Strong Gu snorted coldly: "Then you can eat some losses[2]."

It took out all of the losses from the Predicament's body and gave it to Ren Zu for consumption.

These losses were not big, the quantity was not large either.

Ren Zu was quite surprised, because after these losses were taken out, the originally huge Predicament shrunk by a lot.

Rules and regulation Gu started to explain for Ren Zu: "Oh human, this is not strange. Predicaments vary according to people, since you ate such a huge bitter head earlier, you will have less losses to eat, thus, it became smaller."

Ren Zu became happy: "This is great. Even if I eat all of these losses, I will not reach my limit, it will not fill my stomach completely."

Ren Zu opened his mouth and ate a small loss.

It was so spicy!

Ren Zu could not even speak at this moment.

Continuing to eat.

Ren Zu opened his mouth as he breathed heavily, his empty eye sockets also started to tear up uncontrollably.

Eating again.

Ren Zu's entire body was covered in sweat that merged with the tears flowing out of his eye sockets.

The most uncomfortable thing for Ren Zu was that budding flames started to appear in his heart. These yellowish flames resembled chicks, they gathered together in groups.

The more losses one ate, the more flames of resentment they would feel in their heart.

The more flames of resentment they had, the more uncomfortable it felt, even Ren Zu's several hearts could not take it, they were going to be incinerated soon!

Right at this moment, the heart of nobleness grew in Ren Zu's chest.

Compared to the other hearts, the heart of nobleness was able to endure the most flames of resentment. With this heart to bear the burden, Ren Zu finally managed to endure it.

Ren Zu ate all of the losses.

Strong Gu looked at Ren Zu's bulging belly as he smiled coldly: "Oh human, you are almost at your limit, it is time for us to eat."

Ren Zu breathed roughly as he asked: "What do you want to eat?"

Strong Gu said: "I want to eat your flesh."

Ren Zu was helpless about it, he could only let it eat his flesh.

Ren Zu's skin and flesh were inside Predicament's stomach, he only had his bones, organs, and hair left.

...

In this deep and eerie darkness, only Ming You's thoughts were flickering with much difficulty, radiating the light of hope near the end of his life.

"I... can do it..."

"Come on... come on..."

Food path killer move — Bitter Taste!

Food path killer move — Swallow Loss!

The green claw ghost winged lion was flying in the air, suddenly, its body shook as it fell towards the ground with a pitiful cry.

With a loud sound, it crashed into the desert, creating a deep pit.

The green claw ghost winged lion struggled intensely, causing the sand on the ground to turn into a huge sand wave.

It could not endure the immense feelings of bitterness, the flames of resentment burned intensely in its heart.

It knew that Ming You was the one causing problems in its stomach, it stabbed its claw into its stomach without hesitation!

After spending a long time struggling, it slowly came to a halt as its life force dissipated.

Using the hole that its claw created, Ming You's soul flew out like a trace of smoke, bringing along his immortal essence and Gu worms, escaping from the stomach of the beast.

"I actually survived." Even he did not think that this would be the outcome!

His soul was dim, after floating and moving for some time, he collapsed onto the ground.

Only after resting for a long time did he recover slightly.

Looking at the dark sky, Spectral Soul who was still a young adult snorted coldly before laughing to himself: "Pathetic, truly pathetic. However, in this world, in this world... who does not struggle at death's doors?"

"I swear!" Spectral Soul's figure was blur and vague, he seemed to be pointing at heaven.

He used an extremely firm and determined, yet incomparably weak voice to shout with all his strength: "This is the last time I will struggle before death in my life! From today onwards, only I can cause others to struggle in the face of death, the five regions and two heavens can bear testament to my words!"

Heaven and earth was silent.

Going back to the present, his memories faded away as the battlefield reappeared.

Qing Chou was rolling around in the air, finally, it could not take it anymore as it vomited out Spectral Soul.

Spectral Soul's body was like a phantom, moving rapidly and reaching Qing Chou's back.

He raised his right arm as his five fingers turned black like ink, it was quite peculiar. His five fingernails were longer than his fingers, they were white and sharp, emitting an icy and terrifying aura.

"Go ahead and struggle to death. Don't worry, I will not let any of you feel even the slightest hope of survival!"

Spectral Soul's eyes shined with a dark light, his five fingers stabbed at lightning speed.

Roar—!

Qing Chou's body shook, all of its strength surged again as Spectral Soul quickly absorbed everything.

[1] The Chinese phrase for suffering/hardship is written as bitter head literally. Back

[2] Eat loss is the literal meaning of the phrase that means suffering a loss, being disadvantaged, or ending up in an unfavorable situation. Back

Chapter 2042: Venerable Spectral Soul

Lightning flashed and thunder roared, causing destruction to sovereign immortal aperture.

Mini Southern Border was ravaged by the myriad destruction lightning forest to a pitiful level, countless mountains collapsed, the earth cracked as deep crevices formed. Combat Beast King was bathed in blood as he fought, his injuries were getting more severe, the situation was getting tougher now.

He was using his life to forcefully hold on and maintain the situation.

"Compared to the might of heaven and earth, even if I am a rank eight Gu Immortal, so what?" Combat Beast King had been cultivating in sovereign immortal aperture, he gained a lot of knowledge and his strength rose greatly, giving him a boost of confidence. But now, facing the myriad tribulation, he could feel how tiny and insignificant he was.

The range of the myriad destruction lightning forest expanded again, because Fang Yuan's main body had to deal with the fight outside, he was at a disadvantage. Against this myriad tribulation, even if Fang Yuan put in all his effort, it would still be a dangerous process, and yet half of his attention was drawn away to deal with Spectral Soul.

This was a myriad tribulation, countless rank eights had faltered at this hurdle!

Fang Yuan's situation was quite unique, this was not his first myriad tribulation. He had not just skipped two myriad tribulations, this current one was created by the three thousand heaven path dao marks in his body.

A myriad tribulation created this way was extremely rare even in the long history of humanity.

Forced by the situation, Fang Yuan had to multitask, he dealt with the situation outside while simultaneously observing sovereign immortal aperture.

He looked at the heaven path dao marks that transformed into lightning path and cloud path to create this myriad tribulation, he suddenly comprehended something.

"I think I understand something now." At that instance, he realized the origin of the calamities and tribulations!

In the past, he knew that calamities and tribulations were controlled by the Heavenly Dao, it cared about balance, to take away surpluses while replenishing deficits. Every Gu Immortal and immortal aperture was a mass congregation of dao marks, thus, the Heavenly Dao had to take measures to maintain the balance.

Every once in a while, the Heavenly Dao would unleash its might, creating calamities and tribulations for Gu Immortals. But how could it create these calamities and tribulations? Fang Yuan did not know.

Right now, this question in Fang Yuan's heart got answered by the scene before him.

It turned out that matter what kind of tribulation, it was actually created using heaven path dao marks. The heaven path dao marks could transform into any path, thus, there were the flying frost jumping lightning tribulation, four inferno cloud tribulation, dragon roar tribulation, heavenly drum thunder tribulation, wind flower calamity, snow moon calamity, profound white flying salt calamity...

These tribulations were of the various paths, there were many types of them, Gu Immortals could not guess what would come, thus they faced huge difficulties. The Heavenly Dao would even mimic venerable methods, for example, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's formless hand.

All these different tribulations were merely the manifestation, in essence, they were all heaven path dao marks!

The higher the Gu Immortal's cultivation level, the more dao marks they would have, and the bigger the difference between them and the natural environment. The more imbalanced it was, the more heaven path dao marks would be drawn to them, and the stronger the tribulations they would face.

Nobody in the world could cultivate heaven path, even if a Gu Immortal passed a tribulation successfully, they would not gain heaven path dao marks. These heaven path dao marks would transform into the dao marks of other paths and fuse with the Gu Immortal's immortal aperture.

Thinking about it, back in Crazed Demon Cave, the heaven path dao marks derived many strange and peculiar small worlds, after these worlds were destroyed, they transformed back into heaven path dao marks.

As for the immortal tribulation tempering aperture killer move that Fang Yuan obtained from Lang Ya Sect, it used the same logic.

Immortal tribulation tempering aperture killer move used the blessed land and grotto-heaven as the refinement target, using the killer move to connect the immortal aperture with the five regions world outside, influencing the calamities and tribulations and using it to temper the immortal aperture itself.

Lang Ya blessed land was once located at Northern Plains' crescent lake. Around the vicinity of crescent lake were water path and refinement path dao marks, immortal tribulation tempering aperture killer move was often used to deal with the calamities and tribulations. Most often, water path and refinement path calamities would occur. After passing it, the immortal aperture would gain water path and refinement path dao marks.

The true effect of this move was to affect the transformation of the heaven path dao marks.

In Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's true inheritance, there were also luck path methods to weaken tribulations. For example, Dog Shit Luck and Fortune Rivalling Heaven. He was using luck path dao marks to interfere with the creation of tribulations by the heaven path dao marks, causing a favorable change to occur and weakening the might of the tribulations.

In Beast Calamity grotto-heaven, there was myriad beings assimilation transformation killer move, it limited the transformation of the heaven path dao marks, thus each tribulation turned into a transformation path beast calamity instead.

The exposing heavenly secret killer move that Fang Yuan obtained from Shadow Sect could precisely deduce the content of the following tribulation. Exposing heavenly secret killer move used heavenly secret Immortal Gu as the core, very evidently, it also targeted the root source, the heaven path dao marks, to make its deductions. Thus, each deduction was extremely precise about the content.

Immortal tribulation tempering aperture, luck path methods, myriad beings assimilation transformation, exposing heavenly secret... Fang Yuan had all of these methods, it was a pity that he could not use them now.

The heaven path dao marks restricted his actions, he could not activate any of these moves.

Only by using human path methods to resist heaven path could Fang Yuan gain some time and opportunity to activate other killer moves. Like earlier in Heavenly Court when he used unlimited qi sea killer move to deal with primordial qi wall.

Fang Yuan had a human path formation in sovereign immortal aperture that used the thousand wish tree as the core. But heaven's will was not stupid, it knew about Fang Yuan's information. Myriad destruction lightning forest also appeared in Mini Central Continent, it was attacking the human path formation, making Fang Yuan trapped in a tighter spot.

Roar—!

Beast growls resounded, a large group of soul beasts moved out towards the lightning clouds in the sky.

They charged relentlessly without any concern about their own lives.

These were all soul beasts, most were desolate beasts, there were some ancient soul beasts and four immemorial soul beasts.

These soul beasts were all captured by Fang Yuan in green ghost desert. Among them, the immemorial soul beasts were enslaved when Fang Yuan helped Fang clan to obtain Divine Bean Palace.

These soul beasts were usually kept in Mini Black Heaven.

Right now, Fang Yuan was facing a crisis, he had to make use of them.

The soul beasts were extremely fragile under the myriad tribulation, they were completely defenseless. In just a while, a hundred desolate level soul beasts perished from the lightning bolts, more than ten ancient soul beasts died as well.

Fang Yuan's heart was cold as ice, he did not waver.

The soul beast group had already served its purpose, it drew the firepower away and took away the pressure, allowing Fang Yuan to gain some time.

This included the immemorial soul beasts, without Immortal Gu, they were just high tier cannon fodder against the myriad tribulation, but they were still useful as meat shields after all.

Fang Yuan did not dare to use the soul beasts against Spectral Soul.

The truth was, after Spectral Soul took control of the year beasts, Fang Yuan gave up on this aspect.

A huge amount of strength flowed like a tidal wave into Spectral Soul's body.

Qing Chou struggled intensely, using killer moves to attack itself manically. However, Spectral Soul endured Qing Chou's attacks forcefully as he continued to drain its strength.

Soul beasts existed in this world because Spectral Soul created soul path.

Spectral Soul understood soul beasts too well, not only could he make them loyal to him, he also has methods to extract strength from them to replenish himself.

Qing Chou's struggles became weaker and weaker.

Spectral Soul looked at Qing Chou with great satisfaction, the hatred Gu within its body was already reaching completion, this fool was simply sending itself to death while contributing treasures as well.

Spectral Soul suppressed Qing Chou while keeping his attention on Dragon Palace, all along, he did not relax, he stared at Fang Yuan's main body without looking away.

The entire situation was still under his control!

Whoosh!

Suddenly, winds blew as the air rumbled, two giant hands slammed towards Spectral Soul from the left and right.

One hand was black while the other was white, they were grand and majestic, containing deep profundities, it was the qi path killer move — Yin-yang Great Killer Hands!

At the crucial moment, Fang Yuan's qi path clone arrived.

Spectral Soul smiled coldly, black smoke spewing out of his body, from the smoke, two immemorial soul beasts flew out and slammed into the two qi path giant hands.

The qi path hands grabbed as the two immemorial soul beasts growled in pain, but they did not die just yet.

Qi Sea Ancestor could neither let go of them nor continue grabbing them at this moment.

If he grabbed onto them, his offensive momentum would be halted. If he let go, these two immemorial soul beasts would still attack him later.

Qi Sea Ancestor shouted as he waved both hands, letting them fly far away, bringing the immemorial soul beasts away from the battlefield.

Spectral Soul's goal was achieved, he used two immemorial soul beasts to restrain Qi Sea Ancestor while also wasting his energy. After all, Qi Sea Ancestor had to sustain the two qi path hands to trap the immemorial soul beasts.

Qi Sea and Spectral Soul's first round of fighting ended up as a simple exchange.

Spectral Soul used two immemorial soul beasts while Qi Sea Ancestor wasted some mental energy, immortal essence, timing. Both sides were evenly matched, in fact Spectral Soul lost a bit more, after all, the immemorial soul beasts had rank eight battle strength!

But looking at the big picture, Spectral Soul's gains were slightly higher, he still continued to control the situation.

Because he controlled Soul Pacifying grotto-heaven secretly, it had many immemorial soul beasts, losing two was no issue. In contrast, Qi Sea failed to use this opportunity well, he originally wanted to disrupt Spectral Soul but was interrupted, this chance was wasted.

Spectral Soul made use of his advantage well, he continued to absorb Qing Chou's strength to strengthen himself while weakening Qing Chou. On the whole, he had gained a lot from this first round of combat.

This round was just a tiny projection of their fight, yet it showed Spectral Soul's abundant and rich battle experience, his vision loomed over the entire battlefield. His control of combat was so precise and flawless, even someone like Fang Yuan felt stifled.

Fang Yuan was not giving up obviously, he focused on repairing Dragon Palace while asking Qi Sea Ancestor to attack again.

Spectral Soul focused on three things at once, he suppressed Dragon Palace and used the black smoke spiral to damage it, he absorbed Qing Chou's soul beast strength, he also used killer moves to resist Qi Sea Ancestor's attacks.

Dragon Palace, Qing Chou, and Qi Sea Ancestor, these were three entities with top tier battle strength in the world, yet they could not turn the situation around even by being on the same side!

To speak the truth, Spectral Soul's current strength was not too impressive, but he had the complete dominance over Dragon Palace, he countered Qing Chou's abilities, and he even knew about Qi Sea Ancestor's information.

"His soul path methods are used in succession, the moves complement each other and are tightly connected, this is an exceptional combat system. In contrast, my Qi Sea clone has only existed for a short period of time, he has too few methods that are all easily countered." Fang Yuan's main body understood the reason.

Qi Sea clone's most common offensive method was yin-yang great killer hands and his main defensive method was heavenly astral cloth robe. His foundation was too low, when observed by Spectral Soul, after just a few exchanges of moves, he would be able to create a countermeasure easily.

Be it battle strength, knowledge, or experience, Spectral Soul stood at the peak of the world. After all, he was once the invincible Demon Venerable that dominated the world!

Among the generations of venerables, Spectral Soul was publicly recognized as the one with the deepest killing intent.

He had gone through intense battles, he fought his way to the top, he was an expert that carved out his own bloody path through countless hurdles!

Under his venerable throne, there was a mountain of skeletons and sea of corpses.

Chapter 2043: Dragon Palace Escapes

"Qi Sea Ancestor, how is the situation over there?" Amidst intense battle, Fang Yuan's clone Qi Sea received Qin Ding Ling's transmission.

Qi Sea Ancestor did not speak, he recorded the scene of the battle using an information path Gu worm and sold it to Qin Ding Ling in treasure yellow heaven.

Heavenly Court soon gained an understanding of the battle situation.

Qin Ding Ling was slightly shocked internally, Spectral Soul's strength far surpassed her initial estimations, it seemed like Qi Sea Ancestor could not restrain Spectral Soul, at this rate, Spectral Soul might likely kill Fang Yuan and defeat Qi Sea, he would also absorb Qing Chou, he would be the greatest winner in this clash!

This was something Qin Ding Ling did not want to see.

Fang Yuan and Spectral Soul were supreme demons, it would be great if they both perished, the best scenario would be Longevity Heaven going down with them! That was the result Qin Ding Ling most wanted to see.

"We have our Immortal Gu House, if we join the fight, we can cause some changes to it. Even though Qing Chou is strong, it is a mistake to use it against Spectral Soul. Looking at Spectral Soul's actions, it seems that he is sure that Fang Yuan is inside Dragon Palace. Then has Fairy Zi Wei already succeeded in her deductions and informed Spectral Soul?"

Qin Ding Ling guessed the truth but she was not certain.

She looked at the operating wisdom path formation and Calamity Luck Altar beside it.

If Heavenly Court could exterminate Fairy Zi Wei and the rest, that would be the best. Clipping Spectral Soul's wings prematurely would result in fewer variables in this battle. It was a pity that Calamity Luck Altar was here, most of Longevity Heaven's experts came along with it, Qin Ding Ling was not confident of taking down Fairy Zi Wei at this moment.

"Longevity Heaven..." Qin Ding Ling gritted her teeth.

Among the Heavenly Court Gu Immortals present, she hated Longevity Heaven most deeply. Back then, she was forced to become Giant Sun's immortal concubine. She endured this humiliation and successfully switched to cultivating luck path, she eventually participated in the fate war. But at the crucial moment, Giant Sun immortal zombie's attack tilted the balance of the final battle in his favor.

"Longevity Heaven, I will settle the scores with you one day!" Qin Ding Ling swore in her heart.

Right when Qin Ding Ling was thinking, a rank seven Immortal Gu House flew over.

This Immortal Gu House was owned by Spirit Affinity House, the first supreme elder and second supreme elder were inside it as they brought along an important person, Feng Jin Huang.

"Feng Jin Huang, quickly retrieve the dream realms before us." Qin Ding Ling ordered.

"Yes." The door of the Immortal Gu House opened as Feng Jin Huang stood on the steps, quickly using her method with a solemn expression.

She had dream wings Immortal Gu and the modified pure dream reality seeker transformation. In fact, this killer move was created by Fairy Zi Wei's deductions.

As dream realms turned into human form, they flew into Spirit Affinity House's Immortal Gu House.

Shadow Sect and Longevity Heaven were stirred.

Fairy Zi Wei's eyes shined with brilliance.

Old Man Zheng Yuan quickly asked: "Fairy, do we take action?"

After all, these dream realms belonged by Spectral Soul, his attainment levels were inside them.

Fairy Zi Wei shook her head: "We will wait for now, these dream realms are just a small portion, they are not important. Fang Yuan is our main priority!"

At the moment, Spectral Soul's side had a clear advantage. At this rate of development, Shadow Sect was greatly favored. Fairy Zi Wei did not want to upset the balance now and disrupt the overall situation.

Feng Jin Huang was just a rank five Gu Master, she was not even a rank six Gu Immortal. But her status was quite unique, she was Feng Jiu Ge's daughter!

If anyone attacked her, it might cause Feng Jiu Ge to come.

Feng Jiu Ge's future self had likely disappeared, similar to Hei Lou Lan and Bai Ning Bing. But even so, with Feng Jiu Ge's own strength, he could participate in this fight, he was an uncertain variable.

Especially when this variable was not favorable for Shadow Sect, Fairy Zi Wei wanted to have less problems if possible.

Calamity Luck Altar's Bing Sai Chuan had the same thought, he did not make a move in the end.

Feng Jin Huang was heavily protected by Heavenly Court's immortals as she gradually collected the dream realms.

Qin Ding Ling had a complex emotion.

She eventually made this move, using Feng Jin Huang and thus, Feng Jiu Ge indirectly to intimidate their opponents. Since when did the great Heavenly Court fall to such a level?

The pride in Qin Ding Ling's heart pressured her, but the logic in her mind told her to use all of the resources and influences they could gather!

Qi Sea Ancestor transmitted information again, requesting for Heavenly Court's reinforcement.

Qin Ding Ling rejected his request politely, asking him to persevere some more time.

Thus, Qi Sea Ancestor changed his request: "Sorrowful Wind Mountain Range is closest to Black Heaven Temple, why don't you ask them to send an Immortal Gu House to patrol the periphery of the battlefield. If I am unable to stop Spectral Soul from killing Fang Yuan, we can still rely on Black Heaven Temple."

Qin Ding Ling thought about it but did not tell Qi Sea Ancestor about her orders to Black Heaven Temple, she rejected: "Black Heaven Temple is not strong enough to participate in this battle."

Qi Sea Ancestor replied angrily: "This is a prime opportunity! If Heavenly Court hesitates and loses the chance, either one of these two demons getting stronger will be a problem for the righteous path."

Qin Ding Ling sighed: "Why wouldn't I know that? But Heavenly Court is not as before, we need to act cautiously. If we send Black Heaven Temple's Gu Immortals there, they would only die in vain. Please understand our plight!"

Qi Sea Ancestor felt a little dejected. Since Heavenly Court's leader openly spoke of their weakness, they were really not the Heavenly Court of before, their style of action changed, Fang Yuan could not make use of them easily anymore.

While Qin Ding Ling and Qi Sea Ancestor spoke secretly, Demon Immortal Qi Jue was also asking Spectral Soul: "Fang Yuan's main body is here, why aren't you coming here?"

Fang Yuan placed his will in Myriad Year Flying Warship, he also left behind Immortal Gu and immortal essence, under the effect of familiar face killer move, he could disguise his will very well.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue told Spectral Soul about this but the latter continued to fight Dragon Palace, not showing signs of leaving. This made Demon Immortal Qi Jue quite suspicious.

Spectral Soul directly replied: "Don't forget about Fang Yuan's familiar face. We cannot be sure of his location."

Demon Immortal Qi Jue became increasingly suspicious: "Spectral Soul, are you hiding something from me?"

Spectral Soul replied: "Don't worry, just continue restraining Myriad Year Flying Warship, you will get your due remuneration."

But Demon Immortal Qi Jue did not fall for it, he smiled coldly: "Don't worry indeed, I have a brilliant plan to find out which is Fang Yuan's main body."

Saying so, he suddenly stopped dealing with Myriad Year Flying Warship as he flew towards Spectral Soul's direction.

Myriad Year Flying Warship was stunned for a moment before quickly pulling away from Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

Spectral Soul sensed something amiss, he quickly transmitted: "Qi Jue, don't do anything foolish."

But Demon Immortal Qi Jue was firm: "Sometimes, we need to take a chance right? Or maybe, you can tell me the information that you just obtained?"

Spectral Soul snorted but did not reply.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue turned silent as he flew into the sky with an increased speed.

In a few breaths of time, Myriad Year Flying Warship appeared behind him again.

Seeing this, Demon Immortal Qi Jue laughed loudly: "Oh Spectral Soul, look, I found out the truth already. I can be certain that Fang Yuan's main body is inside Dragon Palace now!"

If Fang Yuan's main body was inside Myriad Year Flying Warship, he would have flown away already. But now, Myriad Year Flying Warship returned to stall Demon Immortal Qi Jue, it showed that Fang Yuan's main body was unwilling to see Spectral Soul gain reinforcements, he had to stop Demon Immortal Qi Jue from leaving.

At this moment, Fang Yuan's plan to deceive his enemies by splitting up has failed completely.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue was a famous demon in history, his seniority was higher than everyone here, including Spectral Soul.

After sensing something wrong, he quickly tested his method to find out the truth.

Spectral Soul snorted coldly, showing displeasure. With Demon Immortal Qi Jue's move, the situation got out of Spectral Soul's control.

Spectral Soul was just using Qi Jue by promising benefits, they were wary of each other in essence, their relationship was merely because of mutual gains. The reason why Spectral Soul did not want Demon Immortal Qi Jue to come over was because this uncertain variable could possibly get greedy and fight with him over the immense benefits of killing Fang Yuan!

Right now, from Demon Immortal Qi Jue's actions, it showed that Spectral Soul's worries were well justified. Demon Immortal Qi Jue definitely had his own ideas.

But Spectral Soul did not fluster.

Back when he lured Demon Immortal Qi Jue to join the battle, he had already thought of this. But there was no helping it, Spectral Soul had just regained his strength, Shadow Sect was still very weak. Because of the many variables in this battle, Spectral Soul had to increase the strength of his side, it was thanks to Fairy Zi Wei communicating with Longevity Heaven earlier, to rope them in with Shadow Sect temporarily, otherwise the situation would have been even more chaotic.

Did Bing Sai Chuan had no such intentions either? Was he really going to watch Spectral Soul kill Fang Yuan like that?

Of course not.

Fairy Zi Wei was a wisdom path great expert, she had deep considerations. She created the formation in front of Heavenly Court, it was to restrain them as well as Longevity Heaven.

This battle to kill Fang Yuan was not as grand as the fate war but it involved four parties, tens of Gu Immortals, and almost all of the peak experts in the current world.

These people plotted against each other and schemed deeply, Spectral Soul could sense acutely that his control over the situation was slipping.

Immortal killer move — Qi Wall!

During the intense battle, Qi Sea Ancestor pushed with both hands as a colossal qi wall formed instantly.

The qi wall was like a mountain as it pressed towards Spectral Soul.

Spectral Soul pointed with his fingers as several immemorial soul beasts appeared, growling as they blocked the qi wall.

But Qi Sea Ancestor shouted suddenly as he raised his right fist, he spread out his fingers as his palm targeted Spectral Soul from afar.

Spectral Soul seemed to have sensed something as black smoke appeared around him in a ball shape, shielding him.

The moment Qi Sea Ancestor's killer move was ready, he moved his palm away and targeted the black smoke spiral instead.

Immortal killer move — Great Qi Hand Explosion!

Bam.

Following an intense explosion, the black smoke spiral was completely torn apart as black qi flew all over the place. Dragon Palace which was greatly damaged moved quickly as it drew a golden trail of light in the sky, rapidly escaping!

At this point in the battle, Dragon Palace finally broke free.

Spectral Soul's attention was drawn by Demon Immortal Qi Jue, Qi Sea Ancestor found this small loophole and quickly made use of his opportunity with some luck.

Spectral Soul looked at Qi Sea Ancestor deeply, other than intense anger and killing intent, there was also praise and admiration in his gaze.

Qi Sea Ancestor had made a brilliant move!

Now that Dragon Palace had escaped, Spectral Soul had to keep up with it, he had to abandon the heavy Qing Chou.

It was such a pity! Spectral Soul was only a bit of time away from completely subduing Qing Chou.

Chapter 2044: Leaving Stealthily

"Fang Yuan, where are you trying to escape to?" Spectral Soul smiled coldly, black smoke oozing out of his body.

An immemorial soul beast as large as a giant python flew out of the black smoke, it pounced at Dragon Palace with strong winds around it.

The orange-golden light flickered on Dragon Palace as a trace of pink smoke flew out.

With the movement of the smoke, the immemorial soul beast easily got suppressed inside Dragon Palace without putting up a resistance.

It was immortal killer move — Dreamy Light Smoke!

Spectral Soul was only afraid of this method from Dragon Palace, but now that it was used, he immediately used the opportunity to move with increased speed, approaching Dragon Palace like a specter.

Immortal killer move — Qi Wall!

Qi Sea Ancestor pushed with both hands as winds blew wildly, a giant qi wall appeared out of nowhere and blocked Spectral Soul.

Spectral Soul snorted coldly, breaking the qi wall but losing his battle opportunity.

Dragon Palace changed directions, the aura of dreamy light smoke became denser again.

Behind it, Qing Chou roared and wanted to chase them but it was powerless, in a few breaths of time, it was left in the dust.

Dragon Palace, Spectral Soul, and Qi Sea Ancestor fought while they traveled rapidly in the sky.

Qi Sea Ancestor played the role of a nuisance perfectly, he prevented Spectral Soul from succeeding multiple times.

Spectral Soul became annoyed, he started to attack Qi Sea Ancestor aggressively.

But at this time, Dragon Palace suddenly retaliated as it shielded Qi Sea Ancestor. Especially with the killer move dreamy light smoke ready to strike at any moment, Spectral Soul could not act too aggressively.

Thus, the situation went into a deadlock!

Spectral Soul had not returned to his peak condition, thus, when fighting against Dragon Palace and Qi Sea Ancestor, his battle strength was not much higher. Once they cooperated and assisted each other, even Spectral Soul felt a sense of helplessness, he could not fight against both enemies, targeting one of them would allow the other to act, it was hard to take action now.

At this time, Spectral Soul could not help but think of Qing Chou.

"I should not have weakened Qing Chou to this extent. If it still had some battle strength left, it would disrupt their cooperation!" Spectral Soul felt a little regret.

He was all alone and did not need cooperation, but Fang Yuan and Qi Sea Ancestor were different, they had to work together intrinsically to resist Spectral Soul.

Qing Chou was overwhelmed by rage, once it joined the battle, it would ruin Fang Yuan and Qi Sea Ancestor's cooperation, Spectral Soul would have a lot of opportunities to strike.

But what Spectral Soul did earlier was not wrong either. If he could subdue Qing Chou completely, Spectral Soul's advantage would rise, he would almost certainly claim victory.

It was a pity Qi Sea Ancestor ruined it!

He was merely a step away from completely subduing Qing Chou, but just that bit of time would allow Fang Yuan to escape from them, Spectral Soul could not take the risk.

This time, Spectral Soul had the advantage of being undercover, but what about next time?

Once Fang Yuan becomes cautious against him, would he have another chance?

Even Spectral Soul could not be sure.

Despite Fairy Zi Wei's deduction method, would Fang Yuan be unable to counter it?

Heavenly Court was the best example, they could not capture Fang Yuan despite countless efforts.

What was the outcome?

Fang Yuan got stronger and stronger, he fought his way to Heavenly Court and destroyed fate Gu!

Even though Fang Yuan was backed by many individuals who paved the way for him, what made all of these people invest in him?

Were there no better candidates?

Even for otherworldly demons, there were many of them in the world.

Fang Yuan was used by heaven's will and all these people, he was obviously someone who was unique and had great value.

Forget about the rest, just his ability to escape was something even Spectral Soul felt admiration towards.

Fang Yuan's attainment in escaping was very deep, he had a scheming and crafty mind! He was most skilled by borrowing others' strength, he could escape under the thumbs of many powerful forces, quickly raising his strength over time.

Spectral Soul had such rich battle experience, he knew deeply that someone like Fang Yuan had to be dealt with seriously. Once he struck, it had to be a fatal blow, he could not give Fang Yuan any time to rest or recuperate. This enemy was too good at making use of opportunity, he could easily gain a new lease on life and turn the situation around.

Fang Yuan was the type of person who could shine with a bit of sunlight, sprout with a bit of water, or create great problems with just a bit of time.

Indeed, Spectral Soul was wary against Fang Yuan.

Even he had to admit this truth.

Because he saw a trace of himself in Fang Yuan!

"Fang Yuan, defending will lead to your eventual loss, how long can you last? I will definitely kill you!" Spectral Soul said coldly, not forgetting to exert mental pressure on Fang Yuan.

"Qi Sea, after this battle, even if you hide, I will find you in Eastern Sea. I will destroy your qi sea and kill all of your subordinates!" Spectral Soul turned around and threatened Qi Sea Ancestor.

Qi Sea clone replied calmly: "The so-called Demon Venerable is actually resorting to trash talking."

Spectral Soul smiled coldly.

Qi Sea Ancestor's expression quickly changed, black smoke appeared around him as it started to invade his body.

Spectral Soul used words to distract Qi Sea Ancestor, even though this was not a weakness, in Spectral Soul's eyes, it was enough to create an opportunity for himself!

Qi Sea Ancestor quickly evaded it as Spectral Soul wanted to pursue him, Dragon Palace flew over and blocked Spectral Soul, bearing some of Qi Sea Ancestor's burden.

Qi Sea Ancestor exerted all his strength to alleviate the problem on him, after regaining his footing, he went back into the battle.

It was a deadlock once again.

But this time, no matter how Spectral Soul provoked him, Qi Sea Ancestor showed no carelessness.

Like this, the three sides fought and whipped up countless storms, the impact of their clash spreading towards the northern direction.

They flew past Sorrowful Wind Mountain Range, entering Intestinal Gorge.

Black Heaven Temple's immortals were hiding in Intestinal Gorge.

Several Immortal Gu Houses were concealed around Intestinal Gorge, leaking no aura at all.

Seeing that the battle far away was approaching them, Black Heaven Temple's immortals immediately turned excited.

"Coming, they're coming!"

"They're finally here."

"The battle is so intense, is that female immortal Spectral Soul who is using the body temporarily?"

"Dragon Palace has been heavily damaged, Fang Yuan has no battle strength left, I've never seen him in a more pathetic state."

"He deserves it! If not for him, fate Gu would not have been destroyed. Be it Spectral Soul or Fang Yuan, they deserve to die!"

Black Heaven Temple's immortals gritted their teeth, they had a different tone when speaking of Qi Sea Ancestor.

"When we take action later, we should avoid Qi Sea Ancestor."

"It was all thanks to him that Heavenly Court's qi harvest fruit was completely removed."

"He is our alliance mate, he does not know that we are here in ambush, we cannot harm him."

Even though Qi Sea Ancestor and Dragon Palace were working together, Black Heaven Temple's Gu Immortals did not feel surprised. Spectral Soul was too strong, they had to work together to resist him. Precisely because of Qi Sea Ancestor's hard work, Fang Yuan and Spectral Soul were still opposing each other, expending their energy.

"Close, they are close."

"Let's do it!"

Black Heaven Temple's Gu Immortals were ready to strike.

Pew!

Right at this moment, Spectral Soul unleashed an aggressive killer move, black smoke rumbled as dark winds howled, several mountains were affected by the winds and instantly got disintegrated into dust.

Bam.

Qi Sea Ancestor had to unleash qi wall killer move to resist the dark winds.

Dragon Palace released intense golden light, shooting out a grand light pillar to fight offense with offense, attacking Spectral Soul.

Right when the pillar was about to hit, Spectral Soul's body flickered as he vanished on the spot, evading the light pillar easily.

The light pillar tore through the sky, it was over a thousand feet long, creating a huge trench on the ground. At that instance, smoke rose as countless mountains collapsed.

A brand new artificially created Earth Trench appeared before the eyes of the Black Heaven Temple immortals!

After this eruption of attacks, Spectral Soul no longer had a chance to attack, he quickly stopped and continued to fight against Qi Sea and Dragon Palace as they flew away.

The Black Heaven Temple immortals hiding in the Immortal Gu Houses were silent.

The battle they saw earlier shook their minds and bodies!

"So this is their real battle strength!" Many people understood this and broke out in cold sweat.

Nobody spoke about attacking anymore.

The atmosphere was quite awkward.

Eventually, Black Heaven Temple's first supreme elder coughed and broke the silence.

He purposely mumbled to himself: "No wonder Heavenly Court's Lady Qin asked us to wait here and observe the situation."

"Indeed, indeed, Lady Qin is very wise."

"What do we do now?"

"Let's continue waiting in ambush, they did not discover us. Maybe we will get a chance again?"

"That is right, even if we do not gain any opportunities, we can't come here and do nothing right? We must collect information about this battle and inform Lady Qin at least."

Rumble!

Right when the Black Heaven Temple immortals were discussing, the intense battle in the sky erupted again.

At once, the sky turned dark, earth shook as mountains rumbled.

The aftermath of their collision created huge air currents that surged out. Trees were uprooted as mountain rocks flew, wild beasts cried out in pain, it was the sight of an apocalypse.

Black Heaven Temple's immortals watched with wide eyes as Spectral Soul unleashed a black soul ball but Dragon Palace evaded it.

The soul ball fell into a nearby valley.

There was no sound, at the instance, with the valley as the core, the surrounding thousand li of mountains and valleys turned into black dust that flew away with the wind. The originally lively mountains vanished soundlessly, only a huge crater was left.

Gulp.

Someone swallowed their saliva, it was clearly heard by the Gu Immortals.

"What was that killer move earlier? It is so strange!"

"There are no records of it in history."

"It is not strange that Spectral Soul is able to use such powerful methods, but if it landed on us..."

"Not just us, even our sect's Immortal Gu Houses might not be able to survive such an attack."

"Let's... leave? Lady Qin asked us to act according to the situation, we are allowed to retreat if needed."

Black Heaven Temple's immortals looked at each other before turning to the first supreme elder.

First supreme elder's expression was extremely dark, he said with a solemn tone: "We need to preserve our strength, we cannot waste it here. If we die now, who will look after Black Heaven Temple? Lady Qin will not blame us, we are planning for the future."

The result was, Black Heaven Temple's immortals came stealthily and watched as the battle in the sky flew away, after that, they stealthily retreated without a sound.

Chapter 2045: Myriad Tribulation's Transformation

"Fang Yuan, this is as far as you go!" Spectral Soul chased for some time before attacking again, he was very confident this time.

At once, dark winds howled, black clouds filled the sky, it was like an immensely thick wall appeared before Dragon Palace.

"This is... quickly retreat!" At this moment, Wu Shuai's expression turned nervous, he noticed that this was a soul path battlefield killer move!

Black clouds spread out as Dragon Palace and Qi Sea Ancestor quickly retreated.

Immortal killer move — Soul Taker Battlefield!

This was Spectral Soul's famous battlefield killer move.

Spectral Soul had used this move to kill countless enemies. Once the battlefield was activated, dark blue soul beasts would be formed within the dense fog, there would be countless soul beasts that appeared unceasingly. Living beings who died in this battlefield would have their souls taken and transformed into soul beasts, under the control of the killer move's user.

When Dragon Palace was trapped by the black smoke spiral, there was still hope of escaping. But if it got trapped by soul taker battlefield, the chances of escaping would be close to zero.

Fang Yuan had Shadow Sect's true inheritance, soul taker battlefield was included in this inheritance, he knew a lot about the move.

But now, Spectral Soul used this move openly, it was likely that he had already modified and improved upon it. In fact, Fang Yuan's knowledge might be a trap from Spectral Soul.

At this moment, Fang Yuan and Qi Sea Ancestor did not dare to continue fighting, they quickly focused on escaping.

Spectral Soul rode on the endless black smoke as he chased after them.

When ordinary Gu Immortals used battlefield killer moves, they would need to cancel it if it could not trap the enemy.

But was Spectral Soul ordinary?

He used the split move technique to split soul taker battlefield into many parts. The first part was the black smoke, Spectral Soul could sustain it and move it around without any problem or weakness.

"Soul taker battlefield was created by Spectral Soul in his early days, he used it until the later part of his life. By then, he created an even stronger battlefield killer move — Hundred Million Slaughterfield. Why isn't he using the stronger killer move? Unless, he does not have the necessary Gu worms?" Fang Yuan guessed.

Spectral Soul was also guessing: "After escaping from Heavenly Court, Fang Yuan has been going north. Where is he trying to go? Northern Plains? If it is Northern Plains, which location is he going to? Crazed Demon Cave?"

Now that the five regions were united and the regional walls vanished, Spectral Soul had a huge advantage. Without the regional walls, Fang Yuan only has several ways to shrug off these pursuers.

Spectral Soul was very familiar with the five regions, he guessed Crazed Demon Cave at the first try.

Even if Spectral Soul could not be certain, he knew that stopping Fang Yuan from going to the north was a wise decision. Thus, Spectral Soul moved his black smoke to spread out across the surroundings, forcing Fang Yuan to change directions as he flew back to Sorrowful Wind Mountain Range.

At the same time, in another battlefield.

"I'm done." Feng Jin Huang panted heavily as she stopped her killer move. Her forehead was covered in sweat. Using pure dream reality seeker transformation killer move like this placed a huge pressure on her.

But it was done now.

Under the supervision of Heavenly Court, Shadow Sect, and Longevity Heaven, more than ten rank eight Gu Immortals watched as Feng Jin Huang kept all of the dream realms away.

Fang Yuan was nowhere in sight!

"Fang Yuan was not hiding here after all." The Gu Immortals were disappointed but also sighed in relief secretly.

Qin Ding Ling immediately asked as she moved her Immortal Gu House closer to the wisdom path formation: "Fairy Zi Wei, I've given you so much time. Right now, tell me, where is Fang Yuan's main body?"

Calamity Luck Altar quickly moved ahead as it blocked Qin Ding Ling, Bing Sai Chuan's voice resounded from within: "Slow down, immortal concubine from Heavenly Court!"

He called Qin Ding Ling an immortal concubine, he was referring to her past as Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's woman.

But soon, Bing Sai Chuan changed the subject to Fairy Zi Wei: "But I hold the same suspicions as Immortal Concubine Qin. Fairy Zi Wei, I hope you can give us a satisfactory answer."

Bing Sai Chuan could not wait either.

Because after such a long time, Fairy Zi Wei still had not given them an answer, it was not like what she said to them earlier.

Fairy Zi Wei stopped using the wisdom path formation as she collected the Gu worms.

She made up an excuse on the spot: "The situation is different from last time, Fang Yuan is prepared against us. However, I found his location after all."

"Where?" Qin Ding Ling asked immediately.

Fairy Zi Wei had already kept away her core Immortal Gu, she answered: "Fang Yuan is in Dragon Palace."

She spoke the truth.

Trying to keep Fang Yuan's location a secret now was pointless.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue had his own plan, he was already heading towards Spectral Soul's location, Myriad Year Flying Warship followed closely behind it.

From one glance, it was obvious where Fang Yuan's main body was.

"We will pursue them!" Qin Ding Ling ordered.

Heavenly Court's Immortal Gu Houses started to fly together as they guarded each other.

Shadow Sect and Longevity Heaven also followed suit.

But the three parties were quite spaced apart, the atmosphere was a little tense.

Fairy Zi Wei's side was quite helpless here, she wanted to stop Heavenly Court here but the alliance with Longevity Heaven was not reliable, they were only allied in name.

As for Heavenly Court?

Qin Ding Ling could not confirm the truth behind Fairy Zi Wei's words, but since Fang Yuan was not inside the dream realms, he had to be in Dragon Palace or Myriad Year Flying Warship. Looking at Spectral Soul's actions, it was more likely that Fang Yuan was inside Dragon Palace.

Before they found Fang Yuan's main body, Qin Ding Ling did not want to target Fairy Zi Wei. It was too much of a waste of time now, and in this period, if either Spectral Soul or Fang Yuan claims victory while Heavenly Court was not around, it would be a huge loss.

For Longevity Heaven, Bing Sai Chuan also wanted to see how things progressed. He did not want to act rashly, because their strength was not enough to suppress everyone, he needed to use his timing well and target Fang Yuan. If he managed to kill Fang Yuan, the gains would be immense.

All three groups targeted Fang Yuan.

It was really a rare chance to kill Fang Yuan, the opportunity would not present itself twice.

Boom!

With a loud sound, Dragon Palace crashed into a mountain like a shooting star.

But Dragon Palace did not stop there, it went deep into the mountain's interior as a result of the huge force that sent it flying.

Qi Sea Ancestor quickly used qi wall to obstruct Spectral Soul from chasing after it.

But Spectral Soul smiled coldly, he moved around Qing Chou.

Instantly, Qing Chou's eyes turned red as it attacked furiously.

Qi Sea Ancestor's attacks were stopped by Qing Chou, using this chance, Spectral Soul flew downwards.

At the moment of crisis, a heavily damaged Dragon Palace flew out of the smoke, dodging Spectral Soul's assault.

Not long ago, Qing Chou joined in the battle against Spectral Soul, but it was made use of instead.

Fang Yuan fell into danger again, Dragon Palace suffered a heavy blow, it was about to break, it could only escape and stall for some time.

The outside battle was tense, but inside Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture, a change had occurred even though the myriad tribulation was still rampaging.

Fang Yuan sacrificed his soul beast group resolutely, not only did they bear the brunt of the tribulation, heaven's will's attention was also drawn away.

The pressure on Fang Yuan lifted by a bit, there was finally a chance for him to activate the human path formation again.

The human path formation erupted with great might as a grand white light pillar shot into the sky, into the depths of the lightning clouds.

At once, the myriad tribulation's lightning clouds froze.

Using this chance, Combat Beast King attacked, scattering countless Gu worms in the sky.

Fang Yuan's divine sense enveloped them as he set up a formation rapidly.

In order to make this counterattack, he had made ample preparations. With his deep formation path attainment, he quickly created a formation in the sky.

Heaven's will reacted after that, sending lightning bolts to attack together.

Combat Beast King roared as he intercepted the lightning bolts without dodging.

After over ten breaths of time, his star armor shattered, he fell to the ground while bathed in blood.

With a loud sound, he created a pit on the ground as he fell unconscious, either dead or alive.

Lightning bolts shot towards the formation again.

At the critical moment, the formation's set up finally succeeded as it turned into a huge basin.

The basin shot out profound light that had a mysterious attractive force, it absorbed all of the lightning bolts that shot out.

The myriad tribulation was very fierce but the basin successfully absorbed and turned it into a pool of lightning plasma.

The lightning bolts continued to attack while the lightning pool grew in volume.

The lightning pool was not special, it was a common resource point for lightning path cultivators, almost all lightning path Gu Immortals would create one in their immortal aperture. It was like how light path Gu Immortals would create a Five Light Mountain.

But this lightning pool's appearance was a huge help to Fang Yuan, it bore the brunt of this myriad destruction lightning forest tribulation. It was even more effective than the old Combat Beast King.

This was because this lightning pool's core was not ordinary, it was a rank eight Immortal Gu that Fang Yuan had — Lightning Gu!

But good times did not last, heaven's will controlled the myriad tribulation to target the newly formed lightning pool. As the water level of this pool rose gradually, it was about to overflow.

Immortal killer move — Unrestrained Heavenly Mark!

Fang Yuan directly used this killer move on the deep blue plasma in the lightning pool.

The plasma seemed to be made of lightning path dao marks, but it was actually formed from a small portion of those three thousand heaven path dao marks.

These dao marks were restrained by the lightning pool, they were sitting ducks. Due to Fang Yuan's killer move, they were quickly refined, the efficiency was much higher than before!

One, two, five... ten dao marks!

The water level of the lightning pool stabilized before falling rapidly.

The lightning in the sky suddenly ceased.

Heaven's will was not stupid, it knew that continuing with this would lead to failure, Fang Yuan would gain much more instead.

It started to transform the myriad tribulation.

Heaven path was inclusive of everything, it contained lightning path, it could turn into countless lighting bolts. It also contained other paths, it naturally had all sorts of forms to take.

Since Fang Yuan made a countermeasure, heaven's will immediately stopped and changed its method to cause destruction to sovereign immortal aperture.

For ordinary myriad tribulations, the content would be fixed once it appeared.

But Fang Yuan's myriad tribulation was special, it was made of over three thousand heaven path dao marks, heaven's will controlled it personally, it could change forms at will.

This undoubtedly raised the difficulty of Fang Yuan's tribulation by many times!

"This is too much..." As the old Combat Beast King woke up gradually, he had already separated from the star sea snail. Deep within the pit, his old body was buried in the fragments of the star sea snail, he looked at the changing myriad tribulation as this old rank eight Gu Immortal showed a deep expression of despair.

At the same time, in the external battlefield.

"Spectral Soul, I will lend you a hand!" Demon Immortal Qi Jue had finally arrived.

Spectral Soul gained reinforcements but he had an unhappy expression, he only snorted in reply.

He knew about Demon Immortal Qi Jue's true intentions, but now was not the time for internal conflict.

Chapter 2046: Falling for a Trap

Demon Immortal Qi Jue arrived and immediately attacked Qi Sea Ancestor. The secluded domain of heaven and earth above his head, Xi Land, was too powerful against qi path.

Qi Sea Ancestor was Dragon Palace's greatest help, now that he was restrained, Dragon Palace's situation became more dangerous.

But soon, Myriad Year Flying Warship arrived too and started to join the fight. Even though Fang Yuan faced much difficulty, he managed to drag this fight on.

Spectral Soul yelled, his body moved like a specter, his palm landed on Dragon Palace again.

Countless soul beast silhouettes appeared on the surface of Dragon Palace like a series of still images, a portion of Dragon Palace shattered, it was damaged both internally and externally.

Dragon Palace unleashed dreamy light smoke, Spectral Soul quickly retreated.

At the next moment, Demon Immortal Qi Jue pointed at Dragon Palace suddenly.

Qi currents gathered, they exploded instantly.

The exterior of Dragon Palace had already been blown to bits, only the main hall was left. Now that it suffered this powerful attack from Demon Immortal Qi Jue, a huge hole appeared on the roof of this main hall, it could be seen from the outside.

Spectral Soul saw this and smiled coldly, not holding back his praise: "Qi Jue, well done!"

At this stage, everyone knew that Dragon Palace was in grave danger, if they worked harder, they would be able to shatter it entirely.

Fang Yuan and Qi Sea Ancestor could cooperate, Demon Immortal Qi Jue and Spectral Soul could do the same as well!

After Demon Immortal Qi Jue joined the fight, he suppressed Qi Sea Ancestor and cooperated with Spectral Soul. Even though they did not have close coordination, these two had abundant battle experience, they could find ways to work together.

And this cooperation pushed Dragon Palace beyond the brink of destruction.

When Fairy Zi Wei, Qin Ding Ling, and Bing Sai Chuan arrived, they saw that Dragon Palace shattered into countless fragments as they scattered everywhere.

Fang Yuan and Wu Shuai, who were inside Dragon Palace were exposed, but they quickly went inside Myriad Year Flying Warship, which came to pick them up.

Myriad Year Flying Warship was significantly faster than Dragon Palace, it immediately moved away and escaped.

The three groups of immortals were stunned before feeling great joy.

"Quick, Fang Yuan is done for!"

"Dragon Palace was actually destroyed!!"

"Even though Myriad Year Flying Warship is fast, in terms of defense, it is inferior to Dragon Palace."

"We must kill Fang Yuan, we must restore Heavenly Court's reputation."

"Fang Yuan destroyed our Imperial Court blessed land, there is deep hatred between him and Longevity Heaven. We will kill him and take all of his true inheritances and Gu worms. We will pull out his soul and torture him for all eternity!"

"Fang Yuan, it is finally time for Shadow Sect to take care of you."

"We will kill Fang Yuan first before we compete among ourselves. We must not let him have any chance of getting away during our conflict!"

The immortals rushed up, they pursued Fang Yuan with great enthusiasm.

This was the greatest predicament that Fang Yuan had ever been in since his rebirth. He was currently chased by the top three super forces in the world, most of the world's strongest experts had gathered behind him. Qin Ding Ling, Fairy Zi Wei, and Bing Sai Chuan were Gu Immortals that left a name for themselves in history, there was even a fearsome being like Spectral Soul.

"Fang Yuan, you cannot escape." Spectral Soul smiled coldly to himself, when he saw that everyone's target was Fang Yuan, he did not chase them away, he allowed everyone to pursue him.

"Stay attentive, defend against Spectral Soul and Longevity Heaven." Qin Ding Ling instructed.

This was truly an amazing sight.

Heavenly Court, Longevity Heaven, and Shadow Sect joined forces to pursue Fang Yuan, but because of their mutual wariness, they did not go all out.

Fang Yuan did not create a situation where the three sides clashed because they all were not simple characters. At the same time, Fang Yuan's grudges with them were too deep, the wealth that he held was also too alluring.

Even if they held back, they were still sufficiently strong, their killer moves were all strange and unpredictable.

Not long afterwards, Myriad Year Flying Warship became covered in damages, many Gu worm corpses fell off it while it flew and escaped.

"At this rate, there is no way out!" Wu Shuai shouted: "Main body, our road to the north has been blocked, we can only go southwest now, this is hopeless. We cannot last much longer, Myriad Year Flying Warship is much frailer than Dragon Palace."

Fang Yuan's main body was sitting down and dealing with the myriad tribulation, he instructed: "Go underground, see if there's any hope underground."

Myriad Year Flying Warship was maneuvering in the sky, dodging Spectral Soul's black soul ball, but a large number of killer moves still landed on it.

The white ship defended against the barrage of killer moves, soon, a portion of the ship turned dim as the white color turned to grey, it floated in the sky. Next, it vanished into thin air after intense winds swept it away.

Myriad Year Flying Warship was like an injured flying fish, it dived downwards, almost crashing to the ground.

"Follow it!"

"This ship will break with three more rounds of attacks."

"Fang Yuan must die!"

"If we cannot obtain it, we will destroy the sovereign immortal aperture along with him, we cannot let others benefit from this."

The three forces made similar decisions as they ordered.

Boom!

Myriad Year Flying Warship dived down underground like a white meteor.

As dust clouds rumbled, earth shook but it could not scare off the pursuers, they followed the hole that Myriad Year Flying Warship created as they dived in.

Bam bam bam...

Many killer moves continued to land on Myriad Year Flying Warship.

Myriad Year Flying Warship was starting to break apart, it was in a critical state.

"Hahaha, Fang Yuan made a foolish move, this is the underground, Myriad Year Flying Warship can't move easily while we can hit it with great precision."

"He can neither go up or down now! Fang Yuan, you demon, you slaughtered innocents and harmed the world, today you will face retribution, this is all just desserts!"

"Offending us will lead to your pitiful end!"

The immortals roared in anger.

Seeing that Fang Yuan was escaping in distress, all of the immortals' morale surged to a peak level.

They just needed to put in a bit more effort to see Fang Yuan die right in front of them.

Within Myriad Year Flying Warship, Wu Shuai was covered in blood. With such intense attacks, Myriad Year Flying Warship could not be repaired in time.

Rumble...

After the immortals made their preparation, they started to attack again with a new wave of moves.

Countless killer moves were unleashed with some distance between them, trying to avoid nullifying each other, the terrifying wave of attacks swept towards Myriad Year Flying Warship layer by layer.

"Die!"

Bam.

At the moment of life and death, Myriad Year Flying Warship crashed into the rock in front and barged into a huge underground space.

Myriad Year Flying Warship had room to maneuver, it dodged most of the killer moves and escaped destruction. It was like a drowning person suddenly breathing in some air.

"What happened?"

"We entered Earth Abyss!"

"Is this Fang Yuan's intention?"

"Chase him, we cannot let him escape."

The immortals were stunned before charging through the rocks, arriving in the underground space.

It turned out that while Spectral Soul chased Fang Yuan, they went towards the southeast from Sorrowful Wind Mountain Range. Demon Immortal Qi Jue came from the east, he cooperated with Spectral Soul to force Fang Yuan to go southwest. Finally, because Fairy Zi Wei and the rest came from the south, Fang Yuan had to go west in the end.

After traveling west for some time, they arrived in Ancient Soul Sect's territory.

Ancient Soul Sect was one of the ten great ancient sects, it had a long history, one of Ancient Soul Sect's territories was a huge underground abyss.

The underground abyss was at least hundreds of thousands of square kilometers in size. The space was extremely large and the underground world was deep and secluded. There were all sorts of caves and tunnels, some were like labyrinths, some had giant underground lakes while some had flat ground.

Countless lifeforms lived here, in Fang Yuan's previous life, endless beast tides emerged from Earth Abyss, attacking the surface and bringing disaster to Central Continent.

Central Continent's ten great ancient sects spent several years before they were finally able to eradicate the beast tide from the surface. Afterwards, both righteous and demonic path Gu Masters and Gu Immortals moved together to explore Earth Abyss.

In the end, they found that this Earth Abyss was unfathomably deep, it had layers after layers, by the time Fang Yuan used Spring Autumn Cicada, they had already discovered a hundred and seven underground layers. It was impossible to estimate how many layers were still left.

"The environment here is complex, there are many lifeforms, the lower we go, the more immemorial desolate beasts there are, this is the best place to escape to." Wu Shuai who was within Myriad Year Flying Warship realized at once.

Using Earth Abyss, Myriad Year Flying Warship's situation started to improve.

But Spectral Soul and the rest also understood Fang Yuan's scheme.

Many Gu Immortals stopped attacking with their full strength, they were wary against each other, but after getting so far, nobody wanted to give up.

Fang Yuan's circumstances were dangerous, even though Myriad Year Flying Warship was not taking as much damage as before, it was still slipping towards the abyss of destruction.

Fang Yuan and Wu Shuai cooperated, they planned to the best of their ability, using the terrain, but still could not shrug off these pursuers.

The only difference was that these pursuers were now grouped into different categories.

The first and closest person to Myriad Year Flying Warship was Spectral Soul.

Followed by Qi Sea Ancestor, Demon Immortal Qi Jue, and Qing Chou.

The final group was Heavenly Court, Longevity Heaven, Shadow Sect's Fairy Zi Wei, and the rest.

Boom!

Myriad Year Flying Warship, which was about to be destroyed, charged through the rocks again as it went to a lower layer.

Countless bats flew and escaped in panic.

In this layer, there were countless bats living around, it was like a huge black tide that had no end in sight.

Ordinary bats were turned into pulp by Myriad Year Flying Warship, while alerted immemorial black bats attacked while moving against the tide.

In this layer, black bats were the absolute rulers, because Myriad Year Flying Warship disturbed them, they were going to punish this daring invader.

"Oh?" Spectral Soul followed closely behind.

He saw the endless black bats, he became joyful and surprised.

"Fang Yuan, even heaven is not helping you, it seems that this layer will be the place you die." Spectral Soul suddenly howled.

As the howling sound spread out, innumerable black bats died, even ancient black bats were not spared. Only immemorial black bats survived, they tried to move with difficulty in the air.

Once Spectral Soul's howling ended, countless bat souls appeared from these bat corpses.

These souls quickly fused with his voice as black smoke enveloped Myriad Year Flying Warship from all directions.

Myriad Year Flying Warship quickly disintegrated from the invasion of the black smoke, it could not hold on anymore.

"Retrieve the core Immortal Gu, we will abandon ship!" Fang Yuan's main body ordered.

Like how they sacrificed Dragon Palace earlier, they took back the core Immortal Gu with all their effort at the end. Dragon Palace's core Immortal Gu Dream Token was already successfully retrieved.

But this was a dangerous move, when Immortal Gu Houses face destruction, the Gu Immortal retrieving the core Immortal Gu could only do their best and leave the rest to chance. There could even be times when they were too hasty to take out the core Immortal Gu, causing it to be severely damaged instead, eventually resulting in the Immortal Gu's destruction.

At the next moment, Myriad Year Flying Warship broke apart entirely, Fang Yuan and Wu Shuai got exposed to the black smoke.

"He's here! I will block him." Wu Shuai stood before Fang Yuan.

"I said this before, your struggles are futile." Spectral Soul approached as he spoke in an icy tone.

Qi Sea Ancestor and the rest had just arrived with the rest, he saw the overwhelming black smoke that shattered the silver-white light, Spectral Soul was attacking Fang Yuan's main body.

"No!" Qi Sea Ancestor could not help them from this distance, he could only shout out in his mind.

At the moment before death, Fang Yuan suddenly smiled: "You fell for my trap, Spectral Soul."

Chapter 2047: Carelessness

When Fairy Zi Wei and the rest arrived, they could only see an endless stream of black bats.

In this layer of the underground abyss, black bats were the sole rulers of all the living beings, right now, they felt provoked, they went into madness and rage.

Immemorial black bats commanded ancient black bats while ancient black bats commanded desolate beast black bats, these desolate beast black bats controlled the countless ordinary bats. When Shadow Sect, Longevity Heaven, and Heavenly Court arrived, the furious black bats poured their anger that had nowhere to be vented at these three parties.

Even though the three parties contained the strongest Gu Immortals in the current world, they could not help but freeze in their steps.

"Why are there so many black bats!"

"We need to kill the immemorial black bats to get rid of these beasts."

"There are too many of them, these black bats are simply endless, we cannot waste time here, our primary goal is still Fang Yuan!"

The three groups charged into the black bat groups, they tried to move in this dangerous environment.

All of the Gu Immortals were top tier rank eight Gu Immortals in the current world, even though there were countless bats, they were still unable to match the immortals in actual combat.

But by the time the immortals got out of the bat groups, they could not see Myriad Year Flying Warship, Spectral Soul, Qing Chou, or others.

"What happened?"

"Where are they? There are no clues left behind at all!"

"This is impossible, we chased them according to the traces left behind from their fight."

The immortals were shocked and uncertain.

Calamity Luck Altar burst out with golden radiance, melting the surrounding bats, a huge space was created immediately.

From within Calamity Luck Altar, Bing Sai Chuan's impatient voice resounded: "Fairy Zi Wei, tell me, where is Fang Yuan?"

Old Man Zheng Yuan snorted coldly: "Why would we know?"

Qin Ding Ling sneered: "Shadow Sect, do you really think we are ignorant of your tricks? You waited and did not chase them, wasn't it because you were trying to disrupt us?"

Qin Ding Ling spoke in a sharp tone, it seemed like she was sowing discord but it sounded like the truth, Shadow Sect got into a predicament immediately.

Fang Yuan, Spectral Soul, Qing Chou, Qi Sea, and Qi Jue all vanished, it was just too strange. The three forces chasing them became extremely anxious.

Fairy Zi Wei was also frowning deeply as she said: "We have lost contact with our master. I believe that other forces have interfered, the important thing is to find them now, if we fight among ourselves, this external force will succeed in their goal."

Bing Sai Chuan spoke in an icy tone, not concealing his killing intent: "Then show me the capabilities of a wisdom path great expert."

"Hmph, just you watch." Fairy Zi Wei said as she started to activate her killer move, making deductions rapidly.

Qin Ding Ling did not speak but her killing intent was not concealed either. If she found any tricks from Shadow Sect, Heavenly Court would definitely attack them immediately.

Creak creak...

The surrounding black bats approached again, the Gu Immortals hesitated for a moment before quickly attacking and resisting the black bats for Fairy Zi Wei.

Fairy Zi Wei's body was shining in a purple-gold light, aurora spread out constantly.

Fairy Zi Wei's expression turned increasingly pale, immortal essence was expended rapidly until her body started shivering. Afterwards, she opened her eyes, purple light filling her pupils.

As the purple-gold light faded away, Fairy Zi Wei's pupils returned to normal.

Her aura was significantly weaker now, it was clear that she had done her best in the deduction.

Under everyone's supervision, she let out a breath of air: "I deduced it, a battlefield killer move enveloped all of them, causing us to not sense them anywhere."

"Battlefield killer move?"

"Who is ambushing them here?"

"Hmph, do you have evidence?"

Fairy Zi Wei sneered, as a wisdom path great expert, she would naturally not end up empty-handed, she immediately split the bat groups apart as she directed the immortals to a trace of earth path aura that was about to dissipate.

After sensing the aura, the immortals started to analyze it.

"It is an earth path killer move indeed!"

"It really seems like a battlefield killer move."

"Watch me, I will find it!"

A certain Gu Immortal of Heavenly Court made his move, he was very confident at the start but soon, he returned without any progress.

Soon, this trace of earth path aura dissipated, only the bat groups remained to fight against the three groups of immortals.

The immortals' expressions were very ugly.

Some were still suspicious about Shadow Sect, some were thinking about ways to find the enclosed immortal battlefield, some were forced to fight against the black bats.

Longevity Heaven's Bing Sai Chuan still held some suspicions.

Fairy Zi Wei had the heaviest mood, she dealt with the black bats as she asked Heavenly Court: "You should be most familiar with this earth path aura! Heavenly Court, what do you think?"

Qin Ding Ling was silent for a moment before she said: "Indeed, this resembles Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's method. We have the same idea now, to find this immortal battlefield and destroy it!"

"So it is Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's force, no wonder..." Bing Sai Chuan realized at once.

In history, among the ten venerables, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable was the most skilled at using immortal battlefield killer moves. His capability in this aspect was publicly known as the number one among venerables! Right now, the Reincarnation Battlefield that he created was still existing in Central Continent, owned by the ten great ancient sects.

Why did Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's force take action?

None of the immortals here were surprised.

Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable and Spectral Soul Demon Venerable were on opposite sides, everyone knew that. Back then, Spectral Soul slaughtered everyone in his way, causing great terror and chaos, all of the people in the five regions lived in fear, the righteous path was weak while the demonic path surged. Ever since Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable started cultivation, he worked hard to turn this trend around, he restored peace to the world and suppressed the demonic path, he brought fortune to the world.

Because of the ideologies of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable and Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, they had always conflicted.

"To find Paradise Earth's battlefield and destroy it, the difficulty is just..." Bing Sai Chuan shook his head, even an expert like him hesitated and felt troubled.

"Why would Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's force take action? And why would they wait here in ambush?" A Gu Immortal asked.

This question made Fairy Zi Wei's mood even heavier, a dark cloud loomed over her, shrouding her face.

"It must be Fang Yuan!" Even though there was no evidence, Fairy Zi Wei still said that with great confidence.

She had fought against Fang Yuan too many times, she was basically the loser each time. This feeling of defeat was too common to Fairy Zi Wei, she had experienced it countless times.

Each time she thought that victory was close, Fang Yuan would turn the situation around.

This current situation was also the same, Fairy Zi Wei felt very familiar with it.

Qin Ding Ling agreed with Fairy Zi Wei's deduction: "We chased after Fang Yuan, but from another perspective, he was leading us here. While chasing and escaping, this route was planned by Fang Yuan. If he cooperated with Paradise Earth's force and created this situation, it is indeed the easiest way. But why would Paradise Earth's force cooperate with a demon like Fang Yuan? We have not seen it ourselves, is this really Paradise Earth's force? Or rather, which force under Paradise Earth is it?"

Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable was the closest venerable to the current era, he naturally left behind the highest number of forces.

Different from other venerables, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable had never intentionally focused on developing any single force.

Heavenly Court had Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable, Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, and Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable, it was developed by the three of them through painstaking effort. Longevity Heaven was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's grotto-heaven, it was the foundation that he had left behind. Shadow Sect was operated by Spectral Soul's split souls for many years, it used Zombie Alliance as the front to slowly accumulate influence and strength.

Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable was different, he helped and assisted many different forces. For example, the Merman Imperial Court in Eastern Sea, it was because he did not want to see the merfolk get bullied. There was also Southern Border's Mushroomman Paradise, it was made because he did not want to see the mushroommen get slaughtered mercilessly.

Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable had the ability to turn an immortal aperture into a paradise, he helped many Gu Immortals in his life, he altered many grotto-heavens and blessed lands.

He even helped to enlighten many legendary immemorial beasts, for example, the blue dragon whale.

Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable did not just help humans, he also helped variant humans, or even other living beings that were in need.

Thus, he was the most loved venerable and also the most merciful. Even though Heavenly Court's Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable also helped out countless living beings, he was mostly focused on helping nature and repairing habitats.

The other venerables all had offensive methods but only Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable did not.

Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable had also left behind his true inheritances in various places. Southern Border's Mushroomman Paradise was one of them, thus, their leader, Southern Border's Gu Immortal Lu Wei Yin, was also called Paradise Earth's inheritor, nobody could refute it. Before the fate war, Fairy Zi Wei even went to the Mushroomman Paradise and borrowed benevolence Gu.

All the immortals could not think of an answer now.

Because of Paradise Earth's actions, many forces and Gu Immortals were related to him in some way. There was no way of knowing which force it was exactly.

"Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable focused on removing Spectral Soul's influence his entire life, he was a merciful and benevolent person who brought peace. Would his force cooperate with a demon like Fang Yuan? It is not impossible. Didn't Heavenly Court cooperate with me temporarily as well?" Fairy Zi Wei's heart was filled with a solemn emotion.

The more she thought, the worse she found the situation.

The reason why Heavenly Court worked with Shadow Sect was so that Fang Yuan and Spectral Soul would fight each other, it would be great if these two demons were killed at the same time!

If Paradise Earth's force and Fang Yuan cooperated while having such thoughts, why would it be impossible?

With Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's status and nature, he would not do something like laying an ambush. But the Immortal Venerable had died already, nobody knew the temperament of the force that he left behind, or even his inheritor!

"This situation must have surpassed master's expectations."

"But there can be a worse situation, that is, Fang Yuan planned all of this. He gave up on Dragon Palace and Myriad Year Flying Warship just so he could lure master into this battlefield."

"No matter what the truth is, I need to do my best to save master!!"

Fairy Zi Wei sensed something amiss, she was very anxious. As a wisdom path great expert, any changes in her emotions needed to be assigned great importance.

Spectral Soul had an advantage against Fang Yuan of course, but against another venerable's force, it would not be so certain. And most importantly, this was the venerable who purposely went against Spectral Soul in history, Paradise Earth!

At the same time, in the earth path battlefield.

Spectral Soul looked at the surrounding sand, his expression turned cold as ice: "Good, very good. So you are Lu Wei Yin, the current generation inheritor of Paradise Earth?"

A Gu Immortal stepped on a yellow cloud, he cupped his fists at Spectral Soul: "Lord Demon Venerable is very perceptive, I have been waiting here for a long time."

At the side, Fang Yuan urged: "Lu Wei Yin, I lured him here already. Don't expect me to take action now, show me your sincerity... urgh!"

Fang Yuan suddenly stopped speaking as he retreated rapidly.

It was too late!

In an instant, Spectral Soul suddenly arrived in front of him using an unknown method.

"Fang Yuan, you are too careless. It is a pity you got this far, but go and die now!" Spectral Soul stretched out his hand as he grabbed Fang Yuan's neck.

Fang Yuan stared with eyes wide open, he could not break free!

Chapter 2048: Illusory Sand Shifting Shadow

Spectral Soul was indeed the Demon Venerable who killed his way to the top!

Any other person would be wary at the first moment and defend against an assault. But he had abundant battle experience, after falling into a trap, he made perfect use of an opportunity to attack instantly!

Undoubtedly, he chose a great timing.

Fang Yuan was pursued by three parties, the pressure was huge, after getting into this safe area, it was not strange that he would relax his mind.

Spectral Soul distracted him with words while preparing his killer move. This move had no aura or commotion, only Wu Yong in the current five regions could match him in this aspect. Once used, Spectral Soul turned the situation around, he grabbed Fang Yuan's neck tightly.

Spectral Soul's move was also extraordinary, it was called soul shattering hand. This move could only be used at an extremely close range, it was a close combat method.

In Gu Immortal battles, close combat was rare. Most engaged in long distance combat, only few paths like transformation path or strength path would focus on hand-to-hand combat. Soul shattering hand had an extremely close range, it was very limited in usage but Spectral Soul still held onto it without discarding it, the reason was because this move had incredible power, once it struck the enemy, it could easily decide the victor of the battle.

At the next moment, soul shattering hand activated!

A smile appeared on Fang Yuan's face again, while Spectral Soul's expression turned grim.

The 'Fang Yuan' in his hand quickly turned into sand and scattered with the wind, it was actually a puppet made of sand!

As yellow sand flew in the air, Fang Yuan's voice could be heard as he praised: "Spectacular indeed! Lu Wei Yin, your effort and time spent to specially create this illusory sand shifting shadow battlefield was not in vain."

Fang Yuan did not conceal his voice, Spectral Soul snorted coldly as he looked for traces, flying past the sand and arriving in front of Fang Yuan.

Spectral Soul attacked again while Fang Yuan did not dodge.

At the next moment, Fang Yuan scattered into countless sand specks again.

It was a rare sight as Spectral Soul finally frowned this time.

Lu Wei Yin's voice was transmitted: "Fang Yuan, you are too kind. The truth is, Friend Spectral Soul is too strong, I had to set up my strongest battlefield killer move. I won't hide it, even though this battlefield originated from Paradise Earth's true inheritance, it has been modified by many generations, it has many changes done to it. The sand puppet double earlier can deceive the enemy's senses and lure away firepower."

"Lu Wei Yin, do you want to lose your Southern Border Mushroomman Paradise? To think my Shadow Sect let you off purposely back then." Spectral Soul called out coldly, he stared at Lu Wei Yin's sand puppet fixedly. He knew that Lu Wei Yin purposely spoke to target his morale, to exert mental pressure on him.

In a battle between experts, every word was a contest. Especially against information path Gu Immortals, every word they said was sharp like a blade or spear, the enemies could not be lax against them.

Fang Yuan ignored Spectral Soul and continued to speak with Lu Wei Yin: "Even though I used up two Immortal Gu Houses to lower this old monster's wariness, this battlefield killer move has such power, it was not a waste. Now, it will depend on you."

Lu Wei Yin knew about Fang Yuan's tribulation, in fact, the heavenly mark killer move that Fang Yuan had was also given to him by Lu Wei Yin!

As a matter of fact, Fang Yuan did not trust Lu Wei Yin. His original destination was not Earth Abyss but Crazed Demon Cave instead. Fang Yuan did not know a lot about Lu Wei Yin's background, there was nothing much about him in the five hundred years of memories either.

Right now, not only was Spectral Soul stuck in the illusory sand shifting shadow battlefield, Fang Yuan was the same.

Fang Yuan's two Immortal Gu Houses, Dragon Palace and Myriad Year Flying Warship, were also destroyed, he lost many Gu worms, even the few core Immortal Gu that he retrieved were all injured.

Spectral Soul snickered: "Fang Yuan, hide well. Maybe Lu Wei Yin will let you out? Hehehe, but it is not a problem, Paradise Earth died long ago, his earth path battlefield cannot trap me for long. Once I decipher this place, it will be your time to die!"

Lu Wei Yin did not answer, he activated the battlefield.

From the yellow sand flying around Spectral Soul, a figure flew out, it was Fang Yuan's Qi Sea clone.

Qi Sea Ancestor saw Spectral Soul and got stunned, it was as if he had just charged through the sandstorm and did not expect to see Spectral Soul here.

But at the next moment, Qi Sea Ancestor made his move, unleashing qi path methods on Spectral Soul.

Spectral Soul snorted coldly, he blocked the attacks and wanted to retaliate but saw that Qi Sea Ancestor got enveloped by the sandstorm, vanishing into thin air.

Spectral Soul immediately chased, he went into the yellow sand, but he could not see any sign of Qi Sea Ancestor.

Another figure approached, it was Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

Spectral Soul was about to speak when he saw that Demon Immortal Qi Jue's expression was strange, he became wary.

As expected, Demon Immortal Qi Jue attacked him at the next moment.

Spectral Soul resisted as he called out: "Qi Jue, what are you doing?"

Demon Immortal Qi Jue snickered: "Qi Sea Ancestor, since you provoked me, I will show you the true power of qi path!"

After hearing this, Spectral Soul became stunned, he thought: "Don't tell me this earth path battlefield has another ability to confuse enemies?"

Since Spectral Soul could perceive the sand puppet as Fang Yuan without realizing so, it was not strange that Demon Immortal Qi Jue would get deceived and mistake him for Qi Sea Ancestor.

Spectral Soul and Demon Immortal Qi Jue fought for over ten rounds, Demon Immortal Qi Jue suffered injuries as he got devoured by the sandstorm again.

Next was Qing Chou.

"Spectral Soul, I want you dead! I want you dead!" Qing Chou was still insane, the rank nine aura on its body was extremely dense, Spectral Soul's heart jumped upon sensing it.

Like this, at times he fought Qi Sea Ancestor, at times he fought Demon Immortal Qi Jue, sometimes, he even faced the legendary immemorial desolate beast Qing Chou.

They started to appear and disappear in the sandstorm, engaging with Spectral Soul while taking turns!

Spectral Soul had outstanding battle strength, far beyond them individually, but whenever he gained some advantage, Lu Wei Yin, who controlled the battlefield, would swap opponents and leave Spectral Soul helpless.

Even after several rounds of attacks, Spectral Soul could not break free from the yellow sand, he could only fight them.

Faraway in the battlefield, Fang Yuan was focusing on his tribulation. Wu Shuai guarded him with a vigilant expression, all around him, countless army ants gathered into a hollow ball, shielding him and Fang Yuan from the outside.

Within the sovereign immortal aperture, the myriad tribulation had already turned into a torrential flood!

Water levels rose, engulfing ten thousand li of land.

Fang Yuan's five regions were all affected, a large number of small sized resource points were completely destroyed, Mini Central Continent's spirit spring forest, Mini Northern Plains' bone burial field, contact heart river bank, Mini Western Desert's eerie fire dragon python, sand gull soil beach, Mini Southern Border's become dragon mound, Heaven Sealing Mountain, and Mini Eastern Sea's jade root lake were all heavily damaged. As for the few resource points that Fang Yuan defended heavily, they also met with a huge impact.

Fang Yuan's losses were severe!

There was no helping it, he had done his best.

The good thing was that his hard work and sacrifices were not in vain, he had already refined more than twenty heaven path dao marks!

Against the initial myriad tribulation, myriad destruction lightning forest, Fang Yuan came up with a countermeasure after great effort. Due to heaven's will's manipulation, the heaven path dao marks immediately changed the tribulation, causing Fang Yuan's previous method to become ineffective.

If this happened to most Gu Immortals in the current world, it would lead to despair. But for Fang Yuan, each time the myriad tribulation transformed, it was a great opportunity for him!

Because he had the killer move exposing heavenly secret.

Exposing heavenly secret allowed Fang Yuan to accurately predict what the next tribulation was, even though he could not prepare for it amply, it was still an opportunity he could use.

After all, the greatest problem and danger of tribulations was that they could not be predicted. Once they were known beforehand, their threat level would fall by many times.

Of course, even if myriad tribulations could be predicted, they were still myriad tribulations. Thus, the sovereign immortal aperture flooded and countless resources were destroyed.

Fang Yuan's losses were huge, but it was not a bad thing entirely!

The myriad tribulation's power continued to fall, because the essence of the Heavenly Dao was to maintain balance, the more losses Fang Yuan suffered, the weaker the tribulation would be, even if heaven's will was here, it could not defy the natural operations of the Heavenly Dao.

More and more heaven path dao marks were refined by Fang Yuan, his speed of refinement was getting faster and faster!

The first step was the hardest, Fang Yuan sacrificed all of his soul beasts to create an opportunity in this biggest predicament of his life.

He succeeded!

Despite the myriad tribulation's rampage, Fang Yuan already managed to regain his footing, he was slowly turning the situation around.

Spectral Soul fell into a tough battle.

Lu Wei Yin controlled the illusory sand shifting shadow battlefield, causing him to be in an extremely passive spot.

Qi Sea Ancestor, Demon Immortal Qi Jue, Qing Chou, and even Lu Wei Yin could attack Spectral Soul at the same time.

Qing Chou was overcome by rage, it was once used by Spectral Soul, but in here, Lu Wei Yin could relocate it easily, Spectral Soul had no opportunities to do so.

As intense winds blew, a sandstorm brewed, suddenly, all of the sand gathered into rocks, they flew around in their own vortexes.

Instantly, countless flying rocks enveloped Spectral Soul.

Spectral Soul waved his hand as smoke flew out, some of the flying rocks melted in the black smoke but most of them pierced through it and shot towards Spectral Soul.

Spectral Soul's figure suddenly vanished, when he reappeared, he was already at the other end of the battlefield.

He dodged almost all of the flying rocks, but after these flying rocks flew into the sandstorm, they turned back into sand.

After that, the sand turned back into yellowish flying rocks that shot towards Spectral Soul.

"This move is called flying sand turning rocks, please evaluate it, Lord Spectral Soul." Lu Wei Yin's voice resounded from within.

"Child's play." Spectral Soul howled as his body shook, black smoke rumbled with him as the center, spreading towards the surroundings with rapid speed.

"Spin." As Spectral Soul vanished within the black smoke, he shouted again.

At the next moment, the black smoke turned into a vortex that started to rotate. Spectral Soul was at the center, he released black smoke while simultaneously absorbing it.

As the flying rocks flew into the black smoke, they corroded into sand before the black smoke swept them into Spectral Soul's immortal aperture.

Seeing this countermeasure, Lu Wei Yin praised: "Brilliant, as expected of Lord Spectral Soul. However, I specially chose the location of my battlefield on this earth vein. No matter how many flying rocks you absorb, this battlefield can draw more earth qi from the earth vein as replenishment. Thus, unless you can deplete the entire earth vein, these flying rocks are endless."

These words did not affect Spectral Soul, the former Demon Venerable sneered with deep killing intent: "Lu Wei Yin, did you think this move only countered your flying sand turning rocks?"

"Oh no." Lu Wei Yin's expression changed, there was no time to react.

At the next moment, all of the flying sand in the sky fell to the ground, a portion of the illusory sand shifting shadow battlefield was corroded by the black smoke, it returned to being a flat yellowish landscape.

"Shifting sand illusion was actually broken so quickly!" Lu Wei Yin's expression was ugly.

Spectral Soul hid his true move deeply, he seemed to be dealing with the killer move, flying sand turning rocks, but his real target was shifting sand illusion. Now that this move was broken, there were no longer any sand puppets left.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue broke out of the illusion, while Fang Yuan's real location was exposed.

"Fang Yuan, how long are you going to hide for?" Spectral Soul flew towards Fang Yuan without hesitation.

Wu Shuai fought to resist him, but the defense of the army ants became torn apart instantly by Spectral Soul.

A black soul ball shot out, after a few breaths of time, it reached Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan remained seated on the ground, he opened his eyes as he smiled lightly: "I don't need to dodge."

Rumble!

An Immortal Gu House suddenly appeared, shielding Wu Shuai and Fang Yuan.

The black soul ball landed on the Immortal Gu House, erupting with immense might. However, this Immortal Gu House remained still like a mountain, it did not move!

"You still have an Immortal Gu House?!" At this moment, Spectral Soul's pupils shrank, he frowned deeply.

Chapter 2049: Spectral Soul's Anxiety

An Immortal Gu House suddenly appeared in the battlefield.

It was like a mountain, but it was not tall. There were clear layers on this mountain from the bottom to the top, it was smooth on the surface, so it resembled a tower made of dozens of giant drums. This Immortal Gu House was yellowish brown, there was also a misty layer of sand covering its surface, giving it a strong feeling of sturdiness and peace.

Rank eight Immortal Gu House — Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress!

This earth path Immortal Gu House was obtained when Fang Yuan explored the dream realm. It was different from most Immortal Gu Houses in essence, because this Immortal Gu House did not have any core Immortal Gu, its core was made of immortal killer moves.

Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress had three core killer moves, the most important one was accumulated soil mountain.

This move was very special, it did not have offense, movement, healing or other aspects. Using this killer move, the Gu Immortal could stack earth path Gu worms to allow them to form an Immortal Gu House! This could be done even if the Gu Immortal using the killer move had zero attainment in formation path itself!

Gaining this killer move was also the same as gaining the foundation of the Immortal Gu House, Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress!

Thus, every Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress had a different appearance. In fact, even for the same Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress, because the earth path Gu worms used were different, they could gain various forms and abilities.

Fang Yuan had created this Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress for some time already. He obtained the complete blueprint from the dream realm, he also gained a large number of earth path Immortal Gu from the blue dragon whale. The truth was, he had already obtained this rank eight Immortal Gu House before the fate war!

Right now, Fang Yuan took out this Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress to change the situation.

Spectral Soul's assault did not work on Fang Yuan, Lu Wei Yin, Qing Chou, and the rest could force him to divert his target to them.

"I thought Fang Yuan was lying earlier to put up a front, I thought he was forced to abandon Myriad Year Flying Warship and Dragon Palace. Now it seems, he intentionally lured me into this trap!" Spectral Soul's heart sank a little.

The truth was, Fang Yuan's act of giving up the two Immortal Gu Houses did lower his wariness. After all, without Myriad Year Flying Warship or Dragon Palace, Fang Yuan really seemed like he was at his wits' end.

To think that he had such a trump card!

Lu Wei Yin also felt surprised, thinking to himself: Fang Yuan was willing to pay such a huge price to lure Spectral Soul here. Is this a form of trust? Or is he testing our first cooperation?

The truth was, Fang Yuan had no other choice.

Even though he had been keeping this Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress a secret, it had one huge drawback. Its speed was too slow! If there was a list of fastest to slowest Immortal Gu Houses, this Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress would definitely rank at the bottom without doubt.

Honestly speaking, Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress was the tortoise among Immortal Gu Houses, its speed was only superior to immortal formations, it was simply helpless. But such weaknesses came with great advantages, Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress had an incredibly powerful defense instead!

If Spectral Soul or Lu Wei Yin knew about Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress' weakness, they would understand Fang Yuan's plight.

If he took out Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress earlier in the battle, he would not be able to get far, he would only be a target board, attacked by everyone. Even though Fang Yuan would have some temporary safety, the other forces could mobilize their people and gather to kill Fang Yuan together.

Thus, he could not stay at one spot, this was Central Continent, Heavenly Court's territory, even though Heavenly Court was weak now, it was still governing the ten great ancient sects!

But here, when Fang Yuan used Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress, the effect was completely different.

Spectral Soul had to defend against the attacks of Lu Wei Yin, Qi Sea Ancestor, and the rest, he did not forget to attack Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress in the meantime.

But Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress remained unmovable, it was a true fortress!

Even someone like Spectral Soul started to be emotionally affected. His main target was Fang Yuan from the start, but to get to him, he would have to destroy this Immortal Gu House. This huge obstacle was causing Spectral Soul to feel anxious internally.

If Spectral Soul ignored Fang Yuan and dealt with the enemies in this battlefield, Fang Yuan would gain more time to recuperate. This was something Spectral Soul did not want to see.

During the intense battle, Spectral Soul looked towards Qing Chou, thinking of using it to create an opening.

But Lu Wei Yin sensed it quickly, once Spectral Soul showed signs of targeting Qing Chou, he would use the battlefield killer move to teleport Qing Chou away.

Qing Chou only targeted its greatest enemy, Spectral Soul, it knew that Lu Wei Yin was trying to help it instead of Spectral Soul, it would not attack him abruptly.

Spectral Soul's plans were thwarted in advance, he transmitted to Demon Immortal Qi Jue: "Qi Jue, focus on destroying this Immortal Gu House, I will definitely satisfy you with the reward!"

Demon Immortal Qi Jue hesitated: "Spectral Soul, you have higher battle strength than me, if you can't succeed, how can I?"

Spectral Soul snorted coldly: "Who says I can't do it? It will merely take some effort. We lack cooperation, the best move now is for me to deal with these enemies and the battlefield while you target Fang Yuan. You have the secluded domain of heaven and earth, Xi, as long as you pay some price, how hard can it be to destroy the Immortal Gu House?"

Spectral Soul's main target was Fang Yuan but now, he had to look away from his target. Firstly, this Immortal Gu House had high defense, destroying it was too troublesome. Secondly, Spectral Soul and Qi Jue were just working together, their relationship was quite shallow, Qi Jue was not reliable at all. Asking him to attack was guarding against him, if anything happened, Spectral Soul could still break out of the battlefield, it was a relatively safer option.

Spectral Soul had the strongest killing nature throughout history, but he was not a fool who lacked wisdom or logic, he was not overwhelmed by his desire to kill.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue also did not want to be trapped in this battlefield, he did not doubt Spectral Soul's decision to destroy the battlefield.

He thought about it for a while before laughing: "My Xi Land can break this earth path Immortal Gu House but the price is very steep, after all, I cultivate qi path and not earth path. After I succeed, it is likely that my Xi Land will be destroyed! But this deal is not impossible, it will depend on you, Spectral Soul, what price can you pay me to make such a huge sacrifice?"

"What, you think I can't afford it?" Spectral Soul asked.

"You are a venerable, you have immense foundation, I am quite looking forward to it. But until now, the true inheritances that you gave me are high in quantity but lack quality, I am quite disappointed."

"Hmph! You mean to say, only venerable inheritances are good enough for you."

"Of course." Demon Immortal Qi Jue spoke openly: "Only venerable true inheritances are of value to me. In fact, I am interested in your true inheritance too!"

Demon Immortal Qi Jue was an old demon, in this situation, he actually wanted to extort Spectral Soul's soul path true inheritance. This was a really shameless thing to do.

Spectral Soul was not willing to take this loss, he replied firmly: "Qi Jue, don't forget about our goal! If you do not put in effort now, how can you kill Fang Yuan? We might both get trapped in this battlefield, ending up as their prey."

Demon Immortal Qi Jue became silent, the situation was quite tense now, this earth path battlefield had unfathomable depths, he had not understood it completely yet.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue was merely testing him earlier, seeing that Spectral Soul was firm in his stance, he decided to work together and get over this hurdle first.

Even though Spectral Soul broke one layer of the earth path battlefield, the combination of Lu Wei Yin, Qing Chou, and Qi Sea Ancestor still placed a huge pressure on him.

Even though Demon Immortal Qi Jue countered Qi Sea Ancestor entirely, due to Lu Wei Yin's control, Qi Sea Ancestor did not fight against Demon Immortal Qi Jue. Qing Chou was actually quite useful here, this beast fought without regard for its life, it created huge problems for Demon Immortal Qi Jue.

Battlefield killer moves were hard to set up, but usually, after they were activated, the Gu Immortal would gain a huge advantage in the domain.

Enslavement path and formation path could allow one to fight against many enemies, it was because these two paths could allow one to gain huge strength if used well.

As for this illusory sand shifting shadow battlefield, it was created by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, modified by generations of inheritors, it was very threatening. Furthermore, this battlefield was created in Earth Abyss, combined with the earth vein, it had an unceasing amount of earth qi, Spectral Soul and Qi Jue were troubled.

Within the sovereign immortal aperture, the myriad tribulation was still continuing.

The myriad tribulation changed again, it was a flood earlier, now it turned into a blazing flame, razing everything to the ground and creating huge heat waves.

"I have already refined more than fifty heaven path dao marks!" Fang Yuan made some new progress.

Each time the myriad tribulation changed, it created danger for him.

But danger was accompanied by opportunity!

Chapter 2050: How Do We Fight This?

Along with his gains, Fang Yuan also paid a hefty price.

Mini Southern Border, which was the most prosperous of the five mini regions, was half devastated.

Immortal Succession Mountain was destroyed, washed away entirely by the flood. This mountain was a mid-sized resource point obtained from Hei Fan grotto-heaven, it once had the ability to help mortals ascend to immortal.

There was also Heaven Sealing Mountain. This mountain was created by Fang Yuan, it was small and unassuming, within the mountain itself, Fang Yuan had once set up a formation to seal his strength path immortal zombie body.

Other than them, there were also up to a hundred mountains and valleys. The greatest losses were Interior Rain Mountain, Copper Seal Mountain, and Bone Bird Peak.

Interior Rain Mountain's peak was always shrouded by a layer of dark clouds from where light rain continued to fall. The drizzling rain was not ordinary rainwater, but rank six immortal material interior rain! This was a resource point that produced water path immortal materials, now it was in ruins.

Copper Seal Mountain was no longer whole, it used to have a red and squarish shape, it was like a large seal was standing upright in Mini Southern Border. This mountain did not have even a trace of soil, it was completely formed from all kinds of copper.

There was mortal level copper like chaotic sky copper, pragna copper, snow flower copper, and so on, and immortal copper like profound grey copper and ascending dragon copper.

Copper Seal Mountain was so special, it was heavily targeted by the myriad tribulation myriad destruction lightning forest. Now, half of the mountain was destroyed and charred, giving out dense smoke and sparks. The entire mountain had turned into a molten state, it emitted a terrible smell.

This mountain once produced domination copper, that was a rank seven immortal material! It was a pity that the tribulation struck, it could no longer produce any.

As for Bone Bird Peak, it used to have a large number of flower wing white bone birds, filled with vitality. Now, the entire mountain had collapsed too, all of the flower wing white bone birds died from the lightning bolts.

Lightning bolts destroyed mountains, floods destroyed forests.

Fang Yuan had originally obtained a large amount of musical trees from Hei Fan grotto-heaven, he created Mini Southern Border's primitive forest using them. After this myriad tribulation, what forest could survive? Not to mention the beautiful qi death birds or the fragrant tea streams.

Mini Southern Border was almost completely devastated.

Only several areas were heavily protected by Fang Yuan.

Among them were the coiling thread caves, stalactite caves, and the dark inkstone mines. These resource points were all underground, it was easier to preserve them. Furthermore, the rockmen lived in these places.

Fire Bird Mountain was an exception, because it was quite isolated, it escaped this disaster.

This mid-sized resource point had fire path birds of all kinds growing in it. At the top of the volcano were fire phoenixes that were suppressed by the formation. The sunset parasol trees on the mountain absorbed lava as nutrients to grow, branches extended as leaves grew, they gave out the beautiful light of the setting sun, it was an amazing sight to behold.

Other than Mini Southern Border, the other four mini regions were also affected to some extent.

Mini Northern Plains' shallow rock beach was obtained from annexing Han Dong blessed land. It was completely washed away by the floods, all of the pinkish red spirit snakes living in it died.

Mini Western Desert's hound desert was obtained from Liu Yong blessed land. There were more than twenty desolate hounds there, they all died without a corpse remaining.

Mini Central Continent and Mini Eastern Sea, even the mini nine heavens were implicated by the myriad tribulation!

However, Fang Yuan could not care about it at this point.

Myriad tribulations had taken so many rank eight Gu Immortals' lives, in the long history of the world, countless geniuses died primarily from them. If he was careless, even Fang Yuan could lose his life!

Fang Yuan not only had to deal with the myriad tribulation, he also had to face the three forces chasing after him!!

If losing some resources meant that he could improve the situation, why wouldn't Fang Yuan do it?

What was more important, his life or these resources?

The answer was obvious.

Only by staying alive could he have any hope for the future.

In fact, even if all of Fang Yuan's resources were destroyed, even if he lost the sovereign immortal body and his clones, as long as he was alive and got through this predicament, as long as he had one breath remaining, he would accept the result.

The most important thing was an unyielding spirit, how could mere success and failure determine his life!

"The loss of these resource points is actually helpful to me. The Heavenly Dao seeks balance, with these resource points gone, the myriad tribulation has weakened proportionately. Thus, my efficiency in refining the heaven path dao marks will continue to become higher! Hmm?"

Fang Yuan's expression suddenly changed.

Rumble!

With an intense sound, Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress shook harshly, hundreds and thousands of Gu worms shattered and died.

It was the move that Demon Immortal Qi Jue had been preparing for a long time!

Demon Immortal Qi Jue!

This old demon who had resisted Limitless Demon Venerable in history, he had vicious methods capable of weakening and damaging Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress. If he was allowed to continue attacking, he would eventually break through Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress.

It was not that Lu Wei Yin or the Qi Sea clone did not try to stop him, but Spectral Soul's continuous attacks hindered them.

Spectral Soul's body surged with black smoke, he attacked and defended at times, unleashing several immemorial soul beasts while using peculiar soul path killer moves. He not only protected Qi Jue, giving him ample time and opportunity to attack, he even probed illusory sand shifting shadow battlefield even further, he managed to break another layer of this battlefield!

"Lu Wei Yin, Qing Chou, and the Qi Sea clone are attacking Spectral Soul but he is still having an easy time. This current Spectral Soul is also just his remnant soul, he is still injured and has not reached the peak state he was in during the time he refined sovereign immortal fetus Gu."

Fang Yuan sighed internally.

He could genuinely feel the depth of Spectral Soul's strength!

"I cannot let this go on, Wu Shuai, go and join the battle, deal with Spectral Soul!" Fang Yuan instructed.

In this current situation, Spectral Soul and the other two forces wanted Fang Yuan dead. On the other hand, Lu Wei Yin carried on Paradise Earth's will, he wanted to exterminate Spectral Soul.

Fang Yuan was the focus, but Spectral Soul was also crucial.

Fang Yuan did not feel great external pressure now, his wariness stemmed from Spectral Soul, he did not hesitate to use all his strength against him.

Wu Shuai joined the fight!

At once, army ants gathered and formed a river of ants, they swept towards Spectral Soul.

Spectral Soul split a portion of his concentration and used killer moves to resist them.

Wu Shuai was Fang Yuan's dragonman clone, he cultivated enslavement path, even though he had not cultivated for long, he inherited the inheritance of the dragonman race, as well as the actual Wu Shuai's true inheritance.

After several rounds of attacks, Lu Wei Yin became hopeful as he thought: "Even though Wu Shuai does not attack often, he has rank eight cultivation level, his battle strength is quite incredible. With him around, we can finally place pressure on Spectral Soul!"

With him controlling the battlefield, even Qing Chou could join the fight, not to mention Wu Shuai who cooperated with them.

Wu Shuai soon mixed in with this group, their tempo became faster as they emitted greater pressure on Spectral Soul.

Spectral Soul was the strongest in the world, but he had not regained his peak strength. Demon Immortal Qi Jue and Qi Sea Ancestor could fight him for over ten rounds even if they could not defeat him.

With Wu Shuai's participation, a qualitative change appeared, it tilted the balance of both sides.

Lu Wei Yin and the rest attacked unceasingly, their attacks did not stop even once.

Spectral Soul started to get into a passive spot as he resisted their joint attacks.

Immortal killer move — Upper-Lower Breathless Qi!

Demon Immortal Qi Jue stretched out two fingers as he pointed at the top and bottom of Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress.

At once, Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress became immobilized, Fang Yuan who was inside had a change of expression, he could not breath smoothly. Even worse was that his injection of immortal essence into Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress became choppy and inconsistent.

Immortal Gu Houses required a lot of immortal essence to work. The same applied to Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress, after getting hit by this move, its defenses became much weaker.

A huge flaw in Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress became exposed.

It was just too slow, it had to resist most killer moves head on. Of course, it had immense defense, it could waste a lot of the enemies' immortal essence.

Thus, Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress was suited for a battle of attrition. Gu Immortals could heal up inside and analyze the enemy's killer moves while using the defense to waste the enemy's immortal essence.

Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress also lacked offensive methods. The truth was, Demon Immortal Qi Jue could ignore Fang Yuan and help Spectral Soul fight against Lu Wei Yin and the rest. Fang Yuan was currently troubled by the myriad tribulation, Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress was of little threat to them in terms of offense.

Immortal killer move — Soul Explosion!

Spectral Soul suddenly turned around, he endured the attacks of Lu Wei Yin and the rest as he pointed with his fingers, more than ten black dots flew out.

The black dots shot towards the top of Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress before turning into more than ten immemorial soul beasts.

These immemorial soul beasts crashed down onto Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress, their mountain-like bodies completely burying the Immortal Gu House.

At the next moment, boom!

A terrifying explosion killed these immemorial soul beasts on the spot, their sacrifices resulted in this intense explosion resembling a giant black ball.

The black ball rapidly expanded, in a few breaths of time, it grew to over the size of a hundred li!

The earth and mountains shook, the entire battlefield started to shake intensely.

Lu Wei Yin's expression changed, he immediately went away to defend the battlefield. If this battlefield broke, even if one corner of it was destroyed, the entire situation would aggravate.

"Spectral Soul is so crafty, he actually had such a terrifying move!" Demon Immortal Qi Jue squinted, retreating to a safe distance: "Soul explosion is not uncommon, it is expected that he would detonate the immemorial soul beasts, but how could he perfectly fuse the detonation of more than ten immemorial soul beasts together like this?"

"Oh no, I wonder how our main body is doing?" Wu Shuai and Qi Sea Ancestor became worried.

"Roar!" Qing Chou was also implicated and got quite injured, the greater the pain, the more maniacal it became.

It did not care about anything, it attacked Spectral Soul again.

Wu Shuai and Qi Sea Ancestor had to follow suit, they could not allow Spectral Soul to absorb Qing Chou's strength.

After using this move, Spectral Soul also turned pale. Against Qing Chou's assault, he focused on defense while trying to recover. It was evident that the move earlier consumed a huge amount of his mental energy!

In truth, this soul explosion was very costly. Immemorial soul beasts had rank eight battle strength, Spectral Soul expended more than ten of them at once!

"I wonder how Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress is now?" Demon Immortal Qi Jue approached Fang Yuan.

As the dust clouds faded away, Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress appeared in everyone's vision again.

They saw that this earth path Immortal Gu House was thirty percent shorter, the surface seemed damaged but no holes were created.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue squinted as he sighed internally: "This Immortal Gu House's defense is likely the highest of all Immortal Gu Houses that currently exist!"

Immortal killer move — Accumulated Soil Mountain!

Within the Immortal Gu House, Fang Yuan injected immortal essence as he activated the core killer move.

Countless earth path Gu worms flew up in sovereign immortal aperture, entering the Immortal Gu House. After three breaths of time, not only did Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress recover fully, its appearance also changed, instead of being round like before, it became more like a tower now, there were edges and sharp corners.

"This?!" Even someone like Demon Immortal Qi Jue stared at this with wide eyes, he felt a little empty internally.

This was too shameless.

Not only did Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress have high defense, its recovery speed was also this fast!

In the current world, most Immortal Gu Houses could not be easily repaired. When replenishing Gu worms, those positions were usually fixed. It was also not as easy as placing Gu worms into these specific positions, there was usually a need to use special Gu worms or killer moves to achieve this.

Immortal Gu Houses were a type of mobile immortal formation, to repair Immortal Gu Houses or immortal formations, one had to consider the influence that these actions would have on the main structure.

But Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress was different.

Looking at one example.

Repairing other Immortal Gu Houses was like stacking a Jenga tower, the Gu Immortals had to put specific Gu worms into specific holes. During this process, the Gu Immortal had to use methods to stabilize the tower while placing the Gu worms to try to prevent it from toppling.

But Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress was the opposite, because the core was made of immortal killer moves, no matter how many earth path Gu worms Fang Yuan put in, they could easily merge with the tower and have great stability. In fact, they could even alter the properties of the tower.

Demon Immortal Qi Jue and Spectral Soul spent so long dealing with Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress, they had finally gotten some information about it, yet after Fang Yuan's modifications, the entire fortress was different than before. Spectral Soul and Qi Jue's probe had to start all over again!

"How do we fight this?" Similar thoughts emerged in the minds of Demon Immortal Qi Jue and Spectral Soul.

Chapter 2051: Giant Spectral Soul

Other Gu Immortals would feel despair at this moment.

"This rascal Fang Yuan is too good at turtling up, how can we kill him?" Demon Immortal Qi Jue asked with a tone that contained anger and frustration.

Spectral Soul also turned silent for a moment before he smiled coldly.

Instantly, a terrifying killing intent seemed to condense and solidify, emanating from his body, everyone could feel their limbs turning cold as they shook in their hearts.

After suffering a setback, Spectral Soul's determination to kill Fang Yuan became even firmer!

"I will dismantle his tortoise shell! Go and deal with the rest, guard me." Spectral Soul said as his soul flew out and devoured Lady Cold Ash's body in one mouthful.

A soul giant that was as large as a mountain appeared before everyone!

The giant's body was black as ink, it had muscular limbs and bulging muscles. There were two heads, one was scary while the other was cold and aloof. The first pair of eyes had blood red light in them, shooting towards heaven, the other pair of eyes was cold as ice, emitting a deep chill.

It also had six hundred pairs of arms that were raised up or lowered, some were tucked in while others were straight, it showed the stance of grasping the sun and moon, it had the potential to catch stars and whip up storms.

"Amazing giant!" Lu Wei Yin's body shook as he praised, fighting spirit surged in him as he shouted: "Then take this move!"

He used all his strength to activate illusory sand shifting shadow battlefield.

Whoosh whoosh whoosh!

Intense winds blew as yellow sand flew, countless rocks moved along, they slammed towards the black soul giant's body like shooting stars.

The black soul giant only watched coldly as it raised its arms.

Two hundred pairs of arms stretched out and stabbed into the sandstorm. The ghost hands stretched out their fingers as they grabbed towards the sandstorm.

Unexpectedly, the formless sandstorm was grabbed onto like silk or threads in the sky!

The black soul giant pulled, snapping sounds could be heard continuously. The sandstorm was pulled apart, wind scattered as clear vision returned to the battlefield.

Lu Wei Yin's eyes were bulging, his expression turned pale, Spectral Soul dealt with the battlefield so easily, he was deeply shocked!

"Let me." Qi Sea Ancestor flew into the sky, staring at the black soul giant at equal heights.

Immortal killer move — Qi Breath Mountain.

Rumble!

A huge translucent mountain created from air currents descended and pressed down immediately.

This move was once used by Duke Long, it was part of Primordial Origin's true inheritance, it managed to send Purple Mountain True Monarch flying. Right now, with Qi Sea Ancestor using it, the power was not to be underestimated.

Giant Spectral Soul looked at the mountain but approached it instead, he raised more than a hundred pairs of arms, at once, the entire battlefield seemed to have hundreds of black trees, resembling a forest!

The hundred pairs of arms blocked the qi mountain, emitting a loud sound.

The five sharp fingers of each of the ghost hands grabbed, the qi current mountain lasted for a breath of time before breaking apart.

Qi Sea Ancestor grunted, he was forced to retreat.

But Spectral Soul did not let him off, the angry head roared loudly and spat out a grand soul river. The soul river was made of countless ghosts and vengeful spirits, they cried out in agony and despair, causing the entire battlefield to freeze up for a moment.

Seeing the power of this move, Qi Sea Ancestor understood that this move was extraordinary, its might was many times higher than the self-detonation of the immemorial soul beasts earlier!

At this moment, Spectral Soul had used his true strength. Not only did he turn into a black soul giant, he even changed his killer moves, each attack became much stronger, they were all vicious and terrifying.

Qi Sea Ancestor waved his hands, two hands flew out of his wide sleeves. His index and middle fingers stretched out and drew a circle in the air, causing wind and clouds to move along.

Immortal killer move — Qi Current Scissors!

A translucent qi current flew out of his sleeves, moving rapidly.

These qi currents seemed weak but they were extremely sharp, they drew an arc in the sky before gathering to form a translucent qi current river.

With a loud sound, the qi current scissors river crashed into the vengeful ghost river!

The qi current scissors was forced back but the soul river also suffered some damage, it still managed to move as it quickly approached Qi Sea Ancestor.

Lu Wei Yin shouted as he activated the battlefield, creating a rock shield that intercepted the soul river at its weak spot.

Qi Sea Ancestor's face was already flushing red, it was a tough contest of strength, he quickly used this chance to escape.

"Spectral Soul, why aren't you going to die!!" At the same time, Qing Chou shouted as it approached from the left.

At the right of Giant Spectral Soul, Wu Shuai wordlessly manipulated his army ants that pressed down like a black cloud, attacking Giant Spectral Soul's head.

Attacked from the left and right!

Spectral Soul did not move, three hundred pairs of arms resisted Qing Chou while a hundred pairs of arms attacked Wu Shuai.

Qing Chou was fighting without regard for its life, it advanced relentlessly.

Spectral Soul snickered as the fingers of his hands gathered into a sharp spear form, this move countered soul beasts!

At the next instant, a hundred pairs of arms stabbed into Qing Chou's body, green-black blood oozed out and dyed the battlefield.

Seeing this blood, a bright light shined on the face of Spectral Soul's angry head, he snickered coldly: "Soul beasts have no blood, but your body seems to have changed under the influence of hatred Gu's refinement. Interesting! After this battle, I will dissect your body before attempting good and thorough research."

In other words, Spectral Soul was completely confident in taking down Qing Chou.

Qing Chou growled in pain, its snake-like neck struggled intensely, its roars almost burst the immortals' eardrums.

Its entire body emitted black smoke, almost the same as Spectral Soul. Not just that, it opened its mouth and shot out more than ten human faced soul balls that were covered in lightning!

All sorts of attacks landed on Giant Spectral Soul, it was like wind blowing on a tree, even though the leaves were moving, the trunk remained still and motionless.

Spectral Soul's arms that were stabbed into Qing Chou pushed deeper, trying to destroy its body from the inside.

Qing Chou cried out continuously, it was heavily injured by Spectral Soul, unable to break free, its blood flowed like a river, this was a gruesome sight.

Seeing this, Wu Shuai who cultivated enslavement path and had a weak body did not dare to take a risk, he quickly retreated. He decided that unless there was no choice, he would only attack from afar.

The army ants were densely packed and moved like a cloud that could gather and split at will, they rushed towards the black soul giant's eyes, nose, and ears.

Spectral Soul's cold head snorted as he breathed out black smoke from his nose. The smoke spread out, wherever it went, army ants died without resistance, a large number of them fell at once.

"As expected of a former Demon Venerable!" Demon Immortal Qi Jue's eyes shined with bright light, he was full of praise.

Spectral Soul unleashed his true strength, it immediately changed the situation!

Even though Lu Wei Yin and the rest had the territorial advantage as well as more people, they still got suppressed by him.

Spectral Soul struck several times to completely block them, after that, he went back and stared at Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress. Four hundred arms stretched out and clenched into fists, they punched at the rank eight earth path Immortal Gu House with black qi covering the fists!

Bam bam bam...

Each punch caused Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress to shake intensely.

As countless fists rained down, black qi also invaded the Immortal Gu House. Soon, the fragments began to fall off Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress' surface, shattering into pieces.

Fang Yuan quickly used his killer move and added in earth path Gu worms to replenish it.

But other trouble came at the same time, inside his sovereign immortal aperture, the myriad tribulation transformed again!

Almost all of the heaven path dao marks gathered into a giant monstrous ball of flesh.

The flesh ball floated in the air, it was large as a mountain, more than ten times of Spectral Soul's size, casting a shadow down onto the ground.

Countless black colored holes appeared on the flesh ball's surface.

As the holes expanded, they emitted a huge suction force, soon, tornadoes began to form from these holes.

As the tornadoes moved, countless resources in the sovereign immortal aperture, even variant humans got swept away and sucked into the flesh ball.

At once, growling and crying could be heard as fatalities rose.

The flesh ball quickly digested them as it slowly expanded in size!

"Oh no, I have never seen this myriad tribulation before, it also seems to be able to grow, it can get stronger and stronger!" Fang Yuan's heart sank.

He needed to deal with Spectral Soul's attacks and the myriad tribulation in his immortal aperture.

Either one required his full attention and strength, nobody else could help him with this.

Fang Yuan could not attend to both ends, he had to choose what to give up.

"Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress can still last some time, but if I let the myriad tribulation grow further, it will exceed the limit of my capabilities!" Realizing the greater problem at hand, Fang Yuan chose to deal with the myriad tribulation.

Most of his attention was placed in the sovereign immortal aperture, his manipulation of Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress became slightly slower.

Combat Beast King had already awakened, he dragged his injured body and stood up while gritting his teeth, listening to Fang Yuan's orders.

Xue Er controlled the situation on the ground, using the ice crystal formation to resist the suction of the tornadoes.

The flesh ball monster floated towards her slowly while being firm as a mountain, there was a huge pressure placed on Xue Er.

Immortal killer move unrestrained heavenly mark was still active, Fang Yuan had not stopped using it even for one moment! But now, its effect had fallen to its lowest point.

Countless thoughts collided in Fang Yuan's mind, it was like a turbulent sea, the sight was spectacular.

Fang Yuan multitasked, he first activated a wisdom path killer move, the quantity of his thoughts expanded abruptly, even his mind seemed small in comparison!

A vast number of thoughts collided, allowing Fang Yuan to think acutely, he was able to use other killer moves now.

There was no choice, Fang Yuan activated the human path formation to interfere with the Heavenly Dao's interference.

As the formation activated, it created a buzzing noise as it shined with a brilliant light. At this step, over half of Fang Yuan's thoughts were already expended!

If this continued, the consumption of thoughts would exceed the production, he would soon run out of thoughts and Fang Yuan would turn into an idiot instantly.

Fang Yuan gritted his teeth but was not flustered, he was prepared for this, there were many of his wills in the human path formation.

Fang Yuan's wills took charge of the formation as it operated, allowing his thoughts to accumulate again. Fang Yuan only had to do the first step of activating the formation.

"Again!" Fang Yuan shouted internally as he activated the wisdom path killer move again.

The thoughts in his mind burst out again like a tsunami, the quantity rose continuously, almost filling up his entire mind!

For wisdom path Gu Immortals, having too many thoughts was a bad idea, they would take up all the space in the mind and prevent any collisions from happening, it was the worst case scenario.

Fang Yuan did not do something stupid, this was part of his expectations.

Seeing that these thoughts were about to fill up his mind, he placed his concentration on the sea of clouds in the sky.

It was a huge and wide sea of clouds!

Chapter 2052: Eat Heart

Looming clouds spread out in the boundless sky, surging like tides as ripples splashed, it seemed like the sea but it also resembled countless cloud mountains, changing forms at will, having unlimited possibilities.

This was a killer move.

This killer move was Fang Yuan's trump card, it was in fact his strongest offensive method at this moment!

Immortal killer move — Unlimited Qi Sea!

This move was — mystical!

After Fang Yuan's modifications, it not only used rank eight Immortal Gu Big Qi as the core, it also had more than ten supplementary qi path Immortal Gu, as well as hundreds of thousands of foundational mortal Gu. There were even qi path immortal materials that could be expended to increase the power of this move.

This move was — incredible!

It could use all of the kinds of qi in this world, life qi, death qi, sword qi, blade qi, dusk qi, dawn qi... the more qi path immortal materials stored in it, the more powerful this move would be. When used offensively, it would expend immortal essence and immortal materials. When used defensively, it would absorb external qi currents.

This move was — powerful and unstoppable!

Qi Xiang left this move behind, resulting in Qi Xiang grotto-heaven surviving many myriad tribulations after his death. Myriad tribulations... most rank eight Gu Immortals in this world did not even dare to challenge their first myriad tribulation, they desperately delayed the time in their immortal aperture. But Qi Xiang grotto-heaven's heavenly spirit could use this move to get past myriad tribulations time and time again.

After annexing this grotto-heaven, Fang Yuan used the light of wisdom to modify unlimited qi sea before the fate war! After that, during this battle, he used this move to break the primordial qi wall and shocked everyone, including Gu Immortals, in the five regions.

The primordial qi wall was the creation of Primordial Origin, it not only had qi path Immortal Gu but also qi path immortal materials. Qi path had one trait, it was able to use qi path immortal materials in place of Gu worms to execute killer moves.

Fang Yuan used unlimited qi sea to break the primordial qi wall, he also absorbed the vast amount of qi path immortal materials inside the qi wall.

After the first time, Fang Yuan broke it again for a second time!

Not long ago in Heavenly Court, he used unlimited qi sea to absorb the immortal material qi currents in the primordial qi wall, breaking it apart.

After absorbing two qi walls and with Fang Yuan's exploration of Qi Sea grotto-heaven, he gained a huge amount of immortal material qi currents, it caused unlimited qi sea's storage to rise to an unprecedented amount. Thus, the power of this move reached a level that felt terrifying even for Fang Yuan!

As Fang Yuan willed, he unleashed the killer move unlimited qi sea!

The sea of qi rumbled, a huge white qi pillar gathered in the sky and shot down at the giant flesh ball monster.

The qi pillar was extremely thick, reaching a level that had never been seen before, even Qi Xiang would gasp at its majesty now.

Not only that, the qi pillar was covered in a layer of shining golden light, it gave off a tough feeling, it was extremely domineering!

Before the white qi pillar hit the flesh ball monster, a terrifying force acted on it from all directions, immobilizing the flesh ball monster in the air.

Boom—!

The white qi pillar crashed into the flesh ball monster like a falling monument, before rushing through it violently.

The huge sound created even deafened Xue Er, who was far away from the battlefield.

The qi pillar had an intense white light, Xue Er, who was hiding in the ice crystal formation had to shut her eyes to prevent them from being blinded.

The flesh ball monster could not resist the power of the qi pillar, it was suppressed on the grassland of Mini Northern Plains.

The grass and soil of the grassland had already been sent flying long ago by raging tornadoes before the qi pillar struck.

Thus, the flesh ball monster was pressed down on the barren grassland by the unstoppable qi pillar!

As the earth shook, hundreds of cracks formed below the flesh ball monster, resembling a spider web.

The white qi pillar was still continuing its assault, it had the power to destroy mountains and split seas! The great flesh ball monster made from the myriad tribulation got pressed on the ground like a defenseless chick, unable to struggle.

Ten feet, twenty feet, thirty feet...

As the flesh ball monster sank into the ground, its body became smaller and smaller. It continued to be disintegrated by the white qi pillar bit by bit!

The black holes all over the giant monster were shut, it tried to curl up, a pitiful cry could be heard from within its body.

This was the cry of heaven's will!

The white qi pillar lasted for twenty breaths of time before fading away.

Not only did the sea of clouds in the sky shrink by eighty percent, the remaining clouds were sparse and thin. Fang Yuan quickly moved them away.

But the flesh ball monster was in a worse condition, its mountain-like body had shrunk to the size of Dragon Palace.

The flesh ball monster did not move, it remained in the pit like a corpse. This pit was over a thousand feet deep!

Fang Yuan's main body breathed roughly, his brain was hurting along with each breath. In order to use this move, he exerted his mind to its limit, he used up too many thoughts, beyond the capabilities of his mind.

The myriad tribulation created from three thousand heaven path dao marks finally paused for the first time.

It was as if it got beaten into shock by Fang Yuan!

The opportunity was rare, Fang Yuan quickly hastened his action and used unrestrained heavenly mark to refine the heaven path dao marks.

In a short while, Fang Yuan refined more than a hundred heaven path dao marks. Together with his earlier gains, he had already refined over a hundred and sixty heaven path dao marks!

When Fang Yuan refined over two hundred heaven path dao marks, the Heavenly Dao finally reacted. The flesh ball in the hole vanished as it started to hail.

However, even though Fang Yuan could take advantage of this chance, he could only sustain this situation as he was forced to place his attention back to the outside world.

Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress was heavily damaged beyond repair, Giant Spectral Soul's attacks were increasing in frequency, he had made huge advancements!

Spectral Soul swore to kill Fang Yuan, Lu Wei Yin and the rest tried to restrain him but Giant Spectral Soul ignored their attacks and endured them, while maintaining his firepower on Fang Yuan.

Even though Fang Yuan was doing his best to repair his Immortal Gu House, the situation was going downhill.

Bam.

Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress could not take it anymore, a hole was created, it connected to the outside!

Through this hole, Giant Spectral Soul's four eyes emitted cold killing intent as he looked at Fang Yuan who was sitting inside.

He saw that Fang Yuan's expression was pale after unleashing unlimited qi sea.

Fang Yuan was in bad shape now!

Spectral Soul had a realization, his incredibly deep battle experience made a decision for him, similar to Fang Yuan, he was going to use his trump card.

Immortal killer move — Eat Heart!

"I comprehended this move in my later years from \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>. Fang Yuan, it is over. The current Peaceful Soil Heavy Mountain Fortress has no way of blocking this attack." Spectral Soul surged with killing intent.

And like what he said.

At the next moment, Fang Yuan grunted, his face became distorted, he grasped his chest in pain.

The intense pain in his heart felt like it was bitten by a fierce beast!

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, chapter five, section thirty-three —

Ren Zu stared at the skeleton head: "Next, I will eat the most important part of the Predicament's body."

Strong Gu laughed: "This is a stupid move! Oh human, your choice is extremely foolish."

The Predicament shook its body as it shrank. At the same time, countless Tribulations flew out of its neck and attacked Ren Zu.

The Tribulations were like fire, burning Ren Zu's bones. The Tribulations were like hammers, charging at Ren Zu as his bones cracked. The Tribulations were like wind and rain, sweeping at Ren Zu's lone body. The Tribulations were like flashing lightning, striking on Ren Zu continuously.

Fear Gu shouted: "Oh heaven, this is too scary, that human will die for sure at this rate."

Courage Gu encouraged: "Oh human, don't be afraid."

Self Gu and attitude Gu shouted together: "I am very strong, I am very strong, all Tribulations are mere drizzles, they are insignificant breezes!"

Weak Gu, betrayal Gu, and fear Gu flew together, wanting to escape with Ren Zu: "Oh human, quickly run. Don't believe in self Gu's words, it has already been deceived."

Ren Zu was trapped in the Tribulations, he could not escape.

When Tribulations loom over you, it is not a simple matter of running away.

"This is too scary, let's go, forget about the human." Weak gu, betrayal Gu, and fear Gu flew away together.

"You traitors!" Self Gu was furious, it grabbed onto these three Gu and bit them all.

The three Gu were injured but they were not stopped by self Gu, they quickly escaped from Ren Zu.

Self Gu wanted to chase them but rules and regulation Gu urged: "Don't chase them. Escaping when Tribulations strike due to fear and weakness, betraying one's self and courage in the process, it will only lead to death. Isn't it good that they are gone? Weak Gu and betrayal Gu are unable to help us, as for fear Gu... if the Tribulations did not appear, fear would have been pointless. But since the Tribulations are here now, fear will only lead to greater pain in the human."

"You are absolutely right." Self Gu stopped.

Hope Gu flickered with light as it supported Ren Zu: "Oh human, as long as you still have hope in your heart during the Tribulations, there will still be hope in this situation."

Strong Gu could not stop laughing: "Oh human, you are truly pitiful, you easily believe in the words of hope. Don't you know? Having only hope during the Tribulations will only cause them to continue longer, hope is the thing that lengthens the person's pain. When you stop bearing any hope, you will feel relaxed in the Tribulations."

Ren Zu did not speak, he endured the attacks of the Tribulations with great difficulty.

No matter how bent his body became, he did not fall.

Strong Gu soon found the reason — on Ren Zu's feet, there was a pair of independent wings. Even though the wings were small, they flapped stubbornly, helping Ren Zu to stand up despite everything.

Strong Gu continued to demoralize Ren Zu: "Oh human, I am starting to admire you. It is a pity that you are going to fall soon, look at your bones, they are covered in cracks now due to the Tribulations."

Ren Zu was silent.

Originally, Ren Zu's bones were shiny and intact, there were no cracks at all. Now, his skeleton was covered in cracks, it seemed like it would shatter at any moment.

All the other Gu worms were silent, only hope Gu gave out light: "Oh human, don't give up! Tribulations are not scary, the scariest thing is a person who has lost hope."

The light of hope Gu penetrated the cracks of Ren Zu's bones, into his bone marrow.

In the life of everyone in this world, cracks would always form at some point, but those were the times where the light of hope would shine in!

Ren Zu's bones absorbed the light of hope, they started to engulf the surrounding Tribulations.

Each crack was like a huge mouth, the larger the crack, the larger the mouth, and the more Tribulations it could devour.

"How could this happen?" Strong Gu was extremely shocked.

The more Tribulations that Ren Zu's skeleton devoured, the stronger and firmer his bones became.

Tribulations could destroy people, but they could also toughen oneself!